<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>AFTER TAKING THE LIBRARY  MANY PAGANS WERE CONVERTED</pattern><template>Hipatia continued teaching and researching while her former students held important positions in the social elite.</template></category><category><pattern>ALEXANDRIA  IN THE PROVINCE OF EGYPT  STILL RETAINED SOME OF ITS LUSTRE POSSESSING TWO OF THE SEVEN WONDERS OF THE ANCIENT WORLD: THE LEGENDARY LIGHTHOUSE  AND THE BIGGEST LIBRARY KNOWN</pattern><template>The library was a not only cultural but a religious symbol a place where the pagans worshiped their ancestral gods.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ORDER OF  PARABOLANOS  MONKS WAS CHARGED TO GO THROUGH THE STREETS AND WATCH FOR CHRISTIAN MORALITY NOW UNEVEN BY THE PRESENCE OF THE JEWS</pattern><template>The Library, years later.</template></category><category><pattern>ALTHOUGH NONE OF HIPATIA'S WORKS REMAIN IT IS KNOWN THAT SHE WAS AN EXCEPTIONAL ASTRONOMER WELL KNOWN FOR THE MATHEMATICAL STUDY OF CONICAL CURVES</pattern><template>One thousand, two hundred years later in the 17th century, astronomer Johannes Kepler described that one of those curves the ellipse, governs the movement of the planets.</template></category><category><pattern>ORESTES WAS OUTLAWED FOREVER AND CIRILO TOOK CONTROL OF THE POWER IN ALEXANDRIA</pattern><template>Later, Cirilo was declared a Saint and Doctor of the Church.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LATE FOURTH CENTURY A D  THE ROMAN EMPIRE BEGAN TO CRUMBLE</pattern><template>Alexandria, in the province of Egypt, still retained some of its lustre possessing two of the Seven Wonders of the ancient world: The legendary lighthouse, and the biggest library known.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LIBRARY WAS A NOT ONLY CULTURAL BUT A RELIGIOUS SYMBOL A PLACE WHERE THE PAGANS WORSHIPED THEIR ANCESTRAL GODS</pattern><template>The traditional pagan worship in the city now coexisted with the Jews, and an unstoppable religion up to now banned: Christianity Library of Alexandria, 391 A.D.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TRADITIONAL PAGAN WORSHIP IN THE CITY NOW COEXISTED WITH THE JEWS  AND AN UNSTOPPABLE RELIGION UP TO NOW BANNED: CHRISTIANITY LIBRARY OF ALEXANDRIA  391 A D</pattern><template>After taking the library, many pagans were converted.</template></category><category><pattern>THE EMPIRE WAS SPLIT IN TWO FOREVER</pattern><template>Many Christians saw this as a sign of the end of the world and decided to prepare by practicing a more holy life.</template></category><category><pattern>HIPATIA CONTINUED TEACHING AND RESEARCHING WHILE HER FORMER STUDENTS HELD IMPORTANT POSITIONS IN THE SOCIAL ELITE</pattern><template>The empire was split in two forever.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LIBRARY  YEARS LATER</pattern><template>The body of Hipatia was mutilated and the remains were dragged through the streets and burned in a fire.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BODY OF HIPATIA WAS MUTILATED AND THE REMAINS WERE DRAGGED THROUGH THE STREETS AND BURNED IN A FIRE</pattern><template>Orestes was outlawed forever and Cirilo took control of the power in Alexandria.</template></category><category><pattern>MANY CHRISTIANS SAW THIS AS A SIGN OF THE END OF THE WORLD AND DECIDED TO PREPARE BY PRACTICING A MORE HOLY LIFE</pattern><template>The order of  Parabolanos  monks was charged to go through the streets and watch for Christian morality now uneven by the presence of the Jews.</template></category><category><pattern>LATER  CIRILO WAS DECLARED A SAINT AND DOCTOR OF THE CHURCH</pattern><template>Although none of Hipatia's works remain it is known that she was an exceptional astronomer well known for the mathematical study of conical curves.</template></category></AIML>