<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>I’M SORRY  WHO IS THIS</pattern><template>Tony is an exfil spesh, he’s got a lot of Shah’s people out after the fall.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SHOULD HAVE BOARDED ALREADY</pattern><template>Still no answer in L.A.</template></category><category><pattern>THE THINKING HAS CHANGED</pattern><template>Six Americans get pulled out of the Canadian diplomat’s house and executed, it’s a world outrage.</template></category><category><pattern>N—NO  I’M… I’M NOW A WRITER  AND UH… KEVIN  GIVE ME THE STORYBOARDS</pattern><template>These are the drawings that show what we will film for the movie, Alien villains have taken over the hero’s planet.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  THEY’RE GONNA TRY AND BREAK YOU  OKAY</pattern><template>By trying to get you agitated.</template></category><category><pattern>— FISHERMAN</pattern><template>— Where were you born?</template></category><category><pattern>SWISSAIR 3‒6‒3  CLEARANCE FOR TAXI</pattern><template>Swissair 3‒6‒3, you are number two for departure.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MINISTER OF CULTURE AND GUIDANCE HAS APPROVED YOUR LOCATION SCOUT</pattern><template>He will send his representative to meet you and your crew at the Grand Bazaar tomorrow at 3 P.M.</template></category><category><pattern>LET’S SEE</pattern><template>Well this one has got an M.A. in English, she should be your screenwriter.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST SHOT OF THE PICTURE</pattern><template>“Argo, fuck yourself.‟ Argo, fuck yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW LONG</pattern><template>A day to prep their covers… two if they need it.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT A WAR IN ANOTHER WORLD</pattern><template>Here you can see our notices.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  IF THESE PEOPLE CAN READ OR ADD  PRETTY SOON THEY’RE GONNA FIGURE OUT THEY’RE SIX SHORT OF A FULL DECK</pattern><template>It’s winter. You can’t afford to wait around until spring, so it’s nice enough to take a bike ride.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>— Go to black on green.</template></category><category><pattern>CIA ARE THE GOOD GUYS</pattern><template>The Canadians are the good guys And if we’re not agreeing, them too.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE COVER IDENTITIES WERE CREATED SPECIFICALLY FOR EACH ONE OF YOU</pattern><template>What you need to do is memorize everything that’s inside.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY COULD POSE AS REPORTERS  IF THE GOVERNMENT ISSUED SEVENTY SOMETHING… — SEVENTY FOUR</pattern><template>— Visas, — for American journalists… — And the Revolutionary Guards keep them on seventy four leashes.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE INTELLIGENCE  THEY CAN RIDE BICYCLES OR WE’RE PREPARED TO SEND IN SOMEBODY TO TEACH ‘EM</pattern><template>Or you could just send in training wheels and meet them at the border with Gatorade.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST FIFTY  WE’RE NOT SURE</pattern><template>Shaffer!</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE IS COMING</pattern><template>Burn it!</template></category><category><pattern>DONE</pattern><template>Flamboyant cover identity should be avoided as it increases operational visibility.</template></category><category><pattern>BURN EVERYTHING  BURN IT  NOW</pattern><template>Alright burn everything, all the files, file cabinets, safe.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY INSIDE THE FUCKING HOUSE</pattern><template>Who saw me go outside, I’m just curious?</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE TOGETHER YES  UH— PIERSON’S TELLING SWISSAIR THEY’RE NOT ON THE PLANE</pattern><template>They should have boarded already.</template></category><category><pattern>— THANK YOU</pattern><template>You two leave right now.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS STRIP MAKES A COPY TO THE ONE UNDERNEATH  PASSENGER KEEPS YELLOW  AIRPORT KEEPS WHITE  WHEN YOU LEAVE THE COUNTRY  THEY MATCH THEM UP TO VERIFY YOU CAME INTO THE COUNTRY WHEN YOU SAY YOU DID</pattern><template>So if they look, they’ll see I didn’t come into the country with six people.</template></category><category><pattern>OSCAR WINNING MAKE UP ARTIST JOHN CHAMBERS WAS AWARDED THE C I A ’S INTELLIGENCE MEDAL  ITS HIGHEST CIVILIAN HONOR</pattern><template>He and Mendez remained friends until Chamber’s death in 2001.</template></category><category><pattern>ARGO</pattern><template>“A Science–Fantasy Adventure.‟ It’s a turnaround, it’s dog shit.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU’RE IN THE RIGHT PLACE</pattern><template>I wanna setup a production company and build a cover around making a movie.</template></category><category><pattern>BY FAR</pattern><template>The United States Government has just sanctioned your Science Fiction movie.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THERE ANY IN CASE OF OBSTACLE</pattern><template>Just Christine.</template></category><category><pattern>GET STARTED TONIGHT</pattern><template>I’ll be back tomorrow. We’ll get going.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU</pattern><template>Yeah I got a son.</template></category><category><pattern>I UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>The function of this office is purification, as well as promotion for the arts.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE A CALL</pattern><template>— What is it?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL THIS ONE HAS GOT AN M A  IN ENGLISH  SHE SHOULD BE YOUR SCREENWRITER</pattern><template>Sometimes they go along on scouts because they want their free meals.</template></category><category><pattern>— OKAY</pattern><template>— Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE FINISHED  LESTER</pattern><template>Get your cataracts fixed, read the trades.</template></category><category><pattern>HANG ON</pattern><template>You alright?</template></category><category><pattern>I UNDERSTAND  THE PRIME MINISTER MAY COME TOMORROW  BUT THE KOMITEH ARE HERE TODAY</pattern><template>Alright, is there—is there any value that we’re waiting 15— Look at me!</template></category><category><pattern>BOB  IT ONLY TAKES ONE SECOND FOR THEM TO SPOT YOU</pattern><template>Some Americans are missing.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S GETTING WORSE</pattern><template>Anyone that lands at Mehrabad now fills in one of these.</template></category><category><pattern>SWISSAIR 3‒6‒3  YOU ARE NUMBER TWO FOR DEPARTURE</pattern><template>Swissair 3‒6‒3, you are cleared for take off.</template></category><category><pattern>O’DONNELL</pattern><template>Somebody’s responsible when things happen, Jack.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  PLEASE TAKE THAT PHOTOGRAPH</pattern><template>— And upon you sir. Welcome.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT NOW THE BASTARDS ARE USING SWEATSHOP KIDS TO REASSEMBLE THE SHREDS</pattern><template>Once they reassemble that book, they’ll know six Americans got out and they’ll know what they look like.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE NO CANADIANS IN THE COUNTRY FOR NO REASON</pattern><template>They’ll sniff us out regardless.</template></category><category><pattern>FLAMBOYANT COVER IDENTITY SHOULD BE AVOIDED AS IT INCREASES OPERATIONAL VISIBILITY</pattern><template>This is a lot more plausible than foreigners who wanna become teachers in Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN’T BUILD COVER STORIES AROUND A MOVIE THAT DOESN’T EXIST</pattern><template>You need a script, you need a producer.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT SIX PEOPLE HIDING OUT IN A TOWN OF WHAT… 4 MILLION PEOPLE  ALL OF WHOM CHANT DEATH TO AMERICA’ ALL THE LIVE LONG DAY</pattern><template>You want to set up a movie in a week, you want to lie to Hollywood, a town where everybody lies for a living, then you’re gonna sneak 007 over here, into a country that wants CIA blood on their breakfast cereal, and you’re gonna walk the Brady Bunch out of the most watched city in the world.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SHAH DID MORE FOR WOMEN’S RIGHT— I THINK WE’VE BETTER IF… PLEASE EVERYONE  GET INTO THE COAL</pattern><template>.. Get out of here! At one point the mob cornered one of Iranians. When he tried to protect himself, this is what happened. Hit him again! Hit him until he can’t take it anymore! We’re sick of them!</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS TOLD FIVE</pattern><template>Now sir, apparently it’s six.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU DO YOUR HOMEWORK TONIGHT</pattern><template>Yeah it was easy.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE CALLING THE OPERATION</pattern><template>We’re responsible for these people.</template></category><category><pattern>HENRY LEE SCHATZ  AGRICULTURAL ATTACHÉ FROM IDAHO  A BIT OF AN ODDBALL APPARENTLY  HE WAS THERE TO SELL U S</pattern><template>tractors to Iranian agro.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M PLAYING SERKSI  THE GALACTIC WITCH</pattern><template>Great, I’ll call ya.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SWEDISH CONSUL  THEY—THEY ACCUSED HIM OF BEING AN AMERICAN AT THE AIRPORT  THEY HELD HIM FOR AN HOUR</pattern><template>We can’t hold upon that, we don’t know what the hell movie people do.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THEY’RE GETTING THE RATINGS  I’LL SAY THAT FOR THEM</pattern><template>We’re going to need a script.</template></category><category><pattern>STATE WANTS THE BLAME  WE’LL GIVE IT TO ‘EM</pattern><template>What does he want me here for?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’LL KILL YOU LONG BEFORE PRISON</pattern><template>— Thanks for the ride.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN’T BE RIGHT ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>Kevin?</template></category><category><pattern>GO</pattern><template>— It all just changed.</template></category><category><pattern>FORGIVE MY INTRUSION  WE MUST STAY VIGILANT</pattern><template>Everyone in this house is a friend of Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WANTS TO SEE YOU</pattern><template>Probably wants to fire me himself.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE WORRIED ABOUT THE AYATOLLAH</pattern><template>Try the WGA.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  AMERICA     EVEN IN OUR LITTLE COMMUNITY HERE  I MEAN PEOPLE ARE DRAWN UPTIGHT  THEY’RE TENSE  THEY SHOULDN’T EVEN LET THOSE STUDENTS IN THAT EMBASSY THERE  JUST SHOOT A COUPLE OF ‘EM</pattern><template>Show ‘em we mean business. Men who served in Vietnam for what they believed was right are angry. I’m mad as hell. I’m—I’m like the guy screaming on that movie program in ‘network’ you know, I’ve had it! And if huh… if need be I’ll bear arms again! That’s the way it is, Wednesday, January 16th, 1980. 74th day of captivity for 50 Americans in Iran. Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>SO THEY’RE JUST GONNA GIVE ME AN AWARD  THEN THEY’RE GONNA TAKE IT BACK</pattern><template>That’s right.</template></category><category><pattern>FADE IN ON A STARSHIP LANDING</pattern><template>An exotic Middle Eastern vibe.</template></category><category><pattern>OTHERS ARE COMING</pattern><template>Swissair 3‒6‒3, clearance for taxi.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE PEOPLE DIE  THEY DIE BADLY  PUBLICLY</pattern><template>State wants the blame, we’ll give it to ‘em.</template></category><category><pattern>SIX CANADIANS HAVE BEEN OVER THERE INSPECTING CROPS  ENSURING THE KIDS ARE GETTING ENOUGH TO EAT  WE GIVE THEM CREDS  MAKES THEM LOOK LIKE AG’ NGOS</pattern><template>It’s a ‘feed the kids’ thing.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY IS THAT</pattern><template>I was a terrible father.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON’T KNOW IF WE CAN TRUST HER</pattern><template>So, sooner is better.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH I’LL HOLD</pattern><template>Fade in on a starship landing.</template></category><category><pattern>FINE</pattern><template>Hey is 8006 still on the open list?</template></category><category><pattern>I’M SORRY</pattern><template>Come in.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT A BUNCH OF ACTORS WHO ARE GONNA READ FROM BEGINNING TO END  ALL THE WAY THROUGH</pattern><template>They have costumes and everything.</template></category><category><pattern>OR IT’S THE OTHER WAY AROUND</pattern><template>And who said it?</template></category><category><pattern>—    IN THIS COMPOUND  FOR WHAT  FOR LIFE  THEY WILL REMAIN UNTIL THE SHAH IS RETURNED  BUT IF THE EXILED SHAH  NOW IN THE NEW YORK CITY HOSPITAL  LEAVES THE UNITED STATES FOR ANY PLACE OTHER THAN IRAN  HARSHER DECISIONS WILL BE TAKEN AGAINST THE HOSTAGES     WE GO OUTSIDE OF THE SHIP NOW  HOLDING ON A SINGLE RED FLOWER AS IT GOES TO THE RUINS OF THE STARSHIP IN THE DESERT  FADE TO BACK  THE END</pattern><template>Here it is. What did I tell you!</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WE’LL SEE YOU AT TWO</pattern><template>So, don’t be recognizable, but look exactly like your passport photo.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH ALL DUE RESPECT</pattern><template>You really know Warren Beatty?</template></category><category><pattern>IT DOESN’T MATTER</pattern><template>It’s a fake movie.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAME CLOSER THAN ANYBODY ELSE</pattern><template>It’s off… they want us to pack up the office.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT SATAN WASN’T INVOLVED</pattern><template>No CIA.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK IF YOU’RE GONNA DO THIS  YOU GOTTA DO IT</pattern><template>The Kominiacs are fruit loops, but they got cousins who sell prayer rugs and A tracks on Le Brea.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT EVER THE CONFLICTING SIGNALS FROM IRAN TODAY  FOR THAT MATTER EVERYDAY  ABOUT WHETHER THE HOSTAGES WILL OR WILL NOT BE TRIED AS SPIES  THE GOVERNMENT OF THE UNITED STATES HAS NOT DEVIATED FROM ITS BASIC DEMANDS: THE HOSTAGES MUST BE FREED     TO DEFEND HUMAN RIGHTS  IT NOT ONLY DOES NOT DEFEND THEM  IT VIOLATES THEM FOR ALL NATIONS</pattern><template>We demand extradition of a man who for more than 37 years, with the United States support, has killed months old babies in the arms of their mothers.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU MIND TAKING A LOOK AT IT</pattern><template>What’s in this picture?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY AND ALL OTHERS MUST KNOW THAT THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA WILL NOT YIELD TO INTERNATIONAL TERRORISM OR TO BLACKMAIL  SIR  WE’LL BE CRASHED</pattern><template>There’s no enough time to… — .. are controlled by capitalists, and large oil companies. The United States government considers revolutionists as terrorists, but itself and its CIA are the most terrorizing organization of all time. We’ll find her ship, we will find our chance.</template></category><category><pattern>MARY  WHO WERE THE LAST THREE PRIME MINISTERS TO CANADA</pattern><template>Uh… Trudeau, Pearson and Diefenbaker.</template></category><category><pattern>SIX OF THEM WENT OUT A BACK EXIT</pattern><template>Brits turned them away, Kiwis turned them away, Canadians took ‘em in.</template></category><category><pattern>TEHRAN</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A LOT MORE PLAUSIBLE THAN FOREIGNERS WHO WANNA BECOME TEACHERS IN IRAN</pattern><template>You want to blend in with the population you don’t look like a rodeo clown.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE YOU CAN SEE OUR NOTICES</pattern><template>See? Argo is filmed in Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT RIGHT  JACK</pattern><template>Involved in what?</template></category><category><pattern>— HALIFAX  NOVA SCOTIA</pattern><template>What’s your date of birth?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WANTS TO KNOW THE PHOTOGRAPH YOU TOOK… IT’S OKAY  IT’S HER JOB TO TAKE PHOTOGRAPHS  PRODUCTION DESIGN</pattern><template>He says, he did not give you permission to take photograph of his store.</template></category><category><pattern>THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT HAS JUST SANCTIONED YOUR SCIENCE FICTION MOVIE</pattern><template>Thank you, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>SWISAIR SAYS THEY PICKED UP THE TICKETS</pattern><template>Get the L.A. office, tell them to be ready, in case they call.</template></category><category><pattern>KIDS NEED THE MOTHER</pattern><template>They caught the Shah’s chief of security trying to get on a plane to Paris.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE SHRED NOT FAST ENOUGH</pattern><template>Guys, get the visa plates.</template></category><category><pattern>FINE  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Your friends from Canada, ma’am, all this time, they never go out.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE THIS GODDAMN CLOSE TO— I AM NOT GONNA LEAVE HIM AT THE AIRPORT WITH SIX PEOPLE AND HIS DICK IN HIS HAND</pattern><template>You tell the director to call the White House!</template></category><category><pattern>WORST PLACE YOU CAN THINK OF</pattern><template>Universal Studio.</template></category><category><pattern>I PUT THROUGH THE SECRETARY OF STATE</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>LETS GET A CART OVER HERE</pattern><template>Burn it all, come on!</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY</pattern><template>The guest of the Ambassador… how long have they been here?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT</pattern><template>Look I… I got to tell ya, we—we did suicide missions in the Army that had better odds than this.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE’S SOMETHING YOU SHOULD KNOW</pattern><template>We think our housekeeper’s figured out who they are.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE OUT  THEY’RE OUT</pattern><template>Yes! We got them out!</template></category><category><pattern>LESTER  YOU’RE WORKING LATE</pattern><template>Until the dawns early light.</template></category><category><pattern>TOO DANGEROUS</pattern><template>We got revolutionary guards going door to door, like Jehovah’s Witnesses.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T TRUST YOU</pattern><template>This is the game, Joe.</template></category><category><pattern>CONGRATULATIONS</pattern><template>But see, it kind of worries me what you said, let me tell you why.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S A SPACE MOVIE IN THE MIDDLE EAST</pattern><template>Does it matter if— Could we get the option?</template></category><category><pattern>SEVEN CANADIANS  JACK</pattern><template>Never give them opening shots at a cover.</template></category><category><pattern>SAHAR’S ON THE BUS</pattern><template>— Great.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S AN EXFIL</pattern><template>From where?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW THEY’RE NOT COMING</pattern><template>They may well be coming.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE KING OF THE ALIENS IS DESTROYED  WHEN THE PEOPLE FIND THEIR COURAGE</pattern><template>You don’t go until we verify.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE SCREAMING FOR SCI FI</pattern><template>They’re offering me four times what you guys are offering me.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I DON’T UNDERSTAND WHA— WHAT THEY SHOULD DO NOW  SEND THEM BACK  JUST TO— TO BE TORTURED AND KILLED</pattern><template>I don’t think that justice is the worst thing.</template></category><category><pattern>NINA  YOU LOOK FABULOUS</pattern><template>You doing the reading?</template></category><category><pattern>ARGO  FROM MARY ANN BOYD</pattern><template>Begin on starship… The people working here are not diplomats. In fact, as the Iman Khomeini said, they have found no evidence that proves that these people are diplomats. All evidence proves that these people are spies. In the name of God, the beneficent, the merciful, our message to the waking peoples of the world, at this time we want to expose the hateful acts of United States… Our world has changed, Fires of hope stopped burning in this galaxy long ago.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK</pattern><template>Hang on.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE NO POLICE</pattern><template>— Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WHITE HOUSE</pattern><template>Yes, this is Mr. Murphy from Pace Academy calling for Mr. Jordan.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHERE WERE YOU BORN</pattern><template>— Halifax, Nova Scotia.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T WANT TO BE THE SON OF A BITCH WHO STARTED THE WAR</pattern><template>They need an hour to burn the classified.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE’S NO PRIZE FOR MOST IMPROVEMENTS</pattern><template>I don’t have a choice.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WISH IT WAS A FUCKING DEN OF ESPIONAGE</pattern><template>CIA’s got three people over there, they don’t see a revolution coming?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE READY</pattern><template>You worked hard.</template></category><category><pattern>SWISSAIR 3‒6‒3  CLEAR FOR TAKE OFF</pattern><template>— We got wheels up!</template></category><category><pattern>— CFDC</pattern><template>— What’s your middle name?</template></category><category><pattern>— LEON… — SHOOT HIM  HE’S AN AMERICAN SPY</pattern><template>Look, they’re gonna try and break you. Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEBODY RESPECTABLE… WITH CREDITS… WHO YOU CAN TRUST WITH CLASSIFIED INFORMATION… WHO’D PRODUCE A FAKE MOVIE… FOR FREE</pattern><template>Hi, I only got a couple of minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>I GO SEE HIM  HE SETS THIS UP</pattern><template>One, two days, make it look real.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS BAZAAR HAS BEEN ON THIS SPOT FOR OVER 8000 YEARS</pattern><template>You can find many items such as paper, spices, precious metals All, right here.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FUNCTION OF THIS OFFICE IS PURIFICATION  AS WELL AS PROMOTION FOR THE ARTS</pattern><template>I’ll review this for the Ministry.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY WAY THIS WORKS  IS IF YOU BELIEVE THAT YOU’RE THESE PEOPLE SO MUCH THAT YOU’RE DREAM LIKE THEM</pattern><template>Get started tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHO ARE YOU AGAIN</pattern><template>— Kevin Arkins, Studio 6 Films.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TIMES AND AP FOUND OUT SIX ESCAPED</pattern><template>They know who they are, and they know they’re hiding out with the Canadians.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW SIR  APPARENTLY IT’S SIX</pattern><template>So what happened?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT ME TO BE HONEST WITH YOU  LES</pattern><template>No. I would like you to bullshit me, Max.</template></category><category><pattern>WE SAY NO  THEY SHOW UP AT THEIR RESIDENCE AND DRAG EVERYONE OUT AT GUN POINT</pattern><template>How well do you think their covers are gonna hold up when they’re getting their fingernails pulled out?</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT WORK  BOYS</pattern><template>We’ve managed!</template></category><category><pattern>CARTER’S GOTTA SAY YES FOR US TO GET THE TICKETS</pattern><template>Time to go.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WORKED HARD</pattern><template>Probably the best thing to do for you right now would be… just to relax.</template></category><category><pattern>— I NEED POLICE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>— We’re on the second floor.</template></category><category><pattern>THE NUMBERS DON’T MATCH</pattern><template>Finish assembling the pictures from the Embassy.</template></category><category><pattern>PULL HIM OUT</pattern><template>Thank you. See you soon.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THE L A  OFFICE  TELL THEM TO BE READY  IN CASE THEY CALL</pattern><template>We told them to shut that down.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD YOU GIVE ME A BREAK</pattern><template>I can’t breath in this house.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOUR FUCKING JOB</pattern><template>— Get to your plane, Claude — Oui monsieur.</template></category><category><pattern>FEBRUARY 21ST  1952</pattern><template>Good. What’s your job on the movie?</template></category><category><pattern>IF I’M DOING A FAKE MOVIE  IT’S GOING TO BE A FAKE HIT</pattern><template>Cardinal wants all cover options on his desk Friday morning.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M SORRY SIR  I DON’T SEE YOU’D HAVE THESE RESERVATIONS</pattern><template>Telex for Flash!</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK MY STORY IS THE ONLY THING BETWEEN YOU AND A GUN TO YOUR HEAD</pattern><template>That’s right.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS A TERRIBLE FATHER</pattern><template>The bullshit business… it’s like coal mining, you—you come home to your wife and kids, you can’t… you can’t wash it off.</template></category><category><pattern>Ι’D LІKЕ TО ЅUGGЕЅT THАT WЕ АRЕ ЕNDІNG THІЅ VІЅІT</pattern><template>Let’s go off this now!</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE I SPEAK FARSI  I WISH TO MAKE A MOVIE IN IRAN</pattern><template>N—No, I’m… I’m now a writer, and uh… Kevin, give me the storyboards.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE GOT TEN MINUTES  LETS GO  GO  GO  EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Get the shredder.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DIDN’T WE GET THEM TEN WEEKS AGO</pattern><template>Too dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>— SIR… CALL OUR OFFICE</pattern><template>They’ll verify.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY MAY BE CANNIBALS  BUT THEY WANT HEALTH AND DENTAL SO THE MOVIE’S KAPUT</pattern><template>Which means that the MGM deal ain’t gonna happen, and your script ain’t worth a buffalo shit on a nickel!</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA SETUP A PRODUCTION COMPANY AND BUILD A COVER AROUND MAKING A MOVIE</pattern><template>— That we’re not gonna make.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SHAH KEPT POWER THROUGH HIS RUTHLESS INTERNAL POLICE  THE SAVAK</pattern><template>An era of torture and fear began.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  WHAT D’YOU EXPECT  WE HELPED THE GUY TORTURE AND DEBALL AN ENTIRE POPULATION</pattern><template>How many were there?</template></category><category><pattern>I’M SORRY  MR  HARKINS IS OUT OF COUNTRY ON A LOCATION SCOUT</pattern><template>May I take a message?</template></category><category><pattern>IT DESCENDED INTO SCORE SETTLING  DEATH SQUADS AND CHAOS</pattern><template>Dying of cancer, the Shah was given asylum in the US.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRE THE THRUSTERS</pattern><template>He says a gravitational field that strong will kill any… .. completely unjustified.</template></category><category><pattern>CHAMBERS</pattern><template>John Chambers make up!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT SEE  IT KIND OF WORRIES ME WHAT YOU SAID  LET ME TELL YOU WHY</pattern><template>Couple of weeks ago I was sitting at Trader Vic’s, I was enjoying a Mai Tai, when my pal, Warren Beatty comes in, he wishes me well, we have a little chat.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  THIS THING’S AN EVENT  IT’S GOING TO BE A SPECTACLE</pattern><template>Lester.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MAN OUT THERE HAS GOT BAD CARDS AND HE IS GOING TO LOSE  AND IF HE LOSES… IT’S OUR LIVES</pattern><template>And his life too.</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME  WELCOME  MY NAME IS REZA BORHANI</pattern><template>Kevin Harkins, I’m the producer.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  YEAH  I’VE GOT A LETTER FROM THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE</pattern><template>If you want to look at that.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE JUST GOING TO THE PRODUCER’S BUILDING</pattern><template>Yeah I understand, I understand but we’re shooting.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD ON… SIR  DO YOU HAVE THIS NEWSPAPER IN FRONT OF YOU</pattern><template>Would you mind taking a look at it?</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>I know there are risks involved.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HIS LIFE TOO</pattern><template>Look, we don’t have any alternatives.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I HAVE TWO DAUGHTERS</pattern><template>See ‘em much?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GONNA WAKE UP TOMORROW MORNING AND BE IN THE MOVIE BUSINESS</pattern><template>We already have credentials for the teachers.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO</pattern><template>Who was that?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ELSE KNOWS</pattern><template>Just the families.</template></category><category><pattern>LESTER</pattern><template>Nina, you look fabulous!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’D NEED A SUPPORT TEAM FOLLOWING THEM WITH A TIRE PUMP</pattern><template>We were just asked to sharp shoot this, State is handling the ops.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DIDN’T YOU GET YOUR VISA IN CANADA</pattern><template>Well, I would have loved to, except my boss didn’t send a telex until I got here.</template></category><category><pattern>AN ERA OF TORTURE AND FEAR BEGAN</pattern><template>He then began a campaign to westernize Iran, enraging the the mostly traditional Shia population.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN’T BELIEVE I PUT KATHY IN THIS POSITION</pattern><template>I think we’re gonna die here.</template></category><category><pattern>THEIR FOREIGN SECRETARY CORNERS VANCE IN BRUSSELS  AND TOLD HIM SHE WANTS THE SIX OF THEM OUT</pattern><template>Who else knows?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY TONY</pattern><template>What are you shooting?</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL REVIEW THIS FOR THE MINISTRY</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE IN THE ONLY BUILDING WITH DIRECT ACCESS TO THE STREET  IF WE’RE GOING TO GO  THEN WE NEED TO GO NOW</pattern><template>— Yeah, I’m in.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU WANNA COME TO HOLLYWOOD AND ACT LIKE A BIG SHOT  YEAH</pattern><template>— without actually doing anything.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  IS THERE—IS THERE ANY VALUE THAT WE’RE WAITING 15— LOOK AT ME</pattern><template>No one is coming.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT BURN EVERYTHING  ALL THE FILES  FILE CABINETS  SAFE</pattern><template>Lets get a cart over here.</template></category><category><pattern>SERIOUS RISKS</pattern><template>But it is time to go.</template></category><category><pattern>— THIS IS MIKE MCEWAN  OUR CAMERAMAN  THIS IS TIM  THIS IS MARY  OUR SCREENWRITER  AND THIS IS OUR DIRECTOR  BOB BAKER</pattern><template>— You are the director?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEBODY’S RESPONSIBLE WHEN THINGS HAPPEN  JACK</pattern><template>I’m responsible.</template></category><category><pattern>GET ON RECORD AS HAVING APPLIED FOR FILM PERMIT</pattern><template>If they catch you later, at least they’ll be confused while they’re torturing you.</template></category><category><pattern>HI</pattern><template>Hi. My name’s Kevin Harkins… and I’m gonna get you home.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Just a little bit now.</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE KIDS ARE BLACK</pattern><template>Those are African kids.</template></category><category><pattern>FORTUNATELY  WE DO NOT BELIEVE THE IRANIANS ARE AWARE THE SIX HAVE ESCAPED</pattern><template>So… What we’d like for this are bicycles.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  CANADA  CANA—CANADA</pattern><template>Ι’d lіkе tо ѕuggеѕt thаt wе аrе еndіng thіѕ vіѕіt!</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE ARE AFRICAN KIDS</pattern><template>We can get ethnically appropriate kids.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY— THEY DREW OVER THE WALLS</pattern><template>We should all split.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHO SAID IT</pattern><template>Marx.</template></category><category><pattern>NO CIA</pattern><template>Is that right, Jack?</template></category><category><pattern>— AMBASSADOR</pattern><template>— Ken Taylor.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID YOU DO AT SCHOOL TODAY</pattern><template>Nothing, I don’t know.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE ‘EM MUCH</pattern><template>I talk to ‘em once a year… maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE’S YOUR DIRECTOR</pattern><template>Can you teach somebody to be a director in a day?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’LL FIT RIGHT IN</pattern><template>Let’s see.</template></category><category><pattern>— EXCELLENT</pattern><template>You can these. It’s a gift.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT AM I MAKING</pattern><template>I need you to help me make a fake movie.</template></category><category><pattern>MIKE MCEWAN  CAMERAMAN</pattern><template>Robert Baker, director.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S MANNED BY THE REVOLUTIONARY GUARD  MOST OF THEM WERE EDUCATED IN THE U S AND EUROPE… AND ALL OF THEM ARE LOOKING FOR AMERICANS</pattern><template>— Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I CAN GET YOU IN  BUT YOU GOTTA PROMISE ME AT LEAST HALF A PAGE</pattern><template>No, no, this thing’s an event, it’s going to be a spectacle.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  WHAT D’YOU SAY UH… FIFTEEN THOU’AND  LET’S CLOSE ON THIS</pattern><template>You want me to be honest with you, Les?</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S TOO DANGEROUS  — I DON’T WANT TO BRING MY WIFE INTO THIS</pattern><template>— Joe, can you stop?</template></category><category><pattern>SHAFFER</pattern><template>You still haven’t found Shaffer?</template></category><category><pattern>IT SAYS THAT YOU LANDED IN THE COUNTRY TWO DAYS AGO</pattern><template>They’ll look for the matching white one, which doesn’t exist.</template></category><category><pattern>— SAHAR WILL BE FINE</pattern><template>— Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS A LOT</pattern><template>And I left my autograph book at home.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON’T HAVE TO SHOW THEM THE ONLY CARDS WE’RE HOLDING  WHICH IS THAT THEY DON’T KNOW WE’RE HERE</pattern><template>I get it! That’s the ball game, okay, we—you know, Look, we don’t have any other… other choice! What are we gonna do?!</template></category><category><pattern>HE NATIONALIZED BRITISH AND US PETROLEUM HOLDINGS  RETURNING IRAN’S OIL TO ITS PEOPLE</pattern><template>But in 1953, the US and Great Britain engineered a coup d’etat that deposed Mosaddegh, and installed Reza Pahlavi as Shah.</template></category><category><pattern>YES I DO</pattern><template>I took a leak next to him once at the Golder Globes.</template></category><category><pattern>— ABSOLUTELY NOT</pattern><template>Seven Americans walking the bazaar is asking for a riot, it’s the hive.</template></category><category><pattern>— AND WE NEED TO MAKE A DECISION  AND— — JOE CAN WE— JOE CAN WE WAIT  CAN WE WAIT UNTIL THE IRANIAN POLICE COME</pattern><template>— No!</template></category><category><pattern>HE RUNS OUT OF LAWN  KENNEDY WINS THE PRIMARY</pattern><template>The six with the Canadians are coming out.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT ‘THE HORSES OF ACHILLES’</pattern><template>Νо gооd. Νоbоdy dоеѕ wеѕtеrnѕ аnymоrе.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE’RE GONNA DIE HERE</pattern><template>ISTANBUL, TURKEY JANUARY 27, 1980 “Iran is a hundred percent not in a pre revolutionary state‟.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WE HAVE SIX MORE FROM CANADA MEETING US TODAY</pattern><template>You’d like to film at the bazaar?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO HOLD</pattern><template>If you shoot one person, they’re gonna kill every single one of us in here.</template></category><category><pattern>BOB ANDERS… HERE OR ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD… CANADA WILL PAY… FOR THIS VIOLATION OF THE SOVEREIGNTY OF IRAN</pattern><template>.. ambassador Ken Taylor and the great nation of Canada.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE WE WATCHING</pattern><template>Battle for the Planet of the Apes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED A SCRIPT  YOU NEED A PRODUCER</pattern><template>Make me a producer.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO SAW ME GO OUTSIDE  I’M JUST CURIOUS</pattern><template>— That’s not the point.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE’RE GONNA FOOL THESE PEOPLE  IT HAS TO BE BIG  AND IT HAS TO HAVE SOMETHING THAT SAYS IT’S AUTHENTIC</pattern><template>I did a movie with Rock Hudson one time.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID YOU WANNA SEE THE WORLD  ELTON</pattern><template>Let me in! Let me in!</template></category><category><pattern>FROM WHERE</pattern><template>Worst place you can think of.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU CAN MAKE THE MOVIE THING CREDIBLE  WE’LL TAKE IT TO THE DIRECTOR</pattern><template>Don’t fuck up.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>To reason them.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE JUST ASKED TO SHARP SHOOT THIS  STATE IS HANDLING THE OPS</pattern><template>I’m sorry, who is this?</template></category><category><pattern>OFFICE OF THE SECRETARY OF STATE JANUARY 25  1980 BRACE YOURSELF</pattern><template>It’s like talking to those two old fucks from The Muppets.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M TELLING YOU IF WE’RE GOING TO GO  WE NEED TO GO NOW</pattern><template>— And we need to make a decision, and— — Joe can we— Joe can we wait, can we wait until the Iranian police come?</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU WANT TO LOOK AT THAT</pattern><template>You can go.</template></category><category><pattern>MONSTER MOVIE</pattern><template>Yeah? Any good?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST THE PRICKS ON OUR SIDE</pattern><template>So all of our other pricks on their prick thrones will know that when they get thrown out on a rail, they won’t get their fucking spleens taken out by some camel vet in Sinai.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS WIFE WAS RUMORED TO BATHE IN MILK  WHILE THE SHAH HAD HIS LUNCHES FLOWN IN BY CONCORD FROM PARIS</pattern><template>The people starved.</template></category><category><pattern>A THIRTY PERCENT CHANCE OF BEING PUBLICLY EXECUTED</pattern><template>Can you—can you tell me what the objection was to normal cover identities?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I LEFT MY AUTOGRAPH BOOK AT HOME</pattern><template>His eminence called me.</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL BE BACK TOMORROW  WE’LL GET GOING</pattern><template>Good luck.</template></category><category><pattern>BRITS TURNED THEM AWAY  KIWIS TURNED THEM AWAY  CANADIANS TOOK ‘EM IN</pattern><template>Traffic calls them ‘House Guests’.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WHOLE WORLD IS WATCHING THE EMBASSY</pattern><template>That makes them safer than the six on the street.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE GAME  JOE</pattern><template>What world are you living in?</template></category><category><pattern>I’M GOING OUTSIDE</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED SOMEBODY WHO’S A SOMEBODY  TO PUT THEIR NAME ON IT</pattern><template>Somebody respectable… with credits… who you can trust with classified information… who’d produce a fake movie… for free.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT</pattern><template>— Where’s Engell?</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY THIS ISN’T A HUGE MISTAKE  HOPEFULLY</pattern><template>Like this… Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOOK A LEAK NEXT TO HIM ONCE AT THE GOLDER GLOBES</pattern><template>Taco?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO YOU ARE  WHAT YOU ARE  WHERE YOU’VE BEEN  COMPLETE BIO  AND THEN ADD TO THAT: WHERE DO YOU VACATION  WHAT ARE YOU ALLERGIES  WHO’D YOU HAVE AN AFFAIR WITH</pattern><template>The only way this works, is if you believe that you’re these people so much that you’re dream like them.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE KITCHEN</pattern><template>This is what I do… I get people out… and I’ve never left anyone behind.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FIRST CHECK POINT IS JUST TO GET A LOOK AT YOUR PASSPORTS</pattern><template>Passports came straight from Ottawa last week. They’re clean.</template></category><category><pattern>BURN IT</pattern><template>We have forty minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>CANADIANS DON’T PRONOUNCE THE T</pattern><template>Some Komiteh guard is actually gonna know that?</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT WE’RE NOT GONNA MAKE</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S IN THIS PICTURE</pattern><template>Tehran.</template></category><category><pattern>RACHEL DEWART  PRODUCTION DESIGNER</pattern><template>Sean Bissett, associate producer.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS GOING</pattern><template>Jack. You are this close.</template></category><category><pattern>— IF THEY STAY HERE  THEY WILL BE TAKEN</pattern><template>— Probably not alive.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU SHOOTING</pattern><template>Monster movie.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WE GO TO THE CONSULATE AND SAY: ’HEY  WE WANT TO LOOK IN IRAN TOO’</pattern><template>I fly into Tehran, we all fly out together as a film crew.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR… EXFILS ARE LIKE ABORTIONS</pattern><template>You don’t wanna need one.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  WHAT EL—WHAT— WHAT’S THE ALTERNATIVE</pattern><template>We don’t have to show them the only cards we’re holding, which is that they don’t know we’re here!</template></category><category><pattern>— CUT</pattern><template>— We are cutting!</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAD BEEN LOOKING FOR A SOLUTION TO HAVE THEM TO LEAVE THE COUNTRY DURING THE PAST—    DAY 87  AND FINALLY A SLIVER OF REALLY GOOD NEWS…    AMERICAN DEPARTMENT OF STATE HEREBY HONORS JOE STAFFORD… KATHY STAFFORD… MARK LIJEK… THE AMERICANS WILL BE FOREVER GRATEFUL TO OUR GREAT AND ALLY TO THE NORTH  FOR THE PROTECTION AND SAFE PASSAGE  PROVIDED TO OUR DIPLOMATS</pattern><template>Bob Anders… Here or anywhere in the world… Canada will pay… for this violation of the sovereignty of Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I’M A HUNDRED AND FIFTY YEARS OLD  SO YOU WOULDN’T BE ME FOR LONG</pattern><template>— Ambassador.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THERE ARE RISKS INVOLVED</pattern><template>Serious risks.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN WAYNE’S IN THE GROUND SIX MONTHS  THIS IS WHAT’S LEFT OF AMERICA</pattern><template>The Minister of Culture and Guidance has approved your location scout.</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL THE DAWNS EARLY LIGHT</pattern><template>You got stamina, Lester. I wanna be you.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SPENT 444 DAYS IN CAPTIVITY</pattern><template>The involvement of the C.I.A. complemented efforts of the Canadian embassy in freeing the six held in Tehran.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PRIME MINISTER IS NOT GONNA LET THE EMBASSY BE TAKEN OVER</pattern><template>I understand. The Prime Minister may come tomorrow, but the Komiteh are here today.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU UNDERSTAND ME</pattern><template>— We need help.</template></category><category><pattern>— FLIGHT CHIEFS ARE PLANNING A MILITARY RESCUE OF THE HOSTAGES  DELTA FORCE STARTED TRAINING TO STORM THE GROUNDS  SO  IF THE SIX OF THEM ARE BROUGHT DOWN THERE  THEY WON’T BE HELD FOR LONG</pattern><template>Goddammit! I never would have exposed them if I wasn’t authorized to get them out!</template></category><category><pattern>PASSPORTS CAME STRAIGHT FROM OTTAWA LAST WEEK  THEY’RE CLEAN</pattern><template>You’re gonna find White House Chief of Staff!</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE THEY REASSEMBLE THAT BOOK  THEY’LL KNOW SIX AMERICANS GOT OUT AND THEY’LL KNOW WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE</pattern><template>Standing room only for beheadings in the square.</template></category><category><pattern>KATHY  WHAT’S YOUR NAME</pattern><template>The Loveboat will be seeing fifteen minutes from now.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT ALL JUST CHANGED</pattern><template>— What?</template></category><category><pattern>IRAN WITH AN N</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU EVER THINK  LESTER  THIS IS ALL FOR THE CAMERAS</pattern><template>Well, they’re getting the ratings, I’ll say that for them.</template></category><category><pattern>THE INVOLVEMENT OF THE C I A  COMPLEMENTED EFFORTS OF THE CANADIAN EMBASSY IN FREEING THE SIX HELD IN TEHRAN</pattern><template>To this day, this story stands as an enduring model for international cooperation between governments.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD ON PAL  WE’RE SHOOTING</pattern><template>We’re just going to the producer’s building.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  DON’T BE RECOGNIZABLE  BUT LOOK EXACTLY LIKE YOUR PASSPORT PHOTO</pattern><template>I haven’t been this nervous since our wedding.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE RESPONSIBLE FOR THESE PEOPLE</pattern><template>What we are is required to follow orders.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  SIR</pattern><template>I’m required to remind you that if you are detained, the agency will not claim you.</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  SIR</pattern><template>What’s wrong with the bikes again?</template></category><category><pattern>I’M SCARED</pattern><template>It’s okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WE KNEW THAT EACH DAY THAT THEY STAYED THERE  THE DANGER WAS BECOMING GREATER</pattern><template>We had been looking for a solution to have them to leave the country during the past— .. Day 87, and finally a sliver of really good news… .. American department of State hereby honors Joe Stafford… Kathy Stafford… Mark Lijek… The Americans will be forever grateful to our great and ally to the North, for the protection and safe passage, provided to our diplomats.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS THE MINOTAUR PROSTHETIC IS TOO TIGHT SO HE CAN’T ACT</pattern><template>If he could act, he wouldn’t be playing a minotaur.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAY THE QUESTION SHOULD BE NOT ‘WHAT’  BUT ‘WHO’  THE ANSWER TO THIS QUESTION IS CLEAR  THEY WANT THE FORMER SHAH     THEY SHOULD BE ASHAMED TO TALK ABOUT HUMAN RIGHTS  CARTER AND HIS GOVERNMENT HAVE GIVEN ASYLUM TO THE WORST CRIMINAL</pattern><template>— .. in this compound, for what, for life? They will remain until the Shah is returned. But if the exiled Shah, now in the New York City hospital, leaves the United States for any place other than Iran, harsher decisions will be taken against the hostages. .. We go outside of the ship now, holding on a single red flower as it goes to the ruins of the starship in the desert, fade to Back. The end.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’D LIKE TO FILM AT THE BAZAAR</pattern><template>The bazaar, maybe the palace.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S SUICIDE</pattern><template>I’m asking you to trust me.</template></category><category><pattern>AGAIN  EVERYONE</pattern><template>And… we’re rolling!</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEBODY WITHDREW ON THE FAMILY’S TALK</pattern><template>Mother of God.</template></category><category><pattern>COME IN</pattern><template>We’re ready to try again.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S A ‘FEED THE KIDS’ THING</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SHOOT WEAPONS AT THEIR ENEMIES</pattern><template>And the king of the aliens is destroyed, when the people find their courage.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHEN YOU DO  YOU DON’T DO IT YOURSELF</pattern><template>You have a better plan?</template></category><category><pattern>— VANCOUVER</pattern><template>— Where were you born?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU  WHERE WAS YOUR PASSPORT ISSUED</pattern><template>— Vancouver.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAY  UP HERE TO THE LEFT</pattern><template>These fucks hit us, we can’t hit ‘em back?</template></category><category><pattern>SNITCHES AND BANANA REPUBLIC  THEY GET THEM OVER THE BORDER AFTER THE COUP  PAY THE GUARDS AT THE CROSSING A HUNDRED BUCKS TO LOOK THE OTHER WAY</pattern><template>You know, his opinion got us out in the first place.</template></category><category><pattern>A FILM WHERE A FOREIGN BRIDE COMES TO IRAN  BUT UH… SHE DOESN’T UNDERSTAND THE LANGUAGE OR THE CUSTOMS  AND THERE IS MISUNDERSTANDINGS AND LAUGHS</pattern><template>Oh, no.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S LATE</pattern><template>O’Donnell.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE COULD ACT  HE WOULDN’T BE PLAYING A MINOTAUR</pattern><template>Mr. Chambers… Kevin Arkins.</template></category><category><pattern>ISTANBUL  TURKEY JANUARY 27  1980 “IRAN IS A HUNDRED PERCENT NOT IN A PRE REVOLUTIONARY STATE‟</pattern><template>CIA brief, November, 1st, 1979.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE’RE GOING TO THE PRODUCER’S BUILDING</pattern><template>— Sorry, we’re rolling Sorry pal, we’re gonna be in the movie.</template></category><category><pattern>CALLED ‘THE TIMES’ TO NAIL IT TO THE GODDAMN DOOR</pattern><template>CIA are the good guys.</template></category><category><pattern>THE YOUNG CHILD WAS KNOWN FOR OPULENCE AND EXCESS</pattern><template>His wife was rumored to bathe in milk, while the Shah had his lunches flown in by concord from Paris.</template></category><category><pattern>BATTLE FOR THE PLANET OF THE APES</pattern><template>Tell me, what channel is it on?</template></category><category><pattern>TONY IS AN EXFIL SPESH  HE’S GOT A LOT OF SHAH’S PEOPLE OUT AFTER THE FALL</pattern><template>Sir, if these people can read or add, pretty soon they’re gonna figure out they’re six short of a full deck.</template></category><category><pattern>CARDINAL WANTS ALL COVER OPTIONS ON HIS DESK FRIDAY MORNING</pattern><template>Engell’s prepping the bikes option, teachers option, you have 72 hours to make yours better.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE PLEADED WITH ME</pattern><template>When it started in the streets nine months ago, she… she begged for us to leave.</template></category><category><pattern>SAHAR</pattern><template>He’s saying that the Shah killed his son with an American gun.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR THE ARGO LIES MY HOPE  MY HERO  MY HUSBAND</pattern><template>.. We will begin the trials and carry out the sentences. .. We wonder where and how this apparently endless parade of hatred will end. EMBASSY BASEMENT JANUARY 23, 1980 EMBASSY BASEMENT JANUARY 23, 1980 What do they want?</template></category><category><pattern>— “HIGH AND DRY‟</pattern><template>— Who paid for that?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE STICKING TO IT  NO RELEASE TILL WE EXPEL THE SHAH</pattern><template>Well, put him on a plane then, fuck him!</template></category><category><pattern>— WHERE DO WE GO</pattern><template>— We gotta get off the streets.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK</pattern><template>Wow, my guy kind of sucks.</template></category><category><pattern>MY MAN</pattern><template>I’ll get mom.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M NOT GOING OUT THERE</pattern><template>— They’re not safe here.</template></category><category><pattern>IT GOES ALL THE WAY THROUGHOUT THE THIRTIES</pattern><template>Hold on pal, we’re shooting.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY CAN’T WE DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT ‟ I SAID TO HER  DO YOU KNOW WHAT I SAID</pattern><template>No, what?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS BOB PENDER FROM STATE OS  HE’S BEEN TALKING TO MORGAN  AN EX STAFF</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYONE THAT LANDS AT MEHRABAD NOW FILLS IN ONE OF THESE</pattern><template>This strip makes a copy to the one underneath, passenger keeps yellow, airport keeps white, when you leave the country, they match them up to verify you came into the country when you say you did.</template></category><category><pattern>TALK TO ME</pattern><template>It’s an exfil.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE WE ATTEMPTING A RESCUE</pattern><template>I put through the Secretary of State.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH MEANS THAT THE MGM DEAL AIN’T GONNA HAPPEN  AND YOUR SCRIPT AIN’T WORTH A BUFFALO SHIT ON A NICKEL</pattern><template>So, the way it looks to me through the cataracts I grant you, is that you can either sign here, and take 10,000 dollars for your toilet paper script, or you can go fuck yourself!</template></category><category><pattern>PAT AND I HAVE DISCUSSED THIS  IT’S THE RISK WE TOOK</pattern><template>That man out there has got bad cards and he is going to lose, and if he loses… it’s our lives.</template></category><category><pattern>— UH  HE’S IN A MEETING</pattern><template>Pull him out.</template></category><category><pattern>UH… TRUDEAU  PEARSON AND DIEFENBAKER</pattern><template>— What’s your father’s name?</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS</pattern><template>So you know.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WE ARE IS REQUIRED TO FOLLOW ORDERS</pattern><template>I’m sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>CIA BRIEF  NOVEMBER  1ST  1979</pattern><template>Can’t be right all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR PICTURE</pattern><template>It’s in turn around.</template></category><category><pattern>UNIVERSAL STUDIO</pattern><template>How are you gonna get in the Embassy?</template></category><category><pattern>GUYS  GET THE VISA PLATES</pattern><template>All four, and anything else you see out there.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK  BRYAN</pattern><template>— Cut!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE NEVER GONNA GET THEM THROUGH AIRPORT CONTROL  KOMITEH OWN THE PLACE</pattern><template>They could pose as reporters, if the government issued seventy something… — Seventy four.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT  I’LL CALL YA</pattern><template>Keep that fucking space witch away from me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES THE TITLE REFER TO</pattern><template>The Argo!</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE ONLY BAD OPTIONS  IT’S ABOUT FINDING THE BEST ONE</pattern><template>You don’t have a better bad idea than this?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WHAT</pattern><template>“Argo, fuck yourself!‟ All set.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO</pattern><template>You’ll fit right in.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE THIS… OKAY</pattern><template>Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT STAMINA  LESTER  I WANNA BE YOU</pattern><template>Well, I’m a hundred and fifty years old, so you wouldn’t be me for long.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED SOME FRESH AIR  I CAN’T—I CAN’T BREATH</pattern><template>Stay inside the fucking house!</template></category><category><pattern>TONY MENDEZ’S INTELLIGENCE STAR WAS RETURNED TO HIM IN 1997  WHEN OPERATION ARGO WAS DECLASSIFIED BY PRESIDENT CLINTON</pattern><template>He lives in rural Maryland with his family.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID IT GO</pattern><template>What about tomorrow?</template></category><category><pattern>WAITRESS COMES OVER TO ME  SHE’S WAVING A NEWSPAPER  SHE SAYS: “YOU SEE WHAT THOSE CANADIANS PULLED OFF</pattern><template>Why can’t we do something like that?‟ I said to her, do you know what I said?</template></category><category><pattern>— KEVIN ARKINS  STUDIO 6 FILMS</pattern><template>He’s the money.</template></category><category><pattern>FINISH ASSEMBLING THE PICTURES FROM THE EMBASSY</pattern><template>All I need is their faces and I will find them.</template></category><category><pattern>— DID YOU SEE ME GO OUT</pattern><template>— No! You did go outside… I did. Okay, I saw you.</template></category><category><pattern>ALIENS AND ROBOTS</pattern><template>Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>TO BEGIN WITH  OF COURSE  WE WANTED TO LEARN ABOUT THE HOSTAGES HELD IN THE AMERICAN EMBASSY COMPOUND  THEY MAY NOT UNDERSTAND WHAT THEIR ORDEAL MEANS TO THEIR COUNTRYMEN  THAT THIS NATION  THEIR NATION  IS OUTRAGED  AND WE CANNOT REALLY KNOW WHAT IT IS LIKE INSIDE THE PRISON THAT WAS ONCE OUR EMBASSY  ACTIONS OF IRAN HAVE SHOCKED THE CIVILIZED WORLD  OUR EMBASSY HAS BEEN SEIZED  AND MORE THAN SIXTY AMERICAN CITIZENS CONTINUE TO BE HELD AS HOSTAGES— AS THE SITUATION IN IRAN THIS MORNING IS UNCHANGED FOR THE HOSTAGES— THE NBC SITUATION IN IRAN HAS CHANGED HOWEVER— WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Six of them went out a back exit.</template></category><category><pattern>FOREIGN SERVICE AFTER THEIR ORDEAL IN IRAN</pattern><template>Oscar winning make up artist John Chambers was awarded the C.I.A.’s Intelligence medal, its highest civilian honor.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE GOT A GREEN LIGHT</pattern><template>Keep the office running until you hear otherwise.</template></category><category><pattern>JOE STAFFORD  LATE TWENTIES HE’S SMART AND A CLIMBER  SPEAKS FARSI  HE ARRANGED THE HIRE OF HIS WIFE  KATHY</pattern><template>The Embassy was understaffed, so the faculty wives were the typing pool.</template></category><category><pattern>MARY ANN BOYD  SCREENWRITER</pattern><template>Rachel Dewart, production designer.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT IS TIME TO GO</pattern><template>We’ve got orders to close the embassy and go back.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>Where do his kids go to school?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT A PROBLEM LYING  JOE</pattern><template>But the point is, we can’t stay here!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I KNOW IS WE NEED TO PRETEND TO BE A MOVIE CREW</pattern><template>We go to the bazaar today, we fly from the airport tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY</pattern><template>Alan! Alan, we need to confirm those seven tickets out of Tehran on Swissair.</template></category><category><pattern>“ARGO  FUCK YOURSELF ‟ ARGO  FUCK YOURSELF</pattern><template>OFFICE OF THE SECRETARY OF STATE JANUARY 25, 1980 Brace yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU’RE DETAINED FOR QUESTIONING THEY WILL BRING OUT SOMEONE WHO KNOWS THAT  YES</pattern><template>Mary, who were the last three Prime Ministers to Canada?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW WOULD I FIND HIM</pattern><template>We’re a fucking spy agency! Find him!</template></category><category><pattern>CEREMONY’S ON THE FOURTEENTH</pattern><template>If they push it a week I can bring Ian, that’s his winter break.</template></category><category><pattern>SIX AMERICANS GET PULLED OUT OF THE CANADIAN DIPLOMAT’S HOUSE AND EXECUTED  IT’S A WORLD OUTRAGE</pattern><template>Six Americans get caught playing movie make–believe with the CIA at the airport and executed, it’s a national embarrassment.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LOVEBOAT WILL BE SEEING FIFTEEN MINUTES FROM NOW</pattern><template>.. insisted that the crisis in Afghanistan will not divert the attention of the United States from the plight of the hostages.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S SAYING THAT THE SHAH KILLED HIS SON WITH AN AMERICAN GUN</pattern><template>No! Canada! Cana—Canada!</template></category><category><pattern>I’M ASKING YOU TO TRUST ME</pattern><template>I don’t trust you.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THEY PUSH IT A WEEK I CAN BRING IAN  THAT’S HIS WINTER BREAK</pattern><template>The op was classified. So… the ceremony’s classified.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL FOUR  AND ANYTHING ELSE YOU SEE OUT THERE</pattern><template>If in doubt, you shred it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS  HE DID NOT GIVE YOU PERMISSION TO TAKE PHOTOGRAPH OF HIS STORE</pattern><template>Well that’s okay, you can tell him he can have it.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING  I DON’T KNOW</pattern><template>Nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE NO IN THE CIA</pattern><template>It’s suicide.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST LET ME DO THE TALKING</pattern><template>I’ve known this guy for 25 years, he’s full of shit, and he comes on hard, but uh… I can handle it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU PLAY ALONG WITH ME TODAY  I PROMISE YOU I WILL GET YOU OUT TOMORROW</pattern><template>Fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID  “JUST—JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER‟</pattern><template>And all I was thinking was… “stay… this is good for me.</template></category><category><pattern>— NICE TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>— This is Mike McEwan, our cameraman, this is Tim, this is Mary, our screenwriter, and this is our director, Bob Baker.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHAT I DO… I GET PEOPLE OUT… AND I’VE NEVER LEFT ANYONE BEHIND</pattern><template>I wish I could believe you, Mr. Harkins.</template></category><category><pattern>DOORS ARE CLOSING FOR FLIGHT 3‒6‒3 TO ZURICH</pattern><template>— We can go.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’LL BE COMING THROUGH TO COLLECT ANY REMAINING ALCOHOLIC BEVERAGES</pattern><template>This film crew is just yourself?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WARREN CONFIDED IN ME THAT THE PICTURE’S GONE OVER BUDGET BECAUSE THE ZULU EXTRAS WANT TO UNIONIZE</pattern><template>They may be cannibals, but they want health and dental so the movie’s kaput!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’LL LOOK FOR THE MATCHING WHITE ONE  WHICH DOESN’T EXIST</pattern><template>You’ll say you don’t know what happened… and if you believe they lost they white set, they’ll believe it too.</template></category><category><pattern>SEAN BISSETT  ASSOCIATE PRODUCER</pattern><template>Alright, let’s go make the movie.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN GET ETHNICALLY APPROPRIATE KIDS</pattern><template>Are there starving kids in Iran?</template></category><category><pattern>INVOLVED IN WHAT</pattern><template>We were surprised as anybody.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH IT WAS EASY</pattern><template>Excellent.</template></category><category><pattern>BY TRYING TO GET YOU AGITATED</pattern><template>You have to know your resume back to front.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SO HOW ABOUT ’THE DO GOODERS’</pattern><template>Six Canadians have been over there inspecting crops, ensuring the kids are getting enough to eat, we give them creds, makes them look like ag’ NGOs.</template></category><category><pattern>CIA’S GOT THREE PEOPLE OVER THERE  THEY DON’T SEE A REVOLUTION COMING</pattern><template>Call it something other then intelligence.</template></category><category><pattern>HE CAN’T KNOW ABOUT IT  NOBODY CAN KNOW ABOUT IT</pattern><template>So they’re just gonna give me an award, then they’re gonna take it back.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE  TWO DAYS  MAKE IT LOOK REAL</pattern><template>I went outside for thirty seconds.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S WRONG WITH THE BIKES AGAIN</pattern><template>We tried to get the message upstairs, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>MARINS TO NUMBER 1</pattern><template>Full back.</template></category><category><pattern>AND BOB ANDERS  SENIOR CONSULAR OFFICER  OLDEST OF THE GROUP  AND MOST LIKELY TO BE GROUP LEADER</pattern><template>They’ve been hiding at the Canadian Ambassador’s residence.</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT’S NOT THE POINT</pattern><template>— That’s not the point Bob.</template></category><category><pattern>ENGELL’S PREPPING THE BIKES OPTION  TEACHERS OPTION  YOU HAVE 72 HOURS TO MAKE YOURS BETTER</pattern><template>Fine.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S OFF… THEY WANT US TO PACK UP THE OFFICE</pattern><template>This can wait. Let’s go get a drink.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOW ‘EM WE MEAN BUSINESS  MEN WHO SERVED IN VIETNAM FOR WHAT THEY BELIEVED WAS RIGHT ARE ANGRY  I’M MAD AS HELL  I’M—I’M LIKE THE GUY SCREAMING ON THAT MOVIE PROGRAM IN ‘NETWORK’ YOU KNOW  I’VE HAD IT  AND IF HUH… IF NEED BE I’LL BEAR ARMS AGAIN  THAT’S THE WAY IT IS  WEDNESDAY  JANUARY 16TH  1980  74TH DAY OF CAPTIVITY FOR 50 AMERICANS IN IRAN  HELLO</pattern><template>My man!</template></category><category><pattern>WE TRIED TO GET THE MESSAGE UPSTAIRS  SIR</pattern><template>You think… you think this is more plausible than teachers?</template></category><category><pattern>MY NAME IS TONY MENDEZ</pattern><template>I’m from New York, my worked construction, my mother teaches elementary school, I have a wife and a ten year old son.</template></category><category><pattern>TRANSCRIPT AND SYNC: JCDR U S  EMBASSY  IRAN NOVEMBER 4  1979 SUBTITLES DOWNLOADED FROM PODNAPISI NET THE CARNIVAL IS A LITTLE BIGGER TODAY  HUH</pattern><template>The windows are supposed to be bulletproof, right?</template></category><category><pattern>— SNOW</pattern><template>— Right.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME IN  LET ME IN</pattern><template>— Burn it all, come on!</template></category><category><pattern>SEEMS HE WAS ATTACHED TO STAR IN ‘ZULU EMPIRE’  WHICH WAS JUST GONNA ANCHOR THAT MGM SLATE</pattern><template>But Warren confided in me that the picture’s gone over budget because the Zulu extras want to unionize.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO DAYS AGO</pattern><template>What was the purpose of your visit?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY FIGHT FOR THEIR FAMILIES AND TAKE BACK THE CITY  THE VILLAINS KNOW HE IS THE CHOSEN ONE  SO  THEY KIDNAP HIS SON IN THE SPICE MARKET</pattern><template>So he and his wife storm the castle.</template></category><category><pattern>IN 1950  THE PEOPLE OF IRAN ELECTED MOHAMMAD MOSADDEGH A SECULAR DEMOCRAT  AS PRIME MINISTER</pattern><template>He nationalized British and US petroleum holdings, returning Iran’s oil to its people.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE BEST BAD IDEA WE HAVE  SIR</pattern><template>By far.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME AMERICANS ARE MISSING</pattern><template>Look at the repaired list of embassy employees.</template></category><category><pattern>IRAN</pattern><template>Look, I can get you in, but you gotta promise me at least half a page.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE FARMERS  BUT THEY LEARN TO FIGHT</pattern><template>They shoot weapons at their enemies.</template></category><category><pattern>— WAIT</pattern><template>Ladies and gentlemen, it is our pleasure to announce that alcoholic beverages are now available as we have cleared Iranian airspace.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T GO UNTIL WE VERIFY</pattern><template>— I understand.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  “SINCE THE INCIDENT  THE NUMBER OF GUARDS AT THE AIRPORT HAS DOUBLED  A THOROUGH BACKGROUND EXAMINATION SHOULD BE EXPECTED‟</pattern><template>The movie cover isn’t strong enough yet, I need another week, Jack.</template></category><category><pattern>THE EXOTIC ORIENTS</pattern><template>Snake charmers, flying carpets.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT</pattern><template>— Flight Chiefs are planning a military rescue of the hostages, Delta Force started training to storm the grounds. So, if the six of them are brought down there, they won’t be held for long.</template></category><category><pattern>DYING OF CANCER  THE SHAH WAS GIVEN ASYLUM IN THE US</pattern><template>The Iranian people took to the streets outside the US embassy, demanding that the Shah be returned, tried… and hanged.</template></category><category><pattern>A DAY TO PREP THEIR COVERS… TWO IF THEY NEED IT</pattern><template>And—and you’ll fly out with them?</template></category><category><pattern>MAZEL TOV  LESTER</pattern><template>I’d rather stay home and count the wrinkles on my dog’s balls.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE A CANADIAN FILM CREW ON A LOCATION SCOUT FOR A SCIENCE FICTION MOVIE</pattern><template>We put it out there, the Canadian producers put it out there.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ANY GOOD</pattern><template>Target audience will hate it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAVE COSTUMES AND EVERYTHING</pattern><template>No, no, no, I can’t, I got, uh, Variety has the exclusive on that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT—WHAT DOES ARGO MEAN</pattern><template>I don’t know.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING MUST’VE HAPPENED</pattern><template>After school I’ve traded baseball cards— Hmm–Hmm… Ok you know those science fiction, Star Trek, Star Wars, they need an exotic location to shoot, Moonscape, Mars, desert, you know… Now image this.</template></category><category><pattern>I GET IT  THAT’S THE BALL GAME  OKAY  WE—YOU KNOW  LOOK  WE DON’T HAVE ANY OTHER… OTHER CHOICE  WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO</pattern><template>Who says that we’ll know our covers well enough?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  ARGO IS FILMED IN IRAN</pattern><template>Of course I speak Farsi, I wish to make a movie in Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>— PROBABLY NOT ALIVE</pattern><template>— Listen to me!</template></category><category><pattern>BARELY CLAIM ME AS IT IS</pattern><template>Is there any in case of obstacle?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IN 1953  THE US AND GREAT BRITAIN ENGINEERED A COUP D’ETAT THAT DEPOSED MOSADDEGH  AND INSTALLED REZA PAHLAVI AS SHAH</pattern><template>The young child was known for opulence and excess.</template></category><category><pattern>BURN EVERYTHING  INCLUDING THE CLASSIFIED  EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Don’t fucking shoot anybody.</template></category><category><pattern>THE THING… LIKE JASON AND THE GOLDEN FLEECE  OR WHAT</pattern><template>No, no, it’s the ship, it’s the— the spaceship, it goes… it goes everywhere, it goes all… …all throughout space.</template></category><category><pattern>NO SIR</pattern><template>What ever the conflicting signals from Iran today, for that matter everyday, about whether the hostages will or will not be tried as spies, the government of the United States has not deviated from its basic demands: the hostages must be freed. .. to defend human rights, it not only does not defend them, it violates them for all nations.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THERE STARVING KIDS IN IRAN</pattern><template>I’m sure there’s some skinny kids in Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S LIKE TALKING TO THOSE TWO OLD FUCKS FROM THE MUPPETS</pattern><template>Aliens and robots?</template></category><category><pattern>MESOPOTAMIA</pattern><template>Egypt?</template></category><category><pattern>COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO I WAS SITTING AT TRADER VIC’S  I WAS ENJOYING A MAI TAI  WHEN MY PAL  WARREN BEATTY COMES IN  HE WISHES ME WELL  WE HAVE A LITTLE CHAT</pattern><template>Seems he was attached to star in ‘Zulu Empire’, which was just gonna anchor that MGM slate.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE GONNA DO A 20 MILLION DOLLARS STAR WARS RIP OFF</pattern><template>You need somebody who’s a somebody, to put their name on it.</template></category><category><pattern>STATE IS COORDINATING IN HOUSE</pattern><template>State?</template></category><category><pattern>HE THEN BEGAN A CAMPAIGN TO WESTERNIZE IRAN  ENRAGING THE THE MOSTLY TRADITIONAL SHIA POPULATION</pattern><template>In 1979, the people of Iran overthrew the Shah.</template></category><category><pattern>AND GET THE HELL OUT</pattern><template>The Captain has informed us that we’re entering Iranian airspace.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ALRIGHT</pattern><template>Okay, tell me who you are?</template></category><category><pattern>THE CANADIANS ARE THE GOOD GUYS AND IF WE’RE NOT AGREEING  THEM TOO</pattern><template>Only. Canada takes the credit, or they’ll retaliate against the hostages.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T HAVE A CHOICE</pattern><template>We say no, they show up at their residence and drag everyone out at gun point.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO HELP ME MAKE A FAKE MOVIE</pattern><template>Well, you’re in the right place.</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE</pattern><template>Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>TRACTORS TO IRANIAN AGRO</pattern><template>Joe Stafford, late twenties he’s smart and a climber, speaks Farsi, he arranged the hire of his wife, Kathy.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S ABOUT A HUNDRED MILITIA AT THE AIRPORT  THAT’S RIGHT</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY WERE THERE</pattern><template>At least fifty. We’re not sure.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST CHRISTINE</pattern><template>I should have brought some books to read in prison.</template></category><category><pattern>— THEY’RE NOT SAFE HERE</pattern><template>Alright, first let’s get these— If they get caught applying for visas to the US… You know what, lets— lets wait five minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE GOT SIXTY IN THE EMBASSY WITH GUNS TO THEIR HEADS RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>The whole world is watching the Embassy.</template></category><category><pattern>MIKE MCEWAN A</pattern><template>Sounds convincing.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL… WHAT CAN I SAY</pattern><template>Congratulations.</template></category><category><pattern>TO REASON THEM</pattern><template>Open the door!</template></category><category><pattern>— MAYBE THEY’RE COOPERATING</pattern><template>— Absolutely not.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>You did good.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU VERY MUCH  HOW ARE YOU</pattern><template>I’m very well. What’s your name?</template></category><category><pattern>IRAN GUESTHOUSE OPERATION IS READY NOW  IF WE DON’T HAVE THE PRESIDENT’S GO AHEAD  THEY ARE GOING TO BE CAPTURED</pattern><template>David, pick up!</template></category><category><pattern>NO SIR  WE HAVE A CONTACT IN— — CHAMBERS</pattern><template>— John Chambers, he’s a Hollywood prosthetics guy, he’s got an Oscar, he did Planet of the Apes he’s done a bunch of contract work for us in the past.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  CHAMBERS… KEVIN ARKINS</pattern><template>Hey Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE GONNA FIND WHITE HOUSE CHIEF OF STAFF</pattern><template>How would I find him?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL FOUR DRAWERS  I WANT THEM SHREDDED  RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>But the shred not fast enough.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO BLEND IN WITH THE POPULATION YOU DON’T LOOK LIKE A RODEO CLOWN</pattern><template>Just gonna wake up tomorrow morning and be in the movie business?</template></category><category><pattern>— OR… SEEDS… CALLED… “SEEDS OF HOPE‟</pattern><template>Hold on… Sir, do you have this newspaper in front of you?</template></category><category><pattern>HALF OF THEM THINK THAT KHOMEINI’S BEEN TOO LENIENT ON THE ONES IN THE EMBASSY</pattern><template>What about the White House?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  WHAT’S YOUR JOB ON THE MOVIE</pattern><template>— Producer.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>— Salam.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN DID PEOPLE FIRST TELL YOU THAT TORTURE WAS GOING ON IN IRAN  THEY WOULD NEVER COME TO ME AND SAY: “WELL SIR  WE HAVE TORTURED THIS FELLOW‟     SADAT OF EGYPT HE CALLS YOU IMAM  FORGIVE ME  HIS WORDS NOT MINE: A LUNATIC  WHY DIDN’T HE HAVE A CHOICE  WHY DO YOU THINK HE DIDN’T HAVE A CHOICE</pattern><template>Because he would have been referred to as a barbarian.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH GOD’S WILL</pattern><template>But those who sit silently have sinned.</template></category><category><pattern>AN EXOTIC MIDDLE EASTERN VIBE</pattern><template>Women gather offering ecstatic libations to the sky gods.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M SERIOUS</pattern><template>I mean no, this is what? The part we say, this is so crazy it might actually work?</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH I COULD BELIEVE YOU  MR  HARKINS</pattern><template>My name is Tony Mendez.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE SAID NO</pattern><template>This is not a long leisure and it never has been, and you don’t decide if it goes!</template></category><category><pattern>PASSPORTS</pattern><template>We’re together yes, uh— Pierson’s telling Swissair they’re not on the plane.</template></category><category><pattern>IRAN’S REVOLUTIONARY GUARD  HAS ROUNDED UP A GANG OF TERRORIST BLAMED FOR ONE MURDER OF A HALF DOZEN FOLLOWERS OF AYATOLLAH KHOMEINI  IT SAYS SECURITY AT KHOMEINI’S HOME NOW HAS BEEN RAISED  THIS BY THE WAY  IS THE 69TH DAY THAT THE AMERICAN HOSTAGES HAVE BEEN HELD IN TEHRAN  THERE IS NO CHANGE REPORTED IN THE HOSTAGE SITUATION  IN THIS COUNTRY  GEORGE MITTY DIED LAST NIGHT  HE WAS EIGHTY FIVE YEARS OLD  YEAH</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’LL VERIFY</pattern><template>.. It goes all the way throughout the thirties.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  NORTH AMERICA ACCENTS GIVES US LIMITED OPTIONS  SO WE GET THE CANADIANS TO ISSUE THEM PASSPORTS</pattern><template>What about English teachers at the international school?</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST TIME ANYONE’S GONNA ASK YOU A QUESTION IS AT THE FIRST CHECK POINT</pattern><template>The first check point is just to get a look at your passports.</template></category><category><pattern>MGM JUST CAPITALIZED FOR SIX NEW FILMS</pattern><template>They’re screaming for Sci Fi.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL THAT’S OKAY  YOU CAN TELL HIM HE CAN HAVE IT</pattern><template>Please, please take that photograph.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S WINTER  YOU CAN’T AFFORD TO WAIT AROUND UNTIL SPRING  SO IT’S NICE ENOUGH TO TAKE A BIKE RIDE</pattern><template>They only way out of that city is the airport.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’LL SNIFF US OUT REGARDLESS</pattern><template>The Swedish Consul, they—they accused him of being an American at the airport, they held him for an hour.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO SAYS THAT WE’LL KNOW OUR COVERS WELL ENOUGH</pattern><template>We’re no in the CIA!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DON’T DO EXFIL’S</pattern><template>They do now.</template></category><category><pattern>ZURICH  IT’S UNDER HARKINS</pattern><template>I’m sorry sir, I don’t see you’d have these reservations.</template></category><category><pattern>SIX PEOPLE’S LIVES DEPEND ON THIS</pattern><template>It’s not enough.</template></category><category><pattern>— RIGHT</pattern><template>So what crops are the ‘do gooders’ inspecting under frosting?</template></category><category><pattern>NO PASSPORTS  NO PLANE</pattern><template>Passports.</template></category><category><pattern>— PRODUCER</pattern><template>Associate producer. What was the last movie you produced?</template></category><category><pattern>THE CANADIANS ARE DONE  THEY SAY THEY’RE BARING TOO MUCH RISK</pattern><template>Their Foreign Secretary corners Vance in Brussels, and told him she wants the six of them out.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT CLEAR  WE KNOW THEY ESCAPED THE EMBASSY</pattern><template>Where are they?</template></category><category><pattern>— WHO PAID FOR THAT</pattern><template>— CFDC.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WANT YOU TO GO TO LA</pattern><template>If you can make the movie thing credible, we’ll take it to the director.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT US TO GO THE GRAND BAZAAR AT THREE O’CLOCK IN THE AFTERNOON</pattern><template>You said a day learning our cover then straight to the airport.</template></category><category><pattern>— JOE  CAN YOU STOP</pattern><template>Joe?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT MISSIONARY</pattern><template>— Or… seeds… called… “seeds of hope‟.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT’S OVER  TONY</pattern><template>— If they stay here, they will be taken.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS FILM A FOREIGN BRIDES FILM</pattern><template>I’m sorry?</template></category><category><pattern>THESE ARE BLANK—YOU KNOW  STAMPS… YEAH  I’LL TAKE CARE OF THIS</pattern><template>How long?</template></category><category><pattern>TRY THE WGA</pattern><template>Just let me do the talking.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR 2 500 YEARS  THIS LAND WAS RULED BY A SERIES OF KINGS KNOWN AS “SHAHS‟</pattern><template>In 1950, the people of Iran elected Mohammad Mosaddegh a secular democrat, as prime minister.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKING TIME OFF</pattern><template>He needs to be, you know… where he is.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE IDENTIFIED BACK ROADS FROM THE CHAMRAN DISTRICT  COUPLE OF RAT LINES THROUGH THE MOUNTAINS TO THE CROSSING NEAR TABRIZ</pattern><template>Cars are off the table, because of the road blocks.</template></category><category><pattern>IRANIAN CONSULATE — TURKEY WHAT WILL BE THE PURPOSE OF YOUR VISIT TO IRAN</pattern><template>Uh… film production. Business.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT ANY KIDS  LESTER</pattern><template>Yeah, I have two daughters.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE WAIT HERE  LET’S UH  STAY TOGETHER</pattern><template>He wants to know the photograph you took… It’s okay, it’s her job to take photographs. Production design.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO SIGNED OFF ON THIS</pattern><template>You! Where was your passport issued?</template></category><category><pattern>YES SIR  IT’LL BE DONE</pattern><template>We want you to go to LA.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE YOU ARE WELL</pattern><template>Thank you very much. How are you?</template></category><category><pattern>“A SCIENCE–FANTASY ADVENTURE ‟ IT’S A TURNAROUND  IT’S DOG SHIT</pattern><template>It’s a space movie in the Middle East.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE AND HIS WIFE STORM THE CASTLE</pattern><template>The people—hold that… the people are inspired to join him.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ARE YOU GONNA GET IN THE EMBASSY</pattern><template>They’re not in the Embassy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BUILD NEW COVER IDENTITIES FOR ‘EM  YOU SEND IN A MOSES  HE TAKES THEM OUT ON A COMMERCIAL FLIGHT</pattern><template>We’ve explored those options.</template></category><category><pattern>MOTHER OF GOD</pattern><template>Yeah I just put Vance on a plane to take the head of eds to a circus, he thinks he can get him to sit on it for now.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T THINK THAT JUSTICE IS THE WORST THING</pattern><template>When did people first tell you that torture was going on in Iran? They would never come to me and say: “Well Sir, we have tortured this fellow‟. .. Sadat of Egypt he calls you Imam, forgive me, his words not mine: A lunatic. Why didn’t he have a choice, why do you think he didn’t have a choice?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’VE BEEN HIDING AT THE CANADIAN AMBASSADOR’S RESIDENCE</pattern><template>Fortunately, we do not believe the Iranians are aware the six have escaped.</template></category><category><pattern>— WAIT WAIT  WAIT A MINUTE</pattern><template>What the hell are you talking about, back stopped, what the hell does that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR</pattern><template>You’re telling me that there is a movie company in Hollywood right now, that is funded by the CIA?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS EXPECTING MORE OF A G MAN LOOK</pattern><template>I think you’re thinking of the FBI, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>LADIES AND GENTLEMEN  IT IS OUR PLEASURE TO ANNOUNCE THAT ALCOHOLIC BEVERAGES ARE NOW AVAILABLE AS WE HAVE CLEARED IRANIAN AIRSPACE</pattern><template>They’re clear.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ALWAYS A FUCKED MISSION</pattern><template>You came closer than anybody else.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S THE MONEY</pattern><template>Look, what d’you say uh… fifteen thou’and, let’s close on this?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MAKES THEM SAFER THAN THE SIX ON THE STREET</pattern><template>Bonnie Sauder’s saying it will be over in twenty four hours.</template></category><category><pattern>HE TOLD THEM THAT THERE ARE SIX OF US  SO THEN THEY’RE EXPECTING SIX  IT WOULD BE SUSPICIOUS NOT TO SHOW UP AT THIS POINT</pattern><template>Goddammit, guys! What else do we have to do?!</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S HALF DEAD AND HE’S IN CHEMO</pattern><template>Well, we took him in, he’s ours now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALLY KNOW WARREN BEATTY</pattern><template>Yes I do.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE ME A PRODUCER</pattern><template>No. You’re… an associate producer at best.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK… YOU THINK THIS IS MORE PLAUSIBLE THAN TEACHERS</pattern><template>Yes, we do. One, there are no more foreign teachers in Iran… And we think everybody knows Hollywood people, and everybody knows they ain’t shootin’ Stalingrad, with Bob Hope directing if it would sell tickets.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T HAVE IT</pattern><template>We got an office, we got business cards, we got a poster.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE ADMITTED TO THE REPUBLIC OF IRAQ</pattern><template>We made history today.</template></category><category><pattern>I ENJOYED YOUR FILMS  THE EARLY ONES</pattern><template>I took this meeting out of respect, because I wanted to say no to your face.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TEACH A RECESS MONKEY TO BE A DIRECTOR IN A DAY</pattern><template>Look if you’re gonna do this, you gotta do it.</template></category><category><pattern>PACE ACADEMY  BUCKHEAD  GEORGIA</pattern><template>White House.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  I CAN’T  I GOT  UH  VARIETY HAS THE EXCLUSIVE ON THAT</pattern><template>Any way to make this more uh… Middle Eastern?</template></category><category><pattern>THE IRAN HOSTAGE CRISIS ENDED ON JANUARY 20  1981  WHEN ALL REMAINING HOSTAGES WERE RELEASED</pattern><template>They spent 444 days in captivity.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LIVES IN VIRGINA WITH HIS MOTHER</pattern><template>You’re divorced?</template></category><category><pattern>JOE</pattern><template>So, we’ll see you at two.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IF THEY LOOK  THEY’LL SEE I DIDN’T COME INTO THE COUNTRY WITH SIX PEOPLE</pattern><template>If they look.</template></category><category><pattern>GET YOUR CATARACTS FIXED  READ THE TRADES</pattern><template>MGM just capitalized for six new films.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN FIND MANY ITEMS SUCH AS PAPER  SPICES  PRECIOUS METALS ALL  RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Uh, right this way.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN DID YOU GET BACK</pattern><template>The Shah escaped on the 747 so laden with gold bars, that they didn’t make it off the runway.</template></category><category><pattern>— WITHOUT ACTUALLY DOING ANYTHING</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>SEVEN AMERICANS WALKING THE BAZAAR IS ASKING FOR A RIOT  IT’S THE HIVE</pattern><template>Seven Canadians, Jack.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MOVIE COVER ISN’T STRONG ENOUGH YET  I NEED ANOTHER WEEK  JACK</pattern><template>You don’t have it.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH</pattern><template>Carter said you were a great American.</template></category><category><pattern>DAVID  PICK UP</pattern><template>Zurich, it’s under Harkins.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY CALLED YOUR BLUFF</pattern><template>— Maybe they’re cooperating.</template></category><category><pattern>FULL BACK</pattern><template>— Look, I need police, — Can anyone hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>— VISAS  — FOR AMERICAN JOURNALISTS… — AND THE REVOLUTIONARY GUARDS KEEP THEM ON SEVENTY FOUR LEASHES</pattern><template>If they’re caught with fake journalist creds, it’s Peter and Jane’s head in a noose in an hour.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU EVER WATCH THE NEWS</pattern><template>What does the title refer to?</template></category><category><pattern>— HELLO</pattern><template>— Jack O’Donnell from CI— Wait, wait! Who?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  SEE YOU SOON</pattern><template>Sahar’s on the bus.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT’S HIS OCCUPATION</pattern><template>— Fisherman.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YES</pattern><template>They’re out!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE DIVORCED</pattern><template>Taking time off.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S YOUR MIDDLE NAME</pattern><template>— Leon… — Shoot him! He’s an American spy.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUEST OF THE AMBASSADOR… HOW LONG HAVE THEY BEEN HERE</pattern><template>They arrived two days ago.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SECOND CHECK POINT IS IMMIGRATION</pattern><template>You’re each gonna hand them one of these.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN ANYBODY HEAR ME</pattern><template>There is a breach.</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN’T MATTER IF I SAW YOU GO OUT OR YOU SEE ME</pattern><template>— Did you see me go out?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST THE FAMILIES</pattern><template>Meanwhile, some genius in our Embassy was keeping a mug book on everybody who worked there.</template></category><category><pattern>— STUDIO 6</pattern><template>— We got a green light.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE CAN TELL STATE HE RAN IT BY HIS BEST EXFIL GUY</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU KEPT BUSY</pattern><template>Fairing out the torture apparatus of our friends fallen dictation.</template></category><category><pattern>THE THIRD CHECK POINT IS THE TRAP</pattern><template>It’s manned by the Revolutionary Guard, most of them were educated in the U.S and Europe… and all of them are looking for Americans.</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHOULD ALL SPLIT</pattern><template>I’m gonna close up my office.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DEMAND EXTRADITION OF A MAN WHO FOR MORE THAN 37 YEARS  WITH THE UNITED STATES SUPPORT  HAS KILLED MONTHS OLD BABIES IN THE ARMS OF THEIR MOTHERS</pattern><template>He said that if the Americans try military force to rescue the hostages, the students will kill them all and blow up the Embassy. Americans were outraged at Iran and anyone Iranian. Before this decision was taken, there was a demonstration in Houston. An Iranian flag was burned, while Anti Iranians demonstrators gathered near the Iranian Consulate. The demonstrators— .. also it’s what led to a decision to scrutinize the bases of the Iranian— They knew exactly what was going on, they knew it.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  LET’S GO MAKE THE MOVIE</pattern><template>Welcome, welcome, my name is Reza Borhani.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYONE IN THIS HOUSE IS A FRIEND OF IRAN</pattern><template>How did it go?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW HER</pattern><template>I was married to her.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE POINT IS  WE CAN’T STAY HERE</pattern><template>If we get caught, you and Pat go on trial for harboring the enemy, you know that.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE TELLING ME THAT THERE IS A MOVIE COMPANY IN HOLLYWOOD RIGHT NOW  THAT IS FUNDED BY THE CIA</pattern><template>— Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SHIP IS TURNING AROUND</pattern><template>Fire the thrusters!</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE GOT ORDERS TO CLOSE THE EMBASSY AND GO BACK</pattern><template>There’s nowhere for them to stay.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW WELL DO YOU THINK THEIR COVERS ARE GONNA HOLD UP WHEN THEY’RE GETTING THEIR FINGERNAILS PULLED OUT</pattern><template>You want us to go the Grand Bazaar at three o’clock in the afternoon?</template></category><category><pattern>GODDAMMIT  GUYS  WHAT ELSE DO WE HAVE TO DO</pattern><template>Alright? What el—what— what’s the alternative?!</template></category><category><pattern>ALAN  ALAN  WE NEED TO CONFIRM THOSE SEVEN TICKETS OUT OF TEHRAN ON SWISSAIR</pattern><template>Engell shut that down.</template></category><category><pattern>SWISSAIR ANNOUNCES FINAL BOARDING TO FLIGHT 3‒6‒3 TO ZURICH  RECESS  BACK TO ONE</pattern><template>— Alright, recess.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON</pattern><template>Passports.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THOSE WHO SIT SILENTLY HAVE SINNED</pattern><template>Yes. Any way I may help, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>THESE ARE THE DRAWINGS THAT SHOW WHAT WE WILL FILM FOR THE MOVIE  ALIEN VILLAINS HAVE TAKEN OVER THE HERO’S PLANET</pattern><template>They fight for their families and take back the city, The villains know he is the chosen one, so, they kidnap his son in the spice market.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  THIS WAY</pattern><template>These are blank—you know, stamps… Yeah, I’ll take care of this.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE MANAGED</pattern><template>You are admitted to the republic of Iraq.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I SPEAK TO A MR  KEVIN HARKINS</pattern><template>I’m sorry, Mr. Harkins is out of country on a location scout.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’VE BEEN HERE AND HOUR  AND—AND YOU’RE ASKING US TO TRUST YOU WITH OUR LIVES  MR… HARKINS</pattern><template>That’s your real name?</template></category><category><pattern>MARX</pattern><template>Groucho said that?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU JUST NEED TO FINISH FILLING OUT THIS SECTION HERE</pattern><template>We need some security.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAVEN’T LEFT THE CANADIAN AMBASSADOR’S HOUSE SINCE IT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Why didn’t we get them ten weeks ago?</template></category><category><pattern>GET IT DOWN TO THE INCINERATOR  IN THE VAULT  NOW</pattern><template>Tear gas is a last resort only.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE’RE ON THE SECOND FLOOR</pattern><template>— You understand me?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS A BREACH</pattern><template>Burn everything! Burn it, now!</template></category><category><pattern>HARDING</pattern><template>I’ll call him back.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO</pattern><template>The bazaar in Tehran is one of the largest in the world.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  YOU DID GO OUTSIDE… I DID  OKAY  I SAW YOU</pattern><template>Bob, it only takes one second for them to spot you.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE CLAIMING THE EMBASSY WAS A DEN OF ESPIONAGE</pattern><template>We wish it was a fucking den of espionage.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST A LITTLE BIT NOW</pattern><template>Please wait here, let’s uh, stay together.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT ENGLISH TEACHERS AT THE INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL</pattern><template>It’s a good idea, but that school’s been closed for eight months.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  IRAQ IS AMAZING</pattern><template>Well, we’re shooting in Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW THAT EVERYDAY THEY CATCH ANOTHER FRIEND OF THE SHAH AT THE AIRPORT</pattern><template>— Joe… — Kangaroo trials, and— And then firing squads just for having American names in their phone books.</template></category><category><pattern>I TALK TO ‘EM ONCE A YEAR… MAYBE</pattern><template>Why is that?</template></category><category><pattern>— PLEASE</pattern><template>— That’s why they’re stating he liked the current regime!</template></category><category><pattern>— THANKS FOR THE RIDE</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S OKAY</pattern><template>Where are they?</template></category><category><pattern>— BURN IT ALL  COME ON</pattern><template>— Right come on, guys!</template></category><category><pattern>THE SIX WITH THE CANADIANS ARE COMING OUT</pattern><template>Who signed off on this?</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT CROPS ARE THE ‘DO GOODERS’ INSPECTING UNDER FROSTING</pattern><template>Sir… Exfils are like abortions.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU GOTTEN PEOPLE OUT THIS WAY BEFORE</pattern><template>This would be a first.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S IN TURN AROUND</pattern><template>Can I come in?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE PACKED OUR BAGS</pattern><template>I said, “just—just a little bit longer‟.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE CAN GO</pattern><template>— Excellent.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES THEY GO ALONG ON SCOUTS BECAUSE THEY WANT THEIR FREE MEALS</pattern><template>Here’s your director.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S—IT’S THEATER OF THE ABSURD</pattern><template>What are our chances?</template></category><category><pattern>CARTER SAID YOU WERE A GREAT AMERICAN</pattern><template>Great American what?</template></category><category><pattern>DON’T FUCKING SHOOT ANYBODY</pattern><template>You don’t want to be the son of a bitch who started the war.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WAIT UNTIL THE WEATHER CLEARS UP  THEN DELIVER THE SIX BIKES  PROVIDE THEM WITH MAPS TO THE TURKISH BORDER</pattern><template>We have intelligence, they can ride bicycles or we’re prepared to send in somebody to teach ‘em.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE THEY</pattern><template>In the kitchen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  HIS OPINION GOT US OUT IN THE FIRST PLACE</pattern><template>If we go out there with fake passports, we are spies, period, that’s execution.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  WE DON’T HAVE ANY ALTERNATIVES</pattern><template>We gotta go.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S A FAKE MOVIE</pattern><template>If I’m doing a fake movie, it’s going to be a fake hit.</template></category><category><pattern>— SORRY  WE’RE ROLLING SORRY PAL  WE’RE GONNA BE IN THE MOVIE</pattern><template>Call my agency.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WHOLE COUNTRY IS WATCHING YOU</pattern><template>They just don’t know it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ONLY WAY OUT OF THAT CITY IS THE AIRPORT</pattern><template>You build new cover identities for ‘em, you send in a Moses, he takes them out on a commercial flight.</template></category><category><pattern>STUDIO 6 PRODUCTIONS</pattern><template>May I speak to a Mr. Kevin Harkins?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID GOOD</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>TACO</pattern><template>Got any kids, Lester?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE GETTING THE HIGHEST AWARD OF MERIT OF THE CLANDESTINE SERVICES OF THESE UNITED STATES</pattern><template>Ceremony’s on the fourteenth.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE A BETTER PLAN</pattern><template>No Sir.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MONTH  YEAH</pattern><template>— Who are you again?</template></category><category><pattern>AMBASSADOR KEN TAYLOR AND THE GREAT NATION OF CANADA</pattern><template>So I’m sitting in Jerry’s this morning, I’m having breakfast.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M TAKING THEM THROUGH</pattern><template>Tony?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  PUT HIM ON A PLANE THEN  FUCK HIM</pattern><template>He’s half dead and he’s in chemo.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  I ONLY GOT A COUPLE OF MINUTES</pattern><template>I’m getting a lifetime achievement award.</template></category><category><pattern>UH… FILM PRODUCTION  BUSINESS</pattern><template>Why didn’t you get your visa in Canada?</template></category><category><pattern>I SAY IT’S BACK ON</pattern><template>— I can’t do it, it’s back stopped!</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN DID YOU COME THROUGH IRAN</pattern><template>Two days ago.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL NEVER MAKE IT THROUGH IMMIGRATION AT THE AIRPORT</pattern><template>I’m serious.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE HAVE A…</pattern><template>— Oh, yeah, I’ve got a letter from the Ministry of Culture.</template></category><category><pattern>TEAR GAS IS A LAST RESORT ONLY</pattern><template>I repeat: only if you’re under threat. In here, we are in America right now, outside of these doors, we are in Iran!</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S NOT ENOUGH</pattern><template>If we’re gonna fool these people, it has to be big, and it has to have something that says it’s authentic.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU TELL THEM NOW  THEY’LL PANIC</pattern><template>I think it’s best if you just don’t show.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE</pattern><template>The exotic orients.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE THE REVOLUTION FORTY PERCENT OF THE MOVIE THEATERS IN TEHRAN WERE SHOWING PORNOGRAPH</pattern><template>I understand.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO’S THE TARGET AUDIENCE</pattern><template>People with eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE TOOK HIM IN  HE’S OURS NOW</pattern><template>Great, so we’ll take any prick as long as he’s got cancer?</template></category><category><pattern>— WE GOT WHEELS UP</pattern><template>— Wait.</template></category><category><pattern>— JOE… — KANGAROO TRIALS  AND— AND THEN FIRING SQUADS JUST FOR HAVING AMERICAN NAMES IN THEIR PHONE BOOKS</pattern><template>You’ve been here and hour, and—and you’re asking us to trust you with our lives, Mr… Harkins.</template></category><category><pattern>— I SAW IN BURMA  THEY GET PEOPLE OUT</pattern><template>Snitches and Banana Republic, they get them over the border after the coup, pay the guards at the crossing a hundred bucks to look the other way.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I WAS TO SAY THAT YOU’RE LOOKING THROUGH THE WRONG END OF THAT VIEW FINDER  WOULD I BE RIGHT</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  MY GUY KIND OF SUCKS</pattern><template>What’s your name?</template></category><category><pattern>NO I WAS SCREAMING HIS NAME ’COS I WAS FUCKING ‘EM</pattern><template>It’s confirmed, sir, six escaped.</template></category><category><pattern>— THEY’RE GETTING THERE</pattern><template>There’s no prize for most improvements.</template></category><category><pattern>TELEX FOR FLASH</pattern><template>Would you mind checking again, please?</template></category><category><pattern>LANDMARK SITES</pattern><template>I see.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAVE NEVER BEEN TESTED</pattern><template>Okay, you just need to finish filling out this section here.</template></category><category><pattern>— LOOK  I NEED POLICE  — CAN ANYONE HEAR ME</pattern><template>— I need police right now.</template></category><category><pattern>WE MADE HISTORY TODAY</pattern><template>“ History starts out as farce and ends up as tragedy‟.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL OF THE HOUSEGUESTS RETURNED TO U S</pattern><template>foreign service after their ordeal in Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>SO ALL OF OUR OTHER PRICKS ON THEIR PRICK THRONES WILL KNOW THAT WHEN THEY GET THROWN OUT ON A RAIL  THEY WON’T GET THEIR FUCKING SPLEENS TAKEN OUT BY SOME CAMEL VET IN SINAI</pattern><template>What about the six who are with the Canadians?</template></category><category><pattern>THE EXILED CLERIC  AYATOLLAH KHOMEINI  RETURNED TO RULE IRAN</pattern><template>It descended into score settling, death squads and chaos.</template></category><category><pattern>COPY D S   CONFIRM THE TICKETS  GO</pattern><template>My apologies, they just came through.</template></category><category><pattern>SIX AMERICANS GET CAUGHT PLAYING MOVIE MAKE–BELIEVE WITH THE CIA AT THE AIRPORT AND EXECUTED  IT’S A NATIONAL EMBARRASSMENT</pattern><template>They are calling the operation.</template></category><category><pattern>— ARE THEY EVEN READY</pattern><template>— They’re getting there.</template></category><category><pattern>IS WHITE HOUSE JOINING</pattern><template>They’re claiming the Embassy was a den of espionage.</template></category><category><pattern>— MARK</pattern><template>— Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE WITH EYES</pattern><template>Talk to me.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD FOR THE CHIEF OF STAFF</pattern><template>Harding?</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S A GOOD IDEA  BUT THAT SCHOOL’S BEEN CLOSED FOR EIGHT MONTHS</pattern><template>Okay, so how about ’the do gooders’?</template></category><category><pattern>ASSOCIATE PRODUCER  WHAT WAS THE LAST MOVIE YOU PRODUCED</pattern><template>— “High and Dry‟.</template></category><category><pattern>SOUNDS CONVINCING</pattern><template>Kathy, what’s your name?</template></category><category><pattern>I’M RESPONSIBLE</pattern><template>I’m taking them through.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M GETTING A LIFETIME ACHIEVEMENT AWARD</pattern><template>Mazel tov, Lester.</template></category><category><pattern>— JOHN CHAMBERS  HE’S A HOLLYWOOD PROSTHETICS GUY  HE’S GOT AN OSCAR  HE DID PLANET OF THE APES HE’S DONE A BUNCH OF CONTRACT WORK FOR US IN THE PAST</pattern><template>I go see him, he sets this up.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN’T HOLD UPON THAT  WE DON’T KNOW WHAT THE HELL MOVIE PEOPLE DO</pattern><template>That’s why I’m here.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY THE BEST THING TO DO FOR YOU RIGHT NOW WOULD BE… JUST TO RELAX</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M FROM NEW YORK  MY WORKED CONSTRUCTION  MY MOTHER TEACHES ELEMENTARY SCHOOL  I HAVE A WIFE AND A TEN YEAR OLD SON</pattern><template>You play along with me today, I promise you I will get you out tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>IF OUR ARTISTS COULD SETTLE IN  WE’LL JUST BE READY TO BEGIN THE READING</pattern><template>Argo. From Mary Ann Boyd.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVEN’T BEEN THIS NERVOUS SINCE OUR WEDDING</pattern><template>Only this isn’t a huge mistake, hopefully.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WINDOWS ARE SUPPOSED TO BE BULLETPROOF  RIGHT</pattern><template>They have never been tested.</template></category><category><pattern>BONNIE SAUDER’S SAYING IT WILL BE OVER IN TWENTY FOUR HOURS</pattern><template>We leave the six where they are.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE FUCKS HIT US  WE CAN’T HIT ‘EM BACK</pattern><template>Mossaddegh, we did it to them first.</template></category><category><pattern>UP LIKE A CARNY RIDE</pattern><template>One month, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH I UNDERSTAND  I UNDERSTAND BUT WE’RE SHOOTING</pattern><template>Swissair announces final boarding to flight 3‒6‒3 to Zurich. Recess, back to one!</template></category><category><pattern>STANDING ROOM ONLY FOR BEHEADINGS IN THE SQUARE</pattern><template>Who’s handling?</template></category><category><pattern>IT MEANS “ARGO  FUCK YOURSELF‟</pattern><template>Will you pay me every attention, ladies and gentlemen?</template></category><category><pattern>EXFIL WANTS YOU TO BURN THE PASSPORTS BEFORE YOU LEAVE</pattern><template>If you tell them now, they’ll panic.</template></category><category><pattern>“ HISTORY STARTS OUT AS FARCE AND ENDS UP AS TRAGEDY‟</pattern><template>Or it’s the other way around.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>Come to bed.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING</pattern><template>It can’t be nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU LAND  YOU SHOULD GO STRAIGHT TO THE MINISTRY OF CULTURE AND… ISLAMIC GUIDANCE  KISS THE RING</pattern><template>Get on record as having applied for film permit.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WANTS TO GIVE YOU THE INTELLIGENCE STAR</pattern><template>You’re getting the highest award of merit of the clandestine services of these United States.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE EACH GONNA HAND THEM ONE OF THESE</pattern><template>It says that you landed in the country two days ago.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PEOPLE STARVED</pattern><template>The Shah kept power through his ruthless internal police, the Savak.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BULLSHIT BUSINESS… IT’S LIKE COAL MINING  YOU—YOU COME HOME TO YOUR WIFE AND KIDS  YOU CAN’T… YOU CAN’T WASH IT OFF</pattern><template>You?</template></category><category><pattern>ENGELL SAYS  IT’S A LOSE–LOSE</pattern><template>These people die, they die badly, publicly.</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL CALL HIM BACK</pattern><template>They’re sticking to it, no release till we expel the Shah.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  I’M IN</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE GOING TO NEED A SCRIPT</pattern><template>I love you.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M SURE THERE’S SOME SKINNY KIDS IN IRAN</pattern><template>What about missionary?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT THE WHITE HOUSE</pattern><template>Carter’s shitting enough bricks to build the pyramids.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE SURPRISED AS ANYBODY</pattern><template>Thank you, Canada.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  SOONER IS BETTER</pattern><template>Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>INSISTED THAT THE CRISIS IN AFGHANISTAN WILL NOT DIVERT THE ATTENTION OF THE UNITED STATES FROM THE PLIGHT OF THE HOSTAGES</pattern><template>.. he seems to be if not impotent, but at least reluctant… The United States finds itself in such bitter confrontation with the Soviet Union over that country’s invasion of Afghanistan… The United States is now moving towards the decision to boycott the summer Olympics in Moscow.</template></category><category><pattern>— THEY’RE NOT COMING</pattern><template>How do you know they’re not coming?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GUY’D BETTER GET THEM</pattern><template>And get the hell out.</template></category><category><pattern>HE NEEDS TO BE  YOU KNOW… WHERE HE IS</pattern><template>Kids need the mother.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THE WAY IT LOOKS TO ME THROUGH THE CATARACTS I GRANT YOU  IS THAT YOU CAN EITHER SIGN HERE  AND TAKE 10 000 DOLLARS FOR YOUR TOILET PAPER SCRIPT  OR YOU CAN GO FUCK YOURSELF</pattern><template>With all due respect.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU—CAN YOU TELL ME WHAT THE OBJECTION WAS TO NORMAL COVER IDENTITIES</pattern><template>There are no Canadians in the country for no reason.</template></category><category><pattern>— GO TO BLACK ON GREEN</pattern><template>Go.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BAZAAR  MAYBE THE PALACE</pattern><template>Landmark sites.</template></category><category><pattern>— KEN TAYLOR</pattern><template>Thank you for what you’re doing.</template></category><category><pattern>TIMOTHY HARRIS  LOCATION MANAGER</pattern><template>Mary Ann Boyd, screenwriter.</template></category><category><pattern>WOMEN GATHER OFFERING ECSTATIC LIBATIONS TO THE SKY GODS</pattern><template>Argo.</template></category><category><pattern>MY GOD</pattern><template>Marins to Number 1.</template></category><category><pattern>ROBERT BAKER  DIRECTOR</pattern><template>Timothy Harris, location manager.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY WANTS TO FIRE ME HIMSELF</pattern><template>He wants to give you the Intelligence Star.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  SISTER  THOSE WHO ARE WITH HIM  RASOOL ALLAH  WE ARE TENDER WITH THEM</pattern><template>But stern against the infidels.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT AN OFFICE  WE GOT BUSINESS CARDS  WE GOT A POSTER</pattern><template>If I’m the Revolutionary Guard, there’s nothing we couldn’t have made at home.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS MARRIED TO HER</pattern><template>Oh my God, Iraq is amazing!</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU WANT TO SELL A LIE… GET THE PRESS TO SELL IT FOR YOU</pattern><template>No no no, press event, then they’re— they’re gonna read through the script.</template></category><category><pattern>EGYPT</pattern><template>Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I TAKE A MESSAGE</pattern><template>Doors are closing for flight 3‒6‒3 to Zurich.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Exfil wants you to burn the passports before you leave.</template></category><category><pattern>TO THIS DAY  THIS STORY STANDS AS AN ENDURING MODEL FOR INTERNATIONAL COOPERATION BETWEEN GOVERNMENTS</pattern><template>All of the Houseguests returned to U.S.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU NEED TO DO IS MEMORIZE EVERYTHING THAT’S INSIDE</pattern><template>Who you are, what you are, where you’ve been, complete bio. And then add to that: where do you vacation, what are you allergies, who’d you have an affair with.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TWO LEAVE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>We’ll leave on the train in half an hour.</template></category><category><pattern>SO… WHAT WE’D LIKE FOR THIS ARE BICYCLES</pattern><template>We’ve identified back roads from the Chamran district, couple of rat lines through the mountains to the crossing near Tabriz.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S ON THE GROUND</pattern><template>— Snow.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALREADY HAVE CREDENTIALS FOR THE TEACHERS</pattern><template>No Sir, we have a contact in— — Chambers.</template></category><category><pattern>CHANCES ARE GOOD</pattern><template>Good? Well, what’s the uh… what’s the number value of good?</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT’S YOUR MIDDLE NAME</pattern><template>What’s your middle name?</template></category><category><pattern>SOME KOMITEH GUARD IS ACTUALLY GONNA KNOW THAT</pattern><template>If you’re detained for questioning they will bring out someone who knows that, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>GROUCHO SAID THAT</pattern><template>Called ‘The Times’ to nail it to the Goddamn door.</template></category><category><pattern>MOSSADDEGH  WE DID IT TO THEM FIRST</pattern><template>The Soviets would put up with this shit, they would fucking invade them.</template></category><category><pattern>WE LEAVE THE SIX WHERE THEY ARE</pattern><template>I’ll go brief the President.</template></category><category><pattern>STILL NO ANSWER IN L A</pattern><template>Sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WE PUT IT OUT THERE  THE CANADIAN PRODUCERS PUT IT OUT THERE</pattern><template>They were looking at Egypt, Istanbul.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE OFFERING ME FOUR TIMES WHAT YOU GUYS ARE OFFERING ME</pattern><template>Well… what can I say?</template></category><category><pattern>IF THEY CATCH YOU LATER  AT LEAST THEY’LL BE CONFUSED WHILE THEY’RE TORTURING YOU</pattern><template>IRANIAN CONSULATE — TURKEY What will be the purpose of your visit to Iran?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  TELL ME WHO YOU ARE</pattern><template>Mike McEwan, cameraman.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED SOME SECURITY</pattern><template>Yes, it is your responsibility— They drew over the walls.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY KNOW WHO THEY ARE  AND THEY KNOW THEY’RE HIDING OUT WITH THE CANADIANS</pattern><template>Somebody withdrew on the family’s talk.</template></category><category><pattern>I FLY INTO TEHRAN  WE ALL FLY OUT TOGETHER AS A FILM CREW</pattern><template>Done.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE GOTTA GET OFF THE STREETS</pattern><template>This way, up here to the left.</template></category><category><pattern>IF IN DOUBT  YOU SHRED IT</pattern><template>We’ve got ten minutes, lets go, go, go, everything!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE HIS KIDS</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>— ALRIGHT  RECESS</pattern><template>— We going again!</template></category><category><pattern>MY APOLOGIES  THEY JUST CAME THROUGH</pattern><template>Swisair says they picked up the tickets.</template></category><category><pattern>TIME TO GO</pattern><template>Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THEY LOOK</pattern><template>When you land, you should go straight to the Ministry of Culture and… Islamic Guidance, kiss the ring.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU MIND CHECKING AGAIN  PLEASE</pattern><template>Copy D.S., confirm the tickets, go!</template></category><category><pattern>IF I’M THE REVOLUTIONARY GUARD  THERE’S NOTHING WE COULDN’T HAVE MADE AT HOME</pattern><template>Six people’s lives depend on this.</template></category><category><pattern>— SALAM</pattern><template>Lester, you’re working late.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE OUR CHANCES</pattern><template>Chances are good.</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN THIS GODDAMN DOOR</pattern><template>You said you wanna see the world, Elton?</template></category><category><pattern>STAY</pattern><template>Show Newsom you got the balls‟.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT AMERICAN WHAT</pattern><template>He didn’t say.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M GONNA CLOSE UP MY OFFICE</pattern><template>My God!</template></category><category><pattern>DON’T FUCK UP</pattern><template>The whole country is watching you.</template></category><category><pattern>CARTER’S SHITTING ENOUGH BRICKS TO BUILD THE PYRAMIDS</pattern><template>The Canadians are done, they say they’re baring too much risk.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KOMINIACS ARE FRUIT LOOPS  BUT THEY GOT COUSINS WHO SELL PRAYER RUGS AND A TRACKS ON LE BREA</pattern><template>You can’t build cover stories around a movie that doesn’t exist.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO GO INTO PRODUCTION WITH THIS IN ONE MONTH</pattern><template>Up like a carny ride.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE FORTY MINUTES</pattern><template>Get it down to the incinerator, in the vault. Now!</template></category><category><pattern>— HOWARD</pattern><template>— What’s his occupation?</template></category><category><pattern>TARGET AUDIENCE WILL HATE IT</pattern><template>Who’s the target audience?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL I NEED IS THEIR FACES AND I WILL FIND THEM</pattern><template>Yes Sir, it’ll be done.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL BEGIN THE TRIALS AND CARRY OUT THE SENTENCES     WE WONDER WHERE AND HOW THIS APPARENTLY ENDLESS PARADE OF HATRED WILL END  EMBASSY BASEMENT JANUARY 23  1980 EMBASSY BASEMENT JANUARY 23  1980 WHAT DO THEY WANT</pattern><template>They say the question should be not ‘what’, but ‘who’. The answer to this question is clear, they want the former Shah, .. They should be ashamed to talk about human rights. Carter and his government have given asylum to the worst criminal.</template></category><category><pattern>— UH  MIKE</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR</pattern><template>Studio 6 Productions.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M CALLING FOR YOU</pattern><template>Did you do your homework tonight?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS NOT A LONG LEISURE AND IT NEVER HAS BEEN  AND YOU DON’T DECIDE IF IT GOES</pattern><template>It is going!</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT’S YOUR FATHER’S NAME</pattern><template>— Howard.</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN THE DOOR</pattern><template>Open this goddamn door!</template></category><category><pattern>LET’S GO OFF THIS NOW</pattern><template>You know, sister, those who are with him, Rasool Allah, we are tender with them.</template></category><category><pattern>DURING THE TAKEOVER SIX PEOPLE ESCAPED</pattern><template>They’re hiding out in Tehran… and that’s who I’m gonna go get.</template></category><category><pattern>TRAFFIC CALLS THEM ‘HOUSE GUESTS’</pattern><template>They haven’t left the Canadian Ambassador’s house since it happened.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TELL THE DIRECTOR TO CALL THE WHITE HOUSE</pattern><template>Do your fucking job!</template></category><category><pattern>GET THE SHREDDER</pattern><template>There are no police.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU TEACH SOMEBODY TO BE A DIRECTOR IN A DAY</pattern><template>You teach a recess monkey to be a director in a day.</template></category><category><pattern>I WENT OUTSIDE FOR THIRTY SECONDS</pattern><template>Alright?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  THEY MADE IT THROUGH THE LOCATION SCOUT</pattern><template>You have a call.</template></category><category><pattern>HE AND MENDEZ REMAINED FRIENDS UNTIL CHAMBER’S DEATH IN 2001</pattern><template>Tony Mendez’s Intelligence Star was returned to him in 1997, when operation Argo was declassified by president Clinton.</template></category><category><pattern>MEANWHILE  SOME GENIUS IN OUR EMBASSY WAS KEEPING A MUG BOOK ON EVERYBODY WHO WORKED THERE</pattern><template>Jesus Christ!</template></category><category><pattern>BAD NEW  BAD NEWS  EVEN WHEN IT’S GOOD NEWS  IT’S BAD NEWS</pattern><template>John Wayne’s in the ground six months, this is what’s left of America.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CANADIAN AMBASSADOR’S HOUSE</pattern><template>Do they stay put?</template></category><category><pattern>CARS ARE OFF THE TABLE  BECAUSE OF THE ROAD BLOCKS</pattern><template>We wait until the weather clears up, then deliver the six bikes, provide them with maps to the Turkish border.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE’RE SHOOTING IN IRAN</pattern><template>Iran with an N?</template></category><category><pattern>I TOOK THIS MEETING OUT OF RESPECT  BECAUSE I WANTED TO SAY NO TO YOUR FACE</pattern><template>Thank you. Very respectful.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  LETS GO</pattern><template>I’m going outside.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OP WAS CLASSIFIED  SO… THE CEREMONY’S CLASSIFIED</pattern><template>He can’t know about it, nobody can know about it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE CLEAR</pattern><template>Yes! Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>GODDAMMIT  I NEVER WOULD HAVE EXPOSED THEM IF I WASN’T AUTHORIZED TO GET THEM OUT</pattern><template>— It’s over, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL GO BRIEF THE PRESIDENT</pattern><template>Right, I’ll through it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE EXPLORED THOSE OPTIONS</pattern><template>You’re never gonna get them through airport control, Komiteh own the place.</template></category><category><pattern>THE EMBASSY WAS UNDERSTAFFED  SO THE FACULTY WIVES WERE THE TYPING POOL</pattern><template>And Bob Anders, senior consular officer, oldest of the group, and most likely to be group leader.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT  SO WE’LL TAKE ANY PRICK AS LONG AS HE’S GOT CANCER</pattern><template>Just the pricks on our side.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN IT STARTED IN THE STREETS NINE MONTHS AGO  SHE… SHE BEGGED FOR US TO LEAVE</pattern><template>She packed our bags.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S WHY I’M HERE</pattern><template>I’m gonna help you, I’m gonna be with you the whole way. This is what I do.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU FOR WHAT YOU’RE DOING</pattern><template>I was expecting more of a G Man look.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN NO  THIS IS WHAT  THE PART WE SAY  THIS IS SO CRAZY IT MIGHT ACTUALLY WORK</pattern><template>— Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Not clear. We know they escaped the embassy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DO HIS KIDS GO TO SCHOOL</pattern><template>Thank you, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FRIENDS FROM CANADA  MA’AM  ALL THIS TIME  THEY NEVER GO OUT</pattern><template>Sahar knows.</template></category><category><pattern>I SHOULD HAVE BROUGHT SOME BOOKS TO READ IN PRISON</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>— JACK O’DONNELL FROM CI— WAIT  WAIT  WHO</pattern><template>Iran Guesthouse operation is ready now, if we don’t have the President’s go ahead, they are going to be captured.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’LL LEAVE ON THE TRAIN IN HALF AN HOUR</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>I REPEAT: ONLY IF YOU’RE UNDER THREAT  IN HERE  WE ARE IN AMERICA RIGHT NOW  OUTSIDE OF THESE DOORS  WE ARE IN IRAN</pattern><template>I’m not going out there!</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I COME IN</pattern><template>The Iran hostage crisis ended on January 20, 1981, when all remaining hostages were released.</template></category><category><pattern>COME TO BED</pattern><template>Another 5 minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  ANY WAY I MAY HELP  SIR</pattern><template>No, only one thing.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S YOUR REAL NAME</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>— I THOUGHT WE DID</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WE TOLD THEM TO SHUT THAT DOWN</pattern><template>There you go.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK I… I GOT TO TELL YA  WE—WE DID SUICIDE MISSIONS IN THE ARMY THAT HAD BETTER ODDS THAN THIS</pattern><template>Sir, the car is here.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAY</pattern><template>— Uh, Mike?</template></category><category><pattern>— RIGHT COME ON  GUYS</pattern><template>The safe and the filing cabinets get long.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DOING THE READING</pattern><template>I’m playing Serksi, the Galactic Witch.</template></category><category><pattern>“ARGO  FUCK YOURSELF ‟ ALL SET</pattern><template>Thanks a lot.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO KNOW YOUR RESUME BACK TO FRONT</pattern><template>Do you really believe your little story’s gonna make a difference when there’s a gun to our heads?</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S ANCIENT TROY</pattern><template>If it’s got horses in it, it’s a western.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS CHRIST</pattern><template>We think it got shredded before they got in.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME  WHAT CHANNEL IS IT ON</pattern><template>Five.</template></category><category><pattern>I’D RATHER STAY HOME AND COUNT THE WRINKLES ON MY DOG’S BALLS</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S YOUR DATE OF BIRTH</pattern><template>February 21st, 1952.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STILL HAVEN’T FOUND SHAFFER</pattern><template>No I was screaming his name ’cos I was fucking ‘em.</template></category><category><pattern>— GREAT</pattern><template>— Sahar will be fine.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU SHOOT ONE PERSON  THEY’RE GONNA KILL EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US IN HERE</pattern><template>I’m telling you if we’re going to go, we need to go now!</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  VERY RESPECTFUL</pattern><template>You’re finished, Lester.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW LONG HAVE THEY BEEN THERE</pattern><template>Sorry?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH I GOT A SON</pattern><template>He lives in Virgina with his mother.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT NOW  GODDAMN IT</pattern><template>Can anybody hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO SET UP A MOVIE IN A WEEK  YOU WANT TO LIE TO HOLLYWOOD  A TOWN WHERE EVERYBODY LIES FOR A LIVING  THEN YOU’RE GONNA SNEAK 007 OVER HERE  INTO A COUNTRY THAT WANTS CIA BLOOD ON THEIR BREAKFAST CEREAL  AND YOU’RE GONNA WALK THE BRADY BUNCH OUT OF THE MOST WATCHED CITY IN THE WORLD</pattern><template>That’s about a hundred militia at the airport. That’s right.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF HERE  AT ONE POINT THE MOB CORNERED ONE OF IRANIANS  WHEN HE TRIED TO PROTECT HIMSELF  THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED  HIT HIM AGAIN  HIT HIM UNTIL HE CAN’T TAKE IT ANYMORE  WE’RE SICK OF THEM</pattern><template>— Yeah! America! .. even in our little community here, I mean people are drawn uptight, they’re tense. They shouldn’t even let those students in that Embassy there. Just shoot a couple of ‘em.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY NEED AN HOUR TO BURN THE CLASSIFIED</pattern><template>I need you to hold.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WILL SEND HIS REPRESENTATIVE TO MEET YOU AND YOUR CREW AT THE GRAND BAZAAR TOMORROW AT 3 P M</pattern><template>They called your bluff.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHERE’S ENGELL</pattern><template>— Uh, he’s in a meeting.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S CONFIRMED  SIR  SIX ESCAPED</pattern><template>I was told five.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU ARE THE DIRECTOR</pattern><template>— Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Pace Academy, Buckhead, Georgia.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CAPTAIN HAS INFORMED US THAT WE’RE ENTERING IRANIAN AIRSPACE</pattern><template>We’ll be coming through to collect any remaining alcoholic beverages.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SOVIETS WOULD PUT UP WITH THIS SHIT  THEY WOULD FUCKING INVADE THEM</pattern><template>Shaffer!</template></category><category><pattern>IF IT’S GOT HORSES IN IT  IT’S A WESTERN</pattern><template>Hey, Kenny please?</template></category><category><pattern>IN 1979  THE PEOPLE OF IRAN OVERTHREW THE SHAH</pattern><template>The exiled cleric, Ayatollah Khomeini, returned to rule Iran.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY WAY TO MAKE THIS MORE UH… MIDDLE EASTERN</pattern><template>Mesopotamia?</template></category><category><pattern>I’M REQUIRED TO REMIND YOU THAT IF YOU ARE DETAINED  THE AGENCY WILL NOT CLAIM YOU</pattern><template>Barely claim me as it is.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE NOT IN THE EMBASSY</pattern><template>During the takeover six people escaped.</template></category><category><pattern>— AND UPON YOU SIR  WELCOME</pattern><template>I hope you are well.</template></category><category><pattern>OR YOU COULD JUST SEND IN TRAINING WHEELS AND MEET THEM AT THE BORDER WITH GATORADE</pattern><template>Tony… It’s three hundred miles to the Turkish border.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS A GRAVITATIONAL FIELD THAT STRONG WILL KILL ANY…    COMPLETELY UNJUSTIFIED</pattern><template>They and all others must know that the United States of America will not yield to International Terrorism or to blackmail. Sir, we’ll be crashed.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOW NEWSOM YOU GOT THE BALLS‟</pattern><template>I can’t believe I put Kathy in this position.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT STERN AGAINST THE INFIDELS</pattern><template>With God’s will.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY IS 8006 STILL ON THE OPEN LIST</pattern><template>Yeah I’ll hold.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP THE OFFICE RUNNING UNTIL YOU HEAR OTHERWISE</pattern><template>— Argo fuck yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>ΝО GООD  ΝОBОDY DОЕЅ WЕЅTЕRNЅ АNYMОRЕ</pattern><template>It’s ancient Troy.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS CAN WAIT  LET’S GO GET A DRINK</pattern><template>He’s late.</template></category><category><pattern>STATE</pattern><template>They don’t do exfil’s.</template></category><category><pattern>— DO THEY SUSPECT SOMETHING</pattern><template>What I know is we need to pretend to be a movie crew.</template></category><category><pattern>A MAN IN SCRANTON IS PLACING A FLAG IN HIS LAWN FOR EVERY DAY OF CAPTIVITY</pattern><template>He runs out of lawn, Kennedy wins the primary.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO’S HANDLING</pattern><template>State is coordinating in house.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I WOULD HAVE LOVED TO  EXCEPT MY BOSS DIDN’T SEND A TELEX UNTIL I GOT HERE</pattern><template>If the guy had an intelligent thought in his head, it would die of loneliness.</template></category><category><pattern>DO THEY STAY PUT</pattern><template>Are we attempting a rescue?</template></category><category><pattern>— COME ON</pattern><template>— I saw in Burma, they get people out.</template></category><category><pattern>﻿1 THIS IS THE PERSIAN EMPIRE KNOWN TODAY AS IRAN</pattern><template>For 2,500 years, this land was ruled by a series of kings known as “Shahs‟.</template></category><category><pattern>CALL MY AGENCY</pattern><template>Sir!</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT’S NOT THE POINT BOB</pattern><template>Doesn’t matter if I saw you go out or you see me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES HE WANT ME HERE FOR</pattern><template>So he can tell State he ran it by his best exfil guy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAME TO US AT A COMPLICATED TIME</pattern><template>Before the revolution forty percent of the movie theaters in Tehran were showing pornograph.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN CHAMBERS MAKE UP</pattern><template>He says the minotaur prosthetic is too tight so he can’t act.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCELLENT</pattern><template>What are we watching?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  WE DO  ONE  THERE ARE NO MORE FOREIGN TEACHERS IN IRAN… AND WE THINK EVERYBODY KNOWS HOLLYWOOD PEOPLE  AND EVERYBODY KNOWS THEY AIN’T SHOOTIN’ STALINGRAD  WITH BOB HOPE DIRECTING IF IT WOULD SELL TICKETS</pattern><template>There are only bad options, it’s about finding the best one.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WAS THAT</pattern><template>— Mark?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  WE GOT THEM OUT</pattern><template>They’re out!</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIDN’T SAY</pattern><template>What happened to your picture?</template></category><category><pattern>— WE ARE CUTTING</pattern><template>Chambers!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’LL SAY YOU DON’T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED… AND IF YOU BELIEVE THEY LOST THEY WHITE SET  THEY’LL BELIEVE IT TOO</pattern><template>Jordan’s in the West Wing, he’s not taking calls.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER SCHOOL I’VE TRADED BASEBALL CARDS— HMM–HMM… OK YOU KNOW THOSE SCIENCE FICTION  STAR TREK  STAR WARS  THEY NEED AN EXOTIC LOCATION TO SHOOT  MOONSCAPE  MARS  DESERT  YOU KNOW… NOW IMAGE THIS</pattern><template>They’re a Canadian film crew on a location scout for a science fiction movie.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SAFE AND THE FILING CABINETS GET LONG</pattern><template>All four drawers, I want them shredded, right now!</template></category><category><pattern>IF THE GUY HAD AN INTELLIGENT THOUGHT IN HIS HEAD  IT WOULD DIE OF LONELINESS</pattern><template>The Times and AP found out six escaped.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE OUT</pattern><template>Great work, boys.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT  BACK STOPPED  WHAT THE HELL DOES THAT MEAN</pattern><template>Carter’s gotta say yes for us to get the tickets.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE NEED HELP</pattern><template>Right now, goddamn it!</template></category><category><pattern>HI  MY NAME’S KEVIN HARKINS… AND I’M GONNA GET YOU HOME</pattern><template>These are the screenplays for your cover identities.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  I’LL THROUGH IT</pattern><template>Iran’s Revolutionary Guard, has rounded up a gang of terrorist blamed for one murder of a half dozen followers of Ayatollah Khomeini. It says security at Khomeini’s home now has been raised. This by the way, is the 69th day that the American hostages have been held in Tehran, there is no change reported in the hostage situation. In this country, George Mitty died last night, he was eighty five years old. Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS FILM CREW IS JUST YOURSELF</pattern><template>No, we have six more from Canada meeting us today.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD FOR THE CHIEF OF STAFF’S OFFICE</pattern><template>The third check point is the trap.</template></category><category><pattern>AM I  AM I REALLY THAT CLOSE</pattern><template>You are this Goddamn close to— I am not gonna leave him at the airport with six people and his dick in his hand.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S YOUR NAME</pattern><template>Mike McEwan A.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T HAVE A BETTER BAD IDEA THAN THIS</pattern><template>This is the best bad idea we have, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT THE SIX WHO ARE WITH THE CANADIANS</pattern><template>We’ve got sixty in the Embassy with guns to their heads right now.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE A FUCKING SPY AGENCY  FIND HIM</pattern><template>The second check point is immigration.</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL GET MOM</pattern><template>I’m calling for you.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT HERE</pattern><template>When did you come through Iran?</template></category><category><pattern>— YES</pattern><template>Is this film a foreign brides film?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE LOOKING FOR LOCATIONS FOR A FILM</pattern><template>— We have a….</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DO NOW</pattern><template>They wanna run it by us, strictly as consultants.</template></category><category><pattern>I’VE KNOWN THIS GUY FOR 25 YEARS  HE’S FULL OF SHIT  AND HE COMES ON HARD  BUT UH… I CAN HANDLE IT</pattern><template>You want to go into production with this in one month?</template></category><category><pattern>SNAKE CHARMERS  FLYING CARPETS</pattern><template>You came to us at a complicated time.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU’RE THINKING OF THE FBI  SIR</pattern><template>Ah. This way.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID THAT IF THE AMERICANS TRY MILITARY FORCE TO RESCUE THE HOSTAGES  THE STUDENTS WILL KILL THEM ALL AND BLOW UP THE EMBASSY  AMERICANS WERE OUTRAGED AT IRAN AND ANYONE IRANIAN  BEFORE THIS DECISION WAS TAKEN  THERE WAS A DEMONSTRATION IN HOUSTON  AN IRANIAN FLAG WAS BURNED  WHILE ANTI IRANIANS DEMONSTRATORS GATHERED NEAR THE IRANIAN CONSULATE  THE DEMONSTRATORS—    ALSO IT’S WHAT LED TO A DECISION TO SCRUTINIZE THE BASES OF THE IRANIAN— THEY KNEW EXACTLY WHAT WAS GOING ON  THEY KNEW IT</pattern><template>But I don’t understand wha— what they should do now, send them back, just to— to be tortured and killed?</template></category><category><pattern>JACK  YOU ARE THIS CLOSE</pattern><template>Am I? Am I really that close?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH IT’S JOHN CHAMBERS  ABOUT THE OFFICE SPACE</pattern><template>It doesn’t matter.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY MAY WELL BE COMING</pattern><template>The police have abandoned their post— If the police are not coming, okay, then the army’s gonna come.</template></category><category><pattern>KEVIN</pattern><template>When did you get back?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE IT IS  WHAT DID I TELL YOU</pattern><template>First shot of the picture.</template></category><category><pattern>AND… WE’RE ROLLING</pattern><template>— We’re going to the producer’s building.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WORLD AM I…</pattern><template>The one where they’re hanging people from construction cranes, Bob!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID A DAY LEARNING OUR COVER THEN STRAIGHT TO THE AIRPORT</pattern><template>— Do they suspect something?</template></category><category><pattern>AND ALL I WAS THINKING WAS… “STAY… THIS IS GOOD FOR ME</pattern><template>Stay.</template></category><category><pattern>THE POLICE HAVE ABANDONED THEIR POST— IF THE POLICE ARE NOT COMING  OKAY  THEN THE ARMY’S GONNA COME</pattern><template>The Prime Minister is not gonna let the embassy be taken over.</template></category><category><pattern>WE THINK IT GOT SHREDDED BEFORE THEY GOT IN</pattern><template>But now the bastards are using sweatshop kids to reassemble the shreds.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP THAT FUCKING SPACE WITCH AWAY FROM ME</pattern><template>You know her?</template></category><category><pattern>TONY… IT’S THREE HUNDRED MILES TO THE TURKISH BORDER</pattern><template>They’d need a support team following them with a tire pump.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER GIVE THEM OPENING SHOTS AT A COVER</pattern><template>— Are they even ready?</template></category><category><pattern>AND—AND YOU’LL FLY OUT WITH THEM</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THIS IS MR  MURPHY FROM PACE ACADEMY CALLING FOR MR  JORDAN</pattern><template>Yeah, I’m afraid it is an emergency.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PEOPLE—HOLD THAT… THE PEOPLE ARE INSPIRED TO JOIN HIM</pattern><template>They are farmers, but they learn to fight.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE’S NO ENOUGH TIME TO… —    ARE CONTROLLED BY CAPITALISTS  AND LARGE OIL COMPANIES  THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT CONSIDERS REVOLUTIONISTS AS TERRORISTS  BUT ITSELF AND ITS CIA ARE THE MOST TERRORIZING ORGANIZATION OF ALL TIME  WE’LL FIND HER SHIP  WE WILL FIND OUR CHANCE</pattern><template>For the Argo lies my hope, my hero, my husband.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN GO</pattern><template>Come on, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE LOOKING AT EGYPT  ISTANBUL</pattern><template>Then we go to the Consulate and say: ’Hey, we want to look in Iran too’.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE VERY EXCITED</pattern><template>You ever watch the news?</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY  CANADA TAKES THE CREDIT  OR THEY’LL RETALIATE AGAINST THE HOSTAGES</pattern><template>Great Satan wasn’t involved.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  WELL  WHAT’S THE UH… WHAT’S THE NUMBER VALUE OF GOOD</pattern><template>A thirty percent chance of being publicly executed?</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  FIRST LET’S GET THESE— IF THEY GET CAUGHT APPLYING FOR VISAS TO THE US… YOU KNOW WHAT  LETS— LETS WAIT FIVE MINUTES</pattern><template>We’re in the only building with direct access to the street, if we’re going to go, then we need to go now!</template></category><category><pattern>— I UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>— Sir… Call our office.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU</pattern><template>Sahar, how are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>— WE GOING AGAIN</pattern><template>Again, everyone!</template></category><category><pattern>ANOTHER 5 MINUTES</pattern><template>She pleaded with me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS THE PURPOSE OF YOUR VISIT</pattern><template>We are looking for locations for a film.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN THESE  IT’S A GIFT</pattern><template>Others are coming.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOTTA GO</pattern><template>These cover identities were created specifically for each one of you.</template></category><category><pattern>ENGELL SHUT THAT DOWN</pattern><template>I say it’s back on!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DO WE NEED THE OPTION</pattern><template>You’re worried about the Ayatollah?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ARGO</pattern><template>The thing… Like Jason and the Golden Fleece, or what?</template></category><category><pattern>THESE ARE THE SCREENPLAYS FOR YOUR COVER IDENTITIES</pattern><template>It’s—it’s theater of the absurd.</template></category><category><pattern>WE THINK OUR HOUSEKEEPER’S FIGURED OUT WHO THEY ARE</pattern><template>We don’t know if we can trust her.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU’RE… AN ASSOCIATE PRODUCER AT BEST</pattern><template>You’re gonna do a 20 million dollars Star Wars rip off.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT TOMORROW</pattern><template>Tomorrow they’ll be ready.</template></category><category><pattern>— I CAN’T DO IT  IT’S BACK STOPPED</pattern><template>— Wait wait, wait a minute!</template></category><category><pattern>HIS EMINENCE CALLED ME</pattern><template>He wants to see you.</template></category><category><pattern>— ARGO FUCK YOURSELF</pattern><template>Your attention please, this is the final calling for British Airways flight 87. We are a nation of 35 millions, and many of these people are looking for to murder them.</template></category><category><pattern>— GET TO YOUR PLANE  CLAUDE — OUI MONSIEUR</pattern><template>First time anyone’s gonna ask you a question is at the first check point.</template></category><category><pattern>BURN IT ALL  COME ON</pattern><template>Burn everything, including the classified. Everything!</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YOU PAY ME EVERY ATTENTION  LADIES AND GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>If our artists could settle in, we’ll just be ready to begin the reading.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  CANADA</pattern><template>We knew that each day that they stayed there, the danger was becoming greater.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN’T BREATH IN THIS HOUSE</pattern><template>I need some fresh air, I can’t—I can’t breath!</template></category><category><pattern>I’M VERY WELL  WHAT’S YOUR NAME</pattern><template>Sahar.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T KNOW</pattern><template>You don’t know?</template></category><category><pattern>IT CAN’T BE NOTHING</pattern><template>Something must’ve happened.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY JUST DON’T KNOW IT</pattern><template>My creation… My creation!</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE WANTED APPLAUSE WE WOULD WOULD HAVE JOINED THE CIRCUS</pattern><template>— I thought we did.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S RIGHT</pattern><template>If we wanted applause we would would have joined the circus.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GO TO THE BAZAAR TODAY  WE FLY FROM THE AIRPORT TOMORROW</pattern><template>We won’t do it.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  RIGHT THIS WAY</pattern><template>This way.</template></category><category><pattern>BEGIN ON STARSHIP… THE PEOPLE WORKING HERE ARE NOT DIPLOMATS  IN FACT  AS THE IMAN KHOMEINI SAID  THEY HAVE FOUND NO EVIDENCE THAT PROVES THAT THESE PEOPLE ARE DIPLOMATS  ALL EVIDENCE PROVES THAT THESE PEOPLE ARE SPIES  IN THE NAME OF GOD  THE BENEFICENT  THE MERCIFUL  OUR MESSAGE TO THE WAKING PEOPLES OF THE WORLD  AT THIS TIME WE WANT TO EXPOSE THE HATEFUL ACTS OF UNITED STATES… OUR WORLD HAS CHANGED  FIRES OF HOPE STOPPED BURNING IN THIS GALAXY LONG AGO</pattern><template>The ship is turning around.</template></category><category><pattern>JORDAN’S IN THE WEST WING  HE’S NOT TAKING CALLS</pattern><template>Where are his kids?</template></category><category><pattern>MY CREATION… MY CREATION</pattern><template>What the fuck, Bryan?</template></category><category><pattern>FAIRING OUT THE TORTURE APPARATUS OF OUR FRIENDS FALLEN DICTATION</pattern><template>It’s getting worse.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  ONLY ONE THING</pattern><template>How long have they been there?</template></category><category><pattern>SWISSAIR 3‒6‒3  YOU ARE CLEARED FOR TAKE OFF</pattern><template>Swissair 3‒6‒3, clear for take off.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID A MOVIE WITH ROCK HUDSON ONE TIME</pattern><template>If you want to sell a lie… get the press to sell it for you.</template></category><category><pattern>MARK AND CORA LIJEK  TWENTY NINE AND TWENTY FIVE  HE’S A CONSULAR OFFICER  SHE’S AN ASSISTANT  NEWLY WEDS  THEY UH… ONLY JUST GOT THERE A COUPLE MONTHS AGO  NO LANGUAGE SKILLS OR IN COUNTRY KNOWLEDGE</pattern><template>Henry Lee Schatz, Agricultural attaché from Idaho, a bit of an oddball apparently, he was there to sell U.S.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE HIDING OUT IN TEHRAN… AND THAT’S WHO I’M GONNA GO GET</pattern><template>What am I making?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE HE WOULD HAVE BEEN REFERRED TO AS A BARBARIAN</pattern><template>— Please!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I’M AFRAID IT IS AN EMERGENCY</pattern><template>Hold for the Chief of Staff’s Office.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE GO OUT THERE WITH FAKE PASSPORTS  WE ARE SPIES  PERIOD  THAT’S EXECUTION</pattern><template>You got a problem lying, Joe?</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE READY TO TRY AGAIN</pattern><template>You’re ready.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY CAUGHT THE SHAH’S CHIEF OF SECURITY TRYING TO GET ON A PLANE TO PARIS</pattern><template>Listen, “since the incident, the number of guards at the airport has doubled, a thorough background examination should be expected‟.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES IT MATTER IF— COULD WE GET THE OPTION</pattern><template>Why do we need the option?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARRIVED TWO DAYS AGO</pattern><template>Forgive my intrusion, we must stay vigilant.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THE REPAIRED LIST OF EMBASSY EMPLOYEES</pattern><template>The numbers don’t match.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE YOU GO</pattern><template>Not here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR ATTENTION PLEASE  THIS IS THE FINAL CALLING FOR BRITISH AIRWAYS FLIGHT 87  WE ARE A NATION OF 35 MILLIONS  AND MANY OF THESE PEOPLE ARE LOOKING FOR TO MURDER THEM</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T KNOW</pattern><template>It means “Argo, fuck yourself‟!</template></category><category><pattern>KEVIN HARKINS  I’M THE PRODUCER</pattern><template>— Nice to meet you.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IT’S THE ARGONAUT</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I WOULD LIKE YOU TO BULLSHIT ME  MAX</pattern><template>Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WANNA RUN IT BY US  STRICTLY AS CONSULTANTS</pattern><template>Engell says, it’s a lose–lose.</template></category><category><pattern>CALL IT SOMETHING OTHER THEN INTELLIGENCE</pattern><template>Hold for the Chief of Staff.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  IT’S THE SHIP  IT’S THE— THE SPACESHIP  IT GOES… IT GOES EVERYWHERE  IT GOES ALL… …ALL THROUGHOUT SPACE</pattern><template>So it’s the Argonaut?</template></category><category><pattern>WE WON’T DO IT</pattern><template>He told them that there are six of us, so then they’re expecting six, it would be suspicious not to show up at this point.</template></category><category><pattern>— TORONTO — “TORONO‟</pattern><template>Canadians don’t pronounce the T.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  KENNY PLEASE</pattern><template>Yeah it’s John Chambers, about the office space.</template></category><category><pattern>SAHAR KNOWS</pattern><template>How about ‘The Horses of Achilles’?</template></category><category><pattern>— LISTEN TO ME</pattern><template>The thinking has changed.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THEY’RE CAUGHT WITH FAKE JOURNALIST CREDS  IT’S PETER AND JANE’S HEAD IN A NOOSE IN AN HOUR</pattern><template>Look, North America accents gives us limited options, so we get the Canadians to issue them passports.</template></category><category><pattern>ARGO — BASED ON A TRUE STORY</pattern><template>Transcript and sync: jcdr U.S. EMBASSY, IRAN NOVEMBER 4, 1979 Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET The carnival is a little bigger today, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WORLD ARE YOU LIVING IN</pattern><template>What world am I…?</template></category><category><pattern>THE IRANIAN PEOPLE TOOK TO THE STREETS OUTSIDE THE US EMBASSY  DEMANDING THAT THE SHAH BE RETURNED  TRIED… AND HANGED</pattern><template>ARGO — Based on a true story.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONE WHERE THEY’RE HANGING PEOPLE FROM CONSTRUCTION CRANES  BOB</pattern><template>It’s too dangerous, — I don’t want to bring my wife into this.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE CALLING IT AGAIN  YOU GOTTA COME BACK</pattern><template>— What?</template></category><category><pattern>TOMORROW THEY’LL BE READY</pattern><template>A man in Scranton is placing a flag in his lawn for every day of captivity.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T WANNA NEED ONE</pattern><template>But when you do, you don’t do it yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I’M SITTING IN JERRY’S THIS MORNING  I’M HAVING BREAKFAST</pattern><template>Waitress comes over to me, she’s waving a newspaper, she says: “You see what those Canadians pulled off?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE YOUR LITTLE STORY’S GONNA MAKE A DIFFERENCE WHEN THERE’S A GUN TO OUR HEADS</pattern><template>I think my story is the only thing between you and a gun to your head.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT REVOLUTIONARY GUARDS GOING DOOR TO DOOR  LIKE JEHOVAH’S WITNESSES</pattern><template>Half of them think that Khomeini’s been too lenient on the ones in the Embassy.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M GONNA HELP YOU  I’M GONNA BE WITH YOU THE WHOLE WAY  THIS IS WHAT I DO</pattern><template>Have you gotten people out this way before?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IT’S BEST IF YOU JUST DON’T SHOW</pattern><template>It was always a fucked mission.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BAZAAR IN TEHRAN IS ONE OF THE LARGEST IN THE WORLD</pattern><template>This Bazaar has been on this spot for over 8000 years.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SHAH ESCAPED ON THE 747 SO LADEN WITH GOLD BARS  THAT THEY DIDN’T MAKE IT OFF THE RUNWAY</pattern><template>But you kept busy.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE’S NOWHERE FOR THEM TO STAY</pattern><template>We will never make it through immigration at the airport.</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT’S WHY THEY’RE STATING HE LIKED THE CURRENT REGIME</pattern><template>The Shah did more for women’s right— I think we’ve better if… Please everyone, get into the coal.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WOULD BE A FIRST</pattern><template>Do you know that everyday they catch another friend of the Shah at the airport?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD</pattern><template>And he said no.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH I JUST PUT VANCE ON A PLANE TO TAKE THE HEAD OF EDS TO A CIRCUS  HE THINKS HE CAN GET HIM TO SIT ON IT FOR NOW</pattern><template>You guy’d better get them.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE GET CAUGHT  YOU AND PAT GO ON TRIAL FOR HARBORING THE ENEMY  YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>Pat and I have discussed this, it’s the risk we took.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  THE CAR IS HERE</pattern><template>You ever think, Lester, this is all for the cameras?</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO NO  PRESS EVENT  THEN THEY’RE— THEY’RE GONNA READ THROUGH THE SCRIPT</pattern><template>I got a bunch of actors who are gonna read from beginning to end, all the way through.</template></category><category><pattern>SAHAR  HOW ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Fine, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SEEMS TO BE IF NOT IMPOTENT  BUT AT LEAST RELUCTANT… THE UNITED STATES FINDS ITSELF IN SUCH BITTER CONFRONTATION WITH THE SOVIET UNION OVER THAT COUNTRY’S INVASION OF AFGHANISTAN… THE UNITED STATES IS NOW MOVING TOWARDS THE DECISION TO BOYCOTT THE SUMMER OLYMPICS IN MOSCOW</pattern><template>Bad new, bad news. Even when it’s good news, it’s bad news.</template></category></AIML>