<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA LET THAT GO</pattern><template>Yeah, owned you....owned you.</template></category><category><pattern>DOM HERE YET</pattern><template>No.   When was the last time you heard from him?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHERE THEY ARE KEEPING THE MONEY</pattern><template>The vault's in the evidence room.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS A REAL SOLID WORK BUT I THINK CAMERA 3 STILL CAUGHT YOU THOUGH</pattern><template>Let's do it again.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  THE MOST MAJOR PLAYER THEY WEIGH THEIR MONEY SO THEY DON'T HAVE TO COST SOMEBODY TO ACCOUNT IT</pattern><template>Right there that's 49 kilos.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD RACE  O'CONNER  THANKS  DOM</pattern><template>The man right there!</template></category><category><pattern>WHATS UP</pattern><template>I thought she was more of a thong man?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT ROAD HITS THROUGH HILL INTO THE FAVELAS COUPLE OF YEARS AGO IT WAS WASHED OUT BY A STORM</pattern><template>So, is dirt from a mile from where you were.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW ME</pattern><template>Its gonna take a little more than money to learn how to cook...that's all.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I KNOW  JUST WHERE TO GET THEM LETS TAKE A RIDE BOYS</pattern><template>Don't hurt yourselfs.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  DID HE JUST LIKE SLAP THAT ASS OR  DID HE LIKE GRAB AND HOLD ON TO IT</pattern><template>Yeah..Hey...this will work.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT ALL THESE SIDE MENUS HERE  FOR DATA ENTRY  LETS CHECK THIS ONE</pattern><template>Look at that. Same building, same order every week.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TURN AROUND AND PUT HANDS BEHIND YOUR BACK</pattern><template>I don't think so.   You are so mistaken to think you got a goddamn choice boy Your mistake ? Thinking you are in america.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE YOU ON THE OTHER SIDE</pattern><template>You guys just copped out a 10 second window Make it count.</template></category><category><pattern>AIN'T NO WAY AROUND THE SYSTEM</pattern><template>The best we can do is peek.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE GUYS ARE GONNA HAVE A LOT OF SURVEILLANCE WE ARE GONNA NEED SOMEONE WHO CAN SCHEDULE THE CIRCUITS</pattern><template>And with those circuits, Reyes is gonna have a  wall  We are gonna need the guys who can punch through those wall What else? Utilities and weapons Someone who ain't afraid to throw down someone who backup every position Yeah? What else we need ?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  OWNED YOU    OWNED YOU</pattern><template>Good race, O'Conner. Thanks, Dom.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THE FBI WANTS TO FIND SOMEBODY THAT'S WHO THEY CALL</pattern><template>Because he never misses his mark.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  NOT JUST FAST</pattern><template>we need a hard ride and air We need something agile.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHY  WE HAVE MANY MORE EXPERIENCED PEOPLE</pattern><template>I like her smile.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  ITS WAY TOO HEAT</pattern><template>I will see you soon, toretto.</template></category><category><pattern>GUYS WHO NEVER LOSE</pattern><template>You know we got that.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS BRAZIL</pattern><template>Come on boss, another day.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN AFTER YOU EVERYTHING SCREWED UP IN LA</pattern><template>Made me free Fall in South America after....</template></category><category><pattern>SO MAKE SURE YOU GOT A LOT OF FIREARM WE FIND THEM  WE TAKE THEM AS A TEAM AND WE BRING THEM BACK</pattern><template>And above all else, we never ever let them get into cars.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WERE 26 HIGH RISK INMATES</pattern><template>Every one on board has been accounted for Except for one   Dominic toretto.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ALL OF IT</pattern><template>You're dead men. You're all dead men.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE  OK</pattern><template>Dom, promise me we stick together.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATS YOU GONNA DO WITH YOUR MONEY</pattern><template>Me?</template></category><category><pattern>CAR FOR CAR</pattern><template>If you want it, come and get it.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE YOU BABY</pattern><template>Change of plans, wait for my call Lets go.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY LIKE SPEED AND GUARANTEE TO GO DOWN THE HARDEST POSSIBLE WAY</pattern><template>So make sure you got a lot of firearm.We find them, we take them as a team and we bring them back.</template></category><category><pattern>AS SOON AS YOU GIVE RICK JAMES HIS JACKET BACK</pattern><template>Sexy legs baby girl.</template></category><category><pattern>UPLOAD THESE FACTS INTO THE DATABASE HAVE THE COMPUTER CROSS CHECK THEM WITH THE OVERHEAD SATELLITES AT EVERY 15 MINUTES</pattern><template>Stand behind in two.</template></category><category><pattern>HELP ME</pattern><template>That's for my team you son of a bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOSE MONEY ARE YOU STEALING</pattern><template>We ain't stealing.</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE    COME ON MAN</pattern><template>Hook a brother up please.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S REYES  I DON'T GIVE A SHIT</pattern><template>Just here to bring in two assholes whose names hit my desk.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLL IT OUT  MIA</pattern><template>You got a straight shot, two blocks Go right.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE GO</pattern><template>Excuse me, buddy Yeah, we have found them.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THAT</pattern><template>How about that?, all motors and no tuning issues?</template></category><category><pattern>IF THESE VEHICLES MOVE ON THE STREETS OF RIO  I WANNA KNOW ABOUT THEM</pattern><template>The beauty of police offices.</template></category><category><pattern>WE KEPT ON GOING IF NOT FOR ROSA</pattern><template>So...listen.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST  WE ARE GONNA NEED A CHAMELEON</pattern><template>Someone who can blend in Anywhere.</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE  ON THE GROUND</pattern><template>I got torreto.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T LIKE MY DESERVE FIRST I CHECKED THE RAIL LINE LIKE YOU ASKED  FOUND A COUPLE OF SPOTS WHERE THEY UNLOADED THE CARS</pattern><template>One set of tracks headed west until it hit the main highway and then disappeared And the another set of tracks headed east 170 inch wheel base, half inch track.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ABOVE ALL ELSE  WE NEVER EVER LET THEM GET INTO CARS</pattern><template>*** lets go hunt.</template></category><category><pattern>GUYS  WE ARE ALL OVER THE NEWS THEY ARE BLAMING US FOR KILLING OF THOSE DEA AGENTS ON THE TRAIN</pattern><template>Which means we just jump to the top of the wanted list.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE'S WHAT MAKES SENSE</pattern><template>All these guys names are on a list. They come up, we take'em down.Not a phone call more, not a bullet less.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW YOU GONNA GET REYES FINGERPRINT OUT OF HERE YOU NEED TO DO SOME MORE RECON</pattern><template>Kinda couple extra guys.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU WANT IT  COME AND GET IT</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>I HEAR YOUR SISTER IS VERY BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>Wherever she hides, i will find her Mia?</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTIME I SEE YOU ON THE OTHER SIDE YOU GUYS JUST COPPED OUT A 10 SECOND WINDOW  MAKE IT COUNT</pattern><template>No...there is too many of them We are not gonna make it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  YOU DIDN'T THINK WE WOULD RECOGNISE YOU WELL  WHAT KIND OF CAR YOU OWN THAT LITTLE COOL MAY RUN THE STREET AROUND HERE BUT THAT MONSTER HAS NEVER SEEN A SET OT TAIL LIGHTS  EVER WELL SHE IS ABOUT TO</pattern><template>Lets go......legend Car for a car.</template></category><category><pattern>DOM  THERE IS A BRIDGE</pattern><template>First is clear We are going to next *** Freeze.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM GOING TO CALL THE EMBASSY  NO   NO  NO</pattern><template>We good...we don't need to call them..For what?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK SO    YOU ARE SO MISTAKEN TO THINK YOU GOT A GODDAMN CHOICE BOY YOUR MISTAKE   THINKING YOU ARE IN AMERICA</pattern><template>You're a long way from home.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY WAY WE CAN BEAT THE CAMERAS  IS WITH INVISIBLE CARS</pattern><template>And i know, just where to get them Lets take a ride boys.</template></category><category><pattern>CHANGE OF PLANS  WAIT FOR MY CALL LETS GO</pattern><template>Where is she going?</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST  TO FIND OUT THE MODEL OF THAT VAULT</pattern><template>Who's the folk you know, do all this.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHERE TO NOW</pattern><template>I don't know Never been to madrid.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL WE HAD A LIFE BEFORE YOU MET US</pattern><template>Alright, well i get to work on the electronics tunneler But there's still another problem Palm scanner And without Reyes hand Print, Houdini himself can not open this bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP</pattern><template>Dom!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE WERE YOU VINCE</pattern><template>Guys all over are asking questions about you Couldn't get out of there without leading them straight to you Had to wait them out.</template></category><category><pattern>A 100 MILLION DOLLARS</pattern><template>And everything we take, we split even.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ELSE</pattern><template>A fast talker. Someone who can bullshit the way out of anything I got that.</template></category><category><pattern>ARREST</pattern><template>I don't feel like i am under arrest.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH MEANS WE JUST JUMP TO THE TOP OF THE WANTED LIST</pattern><template>The feds will get us anywhere, their agents are off the limits.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A MESS</pattern><template>Where you have been Vin.</template></category><category><pattern>START OFF PLAYING HARD TO GET AND  NO MATTER HOW MUCH I CARESS HER  NO MATTER HOW MUCH I LOVE HER IN THE END SHE STILL AIN'T GONNA GIVE UP THAT ASS I GOT THIS    RELAX MAN RELAX</pattern><template>Got it...we got it.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN'T JUST GO SNEAKING AROUND ANY MORE WE DON'T SNEAK THE ONLY THING THAT HE CARES ABOUT IS HIS MONEY</pattern><template>If we pull that, we pull him.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHAT WE ARE TALKING ABOUT IS A 100 MILLION DOLLAR</pattern><template>You sa..Y...wha...t ? Hun...hun...</template></category><category><pattern>NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT</pattern><template>I will just give a minute...it will sink in.</template></category><category><pattern>DO I WANNA KNOW  HOW YOU KNOW ALL THAT</pattern><template>I had a life before you know me O'Conner.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU ARE GONNA GIVE MARTIN LUTHER KING HIS CAR BACK</pattern><template>As soon as you give rick james his jacket back.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BETTER ANSWER SOME GODDAM QUESTIONS</pattern><template>Stop it, both of you.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT IT WOW  THE PLANS WORKING YOU GUYS HAVE EVERY COP CAR IN RIO ON YOUR TAIL</pattern><template>Whats the best drop?</template></category><category><pattern>NO WAGERS  NO BODY ELSE JUST YOU AND ME  ONCE AND FOR ALL YOU SURE  YOU GONNA HANDLE THE DISAPPOINTMENT</pattern><template>Are you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEVER TRUSTED ME</pattern><template>Now, look where its gotten us Look at our family now, i can't go home.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHATS THIS ALL ABOUT DOM</pattern><template>Yeah man, why you drag us half way around the world.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE I AM</pattern><template>We have got some bad news.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  WE ARE</pattern><template>Then we are gonna need a team.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATS YOU BENCHMARK 3 350</pattern><template>My boss sent me here to just make sure everything was safe.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THIS IS A BUST</pattern><template>How you gonna get Reyes fingerprint out of here You need to do some more recon.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE BEING ROBBED  GO AND PULLOVER THE TRAIN</pattern><template>Access card, get the access card.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES THINGS GO STRAY</pattern><template>All i care about is the car.</template></category><category><pattern>A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO  UP IN ECUADOR OR SOMEWHERE</pattern><template>How does it feel ?   Whats that?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST HERE TO BRING IN TWO ASSHOLES WHOSE NAMES HIT MY DESK</pattern><template>Yeah, that's sound like a real hero.</template></category><category><pattern>WILKES  RUN THE PHOTOS OF KNOWN ASSOCIATES OF TORRETTO AND O'CONNER AGAINST CUSTOM ENTRIES IN BRAZIL WITHIN LAST 2 WEEKS</pattern><template>Check planes, trains, boats and everything short of a goddamn space shuttle.</template></category><category><pattern>PLASMA COVER  WILKES I WANT A LIST OF EVERY PLACE WITHIN 50 MILES THAT DISTRIBUTE COMPRESSED GAS TANK</pattern><template>Pass me that evidence bag.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON OUT HERE</pattern><template>Nothing. Please, Dom.</template></category><category><pattern>ROMAN IS RIGHT</pattern><template>We need to get some fresh air.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS GUY IS    HE IS OLD TESTAMENT</pattern><template>Blood, bullets, rap the GOD that's his style.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT SHE WAS MORE OF A THONG MAN</pattern><template>We got the prints.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY ONE ON BOARD HAS BEEN ACCOUNTED FOR EXCEPT FOR ONE   DOMINIC TORETTO</pattern><template>Police believe the identity of men they believe had orchestrated the shocking escape has resulted amazingly in no fatality this afternoon He is former federal agent brian O'Conner.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE NEED TO GET EYES IN THERE</pattern><template>At least, to find out the model of that vault.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS YOUR BOY  WHY WOULD YOU KEEP SOMETHIN LIKE THAT AWAY FROM US</pattern><template>You did it again, huh I have no idea what they are talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM LOOKING FORWARD TO IT</pattern><template>Yep.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING'S IN IT  WE FIND OUT WHAT IT IS</pattern><template>We know what we are up against.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MAN  LETS SEE WHAT WE GOT</pattern><template>Have fun.</template></category><category><pattern>REYES DOESN'T GET AWAY WITH THIS</pattern><template>Its a trap man, you know that.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OK HERE   YEAH</pattern><template>Almost, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YES</pattern><template>You know what's crazy?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALLY LIKE DOING THAT STUFF  HUH</pattern><template>When your life is on the line, that's when you manner by yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>NAH   THAT'S NOT STUPID AT ALL  MAN I LOVE WHAT I DO</pattern><template>You wanna know what i am gonna do with my money.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST TIME I EVER BEEN IN THE FRONT SEAT HEY  ROM WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG</pattern><template>I thought for sure, you be showing up with some chrome spinners or somethin.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED MORE ROOM TO BREATHE</pattern><template>Roman is right.</template></category><category><pattern>HAD TO MAKE A CALL</pattern><template>Hey quit talking, we only got a two minute window.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY       TORETTO</pattern><template>You're under arrest.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  IS DIRT FROM A MILE FROM WHERE YOU WERE</pattern><template>If you headed that way, you will pickup the tracks there Come prepared?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE SET OF TRACKS HEADED WEST UNTIL IT HIT THE MAIN HIGHWAY AND THEN DISAPPEARED AND THE ANOTHER SET OF TRACKS HEADED EAST 170 INCH WHEEL BASE  HALF INCH TRACK</pattern><template>The GT 40 ?  That was missing from the manifest,pretty easy on this rug. Can't move without leaving signs.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT HERE  RIGHT NOW SALUTE  DE FAVELIA</pattern><template>salute...salute...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S FUNNY FROM A GUY WHO TOOK THE OATH OF A COP AND THEN WENT AGAINST EVERYTHING HE STOOD FOR</pattern><template>Or, some wanna be tough guy prick who beat a man half to death with a socket rinch.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  LETS GO THROUGH THE BASICS REAL QUICK</pattern><template>What do we got?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  SOMETIMES I BE OVER THINKING MAYBE AND YOU KNOW I KNOW   WE JUST MET   BUT</pattern><template>You just kinda...gotta.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT WHEN I TOLD YOU HE WAS A COP AND NOT NOW</pattern><template>You never trusted me.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD AFTERNOON OFFICER</pattern><template>License and registration please Yeah! This is big boy stuff We are clear on the right Thanks guys.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THESE GUYS NAMES ARE ON A LIST  THEY COME UP  WE TAKE'EM DOWN NOT A PHONE CALL MORE  NOT A BULLET LESS</pattern><template>Wilkes! We get anything?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A HIT ON THE POLICE SCANNER</pattern><template>Armed robbery in the house of golan.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS A BIG GIG</pattern><template>Couple of high end cars, easy targets.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO IS HIDING</pattern><template>Are you crazy ? Are you crazy?</template></category><category><pattern>DEA TAGS  THIS CAR IS EN SEIZED</pattern><template>Look, who showed up.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE UNDER ARREST</pattern><template>Arrest?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALL GOOD  I PROMISE YOU</pattern><template>Thank you so much for your time I swore to god, if I was on the other side of the glass I will bust your damn face and translate that.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO</pattern><template>Hey Dom, you didn't meet my son Nico I will He is a good kid You know, we named him after you Dominic.</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE BELIEVE THE IDENTITY OF MEN THEY BELIEVE HAD ORCHESTRATED THE SHOCKING ESCAPE HAS RESULTED AMAZINGLY IN NO FATALITY THIS AFTERNOON HE IS FORMER FEDERAL AGENT BRIAN O'CONNER</pattern><template>Appears to be a manhunt underway for three fugitives tonight Multiple federal and local agencies have joined forces In the search for   Dominic toretto and his accomplishes Brian O'Conner and mia toretto.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL GET THERE</pattern><template>Eventually...</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE DON'T PULL THIS JOB OFF  WE ARE PROBABLY DEAD ANYWAY</pattern><template>Lets, make it a million I like that.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  STRAP HIM IN HIS SAFETY BELT   MAN</pattern><template>Give me the remote...going left. Its look like something right over there to the left...what is that?</template></category><category><pattern>REYES KNOWS WE ARE COMING</pattern><template>He's right.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT  LET'S GO</pattern><template>Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S VINCE</pattern><template>That's a good question.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WILL BE SAFE    OK  WELL LET ME JUST COME IN AND TAKE A QUICK PEEK</pattern><template>Nope.   Come on man.</template></category><category><pattern>OK O'CONNER  GIVE ME YOUR BEST SHOT</pattern><template>How was that one ? Camera caught you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAD TO MAKE A CALL  HUH</pattern><template>Shitty call, O'Conner.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GUYS MARK UP A TRACK</pattern><template>O'Conner, lets go get some cars.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY ITS A STEALTH MISSION</pattern><template>We move in and out before they even know we are there.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  THAT'S CRAZY</pattern><template>So, did he just like slap that ass Or, did he like grab and hold on to it?</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE    LOOK MAN I KNOW YOU ARE A TRUE PROFESSIONAL AND I RESPECTS YOU  I PROMISE</pattern><template>You know...it look like you workout a little bit too.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT DOM  RIGHT TURN RIGHT HERE OK GUYS  THERE IS A BIG GROUP COMING AT YOU FROM SOUTH</pattern><template>You have do something, now Lets go wide.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL JUST GIVE A MINUTE   IT WILL SINK IN</pattern><template>We didn't kill those feds.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN  DISAPPEAR     FOREVER NEW PASSPORTS  NEW LIFE  AND NO MORE LOOKING OVER OUR SHOULDER AND WE ARE JUST GONNA BUY OUR FREEDOM</pattern><template>That's right.</template></category><category><pattern>HOOK A BROTHER UP PLEASE</pattern><template>No. And you are not my brother.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT A STRAIGHT SHOT  TWO BLOCKS GO RIGHT</pattern><template>Got it Wow, the plans working You guys have every cop car in Rio on your tail.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A FAIR DEAL</pattern><template>We are less than 24 hours from biggest celebration of our life.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEREVER SHE HIDES  I WILL FIND HER MIA</pattern><template>Hey ..</template></category><category><pattern>THE VAULT'S IN THE EVIDENCE ROOM</pattern><template>Yeah..Um. Can i get everyone's attention right here for a second, we are talkin about breaking into a po lice station.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  WE HAVE PLENTY</pattern><template>Elena Neves.</template></category><category><pattern>BOSS  IF SOMETHING WAS MISSING WE WOULD KNOW</pattern><template>Its a goddamn shame to put a bullshit like that on a classic Here, as well slap some on light on it.</template></category><category><pattern>LETS GO  VINCE</pattern><template>Ladies first.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHATS THE PLAN DOM</pattern><template>Can't just go sneaking around any more We don't sneak The only thing that he cares about is his money.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE GONNA USE THIS INTO ONE LAST JOB</pattern><template>We are gonna take all the Reyes money Every dime of it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE AIN'T STEALING</pattern><template>You tell your boss, exactly who did this.</template></category><category><pattern>US FEDERAL BUREO OF INVESTIGATION</pattern><template>It says caucasian?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  AND YOU ARE NOT MY BROTHER</pattern><template>Brother from another mother?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OK    YEAH  YOU ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>And,here you are? Just like a toretto.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  THE WAY CAR SEEM IS DOWN HERE  WE CAN UNLOAD THEM QUICK AND GET TOP DOLLAR</pattern><template>Its easy money.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TELL YOU LITTLE SOMETHING ABOUT THESE TWO MEN ONE'S A FORMER FEDERAL OFFICER  BEEN IN DEEP COVER FOR 5 YEARS</pattern><template>Knows everyWay we are gonna come from.The other one's a professional criminal, escaped prison twice, Spent half his life on run avoiding folks like you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO SPLIT UP I AM PREGNANT I ALREADY LOST MY FAMILY ONCE I AM NOT GONNA DO THAT AGAIN</pattern><template>Are you kidding me?</template></category><category><pattern>LETS PUT IT BACK TOGETHER AND FIND OUT WHATS MISSING</pattern><template>Hey Dom, what do you remember about your father?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WHAT THIS IS</pattern><template>I got love for you all, but personal ain't good business I can't do this homie.</template></category><category><pattern>GET SOMETHING TO EAT</pattern><template>Yeah She might be right.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GT 40    THAT WAS MISSING FROM THE MANIFEST PRETTY EASY ON THIS RUG  CAN'T MOVE WITHOUT LEAVING SIGNS</pattern><template>Give me the damn stretches The ground rolls into a hard pack and we lost the track too.</template></category><category><pattern>DOM  PROMISE ME WE STICK TOGETHER</pattern><template>I promise.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE TAKING THIS CAR APART FOR A REASON</pattern><template>Lets put it back together and find out whats missing.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL OF THEM</pattern><template>All of them Sounds crazy. Bring us to whole another country so, that we can rob the dude who runs it I thought this is business Sounds personal to me.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOU GOT A     YOU GOT A LITTLE MORE THAN 10 11 MILLION DOLLARS COMING</pattern><template>Whats you gonna do with your money?</template></category><category><pattern>WAS SHE SO SPECIAL TO YOU</pattern><template>I never thought anyone could understand how much.</template></category><category><pattern>CUT US LOOSE</pattern><template>Everything all right? Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT REAL TOUGH</pattern><template>You turn around and put hands behind your back.</template></category><category><pattern>TRACKER'S ON</pattern><template>Got him.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY REFILL THE VIEW  10 SECONDS OSCILLATION</pattern><template>Nah...that's a narrow window man?</template></category><category><pattern>ACCESS CARD  GET THE ACCESS CARD</pattern><template>Dom, there is a bridge.</template></category><category><pattern>FONT COLOR= #FF8C00  ||    FAST FIVE    ||ENJOY    FONT COLOR= ##FF8C00  SUBTITLE CREATED BY SIJUVRM  DOMINIC TORETTO  YOU ARE HEREBY SENTENCED TO SERVE 25 YEARS TO LIFE AT THE LOMPOC MAXIMUM SECURITY PRISON SYSTEM</pattern><template>without the possibility of early parole.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL I CARE ABOUT IS THE CAR</pattern><template>Tell me where it is.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HEARD ME</pattern><template>But why? We have many more experienced people.</template></category><category><pattern>HOBBS IS ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE CITY</pattern><template>We are not gonna get a better window.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE YOU MIGHT    WANNA</pattern><template>Hey Dom, Listen, i know you have a separate job tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT'S CRAZY</pattern><template>There is only four of those cars in the whole world.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MONEY STAYS THOUGH</pattern><template>If i were you, I would probably use the time Make peace with whatever things you got left Because come tomorrow, I will found you.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP IT  BOTH OF YOU</pattern><template>Where were you vince.</template></category><category><pattern>HE USED TO    HE USED TO HAVE A BARBEQUE EVERY SUNDAY AFTER CHURCH FOR EVERYBODY IN THE NEIGHBOURHOOD</pattern><template>If we didn't go to church we didn't get any barbeque.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY SINGLE DAY HE WAS IN THE SHOP AND  EVERY SINGLE NIGHT HE WAS AT THE KITCHEN TABLE WITH MIA HELPING HER WITH HER HOMEWORK</pattern><template>Even after she went to sleep he would stay up for few more hours.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I HAD TO MAKE A CALL</pattern><template>Help me.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S YOUR MAN OVER THERE ON THE TABLE</pattern><template>The plan is busted, this is bullshit man.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE GONNA BE LOOKING FOR THE THREE OF US TOGETHER NOW</pattern><template>We need to split up. You and mia head south i will lead them away.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M MOTIVATED</pattern><template>All right then, lets find ourselves a car.</template></category><category><pattern>NO PAPER TRAILS MEANS NO BANKS</pattern><template>No banks means cash houses.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY    SHIT</pattern><template>Guys i am hearing all this chatter, you just take out a bank ?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>Look, the way car seem is down here, we can unload them quick and get top dollar.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT 100 MILLION DOLLARS IN A SAFE YOU GONNA PUT SOMEBODY ELSE'S HAND PRINT ON IT</pattern><template>How are we supposed to get Reyes's hand Print?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK    I AM WORKING THIS CASE AND I GOT SOME EVIDENCE HERE TO BE HELD</pattern><template>But i need to get in....and check your storage facility first.</template></category><category><pattern>GET DRESSED MAN  WE GOT THINGS TO DO</pattern><template>So, where to now?</template></category><category><pattern>PLUS I PROCURE YOU ARE ONLY THE REAL ONE WHO CAN'T BE BROUGHT  AM I RIGHT</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHEN YOU CALLED ME TO COME TO RIO  I ASSUMED IT WOULD BE FOR SOMETHING MORE EXCITING THAN THIS THIS IS TEJ  THE BEST CIRCUIT MEN IN THE EAST COAST</pattern><template>This is my boy Roman Pearce, we go way back from juvenile I pulled that job with him Miami.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL   YOU KNOW WHAT  WE CAN ALWAYS SHINE TOGETHER BABY</pattern><template>Get dressed man, we got things to do.</template></category><category><pattern>BUSTER</pattern><template>Dom here yet.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  SEE  THERE YOU WITH THAT THEORY MAN</pattern><template>You know me...</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING  PLEASE  DOM</pattern><template>Just, let me have the chip.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY DOM  WHAT DO YOU REMEMBER ABOUT YOUR FATHER</pattern><template>My father...</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN AFTER SHE WENT TO SLEEP HE WOULD STAY UP FOR FEW MORE HOURS</pattern><template>So he could learn the next chapter and help her next day I remember everything about my father.</template></category><category><pattern>YEP</pattern><template>Tracker's on.</template></category><category><pattern>IS ALL THIS REALLY NECESSARY TO APPREHEND TWO MEN</pattern><template>Let me tell you little something about these two men.One's a former federal officer, been in deep cover for 5 years.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY STAY WHEN THEY ARE SUPPOSED TO RUN THEY STEAL GAS AND THEN GIVE IT AWAY</pattern><template>And now they killed three federal agents?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS ONLY FOUR OF THOSE CARS IN THE WHOLE WORLD</pattern><template>And i got the only one in western hemisphere I made a sheikh in abu dhabi an offer he could not refuse.  Huh And, that's a nice lady you got there too.  Oh...absolutely Well...we got to go man.</template></category><category><pattern>ME</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>Of course i am.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT IT   WE GOT IT</pattern><template>Yeah...we are looking at four cameras.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT THEN  LETS FIND OURSELVES A CAR</pattern><template>What do you think?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS   6 X 6</pattern><template>8 x 12 7 x 12. 18 Inch thick steel. Re Enforced wall, with insulated copper core to protect it against thermal lance.</template></category><category><pattern>WE KNOW WHAT WE ARE UP AGAINST</pattern><template>Alright, listen up. The men we're after are professional runners.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY   MAN  I HAVE BEEN THINKING ABOUT OPENING UP A GARAGE BACK HOME</pattern><template>A place where people can bring their cars, and they get completely ripped off, you know what I mean?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STICK WITH THE PLAN IT WAS ALWAYS THE PLAN</pattern><template>Take care of mia.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SECOND THROUGH LAST RACER</pattern><template>What, what is it?</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST IS CLEAR WE ARE GOING TO NEXT *** FREEZE</pattern><template>We had to make a call, huh.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A 1970 CHARGER</pattern><template>Let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE PULL THAT  WE PULL HIM</pattern><template>Are you ready?</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT FOR SURE  YOU BE SHOWING UP WITH SOME CHROME SPINNERS OR SOMETHIN</pattern><template>Ha.....hah....real funny I got a 100,000 that says i can take you all in the next quarter mile.</template></category><category><pattern>LADIES FIRST</pattern><template>See you baby.</template></category><category><pattern>DOM YOU LISTEN TO ME   NOW  OK  YOU CUT LOOSE RIGHT NOW I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU TO GO ON</pattern><template>Yeah! I had to make a call.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE THE HELL CAN I GET ONE OF THESE</pattern><template>Well we had a life before you met us.</template></category><category><pattern>BEAUTY AS IN GOOD</pattern><template>Beauty as in you know...</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I WOULD LOVE TO EXPAND MY OPERATIONS IN YOUR COUNTRY BUT QUITE FRANKLY</pattern><template>No business methods are hard to find.</template></category><category><pattern>MONEY WILL COME AND GO  WE KNOW THAT</pattern><template>The most important thing in life Will always be the people in this room.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  BUT HOW</pattern><template>This thing has already been difficult If it ain't that..</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  ITS THE TAN    YOU KNOW TAN</pattern><template>Look....i am working this case and i got some evidence here to be held.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW I SEE WHY YOU ALWAYS GETTIN ACCIDENTS YOU CAN'T DRIVE A DAMN REMOTE CONTROL CAR I DON'T NEED THIS  I DON'T</pattern><template>Its a crisis.  Shut up right now.</template></category><category><pattern>SET THEM DOWN</pattern><template>Macroy, cover me Watch that Cut us loose! Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO MOVE  WE DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH TIME I GOT SOME FLIGHT OUT  THAT LEAVES RIO DE JANEIRO IN NEXT 5 HOURS</pattern><template>Not to run away....</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE MY WORD VINCE</pattern><template>You were always my brother.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE IS A BEAUTY  THOUGH</pattern><template>Beauty as in good?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I GOT MINE I GOT EYES ON FIVE I KNOW YOU SAID THEY WERE CONSOLIDATING MONEY SOMEWHERE BUT YOU ALL AIN'T GONNA BELIEVE IT</pattern><template>Well, this job has got a little harder.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU READY</pattern><template>I'm ready.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  NOT AS LONG TO FLIP THE RECEIVER</pattern><template>You're going down torretto.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT OUT OF MILITARY PROBABLY THE SAME TIME YOU QUIT SMOKING THE AMOUNT OF CHIPS YOU ATE</pattern><template>The way you always had to keep your hands and mouth busy You are a two packs a day.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS HELL OF A MESS</pattern><template>Yeah, it is.</template></category><category><pattern>TO FINISH THE JOB</pattern><template>Are you crazy Dom ? We can't.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANNA KNOW WHAT I AM GONNA DO WITH MY MONEY</pattern><template>Find some cooking lesson for my man.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT TIME IS ROBBERY AROUND 11' O CLOCK HERE WE GO ENHANCE IT</pattern><template>There faces are covered.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY TO HEAR FOR LOSS OF YOUR MEN</pattern><template>Is all this really necessary to apprehend two men?</template></category><category><pattern>CHEERS   CHEERS     CHEERS</pattern><template>So we in brazil, still a good life.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HMM</pattern><template>Tokyo.</template></category><category><pattern>GOING IN THAT BOUTY  ITS JUST CRAZY    I GOT THIS</pattern><template>What time is robbery Around 11' o clock Here we go Enhance it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE GONNA NEED SOME REAL FAST CARS TO GET TO THIS</pattern><template>And, not just fast...</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  WELL I GET TO WORK ON THE ELECTRONICS TUNNELER BUT THERE'S STILL ANOTHER PROBLEM PALM SCANNER AND WITHOUT REYES HAND PRINT  HOUDINI HIMSELF CAN NOT OPEN THIS BITCH</pattern><template>How do you know its Reyes's hand Print?</template></category><category><pattern>GUYS ALL OVER ARE ASKING QUESTIONS ABOUT YOU COULDN'T GET OUT OF THERE WITHOUT LEADING THEM STRAIGHT TO YOU HAD TO WAIT THEM OUT</pattern><template>That is such a horse shit, that was your job.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THAT  SAME BUILDING  SAME ORDER EVERY WEEK</pattern><template>Its a delivery schedule.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO IN BOUND</pattern><template>Alright! There is an ally coming on your left Yeah! I got it.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WE IN BRAZIL  STILL A GOOD LIFE</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>O'CONNER  LETS GO GET SOME CARS</pattern><template>....Interval...Go have something!</template></category><category><pattern>IF THERE IS ANYTHING ILLEGAL HAPPENING IN RIO  REYES IS INVOLVED</pattern><template>Okay, then so are we.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THE REST WERE SOLD OUT</pattern><template>So, whats this all about Dom?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THIS JOB HAS GOT A LITTLE HARDER</pattern><template>If he is moving it into a police station he has got some serious brass in his pocket.</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE O  ONE TIME  PEAKS PEOPLE WE DON'T LIKE</pattern><template>You know police stations are designed actually to let people in and out.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>I'm not going anywhere. Ok.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW SHIT ABOUT MY DAD I DON'T REMEMBER HIM YELLING  I DON'T REMEMBER HIM SMILING</pattern><template>To be honest with you, I don't remember what the hell he look like I had all the memories....he is just never there You ain't gonna be like that Brian We can't keep running Dom We got to get out We got to get out, now.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER</pattern><template>He used to....he used to have a barbeque every sunday after church For everybody in the neighbourhood.</template></category><category><pattern>8 X 12 7 X 12  18 INCH THICK STEEL  RE ENFORCED WALL  WITH INSULATED COPPER CORE TO PROTECT IT AGAINST THERMAL LANCE</pattern><template>The class 3 electronical lock would sure fire..</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE</pattern><template>You just made a big mistake Took me while to find out that tracking chip.</template></category><category><pattern>CIRCUS CLOWNS I SEE  YOU HAVE ALL MET</pattern><template>Here he is.</template></category><category><pattern>TORETTO AND O'CONNER</pattern><template>They stay when they are supposed to run They steal gas and then give it away?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW ITS REYES'S HAND PRINT</pattern><template>You got 100 million dollars in a safe You gonna put somebody else's hand Print on it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN'T OR WE SHOULDN'T</pattern><template>I think it doesn't change a thing I say we stick to the plan.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT GUCCI FRAMES OR SOMETHIN</pattern><template>No, no...</template></category><category><pattern>DRUGS  NO  THAT'S A DEALER PACK</pattern><template>See, the most major player they weigh their money so they don't have to cost somebody to account it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  TO CONTINUE RECEIVING THEM WOULD REQUIRE WILL OF PORTUGUESE AND THAT'S WHY ALL BRAZILIANS SPEAKS PORTUGUESE TODAY</pattern><template>Now, if you Dominate the people with violence, they will eventually fight back.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE  OUT OF ALL OF US  YOU GOT THE BIGGEST MOUTH</pattern><template>That is for damn certain.</template></category><category><pattern>ALMOST</pattern><template>Wait, Dom Mia was on that train I didn't.....i didn't know i wouldn't do anything to hurt her.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE FACES ARE COVERED</pattern><template>Run it through FRS.</template></category><category><pattern>LOVE THOSE GLASSES  WHERE DID YOU GET THEM FROM</pattern><template>Is it gucci frames or somethin?</template></category><category><pattern>HOBBS WILL FIND YOU YOU HAVE EVERY REASON TO LEAVE WHY STAY     WHY DO YOU</pattern><template>My husband was a good police officer...an honest man...we both grew up here.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS SHE GOING</pattern><template>We are being robbed, go and pullover the train.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU BETTER GET STARTED</pattern><template>They were taking this car apart for a reason.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT THE REASON YOU LET HIM BEAT YOU IN THE QUARTER MILE</pattern><template>That was a baby gift.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S FUNNY  BECAUSE IT GOES BOTH WAYS</pattern><template>You know...</template></category><category><pattern>FOR SURE UN FILTERED</pattern><template>Well, this is a bust.</template></category><category><pattern>NAH   THAT'S A NARROW WINDOW MAN</pattern><template>Can we just stop the scanner and replace the image.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT THEN</pattern><template>We only live once, lets do it.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST  UNTIL WE KILL THAT SON OF A BITCH</pattern><template>So, whats the plan Dom?</template></category><category><pattern>ALMOST  THANK YOU</pattern><template>They are gonna be looking for the three of us together now.</template></category><category><pattern>A PLACE WHERE PEOPLE CAN BRING THEIR CARS  AND THEY GET COMPLETELY RIPPED OFF  YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME THE REMOTE   GOING LEFT  ITS LOOK LIKE SOMETHING RIGHT OVER THERE TO THE LEFT   WHAT IS THAT</pattern><template>Bingo.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  AS SOON AS WE HIT THE FIRST ONE THEY ARE GONNA DO EVERYTHING THEY CAN TO PROTECT THEIR ASSETS</pattern><template>Exactly.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS DEFINITELY NOT JUST A CHIP</pattern><template>Look at all these side menus here, for data entry. Lets check this one.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE WE GOT A JOB</pattern><template>Alright, so target's name is Hernan Reyes.</template></category><category><pattern>EACH TRYING TO GET THE COUNTRY FROM THERE METHODS</pattern><template>The spanish arrive guns blazing, determine to prove who is boss.</template></category><category><pattern>AMBUSH</pattern><template>Wilkes, suppressing fire.</template></category><category><pattern>NO   THANK YOU</pattern><template>No, she can't.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  I GUESS THAT MEANS THERE ARE TWO IN THE WESTERN HEMISPHERE  HUH   HUH WHATS YOUR SMART ASS GOTTA SAY NOW</pattern><template>Well...you know what, we can always shine together baby.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE</pattern><template>Ok. That's crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOU ARE SAYING EACH ONE OF THESE SHIPMENT IS WORTH 10 MILLION DOLLARS</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>NO BANKS MEANS CASH HOUSES</pattern><template>That's right.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE HAPPIEST I HAVE EVER SEEN MY SISTER IT GOES WITH FREE</pattern><template>You know? I wanna another shot.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>No wagers, no Body Else just you and me, once and for all You sure, you gonna handle the disappointment?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW NEVER BEEN TO MADRID</pattern><template>I thought you wanna go to tokyo..</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MAN   THIS IS CRAZY</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT COME ON</pattern><template>Though, you still can drive. You see...</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>Pardon me gentlemen.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING BIG IS GOING DOWN</pattern><template>That's a 1970 charger.</template></category><category><pattern>FIND SOME COOKING LESSON FOR MY MAN</pattern><template>See, see? There you with that theory man?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT TIME DO THEY OPEN</pattern><template>They open the same time when i pull this trigger Want me to open them?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S FOR MY TEAM YOU SON OF A BITCH</pattern><template>Its hell of a mess.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THAT'S 11 MILLION A PIECE  I AM DOWN I AM IN 11 MILLION  SOUNDS LIKE A WHOLE LOTTA VAGINAL ACTIVITY TO ME</pattern><template>You can't pull off all the heist on the same mark, you just can't.</template></category><category><pattern>TO TELL YOU EXACT  ITS SPREAD THROUGHOUT THE CITY AND WE ARE GONNA HIT THEM ALL</pattern><template>All of them.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER MAN</pattern><template>I ain't scared. I am just lettin you all know..</template></category><category><pattern>GOT HIM</pattern><template>I don't understand. Why come here?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY DOM  LISTEN  I KNOW YOU HAVE A SEPARATE JOB TOMORROW</pattern><template>If you need an extra men Mike, you are in You always have been a family.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE ALWAYS MY BROTHER</pattern><template>See, you my brother.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU READING</pattern><template>Tour guide.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HEY   THIS WILL WORK</pattern><template>I'm impressed.   Got it?</template></category><category><pattern>FAMILY JUST GOT BIGGER    YE  H</pattern><template>Something doesn't add up.</template></category><category><pattern>LETS DO THIS OK  I WILL DRIVE IN THAT  COME ON MAN  NO   NO WAY NO  NOT   NOT IN THIS  IN THAT</pattern><template>Are you seRious right now.</template></category><category><pattern>MACROY  COVER ME WATCH THAT CUT US LOOSE  COME ON</pattern><template>Cut us loose!</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT THIS WAY  MY DEAR STAY RIGHT HERE  I WILL BE RIGHT BACK</pattern><template>So, this is your dream..Huh That's enough of me man I take you are enjoying?</template></category><category><pattern>I ALWAYS WANTED ONE OF THOSE</pattern><template>Held the record on the envadeda 3 years running.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW POLICE STATIONS ARE DESIGNED ACTUALLY TO LET PEOPLE IN AND OUT</pattern><template>That's why its a stealth mission.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YEAH IT STILL CAUGHT YOU   THEN I WILL MILK THE HELL OUT OF THAT THING TOO</pattern><template>We are gonna need a faster car.</template></category><category><pattern>IT AIN'T GONNA WORK SPIKES AHEAD DOM    WE GOT SPIKES</pattern><template>We are going right Nah...its too tight...</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>Was she so special to you?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF THERE'S ANYTHING WE CAN DO TO HELP</pattern><template>Two things.</template></category><category><pattern>IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE</pattern><template>Here's what makes sense.</template></category><category><pattern>NO BUSINESS METHODS ARE HARD TO FIND</pattern><template>Let me tell you true story 500 years ago Portuguese and spanish came here.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  I HEARD THEY WERE LOOKING FOR A CHEF</pattern><template>Down at this animal shelter.</template></category><category><pattern>LEAVE RIO  YOU CAN BE FREE I DON'T NEED FREEDOM</pattern><template>You should know that...</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE COMING IN NOW TELL THE MARSHALS TO PREPARE A VEHICLE TO HOME BACK</pattern><template>Ambush!</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD ABOUT YOU    NICE STAKES</pattern><template>Yeah, the rest were sold out.</template></category><category><pattern>SEXY LEGS BABY GIRL</pattern><template>What time do they open?</template></category><category><pattern>IS ANYONE LISTENING TO THOSE WORDS</pattern><template>Anybody? Po Po.</template></category><category><pattern>OK GUYS  ITS SHOWTIME</pattern><template>First team in position, lets go.  Come on lets do this.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CLASS 3 ELECTRONICAL LOCK WOULD SURE FIRE</pattern><template>And a biometric palm scanner.</template></category><category><pattern>BROTHER FROM ANOTHER MOTHER</pattern><template>Look..No one enters the facility but authorized evidence personnel Now stop wasting my time.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T PULL OFF ALL THE HEIST ON THE SAME MARK  YOU JUST CAN'T</pattern><template>Yeah, as soon as we hit the first one they are gonna do everything they can to protect their assets.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS SUCH A HORSE SHIT  THAT WAS YOUR JOB</pattern><template>Enough O'Conner! If he said he didn't do it, he didn't do it.</template></category><category><pattern>DOM'S RIGHT</pattern><template>We got lucky to get away, but what happens next time?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE TRACK THE OWNER OFF THE VEHICLE ID THEY ARE COUPLE OF SHELL COMPANIES IN BETWEEN A CORPORATION OWNED BY A INVESTOR NAMED HERNAN REYES</pattern><template>Investor?</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE PULL OFF THIS JOB  I WILL</pattern><template>Next two lights, a 100,000.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  HE IS GOOD</pattern><template>When the FBI wants to find somebody that's who they call.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SET OFF THE DEAL I THOUGHT THE JOB WAS FOR THE CARS I DID NOT KNOW  ALL THEY WANTED WAS THE CHIP</pattern><template>Damn.</template></category><category><pattern>LICENSE AND REGISTRATION PLEASE YEAH  THIS IS BIG BOY STUFF WE ARE CLEAR ON THE RIGHT THANKS GUYS</pattern><template>Anytime I see you on the other side You guys just copped out a 10 second window, make it count.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY CAME BEARING GIFTS</pattern><template>Mirrors, scissors, things that the native couldn't get own their own.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO SPLIT UP  YOU AND MIA HEAD SOUTH I WILL LEAD THEM AWAY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  WHY WOULD YOU BELIEVE ANYTHING I WOULD TELL YOU</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT LOVE FOR YOU ALL  BUT PERSONAL AIN'T GOOD BUSINESS I CAN'T DO THIS HOMIE</pattern><template>So, what we are talking about is a 100 million dollar.</template></category><category><pattern>EXACTLY</pattern><template>That's all of it.</template></category><category><pattern>OR  SOME WANNA BE TOUGH GUY PRICK WHO BEAT A MAN HALF TO DEATH WITH A SOCKET RINCH</pattern><template>That real tough.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT TORRETO</pattern><template>Hey! Police!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS MY BOY ROMAN PEARCE  WE GO WAY BACK FROM JUVENILE I PULLED THAT JOB WITH HIM MIAMI</pattern><template>I heard about you.   Nice stakes.</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT HOBBS  CHIEF OF POLICE</pattern><template>Sorry to hear for loss of your men.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ALL CLEAR ON THE LEFT</pattern><template>Good afternoon officer.</template></category><category><pattern>//SUBS DEDICATED TO MA MOM AND BUMBO// HOME   SWEET HOME</pattern><template>Now that.</template></category><category><pattern>BINGO</pattern><template>What is this ? 6 x 6?</template></category><category><pattern>TOKYO</pattern><template>You know what all of these places have in common.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WILL LET YOU GO *** FULL OF SHIT I DO NOT KNOW HOW YOU GUYS DO BUSINESS IN YOUR PART OF THE WORLD</pattern><template>But here in Rio... i like all parties to know what they are up against.</template></category><category><pattern>NAH   ITS HOOKED UP INTO A DIGITAL SYNC</pattern><template>Ain't no way around the system.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK</pattern><template>Its definitely not just a chip.</template></category><category><pattern>NUMBER 1 IS IN MOTION</pattern><template>Two is on the move.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT SO</pattern><template>So, what is that?</template></category><category><pattern>THREE DEA AGENTS  ALONG WITH</pattern><template>Of course, this is business.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS A BABY GIFT</pattern><template>No, that's messed up.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT YOU BRIAN</pattern><template>Nah....not a bit.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IN LIFE WILL ALWAYS BE THE PEOPLE IN THIS ROOM</pattern><template>Right here, right now Salute, de favelia...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ASKED FOR ME   I DID</pattern><template>May i ask, why?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD RUN YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Hobbs will find you You have every reason to leave why stay ?   Why do you?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T FEEL LIKE I AM UNDER ARREST</pattern><template>How about you brian?</template></category><category><pattern>THE MAN RIGHT THERE</pattern><template>He left off the throttle with a mile.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  WHO SHOWED UP</pattern><template>Oh! GOD, i am so happy you are ok.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  THE NATIVES KILLED EVERY SINGLE SPANIARD</pattern><template>Personally, i prefer the methods of the portuguese.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS A DELIVERY SCHEDULE</pattern><template>Drugs? No, that's a dealer pack.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST TEAM IN POSITION  LETS GO   COME ON LETS DO THIS</pattern><template>Hey Dom, i got eyes on mia Moscow, berlin, goa, hong kong.</template></category><category><pattern>DID HE JUST SMACK THAT ASS OR  DID HE GRAB THE ASS</pattern><template>Thanks .. Thank you ..</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE  THEY HAVE NOTHING TO LOSE</pattern><template>And, that's the key I go into the favals, and give them something to lose Electricity, running water, school room for their kids And for that taste of the better life I own them.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS A JOB COMING UP I WAS HOPING DOM WAS GONNA BE HERE BY NOW  BUT</pattern><template>This one's clean enough, we can do it without him.</template></category><category><pattern>TORETTO I'LL SEE YOU SOON</pattern><template>No...you won't.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  HOW LONG WERE YOU IN THE ARMY</pattern><template>I got out of military probably the same time you quit smoking The amount of chips you ate.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH ANYBODY CAN TALK SHIT IN SPANISH TWO FAILS  I AM NOT FAIL     TWO FAILS WHO ARE THESE CLOWNS MEN</pattern><template>Circus clowns I see, you have all met.</template></category><category><pattern>TIME WINDOW IS TOO SMALL  MAN</pattern><template>The only way we can beat the cameras, is with invisible cars.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE GONNA SEND THEIR BEST GUYS  WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE ONE THING WE KNOW FOR SURE IS THAT  THEY WANTED THIS CAR</pattern><template>Something's in it. We find out what it is.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT A LOT OF BONES TO BRING YOUR PROBLEMS HERE TORRETO NOT TO MENTION A COP YEAH  WE CAN KEEP THAT ON THE LOW WORD ON THE STREET IS THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE LOOKING FOR YOU TWO</pattern><template>But, you didn't think we would recognise you Well, what kind of car you own That little cool may run the street around here but that monster has never seen a set ot tail lights, ever Well she is about to.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BETTER CHECK THAT TONE</pattern><template>You better answer some goddam questions.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  MILLION DOLLAR A QUARTER MILE</pattern><template>Alright then.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S MOVE MOVE    MOVE    MOVE STOPPED   ABOUT A BLOCK AHEAD</pattern><template>Park it...we are going on foot.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN</pattern><template>She can't.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>HA     HAH    REAL FUNNY I GOT A 100 000 THAT SAYS I CAN TAKE YOU ALL IN THE NEXT QUARTER MILE</pattern><template>Yeah, you broke that like you got a 100 grand.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS A SUICIDE MISSION</pattern><template>That's your man over there on the table.</template></category><category><pattern>EXACTLY WHY YOUR ASS AIN'T BEEN DRIVING  YOU GOTTA RE BLAZE I THINK  I AM IN LOVE</pattern><template>That was a real solid work but i think camera 3 still caught you though.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM NOT GONNA SHUT UP</pattern><template>alright, strap him in his safety belt...man.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEVER LISTENED TO ME</pattern><template>Not when i told you he was a cop and not now.</template></category><category><pattern>HE RUNS THE DRUG SCENE OUT THERE HE HAS NEVER BEEN BUSTED BECAUSE HE DOESN'T LEAVE A PAPER TRAIL</pattern><template>No paper trails means no banks.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HELLO YOU SON OF A BITCH</pattern><template>Wilkes, run the photos of known associates of torretto and O'Conner against custom entries in brazil within last 2 weeks.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE LESS THAN 24 HOURS FROM BIGGEST CELEBRATION OF OUR LIFE</pattern><template>You gotta re fill.</template></category><category><pattern>KNOWS EVERYWAY WE ARE GONNA COME FROM THE OTHER ONE'S A PROFESSIONAL CRIMINAL  ESCAPED PRISON TWICE  SPENT HALF HIS LIFE ON RUN AVOIDING FOLKS LIKE YOU</pattern><template>Well, if there's anything we can do to help...</template></category><category><pattern>SEVEN  DO YOU THINK THAT GUY WITH A FUNNY LOOK IS A TOURIST</pattern><template>So, how long were you in the army?</template></category><category><pattern>ITS A GODDAMN SHAME TO PUT A BULLSHIT LIKE THAT ON A CLASSIC HERE  AS WELL SLAP SOME ON LIGHT ON IT</pattern><template>They took the chip.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIKE HER SMILE</pattern><template>What's the second thing.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW</pattern><template>Sh...it!</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING</pattern><template>That's just it.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE ITS WORTH IT</pattern><template>You should run you know!</template></category><category><pattern>LETS JUST LEAVE IT WITH THAT  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>She is a beauty, though.</template></category><category><pattern>US DIPLOMATIC SECURITY SERVICE ISSUED THE WARRANTS</pattern><template>Agent L.Hobbs.</template></category><category><pattern>TEN TIMES THE TOP OF THE LINE SECURITY</pattern><template>Do i wanna know, how you know all that?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  THAT'S SOME HIGH END SHIT TOO</pattern><template>Marker optics.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BEST WE CAN DO IS PEEK</pattern><template>We are gonna need some real fast cars to get to this.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ALL SET SANTOS  ALL GOOD YEAH  I AM ALWAYS GOOD BRO</pattern><template>Hobbs is on the other side of the city.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS ALL THE AFTERMATH OF A DARING DAYLIGHT BREAKOUT</pattern><template>There were 26 high risk inmates.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BEAUTY OF POLICE OFFICES</pattern><template>A blueprint?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HERE IN RIO    I LIKE ALL PARTIES TO KNOW WHAT THEY ARE UP AGAINST</pattern><template>That's funny, because it goes both ways.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WHOLE TEAM JUST GOT BURNED NOW WE ARE ALL WANTED</pattern><template>Hang on a second.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TELL YOU TRUE STORY 500 YEARS AGO PORTUGUESE AND SPANISH CAME HERE</pattern><template>Each trying to get the country from there methods.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WITH THOSE CIRCUITS  REYES IS GONNA HAVE A  WALL  WE ARE GONNA NEED THE GUYS WHO CAN PUNCH THROUGH THOSE WALL WHAT ELSE  UTILITIES AND WEAPONS SOMEONE WHO AIN'T AFRAID TO THROW DOWN SOMEONE WHO BACKUP EVERY POSITION YEAH  WHAT ELSE WE NEED</pattern><template>Most importantly we are gonna need two persistent drivers Guys who don't crack under pressure.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE GONNA TAKE ALL THE REYES MONEY EVERY DIME OF IT</pattern><template>And then, disappear.....forever New passports, new life, and no more looking over our shoulder And we are just gonna buy our freeDom.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU WANNA GO TO TOKYO</pattern><template>We will get there...</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER THOUGHT ANYONE COULD UNDERSTAND HOW MUCH</pattern><template>But you do.</template></category><category><pattern>WHE  WHE  WHERE DID YOU GET THAT FROM</pattern><template>Popa's mark.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST KINDA   GOTTA</pattern><template>A 100 million dollars.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS GUYS</pattern><template>I see you on the other side.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME WHERE IT IS</pattern><template>And i will let you go *** full of shit I do not know how you guys do business in your part of the world.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR HUSBAND WAS AN OFFICER  WHO WAS GUNNED DOWN IN FAVELA</pattern><template>Six months later you up and join the force?</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE FUN</pattern><template>Alright come on.</template></category><category><pattern>HAN  YOU ARE UP</pattern><template>Sure, gotta make the easy stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A LONG WAY FROM HOME</pattern><template>This is brazil!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HOW IT KEEPS IT OFF THE GRID</pattern><template>I can say this one is razor smart about this pack. I mean its whole network right there, just laid out on its inn Wilkes and tom go from the middle, rest flank north What about me?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TELL YOUR BOSS  EXACTLY WHO DID THIS</pattern><template>Tell him there is more coming Wallah...</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT LUCKY TO GET AWAY  BUT WHAT HAPPENS NEXT TIME</pattern><template>We have no choice but to split up I am pregnant I already lost my family once I am not gonna do that again.</template></category><category><pattern>*** IS PUTTING TOGETHER A TEAM TO SWIPE THEM JUST NEED A FEW MORE WILLING BODIES</pattern><template>But, I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO GET REYES'S HAND PRINT</pattern><template>Han, you are up.</template></category><category><pattern>STANDARD FORENSICS  SWEEP PRINTS  HAIR FIBERS  PRINTS ARE ALL OVER THE CAR ANYTHING ELSE</pattern><template>Yeah, we track the owner off the vehicle ID They are couple of shell companies in between a corporation owned by a investor named Hernan Reyes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T HAVE A PLACE TO HIDE</pattern><template>Who is hiding?</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK PLANES  TRAINS  BOATS AND EVERYTHING SHORT OF A GODDAMN SPACE SHUTTLE</pattern><template>They can change their names but, they can't change their faces.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOOD   WE DON'T NEED TO CALL THEM  FOR WHAT</pattern><template>We good.</template></category><category><pattern>TORRETO   NOPE AIN'T INTERESTED YES YOU ARE  KEEP LOOKING YOU BELIEVE IN GHOSTS</pattern><template>....www.subscene.com....</template></category><category><pattern>A PATROL OFFICER</pattern><template>You heard me.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY DOM  I GOT EYES ON MIA MOSCOW  BERLIN  GOA  HONG KONG</pattern><template>What do they have all in common We are one hour away from rest of that.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA RE FILL</pattern><template>This is some seRious stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>INTERVAL   GO HAVE SOMETHING</pattern><template>//subs dedicated to ma mom and bumbo// Home...sweet home.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN SAY THIS ONE IS RAZOR SMART ABOUT THIS PACK  I MEAN ITS WHOLE NETWORK RIGHT THERE  JUST LAID OUT ON ITS INN WILKES AND TOM GO FROM THE MIDDLE  REST FLANK NORTH WHAT ABOUT ME</pattern><template>Stay here.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PLAN IS BUSTED  THIS IS BULLSHIT MAN</pattern><template>Reyes knows we are coming.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE COULD LEARN THE NEXT CHAPTER AND HELP HER NEXT DAY I REMEMBER EVERYTHING ABOUT MY FATHER</pattern><template>Everything.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TRIPLED THE DETAIL OF THE POLICE STATION ITS GONNA BE A WALL OF GUNFIRE</pattern><template>Reyes doesn't get away with this.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU KIDDING ME</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE   I NEED A TRANSLATOR</pattern><template>Alright, We have plenty...</template></category><category><pattern>TWO IS ON THE MOVE</pattern><template>Yeah, i got mine I got eyes on five I know you said they were consolidating money somewhere But you all ain't gonna believe it.</template></category><category><pattern>DOM  WE ARE GONNA MOVE UP OUR TIME LINE</pattern><template>Yes, but how?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO WE GOT</pattern><template>First, we are gonna need a chameleon.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU SERIOUS RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Oh..Man...this is crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T KILLED THOSE MEN IN THE TRAIN DID YOU</pattern><template>Now, why would you believe anything I would tell you.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE WE TALKING OR WE RACING</pattern><template>Just don't cheat this time.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT'S SOUND LIKE A REAL HERO</pattern><template>That's funny From a guy who took the oath of a cop and then went against everything he stood for?</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE DIDN'T GO TO CHURCH WE DIDN'T GET ANY BARBEQUE</pattern><template>Every single day he was in the shop And, every single night he was at the kitchen table with mia helping her with her homework.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST MADE A BIG MISTAKE TOOK ME WHILE TO FIND OUT THAT TRACKING CHIP</pattern><template>But, not as long to flip the receiver.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FEDS WILL GET US ANYWHERE  THEIR AGENTS ARE OFF THE LIMITS</pattern><template>They are gonna send their best guys, we gotta get out of here One thing we know for sure Is that, they wanted this car.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO THINGS</pattern><template>One   I need a translator.</template></category><category><pattern>COUPLE OF HIGH END CARS  EASY TARGETS</pattern><template>*** is putting together a team to swipe them Just need a few more willing bodies.</template></category><category><pattern>NAH    NOT A BIT</pattern><template>Not even a little bit.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYBODY  PO PO</pattern><template>Five o, one time, peaks people we don't like.</template></category><category><pattern>GUYS   GUYS   GUYS    WE HAVE A PROBLEM</pattern><template>The whole team just got burned now we are all wanted.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAY WHA   THIS SHIT JUST WENT FROM MISSION IMPOSSIBLE TO MISSION FREAKIN' INSANITY</pattern><template>Whatever man!</template></category><category><pattern>IF I WERE YOU  I WOULD PROBABLY USE THE TIME MAKE PEACE WITH WHATEVER THINGS YOU GOT LEFT BECAUSE COME TOMORROW  I WILL FOUND YOU</pattern><template>Toretto I'll see you soon.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE ALL FREE TO MAKE YOUR OWN CHOICES I AM IN</pattern><template>I will ride with you toretto.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SPANISH ARRIVE GUNS BLAZING  DETERMINE TO PROVE WHO IS BOSS</pattern><template>But, the natives killed every single spaniard.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DIDN'T KILL THOSE FEDS</pattern><template>That's Reyes. I don't give a shit.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALIZE WE ARE TALKING ABOUT GOING UP AGAINST MOST POWERFUL GUY IN ALL OVER RIO</pattern><template>Yes. We are.</template></category><category><pattern>I AIN'T SCARED  I AM JUST LETTIN YOU ALL KNOW</pattern><template>Going in that bouty, its just crazy.   I got this.</template></category><category><pattern>CLOSE  BUT NOT ENOUGH</pattern><template>Time window is too small, man.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE CAN'T</pattern><template>What do you mean, she can't?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ALREADY KNOW WHO YOU ARE</pattern><template>Let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOOD</pattern><template>Yes, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>DEA tags, this car is en Seized.</template></category><category><pattern>TOAST</pattern><template>Money will come and go, we know that.</template></category><category><pattern>KINDA COUPLE EXTRA GUYS</pattern><template>Alright, you don't send a man to do a woman's job We gonna figure this out, i promise you.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT NECESSARILY</pattern><template>That road hits through hill into the favelas Couple of years ago it was washed out by a storm.</template></category><category><pattern>49 KILOS IS A MILLION IN TWENTIES</pattern><template>So, you are saying each one of these shipment is worth 10 million dollars.</template></category><category><pattern>A FAST TALKER  SOMEONE WHO CAN BULLSHIT THE WAY OUT OF ANYTHING I GOT THAT</pattern><template>These guys are gonna have a lot of surveillance we are gonna need someone who can schedule the circuits.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO THEY HAVE ALL IN COMMON WE ARE ONE HOUR AWAY FROM REST OF THAT</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  LISTEN UP  THE MEN WE'RE AFTER ARE PROFESSIONAL RUNNERS</pattern><template>They like speed and guarantee to go down the hardest possible way.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT TWO LIGHTS  A 100 000</pattern><template>If we don't pull this job off, we are probably dead anyway.</template></category><category><pattern>ABSOLUTELY   WHATS UP  BOY  WHATS GOING ON</pattern><template>You good.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S RIGHT</pattern><template>They tripled the detail of the police station its gonna be a wall of gunfire.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I NEED TO GET IN    AND CHECK YOUR STORAGE FACILITY FIRST</pattern><template>Nope.   Look man i know you are a true professional and i respects you, i promise.</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN</pattern><template>You should have come clean.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THEN SO ARE WE</pattern><template>If you can *** I want every thing on him Chato, be on the roof. I want you on watch in case somebody comes back for something Mac give me a cross Check on Reyes, full specs, he goes to the john, i want to know how many times he shakes it You got it boss Lets put all this mess together.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS BEEN A WHILE SINCE I HV'BEEN BEHIND THE WHEEL OF ONE OF THESE</pattern><template>First time I ever been in the front seat Hey, rom what took you so long.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT THE PRINTS</pattern><template>Where?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S YOUR PIGGY BANK   YOU KIDDIN ME YUP</pattern><template>Where the hell can i get one of these?</template></category><category><pattern>OK  KEEP GOING STRAIGHT ANOTHER HALF MILE AT DU LUFF SEEKER AND THEN GO LEFT</pattern><template>It ain't gonna work Spikes ahead Dom....we got spikes.</template></category><category><pattern>SH   IT</pattern><template>Holy....shit!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  UM  CAN I GET EVERYONE'S ATTENTION RIGHT HERE FOR A SECOND  WE ARE TALKIN ABOUT BREAKING INTO A PO LICE STATION</pattern><template>Is anyone listening to those words?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE HE NEVER MISSES HIS MARK</pattern><template>This guy is....he is old testament.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO BEAUTIFUL      LOOK AT THOSE DIMPLES SEXY         SEXY</pattern><template>Love those glasses, where did you get them from.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN  SHE CAN'T</pattern><template>Are you seRious right now?</template></category><category><pattern>SIX MONTHS LATER YOU UP AND JOIN THE FORCE</pattern><template>You are motivated.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING DOESN'T ADD UP</pattern><template>Toretto and O'Conner...</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME  BUDDY YEAH  WE HAVE FOUND THEM</pattern><template>Yeah, second through last racer.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT THERE THAT'S 49 KILOS</pattern><template>49 kilos is a million in twenties.</template></category><category><pattern>WE MOVE IN AND OUT BEFORE THEY EVEN KNOW WE ARE THERE</pattern><template>Well, we need to get eyes in there.</template></category><category><pattern>MY SMILE IS NOT THAT GREAT</pattern><template>Your husband was an officer, who was gunned down in Favela.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATS THE BEST DROP</pattern><template>Ok..Keep going straight another half mile at du Luff Seeker And then go left.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD A LIFE BEFORE YOU KNOW ME O'CONNER</pattern><template>Lets just leave it with that, alright.</template></category><category><pattern>HANG ON A SECOND</pattern><template>Us diplomatic security service issued the warrants.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM WHERE I AM SEEING  IT LOOKS LIKE YOU BOTH COULD USE A PAY DAY</pattern><template>What are you reading?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T HURT YOURSELFS</pattern><template>Its been a while since i hv'been behind the wheel of one of these.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WAY YOU ALWAYS HAD TO KEEP YOUR HANDS AND MOUTH BUSY YOU ARE A TWO PACKS A DAY</pattern><template>For sure Un Filtered.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  I GOT THE BOX</pattern><template>We all good, i promise you.</template></category><category><pattern>ENOUGH O'CONNER  IF HE SAID HE DIDN'T DO IT  HE DIDN'T DO IT</pattern><template>Go walk it off.</template></category><category><pattern>BEYOND THE OTHER SIDE OF A WANTED PERSON</pattern><template>Nice long. Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>GUYS I AM HEARING ALL THIS CHATTER  YOU JUST TAKE OUT A BANK</pattern><template>Two in Bound.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS A TRAP MAN  YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>Dom! Listen to them.</template></category><category><pattern>BRIAN</pattern><template>There is something i have to tell you.</template></category><category><pattern>BULLSHIT</pattern><template>Vince, what are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU</pattern><template>Alright, O'Conner Lets see what you got You need to look at that Berlin, 3 am this morning.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE NO CHOICE</pattern><template>Now.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON BOSS  ANOTHER DAY</pattern><template>Come on, its way too heat.</template></category><category><pattern>PASS ME THAT EVIDENCE BAG</pattern><template>Officer Neves, i have been waiting for you.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT IS</pattern><template>You know, i can't let you two go I ain't made that way I will see to it that you bring yourselfs 24 hours.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I AM GOOD   I AM GOOD</pattern><template>.No...thank You!</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T UNDERSTAND  WHY COME HERE</pattern><template>Why risk it all for 20 dollar worth of silver?</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  THIS IS BUSINESS</pattern><template>Sometimes things go stray.</template></category><category><pattern>DOWN AT THIS ANIMAL SHELTER</pattern><template>Where you might....wanna.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S DO IT AGAIN</pattern><template>That's your piggy bank ? You kiddin me yup?</template></category><category><pattern>A 100 MILLION PLUS IN CASH OASIS</pattern><template>That how it keeps it off the grid.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  DOM MIA WAS ON THAT TRAIN I DIDN'T     I DIDN'T KNOW I WOULDN'T DO ANYTHING TO HURT HER</pattern><template>You set off the deal I thought the job was for the cars I did not know. All they wanted was the chip.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM THERE IS MORE COMING WALLAH</pattern><template>Turn it over Its running alright, checks out fine.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL RIDE WITH YOU TORETTO</pattern><template>At least, until we kill that son of a bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SURE GOOD</pattern><template>B'cause you are saying grace.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR SISTER IS STUCK IN THIS LIFE AND WHERE IS LETTY DOM</pattern><template>Where's letty?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY QUIT TALKING  WE ONLY GOT A TWO MINUTE WINDOW</pattern><template>Lets go, vince.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'LL BE HERE</pattern><template>Guys, we are all over the news,they are blaming us for killing of those DEA agents on the train.</template></category><category><pattern>LETS GO      LEGEND CAR FOR A CAR</pattern><template>Car for car?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE HE IS</pattern><template>You know when you called me to come to Rio, i assumed it would be for something more exciting than this This is Tej, the best circuit men in the east coast.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HERE YOU ARE  JUST LIKE A TORETTO</pattern><template>Where's vince?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW WAS THAT ONE   CAMERA CAUGHT YOU</pattern><template>What? Yeah it still caught you   Then i will milk the hell out of that thing too.</template></category><category><pattern>SALUTE   SALUTE</pattern><template>I'm all set Santos, all good Yeah, i am always good bro.</template></category><category><pattern>NO   YOU WON'T</pattern><template>Thanks guys.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT</pattern><template>You are all free to make your own choices I am in.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE WHO CAN BLEND IN ANYWHERE</pattern><template>What else?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WE GOT THAT</pattern><template>Ah.....hell not I see they really stared the bottom of the beer..Huh I guess they did, since your ass is here.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT TO RUN AWAY</pattern><template>To finish the job.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  O'CONNER LETS SEE WHAT YOU GOT YOU NEED TO LOOK AT THAT BERLIN  3 AM THIS MORNING</pattern><template>A team of hikers, hijacked a military convey.</template></category><category><pattern>WITHOUT THE POSSIBILITY OF EARLY PAROLE</pattern><template>This is all the aftermath Of a daring daylight breakout.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT IT  BUT  YOU STILL DIDN'T ANSWER THE QUESTION</pattern><template>Guys...guys...guys....we have a problem.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS A CRISIS   SHUT UP RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>I am not gonna shut up...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>Get out!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW</pattern><template>I hear your sister is very beautiful.</template></category><category><pattern>HOBBS IS THE LEADER OF THE ELITE TASK FORCE FOR THE DSS</pattern><template>So. He is good?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE RIGHT</pattern><template>This is how we are gonna do it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOUR LIFE IS ON THE LINE  THAT'S WHEN YOU MANNER BY YOURSELF</pattern><template>That's a fair deal?</template></category><category><pattern>B'CAUSE YOU ARE SAYING GRACE</pattern><template>Thanks vince.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION</pattern><template>He'll be here.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON BABY  DON'T BE MEAN</pattern><template>Right this way, my dear Stay right here, I will be right back.</template></category><category><pattern>PARDON ME GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>I almost wish i didn't see it.</template></category><category><pattern>STAND BACK  I GOT THIS</pattern><template>Dom, please Dom.</template></category><category><pattern>PARK IT   WE ARE GOING ON FOOT</pattern><template>Hey.......toretto.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU DO</pattern><template>Close, but not enough.</template></category><category><pattern>MY BOSS SENT ME HERE TO JUST MAKE SURE EVERYTHING WAS SAFE</pattern><template>It will be safe.   Ok..Well let me just come in and take a quick peek.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  GOTTA MAKE THE EASY STUFF</pattern><template>Lets go, i will drive.</template></category><category><pattern>MARKER OPTICS</pattern><template>They refill the view, 10 seconds oscillation.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS SOMETHING I HAVE TO TELL YOU</pattern><template>Oh, damn.</template></category><category><pattern>A BLUEPRINT</pattern><template>This is where they are keeping the money.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY DOM  YOU DIDN'T MEET MY SON NICO I WILL HE IS A GOOD KID YOU KNOW  WE NAMED HIM AFTER YOU DOMINIC</pattern><template>You have my word vince.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH SHE MIGHT BE RIGHT</pattern><template>You really like doing that stuff, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>NO   THERE IS TOO MANY OF THEM WE ARE NOT GONNA MAKE IT</pattern><template>You're right, we aren't You are.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS GOT A HIT</pattern><template>Let's move Move....move....move Stopped...about a block ahead.</template></category><category><pattern>POPA'S MARK</pattern><template>Ok O'Conner, give me your best shot.</template></category><category><pattern>OFFICER NEVES  I HAVE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU</pattern><template>You asked for me ? I did.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST  LET ME HAVE THE CHIP</pattern><template>I can take this to them and set things right.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE NOT GONNA FIT</pattern><template>We have no choice.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOING DOWN TORRETTO</pattern><template>I'm right here.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  YOU MY BROTHER</pattern><template>We need to move, we don't have that much time I got some flight out, that leaves Rio de janeiro in next 5 hours.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  POLICE</pattern><template>They already know who you are.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS THING HAS ALREADY BEEN DIFFICULT IF IT AIN'T THAT</pattern><template>We need more room to breathe.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE LONG  YES</pattern><template>Why Rio vince?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU ARE NOT TAKING THAT FROM ME</pattern><template>Wait, wait...hold on a second.</template></category><category><pattern>MOST IMPORTANTLY WE ARE GONNA NEED TWO PERSISTENT DRIVERS GUYS WHO DON'T CRACK UNDER PRESSURE</pattern><template>Guys who never lose.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY RIO VINCE</pattern><template>You mean after you everything screwed up in LA ?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DOES IT FEEL     WHATS THAT</pattern><template>Beyond the other side of a wanted person.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT IF THAT'S OUR GUYS THEN WHATEVER WAS ON THAT CHIP LED THEM DIRECTLY TO THAT HOUSE</pattern><template>Its them for sure.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE GONNA NEED A FASTER CAR</pattern><template>Exactly why your ass ain't been driving. You gotta re Blaze I think, i am in love.</template></category><category><pattern>SHITTY CALL  O'CONNER</pattern><template>Shitty call You two started quite a bit of trouble today.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LET YOU WIN</pattern><template>Bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>PERSONALLY  I PREFER THE METHODS OF THE PORTUGUESE</pattern><template>They came bearing gifts.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY NEED TO BE FREE</pattern><template>You didn't killed those men in the train did you?</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHAT IS THAT</pattern><template>A 100 million plus in cash oasis?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE RIGHT  WE AREN'T YOU ARE</pattern><template>What are you talking about Just let the vault go.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS THEM FOR SURE</pattern><template>How do you know that ?   Because no one else in Rio is stupid enough to rob Reyes.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  STILL ITS A BABY GIFT</pattern><template>No, you are not taking that from me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T DO NOTHING</pattern><template>He let you win.</template></category><category><pattern>A TEAM OF HIKERS  HIJACKED A MILITARY CONVEY</pattern><template>Torreto.  Nope ain't interested Yes you are, keep looking You believe in ghosts.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH MAN  WHY YOU DRAG US HALF WAY AROUND THE WORLD</pattern><template>Because we got a job.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR YOUR TIME I SWORE TO GOD  IF I WAS ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE GLASS I WILL BUST YOUR DAMN FACE AND TRANSLATE THAT</pattern><template>You see, I think I make a better special agent than you ever did Well, that depends on how you define special.</template></category><category><pattern>DOM  LISTEN TO THEM</pattern><template>Run, before its too late.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS GONNA TAKE A LITTLE MORE THAN MONEY TO LEARN HOW TO COOK   THAT'S ALL</pattern><template>But, i heard they were looking for a chef.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I WANNA ANOTHER SHOT</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS FOR DAMN CERTAIN</pattern><template>Hello beautiful......look at those dimples sexy.........sexy.</template></category><category><pattern>REYES OWNS THIS PLACE HE GIVE THINGS TO PEOPLE AND  EVERYTHING HAS A PRICE</pattern><template>People here need a new start.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY RISK IT ALL FOR 20 DOLLAR WORTH OF SILVER</pattern><template>Because its worth it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SAYS CAUCASIAN</pattern><template>Well, its the tan....you know tan.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN TAKE THIS TO THEM AND SET THINGS RIGHT</pattern><template>Get out!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY OPEN THE SAME TIME WHEN I PULL THIS TRIGGER WANT ME TO OPEN THEM</pattern><template>Yeah anybody can talk shit in spanish Two fails, i am not fail.....two fails Who are these clowns men?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU CRAZY   ARE YOU CRAZY</pattern><template>Do you know whose house this is?</template></category><category><pattern>HELD THE RECORD ON THE ENVADEDA 3 YEARS RUNNING</pattern><template>You got a lot of bones to bring your problems here torreto Not to mention a cop Yeah, we can keep that on the low Word on the street is that a lot of people are looking for you two.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE GOT SOME BAD NEWS</pattern><template>You don't like my deserve first I checked the rail Line like you asked, found a couple of spots where they unloaded the cars.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOOD</pattern><template>Here, i got the box.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU BROKE THAT LIKE YOU GOT A 100 GRAND</pattern><template>If we pull off this job, I will.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  DAMN</pattern><template>What a mess.</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT L HOBBS</pattern><template>Hold on a second.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT     BECAUSE NO ONE ELSE IN RIO IS STUPID ENOUGH TO ROB REYES</pattern><template>Number 1 is in motion.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  I THINK I MAKE A BETTER SPECIAL AGENT THAN YOU EVER DID WELL  THAT DEPENDS ON HOW YOU DEFINE SPECIAL</pattern><template>Oh..Man, lets see what we got.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE CARE OF MIA</pattern><template>Dom you listen to me ..Now..Ok  you cut loose right now I thought i told you to go on.</template></category><category><pattern>INVESTOR</pattern><template>If there is anything illegal happening in Rio, Reyes is involved.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THIS IS YOUR DREAM  HUH THAT'S ENOUGH OF ME MAN I TAKE YOU ARE ENJOYING</pattern><template>Absolutely...whats up..Boy, whats going on?</template></category><category><pattern>*** LETS GO HUNT</pattern><template>Agent Hobbs? Chief of police.</template></category><category><pattern>SHITTY CALL YOU TWO STARTED QUITE A BIT OF TROUBLE TODAY</pattern><template>Three of my men dead.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT   WHA DO YOU MEAN</pattern><template>Why me?</template></category><category><pattern>LETS  MAKE IT A MILLION I LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Alright, million dollar a quarter mile.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  THAT'S THE KEY I GO INTO THE FAVALS  AND GIVE THEM SOMETHING TO LOSE ELECTRICITY  RUNNING WATER  SCHOOL ROOM FOR THEIR KIDS AND FOR THAT TASTE OF THE BETTER LIFE I OWN THEM</pattern><template>Gentlemen.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  THERE IS AN ALLY COMING ON YOUR LEFT YEAH  I GOT IT</pattern><template>Alright Dom, right turn right here Ok guys, there is a big group coming at you from south.</template></category><category><pattern>BLOOD  BULLETS  RAP THE GOD THAT'S HIS STYLE</pattern><template>And right now he is hunting us?</template></category><category><pattern>ITS  OK   WAIT</pattern><template>Reyes's guys were waiting for me at the market And, vince saved my life You hungry?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ONLY LIVE ONCE  LETS DO IT</pattern><template>What do you say Dom?</template></category><category><pattern>WILKES  WE GET ANYTHING</pattern><template>Standard forensics, sweep prints, hair fibers. Prints are all over the car Anything else?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  LOOK WHERE ITS GOTTEN US LOOK AT OUR FAMILY NOW  I CAN'T GO HOME</pattern><template>Your sister is stuck in this life and where is letty Dom?</template></category><category><pattern>HELL YEAH  WE CAN'T DO THIS</pattern><template>We can't or we shouldn't.</template></category><category><pattern>AND EVERYTHING WE TAKE  WE SPLIT EVEN</pattern><template>So, that's 11 million a piece, I am down I am in 11 million? Sounds like a whole lotta vaginal activity to me.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT   HOLD ON A SECOND</pattern><template>Did he just smack that ass or, Did he grab the ass...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS HOW WE ARE GONNA DO IT</pattern><template>We are gonna use this into one last job.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THE FOLK YOU KNOW  DO ALL THIS</pattern><template>Wait...wha do you mean?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL OF THEM SOUNDS CRAZY  BRING US TO WHOLE ANOTHER COUNTRY SO  THAT WE CAN ROB THE DUDE WHO RUNS IT I THOUGHT THIS IS BUSINESS SOUNDS PERSONAL TO ME</pattern><template>Is that what this is?</template></category><category><pattern>SPECIAL AGENT O'CONNER</pattern><template>Us federal bureo of investigation.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP LOOKING</pattern><template>Boss, if something was missing we would know.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SA  Y   WHA   T   HUN   HUN</pattern><template>See, sometimes i be over Thinking maybe and you know i know...we just met...but.</template></category><category><pattern>STAND BEHIND IN TWO</pattern><template>If these vehicles move on the streets of Rio, i wanna know about them.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  SHE CAN'T</pattern><template>What do you mean?</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD ON A SECOND</pattern><template>Hey Dom, Is that the guy you saw in the favela ?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW   IT LOOK LIKE YOU WORKOUT A LITTLE BIT TOO</pattern><template>Whats you benchmark 3 350.</template></category><category><pattern>RUN IT THROUGH FRS</pattern><template>Well, hello you son of a bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>EVENTUALLY</pattern><template>This is the happiest i have ever seen my sister It goes with free.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU CAN *** I WANT EVERY THING ON HIM CHATO  BE ON THE ROOF  I WANT YOU ON WATCH IN CASE SOMEBODY COMES BACK FOR SOMETHING MAC GIVE ME A CROSS CHECK ON REYES  FULL SPECS  HE GOES TO THE JOHN  I WANT TO KNOW HOW MANY TIMES HE SHAKES IT YOU GOT IT BOSS LETS PUT ALL THIS MESS TOGETHER</pattern><template>Well, that's gonna take a while.</template></category><category><pattern>BEAUTY AS IN YOU KNOW</pattern><template>start off playing hard to get And, no matter how much i caress her, no matter how much i love her in the end she still ain't gonna give up that ass I got this....relax man relax.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE SECOND THING</pattern><template>Stay the fu*k out of my way!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M IMPRESSED    GOT IT</pattern><template>Got it. But, you still didn't answer the question.</template></category><category><pattern>ARMED ROBBERY IN THE HOUSE OF GOLAN</pattern><template>Alright if that's our guys then whatever was on that chip led them directly to that house.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I GOT THE ONLY ONE IN WESTERN HEMISPHERE I MADE A SHEIKH IN ABU DHABI AN OFFER HE COULD NOT REFUSE   HUH AND  THAT'S A NICE LADY YOU GOT THERE TOO   OH   ABSOLUTELY WELL   WE GOT TO GO MAN</pattern><template>Lets do this Ok, i will drive In that? Come on man..No...no way No..Not...not in this, in that!</template></category><category><pattern>MIRRORS  SCISSORS  THINGS THAT THE NATIVE COULDN'T GET OWN THEIR OWN</pattern><template>But, to continue receiving them would require will of portuguese And that's why all brazilians speaks portuguese today.</template></category><category><pattern>VINCE  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Quite, you have been tracked.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WE ARE GONNA NEED A TEAM</pattern><template>Alright, lets go through the basics real quick.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT JUST LET THE VAULT GO</pattern><template>Get out of there.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME THE DAMN STRETCHES THE GROUND ROLLS INTO A HARD PACK AND WE LOST THE TRACK TOO</pattern><template>Not necessarily.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE GOING RIGHT NAH   ITS TOO TIGHT</pattern><template>we are not gonna fit.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  YOU DON'T SEND A MAN TO DO A WOMAN'S JOB WE GONNA FIGURE THIS OUT  I PROMISE YOU</pattern><template>Whats up?</template></category><category><pattern>APPEARS TO BE A MANHUNT UNDERWAY FOR THREE FUGITIVES TONIGHT MULTIPLE FEDERAL AND LOCAL AGENCIES HAVE JOINED FORCES IN THE SEARCH FOR   DOMINIC TORETTO AND HIS ACCOMPLISHES BRIAN O'CONNER AND MIA TORETTO</pattern><template>Despite every eye in the country looking for them Where toretto and O'Conner are now is any ones guess Let's get out of here Mia...</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOUR DREAM IS TO START A DAY JOB</pattern><template>That's...that's stupid...man, why would..</template></category><category><pattern>GO WALK IT OFF</pattern><template>Look, i would love to expand my operations in your country But quite frankly.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M READY</pattern><template>Holl it out, mia?</template></category><category><pattern>WILKES  SUPPRESSING FIRE</pattern><template>Set them down.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS    THANK YOU</pattern><template>Its your boy. Why would you keep somethin like that away from us.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IT DOESN'T CHANGE A THING I SAY WE STICK TO THE PLAN</pattern><template>You say wha...this shit just went from mission impossible to mission freakin' insanity.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT'S MESSED UP</pattern><template>But, still its a baby gift.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY HERE</pattern><template>Police! On the ground!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS ONE'S CLEAN ENOUGH  WE CAN DO IT WITHOUT HIM</pattern><template>Its a big gig.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Dom!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY DOM  IS THAT THE GUY YOU SAW IN THE FAVELA</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHOSE HOUSE THIS IS</pattern><template>Whose money are you stealing?</template></category><category><pattern>I ALMOST WISH I DIDN'T SEE IT</pattern><template>Almost.</template></category><category><pattern>DESPITE EVERY EYE IN THE COUNTRY LOOKING FOR THEM WHERE TORETTO AND O'CONNER ARE NOW IS ANY ONES GUESS LET'S GET OUT OF HERE MIA</pattern><template>Buster....</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GUYS JUST COPPED OUT A 10 SECOND WINDOW MAKE IT COUNT</pattern><template>Come on baby, don't be mean.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT THAT   ALL MOTORS AND NO TUNING ISSUES</pattern><template>I always wanted one of those.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU CRAZY DOM   WE CAN'T</pattern><template>Its a suicide mission.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH   WE ARE LOOKING AT FOUR CAMERAS</pattern><template>Now, that's some high end shit too.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>To tell you exact, its spread throughout the city And we are gonna hit them all?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE DO SOMETHING  NOW LETS GO WIDE</pattern><template>Yeah!</template></category><category><pattern>THREE YEARS AGO  HAS WAS MURDERED IN THE STREETS RIGHT OUTSIDE OUT OUR DOOR</pattern><template>Reyes owns this place He give things to people And, everything has a price.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE NOT GONNA GET A BETTER WINDOW</pattern><template>Ok guys, its showtime.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MAKES SIX BODYGUARDS</pattern><template>Seven, do you think that guy with a funny look is a tourist?</template></category><category><pattern>SO   LISTEN</pattern><template>There is a job coming up I was hoping Dom was gonna be here by now, but...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I CAN'T LET YOU TWO GO I AIN'T MADE THAT WAY I WILL SEE TO IT THAT YOU BRING YOURSELFS 24 HOURS</pattern><template>The money stays though.</template></category><category><pattern>TOUR GUIDE</pattern><template>Yeah? Hmm..</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GOD  I AM SO HAPPY YOU ARE OK</pattern><template>I thought i told you to lay low   we were running out of fuel.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL</pattern><template>Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF THERE</pattern><template>You're father now, brian No i am not even....</template></category><category><pattern>DOM</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW THEY KILLED THREE FEDERAL AGENTS</pattern><template>It doesn't make any sense.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ME</pattern><template>Because, Out of all of us, you got the biggest mouth.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU SAY DOM</pattern><template>Are we talking or we racing?</template></category><category><pattern>LETS GO  I WILL DRIVE</pattern><template>That makes six bodyguards.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE IS MOVING IT INTO A POLICE STATION HE HAS GOT SOME SERIOUS BRASS IN HIS POCKET</pattern><template>Hell yeah, we can't do this.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE YOU SIR</pattern><template>Special agent O'Conner.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL SEE YOU SOON  TORETTO</pattern><template>I am looking forward to it.</template></category><category><pattern>MY HUSBAND WAS A GOOD POLICE OFFICER   AN HONEST MAN   WE BOTH GREW UP HERE</pattern><template>Three years ago, has was murdered in the streets Right outside out our door.</template></category><category><pattern>ELENA NEVES</pattern><template>A patrol officer?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  NO ONE ENTERS THE FACILITY BUT AUTHORIZED EVIDENCE PERSONNEL NOW STOP WASTING MY TIME</pattern><template>I am going to call the embassy. No...no, no.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS EASY MONEY</pattern><template>From where i am seeing, It looks like you both could use a pay day.</template></category><category><pattern>NO    WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU HEARD FROM HIM</pattern><template>A couple of weeks ago, up in ecuador or somewhere.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU TO LAY LOW   WE WERE RUNNING OUT OF FUEL</pattern><template>Had to make a call.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE DEAD MEN  YOU'RE ALL DEAD MEN</pattern><template>You don't have a place to hide.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU HEADED THAT WAY  YOU WILL PICKUP THE TRACKS THERE COME PREPARED</pattern><template>I'm motivated.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LEFT OFF THE THROTTLE WITH A MILE</pattern><template>You didn't do nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY CAN CHANGE THEIR NAMES BUT  THEY CAN'T CHANGE THEIR FACES</pattern><template>Something big is going down.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO GET SOME FRESH AIR</pattern><template>Its got a hit.</template></category><category><pattern>I PROMISE</pattern><template>Family just got bigger... ye..H.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOOK THE CHIP</pattern><template>We got a hit on the police scanner.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE YOU HAVE BEEN VIN</pattern><template>You better check that tone.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I ASK  WHY</pattern><template>My smile is not that great.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID IT AGAIN  HUH I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THEY ARE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>Toast!</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU NEED AN EXTRA MEN MIKE  YOU ARE IN YOU ALWAYS HAVE BEEN A FAMILY</pattern><template>Thank you!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S LETTY</pattern><template>Plasma cover, Wilkes i want a list of every place within 50 miles that distribute compressed gas tank.</template></category><category><pattern>RUN  BEFORE ITS TOO LATE</pattern><template>Leave Rio, you can be free I don't need freeDom.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY THE FU*K OUT OF MY WAY</pattern><template>Brian.</template></category><category><pattern>TO BE HONEST WITH YOU  I DON'T REMEMBER WHAT THE HELL HE LOOK LIKE I HAD ALL THE MEMORIES    HE IS JUST NEVER THERE YOU AIN'T GONNA BE LIKE THAT BRIAN WE CAN'T KEEP RUNNING DOM WE GOT TO GET OUT WE GOT TO GET OUT  NOW</pattern><template>You're right.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE MOTIVATED</pattern><template>Plus i procure you are only the real one who can't be brought. Am i right?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S   THAT'S STUPID   MAN  WHY WOULD</pattern><template>Nah...that's not stupid at all..Man I love what I do.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THAT'S GONNA TAKE A WHILE</pattern><template>Then you better get started.</template></category><category><pattern>QUITE  YOU HAVE BEEN TRACKED</pattern><template>Its..Ok...wait.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE FATHER NOW  BRIAN NO I AM NOT EVEN</pattern><template>you stick with the plan It was always the plan.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  IF YOU DOMINATE THE PEOPLE WITH VIOLENCE  THEY WILL EVENTUALLY FIGHT BACK</pattern><template>Because, they have nothing to lose.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN WE JUST STOP THE SCANNER AND REPLACE THE IMAGE</pattern><template>Nah...its hooked up into a digital sync.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT ALL OF THESE PLACES HAVE IN COMMON</pattern><template>No?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS SOME SERIOUS STUFF</pattern><template>No, I am good...I am good...</template></category><category><pattern>AND RIGHT NOW HE IS HUNTING US</pattern><template>Dom, we are gonna move up our time line.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD HAVE COME CLEAN</pattern><template>What's going on out here?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>Get something to eat.</template></category><category><pattern>TURN IT OVER ITS RUNNING ALRIGHT  CHECKS OUT FINE</pattern><template>Keep looking.</template></category><category><pattern>DOM  PLEASE DOM</pattern><template>Stop!</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED A HARD RIDE AND AIR WE NEED SOMETHING AGILE</pattern><template>You guys mark up a track.</template></category><category><pattern>MADE ME FREE FALL IN SOUTH AMERICA AFTER</pattern><template>We kept on going if not for rosa...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S JUST IT</pattern><template>I Don't know shit about my dad I don't remember him yelling, I don't remember him smiling.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  SO TARGET'S NAME IS HERNAN REYES</pattern><template>He runs the drug scene out there He has never been busted because he doesn't leave a paper trail.</template></category><category><pattern>AND A BIOMETRIC PALM SCANNER</pattern><template>Ten times the top of the line security.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS VINCE</pattern><template>Cheers...cheers.....cheers.</template></category><category><pattern>REYES'S GUYS WERE WAITING FOR ME AT THE MARKET AND  VINCE SAVED MY LIFE YOU HUNGRY</pattern><template>Yeah, sure Good!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO</pattern><template>Who are you sir?</template></category><category><pattern>THREE OF MY MEN DEAD</pattern><template>Three dea agents, along with.</template></category><category><pattern>AH     HELL NOT I SEE THEY REALLY STARED THE BOTTOM OF THE BEER  HUH I GUESS THEY DID  SINCE YOUR ASS IS HERE</pattern><template>When you are gonna give martin luther king his car back?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST DON'T CHEAT THIS TIME</pattern><template>You gotta let that go.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE HERE NEED A NEW START</pattern><template>They need to be free.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT</pattern><template>You never listened to me.</template></category><category><pattern>THOUGH  YOU STILL CAN DRIVE  YOU SEE</pattern><template>now i see why you always gettin accidents You can't drive a damn remote control car I don't need this, i don't....</template></category></AIML>