<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>GO  THEREFORE  TELL THY MASTER HERE I AM</pattern><template>My ransom is this frail and worthless trunk, my army but a weak and sickly guard.</template></category><category><pattern>BY JESHU  I AM YOUR MAJESTY'S COUNTRYMAN</pattern><template>I care not who know it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHAT PREVENTION</pattern><template>The king is full of grace and fair regard.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DAUPHIN LONGS FOR MORNING</pattern><template>He longs to eat the English.</template></category><category><pattern>ALAS  YOUR TOO MUCH LOVE AND CARE OF ME</pattern><template>are heavy orisons against this poor wretch.</template></category><category><pattern>MARRY  IF YOU WOULD PUT ME TO VERSES OR TO DANCE FOR YOUR SAKE  WHY  YOU UNDID ME</pattern><template>If I could win a lady at leapfrog or by vaulting into my saddle...</template></category><category><pattern>AND I HAVE BUILT TWO CHANTRIES</pattern><template>where the sad and solemn priests sing still for Richard's soul.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD AND HIS ANGELS GUARD YOUR SACRED THRONE AND MAKE YOU LONG BECOME IT</pattern><template>Sure we thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO  I WILL</pattern><template>but we have heard the chimes at midnight, master Harry.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR ANY THAT TREADS BUT ON FOUR HOOVES</pattern><template>When I bestride him, I soar.</template></category><category><pattern>DICED NOT ABOVE SEVEN DAYS A WEEK</pattern><template>Went to a bawdy house not above once in the quarter.</template></category><category><pattern>WORK  WORK YOUR THOUGHTS  AND IN THEM SEE A SIEGE</pattern><template>Behold the ordinance on their carriages, with fatal mouths gaping on girded harflew.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE THE BEST ARMOR IN THE WORLD</pattern><template>Would it were day.</template></category><category><pattern>DE  MAILS</pattern><template>De nails, madame.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE CUSTOMS CURTSY TO GREAT KINGS</pattern><template>You and I cannot be confined within the weak list of a country's fashion.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  CAN ANY OF YOUR NEIGHBORS TELL  KATE  I'LL ASK THEM</pattern><template>By mine honor, in true English, I swear I love thee, by which honor I dare not swear thou lovest me.</template></category><category><pattern>UNDER SIR THOMAS ERPINGHAM</pattern><template>A good old commander and a most kind gentleman.</template></category><category><pattern>DE HAND  DE FINGRES ETDE NAILS</pattern><template>C'est bien dit, madame.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SOME ARE YET UNGOTTEN AND UNBORN</pattern><template>that shall have cause to curse the Dauphin's scorn.</template></category><category><pattern>MY LORD OF CAMBRIDGE AND MY KIND LORD OF MASHAM</pattern><template>and you, my gentle knight, give me your thoughts.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WILL WITH ALL EXPEDIENCE MARCH UPON US</pattern><template>All things are ready if our minds be so!</template></category><category><pattern>WITH FULL ACCORD TO ALL OUR JUST DEMANDS</pattern><template>I have but with a cursorary eye...</template></category><category><pattern>AND SAY   TOMORROW IS SAINT CRISPIN'S   THEN WILL HE STRIP HIS SLEEVE AND SHOW HIS SCARS</pattern><template>and say,  these wounds I had on Crispin's day.  Old men forget, yet all shall be forgot but he'll remember with advantages...</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FAIR SHOW SHALL SUCK AWAY THEIR SOULS  LEAVING THEM BUT THE SHALES AND HUSKS OF MEN</pattern><template>There is not work enough for all our hands.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ANYTHING THAT MIGHT NOT MISBECOME THE MIGHTY SENDER  DOTH HE PRIZE YOU AT</pattern><template>Thus says my king.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE IN GOD'S HAND  BROTHER  NOT IN THEIRS</pattern><template>March to the bridge.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE HATH GOOD LEAVE</pattern><template>Fair Katherine, and most fair, will you vouchsafe to teach a soldier...</template></category><category><pattern>YON ISLAND CARRIONS  DESPERATE OF THEIR BONES  ILL FAVOREDLY BECOME THE MORNING FIELD</pattern><template>They have said their prayers, and they stay for death.</template></category><category><pattern>DE NICK     MMM</pattern><template>Et le menton?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SO  I DO BESEECH YOUR MAJESTY</pattern><template>Be patient, for you shall remain with us!</template></category><category><pattern>ET  UH  VOUS ETES MIENNE</pattern><template>It is as easy for me, Kate, to conquer the kingdom...</template></category><category><pattern>I SHOULD BE ANGRY WITH YOU IF TIME WERE CONVENIENT</pattern><template>Let it be a quarrel between us, if you live!</template></category><category><pattern>MY HOST PISTOL</pattern><template>You must come to my master, and you, hostess!</template></category><category><pattern>IN ELYSIUM</pattern><template>Next day after dawn, doth rise and help Hyperion to his horse...</template></category><category><pattern>TONIGHT    IN HARFLEW WILL WE BE YOUR GUEST</pattern><template>Tomorrow... for the march are we addressed.</template></category><category><pattern>AND PRAY  TAKE HEED HOW YOU IMPAWN OUR PERSON  HOW YOU AWAKE OUR SLEEPING SWORD OF WAR</pattern><template>We charge you, in the name of God, take heed.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL MET  CORPORAL NYM</pattern><template>Good morrow, Lieutenant Bardolph.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CONSTABLE OF FRANCE</pattern><template>I pray thee bear my former answer back.</template></category><category><pattern>AND JUSTLY AND RELIGIOUSLY UNFOLD</pattern><template>why the law salique that they have in France, or should or should not bar us in our claim.</template></category><category><pattern>ALICE</pattern><template>Alice, tu as ete en angleterre, et tu parles bien le langage.</template></category><category><pattern>ET LE COUDE</pattern><template>D'elbow.</template></category><category><pattern>PRINCE DAUPHIN  YOU SHALL STAY WITH US IN ROUEN</pattern><template>Not so, I do beseech your majesty.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL THE CONSTABLE WE ARE BUT WARRIORS FOR THE WORKING DAY</pattern><template>Our gayness and our gilt are all besmirched...</template></category><category><pattern>INDIFFERENT  OR RATHER SWAYING MORE UPON OUR PART</pattern><template>For I have made an offer to his majesty, as touching France.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S VERY SICK AND WOULD TO BED</pattern><template>Good Bardolph, put thy face between his sheets and do the office of a warming pan.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I BESTRIDE HIM  I SOAR</pattern><template>I am a hawk, and he is pure air and fire!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  KATE</pattern><template>I will tell thee in French...</template></category><category><pattern>OR ELSE WHAT FOLLOWS</pattern><template>Bloody constraint.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CONSIDER IT WAS EXCESS OF WINE THAT SET HIM ON  AND ON HIS MORE ADVICE WE PARDON HIM</pattern><template>That's mercy, but too much security.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL TELL THEE IN FRENCH</pattern><template>which I am sure will hang about my tongue...</template></category><category><pattern>SO DO THE KINGS OF FRANCE</pattern><template>unto this day.</template></category><category><pattern>BARDOLPH  BE BLITHE</pattern><template>Nym, rouse thy vaunting veins.</template></category><category><pattern>SCORN AND DEFIANCE  SLIGHT REGARD  CONTEMPT</pattern><template>and anything that might not misbecome the mighty sender, doth he prize you at.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT</pattern><template>Adieu.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO LIVE HONESTLY BY THE PRICK OF THEIR NEEDLES  BUT IT SHALL BE THOUGHT WE KEEP A BAWDY HOUSE STRAIGHT</pattern><template>Pish!</template></category><category><pattern>UN PEU  MADAME</pattern><template>Je te prie, m'enseignez.</template></category><category><pattern>SAUF VOTRE HONNEUR  D'ELBOW</pattern><template>Ainsi dis je: D'elbow, de nick, Etde chin.</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL 421 YEARS AFTER DEFUNCTION OF KING PHARAMOND  IDLY SUPPOSED THE FOUNDER OF THIS LAW</pattern><template>King Pepin, which deposed childeric, did, as heir general, being descended of blithild, which was the daughter to king Clothair, make claim and title to the crown of France.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD BE WITH YOU</pattern><template>My name is Pistol called.</template></category><category><pattern>OR TAKE THAT PRAISE FROM GOD WHICH IS HIS ONLY</pattern><template>Is it not lawful, an't please your majesty, to tell how many is killed?</template></category><category><pattern>LET US OUR LIVES  OUR SOULS  OUR DEBTS  OUR CAREFUL WIVES  OUR CHILDREN</pattern><template>and our sins lay on the king.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A LITTLE BODY WITH A MIGHTY HEART</pattern><template>What mightst thou do that honor would thee do...</template></category><category><pattern>THE LET WHY GENTLE PEACE</pattern><template>should not expel these inconveniences...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT TO HIM FROM ENGLAND</pattern><template>Scorn and defiance, slight regard, contempt...</template></category><category><pattern>SO IT IS CLEAR AS IS THE SUMMER SUN</pattern><template>All appear to hold in right and title of the female.</template></category><category><pattern>A VERY LITTLE LITTLE LET US DO  AND ALL IS DONE</pattern><template>Then let the trumpets sound the tucket sonance and the note to mount...</template></category><category><pattern>FIRE ANSWERS FIRE  AND THROUGH THEIR PALY FLAMES  EACH BATTLE SEES THE OTHER'S UMBERED FACE</pattern><template>Steed threatens steed in high and boastful neighs, piercing the night's dull ear.</template></category><category><pattern>TO MAKE DIVORCE OF THEIR INCORPORATE LEAGUE</pattern><template>that English may as French, French Englishmen, receive each other.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL PAY ME THE EIGHT SHILLINGS I WON OF YOU AT BETTING</pattern><template>Base is the slave that pays.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SUM OF ALL OUR ANSWER IS BUT THIS: WE WOULD NOT SEEK A BATTLE AS WE ARE  NOR  AS WE ARE  WE SAY WE WILL NOT SHUN IT</pattern><template>So tell your master.</template></category><category><pattern>AND OF BRETAGNE  OF BRABANT AND OF ORLEANS SHALL MAKE FORTH</pattern><template>And you, prince Dauphin...</template></category><category><pattern>PRITHEE  HONEY SWEET HUSBAND  LET ME BRING THEE TO STAINES</pattern><template>No, for my manly heart doth yearn.</template></category><category><pattern>UP  PRINCES  AND WITH SPIRIT OF HONOR EDGED MORE SHARPER THAN YOUR SWORDS  HIE TO THE FIELD</pattern><template>Bar Harry England, that sweeps through our land...</template></category><category><pattern>QUE DIT IL  QUE JE SUIS SEMBLABLE A LES ANGES</pattern><template>Qui, vraiment, sauf votre grace, ainsi dit il.</template></category><category><pattern>LET IT NOT DISGRACE ME IF I DEMAND BEFORE THIS ROYAL VIEW</pattern><template>why that the naked, poor and mangled peace...</template></category><category><pattern>IF THOU WEAR ME</pattern><template>Better and better.</template></category><category><pattern>OLD DO I WAX  AND FROM MY WEARY LIMBS HONOR IS CUDGELED</pattern><template>Well, bawd I'll turn...</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE MORE I COME TO KNOW OF THEE  IF FOR THEY RANSOM  THOU WILT NOW COMPOUND BEFORE THY MOST ASSURED OVERTHROW</pattern><template>Who hast sent thee now?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT YOU CLAIM HEAR NO MORE OF YOU</pattern><template>This the Dauphin speaks.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF TO LIVE  THE FEWER MEN  THE GREATER SHARE OF HONOR</pattern><template>God's will, I pray thee, wish not one man more.</template></category><category><pattern>AND OUR SINS LAY ON THE KING</pattern><template>We must bear all.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IT BE</pattern><template>By Cheshu, he is an ass in the world.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IN THE FIELD LIE SLAIN</pattern><template>Of princes in this number, 126.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR MANY A THOUSAND WIDOWS SHALL THIS HIS MOCK  MOCK OUT OF THEIR DEAR HUSBANDS  MOCK MOTHERS FROM THEIR SONS  MOCK CASTLES DOWN</pattern><template>And some are yet ungotten and unborn...</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN TO BURY THEM</pattern><template>To sort our nobles from our common men.</template></category><category><pattern>A GOOD SOFT PILLOW FOR THAT GOOD WHITE HEAD WERE BETTER THAN A CHURLISH TURF OF FRANCE</pattern><template>Not so, my liege.</template></category><category><pattern>I CANNOT TELL</pattern><template>Well, can any of your neighbors tell, Kate? I'll ask them.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THREE CORRUPTED MEN</pattern><template>One, Richard Earl of Cambridge, and the second, Henry Lord Scroop of Masham, and the third, Sir Thomas Grey, knight, of Northumberland, have for the gilt of France...</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING'S A BAWCOCK AND A HEART OF GOLD  A LAD OF LIFE  AN IMP OF FAME  OF PARENTS GOOD  OF FIST MOST VALIANT</pattern><template>I kiss his dirty shoe, and from heartstring, I love the lovely bully.</template></category><category><pattern>D'ELBOW   JE M'EN FAIS LA REPETITION</pattern><template>De tous les mots que vous m'avez appris des a present.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR AFTER I SAW HIM FUMBLE WITH THE SHEETS</pattern><template>and play with flowers and smile upon his finger's ends, I knew there was but one way.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT PRIVATE MEN ENJOY</pattern><template>And what have kings that privates have not too...</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME YOUR ANSWER    I'FAITH DO    AND SO CLAP HANDS AND A BARGAIN  HOW SAY YOU  LADY</pattern><template>Sauf votre honneur, me understand well.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE IT  BRAVE YORK</pattern><template>Now, soldiers, march away, and how thou pleasest, God, dispose the day.</template></category><category><pattern>CRISPIN CRISPIAN SHALL NE'ER GO BY  FROM THIS DAY TO THE ENDING OF THE WORLD  BUT WE IN IT SHALL BE REMEMBERED</pattern><template>We few, we happy few, we band of brothers.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  WELCOME  KATE  AND BEAR ME WITNESS ALL</pattern><template>That here I kiss her as my sovereign queen.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE WATER IN WYE</pattern><template>cannot wash your majesty's Welsh blood out of your body, I can tell you that.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR WE CAN'T LODGE OR BOARD A DOZEN OR 14 GENTLEWOMEN</pattern><template>who live honestly by the prick of their needles, but it shall be thought we keep a bawdy house straight.</template></category><category><pattern>NO KING OF ENGLAND IF NOT KING OF FRANCE</pattern><template>Prithee, honey sweet husband, let me bring thee to staines.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SECRET WHISPERS OF EACH OTHER'S WATCH</pattern><template>Fire answers fire, and through their paly flames, each battle sees the other's umbered face.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING IS NOT TO ANSWER IT</pattern><template>I do not desire he should answer for me.</template></category><category><pattern>MY LORD  I'LL TELL YOU</pattern><template>That self bill is urged, which, in the 11th year...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHEN OUR THROATS ARE CUT  HE MAY BE RANSOMED  AND WE NE'ER THE WISER</pattern><template>If I live to see it, I'll never trust his word after.</template></category><category><pattern>ANCIENT PISTOL  I DO PARTLY UNDERSTAND YOUR MEANING</pattern><template>Why, then, rejoice therefore!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  MY GOOD LORD  HOW NOW FOR THE MITIGATION</pattern><template>Of this bill urged by the commons?</template></category><category><pattern>FOR IF YOU HIDE THE CROWN  EVEN IN YOUR HEARTS  THERE WILL HE RAKE FOR IT</pattern><template>Therefore, in fierce tempest is he coming, in thunder and in earthquake, like a Jove, that if requiring fail, he will compel.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER KING OF ENGLAND HAD NOBLES RICHER AND MORE LOYAL SUBJECTS</pattern><template>whose hearts have left their bodies here in England...</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE THE SAD AND SOLEMN PRIESTS SING STILL FOR RICHARD'S SOUL</pattern><template>More will I do...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT ALL THESE  THRICE GORGEOUS CEREMONY  NOT ALL THESE  LAID IN BED MAJESTICAL  CAN SLEEP SO SOUNDLY</pattern><template>as the wretched slave, Who, with a body filled and vacant mind, gets him to rest, crammed with distressful bread, never sees horrid night, the child of hell, but like a lackey, from the rise to the set...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IN LOVING ME  YOU SHOULD LOVE THE FRIEND OF FRANCE  FOR I LOVE FRANCE SO WELL THAT I WILL NOT PART WITH A VILLAGE OF IT</pattern><template>I will have it all mine.</template></category><category><pattern>ET LE MENTON</pattern><template>De chin.</template></category><category><pattern>N'AVEZ VOUS PAS DEJA OUBLIE CE QUE JE VOUS AI ENSEIGNE</pattern><template>Non, je reciterai a vous promptement: De hand, de fingres.</template></category><category><pattern>AYE  I PRAISE GOD  AND I HAVE MERITED SOME LOVE AT HIS HANDS</pattern><template>Bardolph, a soldier firm and sound of heart...</template></category><category><pattern>BLOODY CONSTRAINT</pattern><template>For if you hide the crown, even in your hearts, there will he rake for it.</template></category><category><pattern>SAUF VOTRE HONNEUR  ME UNDERSTAND WELL</pattern><template>Marry, if you would put me to verses or to dance for your sake, why, you undid me.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT BEATS UPON THE HIGH SHORE OF THIS WORLD</pattern><template>No, not all these, thrice gorgeous ceremony, not all these, laid in bed majestical, can sleep so soundly...</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS AS VIRTUOUS AS A GENTLEMAN NEED TO BE</pattern><template>Virtuous enough.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CHARGE YOU  IN THE NAME OF GOD  TAKE HEED</pattern><template>For never two such kingdoms did contend without much fall of blood.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT SAYS SHE  FAIR ONE</pattern><template>That the tongues of men are full of deceits?</template></category><category><pattern>TO NEW STORE FRANCE WITH BASTARD WARRIORS</pattern><template>Where is Montjoy, the herald?</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN FLUELLEN</pattern><template>Shh!</template></category><category><pattern>AND TO ENGLAND THEN  WHERE NE'ER FROM FRANCE ARRIVED</pattern><template>more happy men.</template></category><category><pattern>I ARREST THEE OF HIGH TREASON BY THE NAME OF RICHARD EARL OF CAMBRIDGE</pattern><template>I arrest thee of high treason by the name of Thomas Grey, Knight of Northumberland.</template></category><category><pattern>TRAILEST THOU THE PUISSANT PIKE  EVEN SO</pattern><template>What are you?</template></category><category><pattern>IN LITTLE ROOM CONFINING MIGHTY MEN</pattern><template>mangling by starts the full course of their glory.</template></category><category><pattern>TO BRING FORTH SO GREAT AN OBJECT</pattern><template>Can this cockpit hold the vasty fields of France or may we cram within this wooden  o ...</template></category><category><pattern>AT ONE TIME BRING IN TO ANY OF YOUR ANCESTORS</pattern><template>Call in the messengers sent from the Dauphin.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DID US GREAT GOOD</pattern><template>Do we all holy rites.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR ME</pattern><template>Hark how our steeds for present service neigh.</template></category><category><pattern>A GOOD OLD COMMANDER AND A MOST KIND GENTLEMAN</pattern><template>I pray ya, what thinks he of our estate?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN LET THE TRUMPETS SOUND THE TUCKET SONANCE AND THE NOTE TO MOUNT</pattern><template>for our approach will so much dare the field...</template></category><category><pattern>MAY IT BE POSSIBLE THAT FOREIGN HIRE</pattern><template>could out of thee extract one spark of evil that might annoy my finger?</template></category><category><pattern>THUS SAYS MY KING</pattern><template>Say, if my father render a fair return, it is against my will, for I desire nothing but odds with England.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE WILL EAT ALL HE KILLS</pattern><template>He never did harm that I heard of.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MY SOVEREIGN  TAKE UP THE ENGLISH SHORT  AND LET THEM KNOW OF WHAT A MONARCHY YOU ARE THE HEAD</pattern><template>Self love, my liege, is not so vile a sin as self neglecting.</template></category><category><pattern>BE IN THEIR FLOWING CUPS FRESHLY REMEMBERED</pattern><template>This story shall a good man teach his son.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE THE LATE COMMISSIONERS</pattern><template>I one, my lord.</template></category><category><pattern>SO ARE YOU  PRINCES ENGLISH  EVERY ONE</pattern><template>My duty to you both, on equal love, great kings of France...</template></category><category><pattern>BASE TYKE</pattern><template>Callest thou me host?</template></category><category><pattern>GOD BLESS IT AND PRESERVE IT  SO LONG AS IT PLEASES HIS GRACE</pattern><template>and his majesty too.</template></category><category><pattern>THROUGH THE COUNTRY THERE BE NOTHING COMPELLED FROM THE VILLAGES  NOTHING TAKEN BUT PAID FOR  NONE OF THE FRENCH UPBRAIDED OR ABUSED IN DISDAINFUL LANGUAGE</pattern><template>For when lenity and cruelty play for a kingdom, the gentler gamester is the soonest winner.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THE ENEMY IS AN ASS AND A FOOL AND A PRATING COXCOMB  IS IT MEET THAT WE SHOULD ALSO BE AN ASS</pattern><template>and a fool and a prating coxcomb in your conscience now?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT ISLAND OF ENGLAND BREEDS VERY VALIANT CREATURES</pattern><template>Now is it time to arm.</template></category><category><pattern>SAY  IF MY FATHER RENDER A FAIR RETURN  IT IS AGAINST MY WILL  FOR I DESIRE NOTHING BUT ODDS WITH ENGLAND</pattern><template>And to that end, as matching to his youth and vanity, I did present him with the Paris balls!</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM I'LL KNOCK HIS LEEK ABOUT HIS PATE UPON SAINT DAVY'S DAY</pattern><template>Do not wear your dagger in your cap that day, lest he knock that about yours.</template></category><category><pattern>MY ROYAL COUSIN  TEACH YOU OUR PRINCESS ENGLISH</pattern><template>I would have her learn, my fair cousin, how perfectly I love her, and that is good english.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MERCY  BUT TOO MUCH SECURITY</pattern><template>Let him be punished, lest example breed by his sufferance, more of such a kind.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT LOOK TO BE WASHED OFF WITH THE NEXT TIDE</pattern><template>He hath not told his thought to the king?</template></category><category><pattern>GO YOU AND ENTER HARFLEW</pattern><template>There remain and fortify it strongly against the French.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS LIPS BLOWS AT HIS NOSE</pattern><template>'tis like a coal of fire...</template></category><category><pattern>ENGLAND SHALL REPENT HIS FOLLY</pattern><template>Bid him, therefore, consider of his ransom...</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I FELT TO HIS KNEES  AND SO UPWARD    AND UPWARD  AND ALL WAS AS</pattern><template>cold as any stone.</template></category><category><pattern>BRAGGART VILE</pattern><template>Ah, hear me when I say, he that strikes the first stroke, I'll run him up to the hilts, as I'm a soldier.</template></category><category><pattern>GET UP</pattern><template>Shh!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAVE SAID THEIR PRAYERS  AND THEY STAY FOR DEATH</pattern><template>A very little little let us do, and all is done.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING IS NOT BOUND TO ANSWER THE PARTICULAR ENDINGS OF HIS SOLDIERS</pattern><template>nor the father of his son, for they purpose not their deaths when they purpose their services.</template></category><category><pattern>FOLLOW  FOLLOW</pattern><template>For who is he whose chin is but enriched with one appearing hair...</template></category><category><pattern>I CANNOT KISS</pattern><template>That's the humor of it.</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE SCIENCES WHICH SHOULD BECOME OUR COUNTRY  BUT GROW LIKE SAVAGES  AS SOLDIERS WILL</pattern><template>that nothing do but meditate on blood...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HEAR HIM ALL NIGHT</pattern><template>If the enemy is an ass and a fool and a prating coxcomb, is it meet that we should also be an ass...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW NOW  FLUELLEN  COMEST THOU FROM THE BRIDGE</pattern><template>Aye, so please your majesty.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL JOIN TOGETHER AT THE LATTER DAY AND CRY ALL   WE DIED AT SUCH A PLACE   SOME SWEARING  SOME CRYING FOR A SURGEON  SOME UPON THEIR WIVES LEFT POOR BEHIND THEM  SOME UPON THE DEBTS THEY OWE  SOME UPON THEIR CHILDREN RAWLY LEFT</pattern><template>I'm afeared there are few die well...</template></category><category><pattern>AND SICKNESS GROWING UPON OUR SOLDIERS  WE WILL RETIRE TO CALAIS</pattern><template>Tonight... in Harflew will we be your guest.</template></category><category><pattern>LET THERE BE SUNG NON NOBISANDTE DEUM</pattern><template>The dead with charity enclosed in clay.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LORD IN HEAVEN BLESS THEE  NOBLE HARRY</pattern><template>God have mercy, old heart.</template></category><category><pattern>IN TERRAM SALICAM MULIERES NE SUCCEDANT    NO WOMAN SHALL SUCCEED IN SALIQUE LAND   WHICH SALIQUE LAND THE FRENCH UNJUSTLY GLOZE</pattern><template>to be the realm of France.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THE LAND SALIQUE LIES IN GERMANY</pattern><template>between the floods of Sala and of Elbe.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HAVE DARED ON THIS UNWORTHY SCAFFOLD</pattern><template>to bring forth so great an object.</template></category><category><pattern>TO THIS ADD DEFIANCE  AND TELL HIM  FOR CONCLUSION   HE HATH BETRAYED HIS FOLLOWERS</pattern><template>whose condemnation is pronounced.  So far my king and master, so much my office.</template></category><category><pattern>A NEST OF HOLLOW BOSOMS WHICH HE FILLS WITH TREACHEROUS CROWNS</pattern><template>and three corrupted men.</template></category><category><pattern>HARRY THE KING  BEDFORD AND EXETER  WARWICK AND TALBOT  SALISBURY AND GLOUCESTER</pattern><template>be in their flowing cups freshly remembered.</template></category><category><pattern>AND A FOOL AND A PRATING COXCOMB IN YOUR CONSCIENCE NOW</pattern><template>I will speak lower.</template></category><category><pattern>AND FATE OF HIM</pattern><template>Ambassadors from Harry, king of England, do crave admittance to your majesty.</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  LORD CONSTABLE  HASTE ON MONTJOY</pattern><template>Prince Dauphin, you shall stay with us in Rouen.</template></category><category><pattern>JE QUAND SUR LE POSSESSION DE FRANCE</pattern><template>et, uh, quand vous avez la possession, uh, de moi...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  OH  OH  OH</pattern><template>Do not, when thou art king, hang a thief.</template></category><category><pattern>TO SWEARING AND STERN LOOKS  DIFFUSED ATTIRE  AND EVERYTHING THAT SEEMS</pattern><template>unnatural.</template></category><category><pattern>AYE</pattern><template>Tell him I'll knock his leek about his pate upon Saint Davy's day.</template></category><category><pattern>GO AND BRING THEM</pattern><template>You see, this chase is hotly followed, friends.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID ONCE THE DEVIL WOULD HAVE HIM ABOUT WOMEN</pattern><template>Well, he did in some sort...</template></category><category><pattern>COULD OUT OF THEE EXTRACT ONE SPARK OF EVIL THAT MIGHT ANNOY MY FINGER</pattern><template>'Tis so strange...</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEIR MOST REVEREND HEADS DASHED TO THE WALLS  YOUR NAKED INFANTS SPITTED UPON PIKES</pattern><template>whiles the mad mothers with their howls confused...</template></category><category><pattern>THAN IN THE TONGUES OF THE FRENCH COUNCIL</pattern><template>Here comes your father.</template></category><category><pattern>IL EST FORT BON ANGLAIS</pattern><template>Dites moi I'anglais pour le bras.</template></category><category><pattern>STARS  MONTJOY</pattern><template>Some of them will fall tomorrow, I hope.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO I WOULD HE WERE  AND I BY HIM</pattern><template>At all adventures, so we were quit here.</template></category><category><pattern>THE POOR  CONDEMNED ENGLISH  LIKE SACRIFICES  BY THEIR WATCHFUL FIRES SIT PATIENTLY</pattern><template>and inly ruminate the morning's danger.</template></category><category><pattern>HUGH CAPET  ALSO  WHO USURPED THE CROWN OF CHARLES  THE DUKE OF LORRAINE  SOLE HEIR MALE OF THE TRUE LINE AND STOCK OF CHARLES THE GREAT  COULD NOT KEEP QUIET IN HIS CONSCIENCE WEARING THE CROWN OF FRANCE</pattern><template>until satisfied that fair queen Isabel, his grandmother, was lineal of the Lady Ermengare, daughter to Charles, the aforesaid duke of Lorraine, by the which marriage the line of Charles the great...</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT POSSIBLE THAT I SHOULD LOVE THE ENEMY OF FRANCE</pattern><template>No, kate.</template></category><category><pattern>LE MENTON  DE CHIN</pattern><template>Oui, sauf votre honneur, en verite, vous prononcez les mots aussi droit que les natifs d'angleterre.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN  RICHARD EARL OF CAMBRIDGE  THERE IS YOURS</pattern><template>There yours, Lord Scroop of Masham, and sir knight, Grey of Northumberland, this same is yours.</template></category><category><pattern>TO MARK THE FULL FRAUGHT MAN</pattern><template>and best indued with some suspicion.</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE MORE  OR CLOSE THE WALL UP WITH OUR ENGLISH DEAD</pattern><template>In peace there's nothing so becomes a man as modest stillness and humility.</template></category><category><pattern>WENT TO A BAWDY HOUSE NOT ABOVE ONCE IN THE QUARTER</pattern><template>Oh!</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS SO SHAKED WITH A BURNING QUOTIDIAN FEVER</pattern><template>that it is most lamentable to behold.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SPEAK PROUDLY</pattern><template>Tell the constable we are but warriors for the working day.</template></category><category><pattern>FOLLOW YOUR SPIRIT  AND UPON THIS CHARGE  CRY   GOD FOR HARRY  ENGLAND AND SAINT GEORGE   GOD FOR HARRY  ENGLAND AND SAINT GEORGE</pattern><template>Up to the breach, you dogs!</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S IN ARTHUR'S BOSOM  IF EVER A MAN WENT TO ARTHUR'S BOSOM</pattern><template>He made a finer end and went away an it had been any Christian child.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE ENOUGH YET LIVING IN THE FIELD TO SMOTHER UP THE ENGLISH IN OUR THRONGS</pattern><template>if any order might be thought upon.</template></category><category><pattern>SPEAK  CAPTAIN  FOR HIS LIFE  AND I WILL THEE REQUITE</pattern><template>Ancient Pistol, I do partly understand your meaning.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW ARE WE WELL RESOLVED  AND BY GOD'S HELP AND YOURS  THE NOBLE SINEWS OF OUR POWER  FRANCE BEING OURS  WE'LL BEND IT TO OUR ALL</pattern><template>or break it all to pieces.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR MAJESTYENTENDS BETTERQUE MOI</pattern><template>Ah, it is not a fashion for the maids in France to kiss before they are married?</template></category><category><pattern>MY LORD OF ORLEANS AND MY LORD HIGH CONSTABLE  YOU TALK OF HORSE AND ARMOR</pattern><template>You are as well provided of both as any prince in the world.</template></category><category><pattern>TERMS SUCH AS WILL ENTER AT A LADY'S EAR</pattern><template>and plead his love suit to her gentle heart?</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP CLOSE</pattern><template>I thee command.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  PRINCES FRENCH AND PEERS  HEALTH TO YOU ALL</pattern><template>Right joyous are we to behold your face, most worthy brother England.</template></category><category><pattern>WE    ARE THE MAKERS OF MANNERS  KATE</pattern><template>Therefore, patiently...</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN MACMORRIS  I BESEECH YOU NOW  A FEW DISPUTATIONS AS PARTLY TOUCHING THE DISCIPLINES OF THE WAR  PARTLY TO SATISFY MY OPINION</pattern><template>and partly for the satisfaction of my mind, as touching the direction of the military discipline.</template></category><category><pattern>MAIS JE ME SOUVIENDRAI</pattern><template>Les doigts?</template></category><category><pattern>ALAS  SHE HATH FROM FRANCE TOO LONG BEEN CHASED  AND ALL HER HUSBANDRY DOTH LIE ON HEAPS  CORRUPTING IN ITS OWN FERTILITY</pattern><template>And as our vineyards, fallows, meads and hedges, defective in their natures, grow to wildness, even so our houses and ourselves, our children have lost...</template></category><category><pattern>CANST THOU LOVE ME</pattern><template>I cannot tell.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SHALL PLEASE HIM  KATE</pattern><template>Then it shall also content me.</template></category><category><pattern>CANNOT WASH YOUR MAJESTY'S WELSH BLOOD OUT OF YOUR BODY  I CAN TELL YOU THAT</pattern><template>God bless it and preserve it, so long as it pleases his grace...</template></category><category><pattern>GET YOU THEREFORE HENCE  POOR MISERABLE WRETCHES  TO YOUR DEATH  THE TASTE WHEREOF GOD OF HIS MERCY GIVE YOU PATIENCE TO ENDURE</pattern><template>and true repentance of all your dear offenses.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR THIS REVOLT OF THINE  METHINKS  IS LIKE ANOTHER FALL OF MAN</pattern><template>I arrest thee of high treason by the name of Richard Earl of Cambridge.</template></category><category><pattern>I PRAY YA  WHAT THINKS HE OF OUR ESTATE</pattern><template>Even as men wrecked upon a sand...</template></category><category><pattern>FOR MY PART  I CARE NOT</pattern><template>I say little, but when time shall serve, there shall be smiles.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL HAVE IT ALL MINE</pattern><template>And, Kate, when France is mine, and I am yours, then yours is France, and you are mine.</template></category><category><pattern>OH</pattern><template>Fair Katherine, if you will love me soundly with your French heart, glad to hear you confess it brokenly with your English Do you like me, Kate?</template></category><category><pattern>FAREWELL</pattern><template>Adieu.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR PLAY</pattern><template>My lord, I'll tell you.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GUILT INDEED</pattern><template>confirmed conspiracy with fearful France, and by their hands this grace of kings must die, ere he take ship for France.</template></category><category><pattern>MA FOI  J'OUBLIE LES DOIGTS</pattern><template>Mais je me souviendrai.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS LIBERAL EYE DOTH GIVE TO EVERYONE  THAWING COLD FEAR</pattern><template>that mean and gentle all...</template></category><category><pattern>IF NOT  TO SAY TO THEE THAT I SHALL DIE  'TIS TRUE  BUT FOR THY LOVE  BY THE LORD  NO</pattern><template>Yet I love thee too.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOULD NOT EXPEL THESE INCONVENIENCES</pattern><template>and bless us with her former qualities.</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE MORE BACK AGAIN</pattern><template>We are enough yet living in the field to smother up the English in our throngs...</template></category><category><pattern>NOW ATTEST THAT THOSE WHOM YOU CALLED FATHERS DID BEGET YOU</pattern><template>And you, good yeoman, whose limbs were made in England, show us here the mettle of your pasture.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE THEY WILL NOT COME UPON US NOW</pattern><template>We are in god's hand, brother, not in theirs.</template></category><category><pattern>OF PRINCES IN THIS NUMBER  126</pattern><template>Added to these, of knights, esquires and gallant gentlemen, eight thousand and four hundred...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT PARDON  GENTLES ALL  THE FLAT  UNRAISED SPIRITS</pattern><template>that have dared on this unworthy scaffold...</template></category><category><pattern>FOR OUR APPROACH WILL SO MUCH DARE THE FIELD</pattern><template>that England shall crouch down in fear... and yield!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HARD CONDITION</pattern><template>Twin born with greatness, subject to the breath of every fool.</template></category><category><pattern>BE PATIENT  FOR YOU SHALL REMAIN WITH US</pattern><template>Now forth, lord constable and princes all, and quickly bring us word of England's fall.</template></category><category><pattern>HE PARTED EVEN JUST BETWEEN 12:00 AND 1:00  EVEN AT THE TURNING OF THE TIDE</pattern><template>For after I saw him fumble with the sheets...</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL SATISFIED THAT FAIR QUEEN ISABEL  HIS GRANDMOTHER  WAS LINEAL OF THE LADY ERMENGARE  DAUGHTER TO CHARLES  THE AFORESAID DUKE OF LORRAINE  BY THE WHICH MARRIAGE THE LINE OF CHARLES THE GREAT</pattern><template>was reunited to the crown of France.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HIS KINSMAN TOO</pattern><template>The figo with thee then.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM HIM  AND THUS HE GREETS YOUR MAJESTY</pattern><template>He wills you, in the name of God almighty, that you divest yourself and lay apart...</template></category><category><pattern>POOR SIR JOHN</pattern><template>A good portly man of faith.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR CERTAINLY SHE DID YOU WRONG  FOR YOU WERE BETROTHED TO HER</pattern><template>How now, mine host Pistol?</template></category><category><pattern>MY COUSIN WESTMORELAND</pattern><template>No, my fair cousin.</template></category><category><pattern>IN YOUR CONSCIENCE  NOW  IS IT NOT</pattern><template>'Tis certain there's not a boy left alive.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HOPE TO MAKE THE SENDER BLUSH AT IT</pattern><template>Therefore, my lords, omit no happy hour...</template></category><category><pattern>A    A CORNISH NAME</pattern><template>No, I am a Welshman.</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS CERTAIN THERE'S NOT A BOY LEFT ALIVE</pattern><template>I was not angry since I came to France!</template></category><category><pattern>WILL IT NEVER BE DAY</pattern><template>I will trot tomorrow a mile, and my way shall be paved with English faces.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SEE</pattern><template>Uh, oh...</template></category><category><pattern>IN MATTERS OF DEFENSE  'TIS BEST TO WEIGH THE ENEMY MORE MIGHTY THAN HE SEEMS</pattern><template>Think we king Harry strong.</template></category><category><pattern>AS DID THE FORMER LIONS OF YOUR BLOOD</pattern><template>Never king of England had nobles richer and more loyal subjects...</template></category><category><pattern>THE NAME OF AGINCOURT</pattern><template>Ready!</template></category><category><pattern>AND HIS MAJESTY TOO</pattern><template>Thanks, good my countryman.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MORE THAN WE KNOW</pattern><template>Aye, and more than we should seek after.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING WILL BE GONE FROM SOUTHAMPTON</pattern><template>Farewell, hostess.</template></category><category><pattern>WERE ALL THY CHILDREN KIND AND NATURAL</pattern><template>But see, thy fault France hath in thee found out.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO TWICE A DAY THEIR WITHERED HANDS</pattern><template>hold up toward heaven to pardon blood.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DUKE WILL HEAR THY VOICE</pattern><template>Speak, captain, for his life, and I will thee requite.</template></category><category><pattern>SUCH A MIGHTY SUM AS NEVER DID THE CLERGY</pattern><template>at one time bring in to any of your ancestors.</template></category><category><pattern>I COME TO THEE FOR CHARITABLE LICENSE</pattern><template>that we may wander o'er this bloody field to book our dead...</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN TO CALAIS</pattern><template>and to England then, where ne'er from France arrived...</template></category><category><pattern>COLD AS ANY STONE</pattern><template>They say he cried out for sack.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD BARDOLPH  PUT THY FACE BETWEEN HIS SHEETS AND DO THE OFFICE OF A WARMING PAN</pattern><template>Away, you rogue.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR THE DAUPHIN  I STAND HERE FOR HIM</pattern><template>What to him from England?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS STORY SHALL A GOOD MAN TEACH HIS SON</pattern><template>Crispin Crispian shall ne'er go by, from this day to the ending of the world, but we in it shall be remembered.</template></category><category><pattern>O  FOR HONOR OF OUR LAND</pattern><template>By faith and honor, our madams mock at us and plainly say our mettle is bred out!</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN AS MEN WRECKED UPON A SAND</pattern><template>that look to be washed off with the next tide.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS CASTLE CALLED</pattern><template>that stands hard by?</template></category><category><pattern>MY SOVEREIGN LORD</pattern><template>Bestow yourself with speed!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW SITS THE WIND FAIR  AND WE WILL ABOARD</pattern><template>My lord of Cambridge and my kind lord of Masham...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU PAY HIM THEN</pattern><template>You'll never trust his word after?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE GLAD THE DAUPHIN IS SO PLEASANT WITH US</pattern><template>His present and your pains we thank you for.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS LODGING LIKES ME BETTER</pattern><template>since I may say,  Now lie I like a king.  Lend me thy cloak, Sir Thomas.</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHALL  MY LIEGE</pattern><template>Shall I attend your grace?</template></category><category><pattern>PROUD OF THEIR NUMBERS AND SECURE IN SOUL  THE CONFIDENT AND OVER LUSTY FRENCH</pattern><template>do the low rated English play at dice...</template></category><category><pattern>O'ERHANG AND JETTY HIS CONFOUNDED BASE  SWILLED WITH THE WILD AND WASTEFUL OCEAN</pattern><template>Now set the teeth and stretch the nostril wide, hold hard the breath and bend up every spirit to his full height!</template></category><category><pattern>WITH WHAT GREAT STATE HE HEARD THEIR EMBASSY  HOW WELL SUPPLIED WITH NOBLE COUNSELORS  HOW MODEST IN EXCEPTION AND WITHAL HOW TERRIBLE</pattern><template>in constant resolution.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HERE I KISS HER AS MY SOVEREIGN QUEEN</pattern><template>God, the best maker of all marriages, combine our hearts in one, our realms in one.</template></category><category><pattern>I ARREST THEE OF HIGH TREASON BY THE NAME OF HENRY LORD SCROOP OF MASHAM</pattern><template>Hear your sentence.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ENEMY IS LOUD</pattern><template>You hear him all night.</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE MORE UNTO THE BREACH  DEAR FRIENDS</pattern><template>Once more, or close the wall up with our English dead!</template></category><category><pattern>FORTUNE IS BARDOLPH'S FOE AND FROWNS ON HIM</pattern><template>for he hath stolen a pax and hanged must he be.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR US</pattern><template>Yes, my conscience.</template></category><category><pattern>AWAY  YOU ROGUE</pattern><template>Faith, he's very ill.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOR IT IS NOT MEET HE SHOULD</pattern><template>I think the king is but a man as I am.</template></category><category><pattern>CONVEY THEM WITH SAFE CONDUCT</pattern><template>Fare you well.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM CAMP TO CAMP THROUGH THE FOUL WOMB OF NIGHT</pattern><template>the hum of either army stilly sounds...</template></category><category><pattern>MY BROTHER GLOUCESTER'S VOICE</pattern><template>I know thy errand.</template></category><category><pattern>PLANT NEIGHBORHOOD</pattern><template>and Christian like accord in their sweet bosoms...</template></category><category><pattern>O PEACE  PRINCE DAUPHIN</pattern><template>You're too much mistaken in this king.</template></category><category><pattern>TENNIS BALLS  MY LIEGE</pattern><template>We are glad the Dauphin is so pleasant with us.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A STEM OF THAT VICTORIOUS STALK</pattern><template>And let us fear the native mightiness...</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I WILL KISS YOUR LIPS  KATE</pattern><template>Les dames et demoiselles pour etre baisees devant leur noces...</template></category><category><pattern>AND LET US FEAR THE NATIVE MIGHTINESS</pattern><template>and fate of him.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD BE PRAISED AND BLESSED</pattern><template>any hurt in the world, but keeps the bridge most valiantly, with excellent discipline.</template></category><category><pattern>DO THOU AMEND THY FACE  AND I'LL AMEND MY LIFE</pattern><template>If sack and sugar be a fault, then God help the wicked.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS REUNITED TO THE CROWN OF FRANCE</pattern><template>So it is clear as is the summer sun.</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE HAND OF THAT BLACK NAME  EDWARD  BLACK PRINCE OF WALES</pattern><template>This is a stem of that victorious stalk.</template></category><category><pattern>HENRY THE SIXTH  IN INFANT BANDS CROWNED KING OF FRANCE AND ENGLAND DID THIS KING SUCCEED</pattern><template>whose state so many had the managing...</template></category><category><pattern>IF THE OPPOSED NUMBERS PLUCK THEIR HEARTS FROM THEM</pattern><template>Not today, o God, oh, not today.</template></category><category><pattern>SO    CONSTANT AND UNSPOTTED DIDST THOU SEEM</pattern><template>that this thy fall hath left a kind of blot...</template></category><category><pattern>CALLEST THOU ME HOST</pattern><template>Now, by this hand, I swear I scorn the term!</template></category><category><pattern>JE PENSE QUE JE SUIS LE BON ECOLIER</pattern><template>J'ai gagne deux mots d'anglais vitement.</template></category><category><pattern>COMMENT APPELEZ VOUS LE COL</pattern><template>De  nick,  madame.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW TO OUR FRENCH CAUSES</pattern><template>Who are the late commissioners?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW FORTH  LORD CONSTABLE AND PRINCES ALL  AND QUICKLY BRING US WORD OF ENGLAND'S FALL</pattern><template>Come. Come in.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING'S A GOOD KING  BUT IT MUST BE AS IT MAY</pattern><template>He passes some humors and careers.</template></category><category><pattern>NYM  THOU HAST SPOKE THE RIGHT</pattern><template>His heart is fracted and... corroborate.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT TELL THE DAUPHIN I WILL KEEP MY STATE  BE LIKE A KING AND SHOW MY SAIL OF GREATNESS</pattern><template>when I do rouse me in my throne of France.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SHALL HAVE NONE  I SWEAR  BUT THESE MY JOINTS</pattern><template>Which, if they have as I shall leave of them, shall yield them little.</template></category><category><pattern>NAMELY  THE CROWN</pattern><template>Willing you overlook this pedigree.</template></category><category><pattern>WE TALK  AND  BY CHRIST  DO NOTHING</pattern><template>By the mass, ere these eyes of mine take themselves to slumber, I'll do good service, or I'll lie in the ground for it.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR I AM SURE WHEN HE SHALL SEE OUR ARMY  HE'LL DROP HIS HEART INTO THE SINK OF FEAR</pattern><template>and, for achievement, offer us his ransom.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULD LAY ON LIKE A BUTCHER AND SIT LIKE A JACKANAPES  NEVER OFF</pattern><template>But before God, Kate, I cannot look greenly...</template></category><category><pattern>IF  DUKE OF BURGUNDY  YOU WOULD THE PEACE</pattern><template>whose want gives growth to the imperfections which you have cited, then you must buy that peace...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT NEVER WAR ADVANCE</pattern><template>his bleeding sword...</template></category><category><pattern>O'ERBLOWS THE FILTHY AND CONTAGIOUS CLOUDS</pattern><template>of heady murder, spoil and villainy!</template></category><category><pattern>THE FRENCH  ADVISED BY GOOD INTELLIGENCE</pattern><template>of this most dreadful preparation, shake in their fear...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HIS NOSE IS EXECUTED AND HIS FIRE'S OUT</pattern><template>Get up!</template></category><category><pattern>THOU SPEAKEST CHEERFULLY</pattern><template>Qui va la?</template></category><category><pattern>IT SORTS WELL WITH YOUR FIERCENESS</pattern><template>Captain Fluellen.</template></category><category><pattern>HANDLE WOMEN</pattern><template>But then he was rheumatic and talked of the whore of Babylon.</template></category><category><pattern>NYM  ROUSE THY VAUNTING VEINS</pattern><template>Boy, bristle thy courage up.</template></category><category><pattern>BOY  BRISTLE THY COURAGE UP</pattern><template>For Falstaff is dead, and we must yearn therefore.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT DAY AFTER DAWN  DOTH RISE AND HELP HYPERION TO HIS HORSE</pattern><template>and follows so the ever running year...</template></category><category><pattern>AMEN</pattern><template>Thus far, with rough and all unable pen...</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD UP TOWARD HEAVEN TO PARDON BLOOD</pattern><template>And I have built two chantries...</template></category><category><pattern>HMPH</pattern><template>That island of England breeds very valiant creatures.</template></category><category><pattern>DE NICK  DE CHIN  DE FOOT ET 'LE COUN</pattern><template>'Tis certain...</template></category><category><pattern>TILL IN HER ASHES SHE LIE BURIED</pattern><template>Therefore, you men of Harflew, take pity of your town and of your people...</template></category><category><pattern>COMPRISED WITHIN THE FORE RANK OF OUR ARTICLES</pattern><template>She hath good leave.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  MY GOOD KNIGHT</pattern><template>I and my bosom must debate a while, and then I would no other company.</template></category><category><pattern>SAVE CEREMONY</pattern><template>And what art thou, thou idle ceremony?</template></category><category><pattern>POSSESS THEM NOT WITH FEAR</pattern><template>Take from them now their sense of reckoning...</template></category><category><pattern>THEY CALL IT AGINCOURT</pattern><template>Then call we this...</template></category><category><pattern>THE DUKE OF EXETER DOTH LOVE THEE WELL</pattern><template>Aye, I praise God, and I have merited some love at his hands.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TOWN IS BESIEGED  AND THE TRUMPET CALLS US TO THE BREACH</pattern><template>We talk, and, by Christ, do nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>OUI  THAT THE TONGUES OF THE MENS IS BE FULL OF DECEITS</pattern><template>That is the princess.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  THEREFORE  TELL ME  MOST FAIR KATHERINE  WILL YOU HAVE ME</pattern><template>Come, your answer in broken music, for thy voice is music, and thy English, broken.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY SUBJECT'S DUTY IS THE KING'S  BUT EVERY SUBJECT'S SOUL IS HIS OWN</pattern><template>'Tis certain.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WITH US</pattern><template>She is our capital demand...</template></category><category><pattern>WILLING YOU OVERLOOK THIS PEDIGREE</pattern><template>And when you find him evenly derived...</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD I WERE WITH HIM  WHERESOME'ER HE IS  EITHER IN HEAVEN OR IN HELL</pattern><template>Nay, sure, he's not in hell.</template></category><category><pattern>10 000 FRENCH</pattern><template>that in the field lie slain.</template></category><category><pattern>BROTHER  WE SHALL</pattern><template>Yet leave our cousin Katherine...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST NOT DARE FOR SHAME TO TALK OF MERCY</pattern><template>For your own reasons turn into your bosoms as dogs upon their masters worrying you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ON IT HAVE BESTOWED MORE CONTRITE TEARS</pattern><template>than from it issued forced drops of blood.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS NOTE DOTH TELL ME OF</pattern><template>10,000 French...</template></category><category><pattern>HE MAY SHOW WHAT OUTWARD COURAGE HE WILL  BUT I BELIEVE AS COLD A NIGHT AS 'TIS</pattern><template>that he could wish himself in Thames up to the neck.</template></category><category><pattern>TOMORROW</pattern><template>Shall you know our mind at full.</template></category><category><pattern>WERE BUT YESTERDAY DUBBED KNIGHTS</pattern><template>Here was a royal fellowship of death.</template></category><category><pattern>A GOOD PORTLY MAN OF FAITH</pattern><template>Aye, to a cheerful look, a pleasing eye...</template></category><category><pattern>MMM</pattern><template>O seigneur dieu!</template></category><category><pattern>FOR THE WASTEFUL VENGEANCE THAT SHALL FLY WITH THEM</pattern><template>For many a thousand widows shall this his mock, mock out of their dear husbands, mock mothers from their sons, mock castles down.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THY ERRAND</pattern><template>I will go with thee.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS MY GRACIOUS LORD OF CANTERBURY</pattern><template>God and his angels guard your sacred throne and make you long become it.</template></category><category><pattern>DE FOOT  MADAME  ET DE COUN</pattern><template>F footet 'le coun.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT MIGHTST THOU DO THAT HONOR WOULD THEE DO</pattern><template>were all thy children kind and natural?</template></category><category><pattern>COMMENT APPELEZ VOUS LES ONGLES</pattern><template>Les ongles?</template></category><category><pattern>HOWBEIT  THEY WOULD HOLD UP THIS SALIQUE LAW</pattern><template>to bar your highness claiming from the female.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME OF THEM WILL FALL TOMORROW  I HOPE</pattern><template>And yet my sky shall not want.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HAUNTED US IN OUR FAMILIAR PATHS</pattern><template>Witness our too much memorable shame...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT SEE  THY FAULT FRANCE HATH IN THEE FOUND OUT</pattern><template>A nest of hollow bosoms which he fills with treacherous crowns...</template></category><category><pattern>QUESTION  YOUR GRACE  THE LATE AMBASSADORS</pattern><template>With what great state he heard their embassy, how well supplied with noble counselors, how modest in exception and withal how terrible...</template></category><category><pattern>IF LITTLE FAULTS PROCEEDING ON DISTEMPER SHALL NOT BE WINKED AT  HOW SHALL WE STRETCH OUR EYE WHEN CAPITAL CRIMES  CHEWED  SWALLOWED AND DIGESTED  APPEAR BEFORE US</pattern><template>We'll yet enlarge that man, though Cambridge, Scroop and Grey, in their dear care and tender preservation...</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS TO YOUR MAJESTY</pattern><template>I hope they will not come upon us now.</template></category><category><pattern>I WEAR IT FOR A MEMORABLE HONOR  FOR I AM WELSH  YOU KNOW  GOOD MY COUNTRYMAN</pattern><template>All the water in Wye...</template></category><category><pattern>BANISH PLUMP JACK  AND BANISH ALL THE WORLD</pattern><template>I do. I will.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT SHALL BE AS IT MAY</pattern><template>Come, I will bestow a breakfast to make you friends, and we'll be all three sworn brothers to France.</template></category><category><pattern>ET  UH  QUAND VOUS AVEZ LA POSSESSION  UH  DE MOI</pattern><template>Let me see...</template></category><category><pattern>HERALD  ARE THE DEAD NUMBERED</pattern><template>Here is the number of the slaughtered French.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT ILL DISPOSED IN BRAWL RIDICULOUS</pattern><template>the name of Agincourt.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU</pattern><template>As good a gentleman as the emperor.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE HEAVY ORISONS AGAINST THIS POOR WRETCH</pattern><template>If little faults proceeding on distemper shall not be winked at, how shall we stretch our eye when capital crimes, chewed, swallowed and digested, appear before us?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS STAR OF ENGLAND</pattern><template>Fortune made his sword...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT TELL ME  KATE  CANST THOU UNDERSTAND THUS MUCH ENGLISH</pattern><template>Canst thou love me?</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS AS ERRANT A PIECE OF KNAVERY  MARK YOU NOW  AS CAN BE OFFERED</pattern><template>In your conscience, now, is it not?</template></category><category><pattern>AND A TRUE LOVER OF THE HOLY CHURCH</pattern><template>The courses of his youth promised it not.</template></category><category><pattern>SUPPOSE THE AMBASSADOR FROM THE FRENCH COMES BACK  TELLS HARRY THAT THE KING DOES OFFER HIM KATHERINE  HIS DAUGHTER  AND WITH HER TO DOWRY  SOME PETTY AND UNPROFITABLE DUKEDOMS</pattern><template>The offer likes him not.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHEN THE BLAST OF WAR BLOWS IN OUR EARS  THEN IMITATE THE ACTION OF THE TIGER</pattern><template>Stiffen the sinews, summon up the blood, disguise fair nature with hard favored rage.</template></category><category><pattern>OUI  VRAIMENT</pattern><template>Oh, kate.</template></category><category><pattern>SMALL TIME  BUT IN THAT SMALL MOST GREATLY LIVED</pattern><template>this star of England.</template></category><category><pattern>WOE THE WHILE</pattern><template>Lie drowned and soaked in mercenary blood.</template></category><category><pattern>LET LIFE BE SHORT</pattern><template>Else shame will be too long!</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL SPEAK LOWER</pattern><template>I pray you and beseech you that you will.</template></category><category><pattern>THE VERY CASQUES THAT DID AFFRIGHT THE AIR AT AGINCOURT</pattern><template>Oh, pardon.</template></category><category><pattern>AS MAN AND WIFE  BEING TWO  ARE ONE IN LOVE  SO BE THERE 'TWIXT OUR KINGDOMS SUCH A SPOUSAL</pattern><template>that never may ill office or fell jealousy...</template></category><category><pattern>AND BE ASSURED YOU'LL FIND A DIFFERENCE  AS WE  HIS SUBJECTS  HAVE IN WONDER FOUND  BETWEEN THE PROMISE OF HIS GREENER DAYS AND THESE HE MASTERS NOW</pattern><template>Tomorrow...</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YOU YIELD AND THIS AVOID</pattern><template>Or, guilty in defense, be thus destroyed?</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  THE BEST MAKER OF ALL MARRIAGES  COMBINE OUR HEARTS IN ONE  OUR REALMS IN ONE</pattern><template>As man and wife, being two, are one in love, so be there 'twixt our kingdoms such a spousal...</template></category><category><pattern>MY SKIN HANGS ABOUT ME LIKE AN OLD LADY'S LOOSE GOWN</pattern><template>Company, villainous company have been the spoil of me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND TO THAT END  AS MATCHING TO HIS YOUTH AND VANITY  I DID PRESENT HIM WITH THE PARIS BALLS</pattern><template>He'll make your Paris Louvre shake for it.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OFFER LIKES HIM NOT</pattern><template>And the nimble gunner with linstock now the devilish cannon touches, and down goes all before them!</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSEZ MOI  JE VOUS SUPPLIE  MON TRES PUISSANT SEIGNEUR</pattern><template>Then I will kiss your lips, Kate.</template></category><category><pattern>O PERDURABLE SHAME</pattern><template>Shame and eternal shame.</template></category><category><pattern>TO KISS</pattern><template>Your majestyentends betterque moi.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU WERE SO FAT  SIR JOHN  THAT YOU MUST INDEED BE OUT OF ALL COMPASS</pattern><template>Do thou amend thy face, and I'll amend my life.</template></category><category><pattern>YET  GOD BEFORE  TELL HIM WE WILL COME ON  THOUGH FRANCE HIMSELF AND SUCH ANOTHER NEIGHBOR STAND IN OUR WAY</pattern><template>So, Montjoy, fare you well.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  PARDON</pattern><template>Let us, ciphers to this great account, on your imaginary forces work.</template></category><category><pattern>DE IS NOT</pattern><template>God be praised and blessed...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW NOW  SIR JOHN   QUOTH I</pattern><template>What, man?</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR MAJESTY SHALL MOCK AT ME</pattern><template>I cannot speak your England.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THE ENGLISH HAD ANY APPREHENSION  THEY WOULD RUN AWAY</pattern><template>Hmph.</template></category><category><pattern>IL EST MEILLEUR QUE I'ANGLAIS LEQUEL JE PARLE</pattern><template>No, faith, it is not.</template></category><category><pattern>COME  COME IN</pattern><template>Captain Fluellen?</template></category><category><pattern>BIDS THEM GOOD MORROW WITH A MODEST SMILE</pattern><template>and calls them  Brothers, friends and countrymen.  A largesse universal, like the sun...</template></category><category><pattern>WILL IT NEVER BE MORNING</pattern><template>My lord of Orleans and my lord High Constable, you talk of horse and armor?</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN MACMORRIS  I THINK  LOOK YOU  UNDER YOUR CORRECTION  THERE ARE NOT MANY OF YOUR NATION</pattern><template>What is my nation?</template></category><category><pattern>AND ALL OUR PRINCES CAPTIVED</pattern><template>by the hand of that black name, Edward, black prince of Wales.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS THE KING</pattern><template>The king himself has rode to view their battle.</template></category><category><pattern>LET US CONDOLE THE KNIGHT  FOR  LAMBKINS  WE WILL LIVE</pattern><template>The French, advised by good intelligence...</template></category><category><pattern>DE HAND   MM HMM</pattern><template>Et les doigts?</template></category><category><pattern>FOR  MY GOOD LIEGE  SHE IS SO IDLY KINGED BY A VAIN  GIDDY  SHALLOW  HUMOROUS YOUTH  THAT FEAR ATTENDS HER NOT</pattern><template>O peace, prince dauphin.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ALL NIGHT SLEEPS</pattern><template>in Elysium.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW IF THESE MEN DO NOT DIE WELL  IT WILL BE A BLACK MATTER FOR THE KING THAT LED THEM TO IT</pattern><template>So if a son that is by his father sent about merchandise...</template></category><category><pattern>WITH FULL POWER UPON US  AND MORE THAN CAREFULLY IT US CONCERNS TO ANSWER ROYALLY IN OUR DEFENSES</pattern><template>Therefore, the dukes of Berri...</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID THEY WERE</pattern><template>devils incarnate.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN DIE AND BE DAMNED</pattern><template>and figo for thy friendship!</template></category><category><pattern>IF SACK AND SUGAR BE A FAULT  THEN GOD HELP THE WICKED</pattern><template>Mmm? If to be old and merry is a sin, if to be fat is to be hated, then no, my good lord, when thou art king, banish Pistol, banish Bardolph, banish Nym.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD'S WILL  I PRAY THEE  WISH NOT ONE MAN MORE</pattern><template>Rather, proclaim it, Westmoreland, through my host, that he which hath no stomach to this fight...</template></category><category><pattern>CHEERLY TO SEA</pattern><template>The signs of war advance.</template></category><category><pattern>AND PARTLY FOR THE SATISFACTION OF MY MIND  AS TOUCHING THE DIRECTION OF THE MILITARY DISCIPLINE</pattern><template>That is the point. It is no time to discourse, so Christ save me.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR LOOK YOU  THE MINES IS NOT ACCORDING TO THE DISCIPLINES OF WAR</pattern><template>By Cheshu, I think he will blow up all, if there is not better direction.</template></category><category><pattern>CE SONT MOTS DE SON MAUVAIS CORRUPTIBLE  GROS  ET IMPUDIQUE ET NON POUR LES DAMES D'HONNEUR D'USER</pattern><template>Je ne voudrais prononcer ces mots devants les seigneurs de france pour tout le monde.</template></category><category><pattern>AND LET US DO IT WITH NO SHOW OF FEAR</pattern><template>No, with no more than if we heard that England were busied with, uh, a Whitsun morris dance.</template></category><category><pattern>STAND FOR YOUR OWN</pattern><template>Unwind your bloody flag.</template></category><category><pattern>KILL THE BOYS AND THE LUGGAGE</pattern><template>'Tis expressly against the law of arms.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM OUR BROTHER ENGLAND</pattern><template>From him, and thus he greets your majesty.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NIGHTS WITH SLEEP</pattern><template>had the forehand and vantage...</template></category><category><pattern>THUS COMES THE ENGLISH</pattern><template>with full power upon us, and more than carefully it us concerns to answer royally in our defenses.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR THE WHICH SUPPLY  ADMIT ME  CHORUS  TO THIS HISTORY  WHO  PROLOGUE LIKE  YOUR HUMBLE PATIENCE PRAY</pattern><template>gently to hear, kindly to judge...</template></category><category><pattern>AND TELL THE PLEASANT PRINCE THIS MOCK OF HIS</pattern><template>hath turned his balls to gunstones, and his soul shall stand sore charged...</template></category><category><pattern>PAID MONEY THAT I BORROWED  THREE OR FOUR TIMES</pattern><template>Lived well and in good compass.</template></category><category><pattern>BASE IS THE SLAVE THAT PAYS</pattern><template>By this sword, he that makes the first thrust, I'll kill him, by this sword, I will.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHEN YOU FIND HIM EVENLY DERIVED</pattern><template>from his most famed of famous ancestors, Edward the III, he bids you then resign your crown and kingdom, indirectly held from him, the native and true challenger.</template></category><category><pattern>IN AID WHEREOF  WE OF THE SPIRITUALITY WILL RAISE YOUR HIGHNESS</pattern><template>such a mighty sum as never did the clergy...</template></category><category><pattern>NOR SHALL MY NELL KEEP LODGERS</pattern><template>No, by my troth, not long.</template></category><category><pattern>NOR GASP OUT MY ELOQUENCE NOR I HAVE NO CUNNING IN PROTESTATION</pattern><template>If thou canst love a fellow of this temper, Kate, that never looks in his glass for love of anything he sees there, let thine eye be thy cook.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH MUST PROPORTION THE LOSSES WE HAVE BORNE</pattern><template>which in weight to re answer his pettiness would bow under.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO  LIKE A FOUL AND UGLY WITCH  DOTH LIMP SO TEDIOUSLY AWAY</pattern><template>I have the best armor in the world.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THIS  WHICH THEY PRODUCE FROM PHARAMOND</pattern><template>In terram salicam mulieres ne succedant.   No woman shall succeed in Salique land.  Which Salique land the French unjustly gloze...</template></category><category><pattern>I THEE COMMAND</pattern><template>Farewell.</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS A FEARFUL ODDS</pattern><template>Oh, that we now had here but one ten thousand of those men in England...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT INFINITE HEART'S EASE MUST KINGS NEGLECT</pattern><template>that private men enjoy?</template></category><category><pattern>ELLE EST APPELEE DE  HAND</pattern><template>De hand.  Mm hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>UNLESS THE DAUPHIN BE IN PRESENCE HERE  TO WHOM EXPRESSLY I BRING GREETING TO</pattern><template>For the Dauphin, I stand here for him.</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  MY LORDS  OMIT NO HAPPY HOUR</pattern><template>that may give furtherance to our expedition.</template></category><category><pattern>WHILES YET MY SOLDIERS ARE IN MY COMMAND  WHILES YET THE COOL AND TEMPERATE WIND OF GRACE</pattern><template>o'erblows the filthy and contagious clouds...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  THIS CHASE IS HOTLY FOLLOWED  FRIENDS</pattern><template>Good my sovereign, take up the English short, and let them know of what a monarchy you are the head.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DEAD WITH CHARITY ENCLOSED IN CLAY</pattern><template>And then to Calais...</template></category><category><pattern>AS IN THE KING'S COMPANY  HIS CAUSE BEING JUST AND HIS QUARREL HONORABLE</pattern><template>That's more than we know.</template></category><category><pattern>BEAR THEM HENCE</pattern><template>Now, Lords, for France, the enterprise whereof shall be to you, as us, like glorious, since God so graciously hath brought to light this dangerous treason lurking in our way.</template></category><category><pattern>FORTUNE MADE HIS SWORD</pattern><template>by which the world's best garden he achieved...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THOU SHALT</pattern><template>We would have all such offenders so cut off.</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS EXPRESSLY AGAINST THE LAW OF ARMS</pattern><template>'Tis as errant a piece of knavery, mark you now, as can be offered.</template></category><category><pattern>PROMISED TO HARRY AND HIS FOLLOWERS</pattern><template>Well met, Corporal Nym.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE YOU STAND LIKE GREYHOUNDS IN THE SLIPS  STRAINING UPON THE START</pattern><template>The game's afoot!</template></category><category><pattern>DO SINFULLY MISCARRY UPON THE SEA  THE IMPUTATION OF HIS WICKEDNESS  BY YOUR RULE  SHOULD BE IMPOSED UPON THE FATHER THAT SENT HIM</pattern><template>But this is not so.</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS CERTAIN</pattern><template>Eevery man that dies ill, the ill upon his own head.</template></category><category><pattern>LET IT BE A QUARREL BETWEEN US  IF YOU LIVE</pattern><template>Be friends, you English fools! Be friends!</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR HIGHNESS BADE ME ASK FOR IT TODAY  SO DID YOU ME</pattern><template>And I.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD'S WILL  MY LIEGE</pattern><template>You and I alone, without more help, could fight this royal battle.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE AS WELL PROVIDED OF BOTH AS ANY PRINCE IN THE WORLD</pattern><template>I will not change my horse...</template></category><category><pattern>IL FAUT QUE J'APPRENNE A PARLER</pattern><template>Comment appelez vous la main en anglais?</template></category><category><pattern>THOU DOST NOT WISH MORE HELP FROM ENGLAND  COZ</pattern><template>God's will, my liege.</template></category><category><pattern>AT ALL ADVENTURES  SO WE WERE QUIT HERE</pattern><template>I think he would not wish himself anywhere but where he is.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR WHEN LENITY AND CRUELTY PLAY FOR A KINGDOM  THE GENTLER GAMESTER IS THE SOONEST WINNER</pattern><template>Thus says my king,  Say thou to Harry of England,  though we seemed dead, we did but sleep.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  MONTJOY  FARE YOU WELL</pattern><template>The sum of all our answer is but this: We would not seek a battle as we are, nor, as we are, we say we will not shun it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH  IF THEY HAVE AS I SHALL LEAVE OF THEM  SHALL YIELD THEM LITTLE</pattern><template>Tell the constable.</template></category><category><pattern>AND BUT FOR CEREMONY</pattern><template>such a wretch, winding up days of toil...</template></category><category><pattern>LET HIM BE PUNISHED  LEST EXAMPLE BREED BY HIS SUFFERANCE  MORE OF SUCH A KIND</pattern><template>Oh, let us yet be merciful.</template></category><category><pattern>OR DO NOT LEARN FOR WANT OF TIME</pattern><template>those sciences which should become our country, but grow like savages, as soldiers will...</template></category><category><pattern>AND IN A CAPTIVE CHARIOT INTO ROUEN BRING HIM OUR PRISONER</pattern><template>This becomes the great.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WOULD HAVE SOLD YOUR KING TO SLAUGHTER  HIS PRINCES AND HIS PEERS TO SERVITUDE  HIS SUBJECTS TO OPPRESSION AND CONTEMPT</pattern><template>and his whole kingdom into desolation!</template></category><category><pattern>THINK YOU NOT THAT THE POWERS WE BEAR WITH US</pattern><template>will cut their passage through the force of France?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD HUSBAND  COME HOME PRESENTLY</pattern><template>Come, shall I make you two friends?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  FOR MY MANLY HEART DOTH YEARN</pattern><template>Bardolph, be blithe.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU AND I ALONE  WITHOUT MORE HELP  COULD FIGHT THIS ROYAL BATTLE</pattern><template>You know your places!</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR REPROOF IS SOMETHING TOO ROUND</pattern><template>I should be angry with you if time were convenient.</template></category><category><pattern>WHILES ANY SPEAKS THAT FOUGHT WITH US</pattern><template>upon Saint Cispin's day!</template></category><category><pattern>LET US  CIPHERS TO THIS GREAT ACCOUNT  ON YOUR IMAGINARY FORCES WORK</pattern><template>For it is your thoughts that now must deck our kings, carry them here, there, jumping o'er times, turning the accomplishment of many years into an hourglass.</template></category><category><pattern>BARDOLPH  A SOLDIER FIRM AND SOUND OF HEART</pattern><template>and buxom valor, hath by cruel fate and giddy fortune's furious, fickle wheel...</template></category><category><pattern>SO IF A SON THAT IS BY HIS FATHER SENT ABOUT MERCHANDISE</pattern><template>do sinfully miscarry upon the sea, the imputation of his wickedness, by your rule, should be imposed upon the father that sent him?</template></category><category><pattern>THE COURSES OF HIS YOUTH PROMISED IT NOT</pattern><template>Since his addiction was to courses vain, his hours filled up with riots, banquets, sports and never noted in him any study.</template></category><category><pattern>DE NAILS  MADAME</pattern><template>De nails, madame.    De arma, de belbow.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE IS OUR CAPITAL DEMAND</pattern><template>comprised within the fore rank of our articles.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRE</pattern><template>Why, all our ranks are broke.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN LEND THE EYE A TERRIBLE ASPECT</pattern><template>Let it pry through the portage of the head like the brass cannon.</template></category><category><pattern>AHH</pattern><template>Oh, now, who will behold the royal captain of this ruined band, walking from watch to watch, from tent to tent?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT NEVER MAY ILL OFFICE OR FELL JEALOUSY</pattern><template>which troubles oft the bed of blessed marriage...</template></category><category><pattern>I PRAY THEE BEAR MY FORMER ANSWER BACK</pattern><template>Bid them achieve me and then sell my bones!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT ONE THAT IS LIKE TO BE EXECUTED FOR ROBBING A CHURCH</pattern><template>One Bardolph, if your majesty know the man.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL DO AS I MAY</pattern><template>It is certain, corporal, that Ancient Pistol is married to Nell quickly.</template></category><category><pattern>OF FIGHTING MEN  THEY HAVE FULL THREESCORE THOUSAND</pattern><template>That's five to one.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS AS EASY FOR ME  KATE  TO CONQUER THE KINGDOM</pattern><template>as to speak so much more French!</template></category><category><pattern>THE DEVIL TAKE ORDER NOW</pattern><template>I'll to the throng!</template></category><category><pattern>LES ONGLES</pattern><template>Nous les appelons de nails.</template></category><category><pattern>MY LORD OF WESTMORELAND  UNCLE EXETER  WE WILL ABOARD TONIGHT</pattern><template>Why, how now, gentlemen what see you in those papers that you lose so much complexion?</template></category><category><pattern>AND GENTLEMEN IN ENGLAND NOW ABED</pattern><template>shall think themselves accursed they were not here...</template></category><category><pattern>HE SEEMS</pattern><template>indifferent, or rather swaying more upon our part.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT ENGLISH MAY AS FRENCH  FRENCH ENGLISHMEN  RECEIVE EACH OTHER</pattern><template>God speak this.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR PEACE ITSELF SHOULD NOT SO DULL A KINGDOM  BUT THE DEFENSES  MUSTERS  PREPARATIONS SHOULD BE MAINTAINED  ASSEMBLED AND COLLECTED  AS WERE A WAR IN EXPECTATION</pattern><template>Therefore, I say 'tis meet we all go forth to view...</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YOU SHOG OFF</pattern><template>Pistol, I will prick your guts a little in good terms, as I may.</template></category><category><pattern>ADIEU</pattern><template>Follow, follow.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DUKE OF GLOUCESTER  TO WHOM THE ORDER</pattern><template>of the siege is given, is altogether directed by an Irishman.</template></category><category><pattern>TO FRANCE</pattern><template>Thus comes the English...</template></category><category><pattern>SO CHRIST SAVE ME  I WILL CUT OFF YOUR HEAD</pattern><template>How yet resolves the governor of the town?</template></category><category><pattern>WITHSTANDING THE POOR AND UNTEMPERING EFFECT OF MY VIS NOW BESHREW MY FATHER'S AMBITION</pattern><template>He was thinking of civil wars when he got me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND PLEAD HIS LOVE SUIT TO HER GENTLE HEART</pattern><template>Your majesty shall mock at me.</template></category><category><pattern>LET HIM DEPART</pattern><template>His passport shall be made...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE POWER ENOUGH</pattern><template>And in a captive chariot into Rouen bring him our prisoner.</template></category><category><pattern>IN CONSTANT RESOLUTION</pattern><template>Well, 'tis not so, my lord high constable.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER WAS MONARCH BETTER FEARED AND LOVED THAN IS YOUR MAJESTY</pattern><template>We therefore have great cause of thankfulness.</template></category><category><pattern>WITNESS OUR TOO MUCH MEMORABLE SHAME</pattern><template>when cressy battle fatally was struck...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I CANNOT TELL WHAT ISBAISERIN ENGLISH</pattern><template>To kiss?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS THE NUMBER OF OUR ENGLISH DEAD</pattern><template>Edward, the duke of York,  the earl of Suffolk,  Sir Richard Ketly, Davy Gam, esquire.  None else of name...</template></category><category><pattern>AYE  SO PLEASE YOUR MAJESTY</pattern><template>The duke of Exeter hath very gallantly maintained the bridge.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL THE CONSTABLE</pattern><template>I shall, king Harry.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE  RICHARD EARL OF CAMBRIDGE  AND THE SECOND  HENRY LORD SCROOP OF MASHAM  AND THE THIRD  SIR THOMAS GREY  KNIGHT  OF NORTHUMBERLAND  HAVE FOR THE GILT OF FRANCE</pattern><template>oh, guilt indeed...</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW NO WAYS TO MINCE IT IN LOVE  BUT DIRECTLY TO SAY   I LOVE YOU   THEN  IF YOU URGE ME FARTHER THAN TO SAY   DO YOU IN FAITH   I WEAR OUT MY SUIT</pattern><template>Give me your answer... i'faith do... and so clap hands and a bargain. How say you, lady?</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS THE BEST HORSE OF EUROPE</pattern><template>Will it never be morning?</template></category><category><pattern>NO DOUBT  MY LIEGE  IF EACH MAN DO HIS BEST  I DOUBT NOT THAT</pattern><template>Never was monarch better feared and loved than is your majesty.</template></category><category><pattern>NAY  IT SHALL PLEASE HIM WELL  KATE</pattern><template>It shall please him, Kate.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE GOD  HIS GRACE IS BOLD TO TRUST THESE TRAITORS</pattern><template>They shall be apprehended by and by.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL NEVER TRUST HIS WORD AFTER</pattern><template>Come. 'tis a foolish saying.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS MY NATION</pattern><template>Who talks of my nation is a villain...</template></category><category><pattern>AND HIDES A SWORD  FROM HILTS UNTO THE POINT  WITH CROWNS IMPERIAL  CROWNS AND CORONETS</pattern><template>promised to Harry and his followers.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS HEART IS FRACTED AND    CORROBORATE</pattern><template>The king's a good king, but it must be as it may.</template></category><category><pattern>LET HOUSEWIFERY APPEAR</pattern><template>Keep close.</template></category><category><pattern>I CARE NOT WHO KNOW IT</pattern><template>I shall confess it to all the world!</template></category><category><pattern>TWIN BORN WITH GREATNESS  SUBJECT TO THE BREATH OF EVERY FOOL</pattern><template>What infinite heart's ease must kings neglect...</template></category><category><pattern>UNNATURAL</pattern><template>And my speech entreats that I may know...</template></category><category><pattern>THE FRENCH ARE BRAVELY IN THEIR BATTLE SET</pattern><template>and will with all expedience march upon us!</template></category><category><pattern>TSK</pattern><template>Old do I wax, and from my weary limbs honor is cudgeled.</template></category><category><pattern>HE PASSES SOME HUMORS AND CAREERS</pattern><template>Let us condole the knight, for, lambkins, we will live.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD HAVE MERCY  OLD HEART</pattern><template>Thou speakest cheerfully.</template></category><category><pattern>YET KEEP THE FRENCH THE FIELD</pattern><template>Kill the boys and the luggage.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE WOULD NOT WISH HIMSELF ANYWHERE BUT WHERE HE IS</pattern><template>Then I would he were here alone.</template></category><category><pattern>AND OF WOMEN</pattern><template>No, that he did not.</template></category><category><pattern>COME YOU FROM THE BRIDGE</pattern><template>Is the duke of Exeter safe?</template></category><category><pattern>OUI  SAUF VOTRE HONNEUR  EN VERITE  VOUS PRONONCEZ LES MOTS AUSSI DROIT QUE LES NATIFS D'ANGLETERRE</pattern><template>Je ne doute point d'apprendre par la grace de dieu, et en peu de temps.</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  TO OUR BEST MERCY GIVE YOURSELVES  OR  LIKE TO MEN PROUD OF DESTRUCTION  DEFY US TO OUR WORST</pattern><template>For as I am a soldier, if I begin the battery once again, I will not leave the half achieved Harflew...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MEAN AND GENTLE ALL</pattern><template>behold, as may unworthiness define, a little touch of Harry in the night.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  KATE</pattern><template>Nice customs curtsy to great kings.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS MONTJOY  THE HERALD</pattern><template>Speed him hence.</template></category><category><pattern>I CANNOT TELL WHAT IS THAT</pattern><template>No, kate?</template></category><category><pattern>LE DOIGTS  DE FINGRES</pattern><template>Mm hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>MY MOST REDOUBTED FATHER  IT IS MOST MEET WE ARM US AGAINST THE FOE</pattern><template>For peace itself should not so dull a kingdom, but the defenses, musters, preparations should be maintained, assembled and collected, as were a war in expectation.</template></category><category><pattern>Y YOUR MAJESTY SAYS VERY TRUE</pattern><template>If your majesty is remembered of it, the Welshmen did good service in a garden where leeks did grow, wearing leeks in their Monmouth caps, which, as your majesty know, to this hour is an honorable badge of service.</template></category><category><pattern>BY YOUR OWN COUNSEL IS SUPPRESSED AND KILLED</pattern><template>You must not dare for shame to talk of mercy!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT FEATS HE DID THAT DAY</pattern><template>Then shall our names, familiar in their mouths as household words...</template></category><category><pattern>IF THOU WOULD HAVE SUCH A ONE  TAKE ME</pattern><template>And take me, take a soldier.</template></category><category><pattern>SO GET YOU HENCE IN PEACE  AND TELL THE DAUPHIN</pattern><template>his jest... will savor but of shallow wit...</template></category><category><pattern>LIVED WELL AND IN GOOD COMPASS</pattern><template>What? You were so fat, Sir John, that you must indeed be out of all compass.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS NOT ANGRY SINCE I CAME TO FRANCE</pattern><template>Until this instant!</template></category><category><pattern>SHOULD NOT IN THIS BEST GARDEN OF THE WORLD  OUR FERTILE FRANCE  PUT UP HER LOVELY VISAGE</pattern><template>Alas, she hath from France too long been chased, and all her husbandry doth lie on heaps, corrupting in its own fertility.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  MY CONSCIENCE</pattern><template>He did us great good.</template></category><category><pattern>THOUGH ALL THAT I CAN DO</pattern><template>is nothing worth...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW YET RESOLVES THE GOVERNOR OF THE TOWN</pattern><template>This is the latest parle we will admit.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I NEED NOT BE ASHAMED OF YOUR MAJESTY  PRAISED BE GOD  SO LONG AS YOUR MAJESTY IS AN HONEST MAN</pattern><template>God keep me so.</template></category><category><pattern>SWORE A LITTLE</pattern><template>Diced not above seven days a week.</template></category><category><pattern>DO ALL EXPECT THAT YOU SHOULD ROUSE YOURSELF</pattern><template>as did the former lions of your blood.</template></category><category><pattern>LA MAIN</pattern><template>Elle est appelee de  hand.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU  PRINCE DAUPHIN</pattern><template>My most redoubted father, it is most meet we arm us against the foe.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BY MY TROTH  NOT LONG</pattern><template>For we can't lodge or board a dozen or 14 gentlewomen...</template></category><category><pattern>HIS BLEEDING SWORD</pattern><template>'twixt England and fair France.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR GRANDFATHER OF FAMOUS MEMORY  AN'T PLEASE YOUR MAJESTY  AND YOUR GREAT UNCLE  EDWARD  THE BLACK PRINCE OF WALES  AS I HAVE READ IN THE CHRONICLES  FOUGHT A MOST BRAVE BATTLE HERE IN FRANCE</pattern><template>They did, Fluellen.</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE MY PENITENCE COMES  AFTER ALL  IMPLORING PARDON</pattern><template>My liege!</template></category><category><pattern>DO BREAK THE CLOUDS</pattern><template>What say you?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT SWEET JACK FALSTAFF  ALIANT JACK FALSTAFF  AND THEREFORE MORE VALIANT BEING AS HE IS  OLD JACK FALSTAFF  BANISH NOT HIM THY HARRY'S COMPANY</pattern><template>Banish plump Jack, and banish all the world.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THOSE SUNS OR STARS ON IT</pattern><template>Stars, Montjoy.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YET MY SKY SHALL NOT WANT</pattern><template>Will it never be day?</template></category><category><pattern>AN OATH OF MICKLE MIGHT  AND FURY SHALL ABATE</pattern><template>My host Pistol!</template></category><category><pattern>AND BE IT DEATH PROCLAIMED THROUGH OUR HOST</pattern><template>to boast of this...</template></category><category><pattern>BY CHESHU  I THINK HE WILL BLOW UP ALL  IF THERE IS NOT BETTER DIRECTION</pattern><template>The duke of Gloucester, to whom the order...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THY NAME</pattern><template>Uh, Harry Le Roy.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN CALL WE THIS</pattern><template>the field of Agincourt...</template></category><category><pattern>CONFIRMED CONSPIRACY WITH FEARFUL FRANCE  AND BY THEIR HANDS THIS GRACE OF KINGS MUST DIE  ERE HE TAKE SHIP FOR FRANCE</pattern><template>The traitors are agreed.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  LORDS  FOR FRANCE  THE ENTERPRISE WHEREOF SHALL BE TO YOU  AS US  LIKE GLORIOUS  SINCE GOD SO GRACIOUSLY HATH BROUGHT TO LIGHT THIS DANGEROUS TREASON LURKING IN OUR WAY</pattern><template>Cheerly to sea.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY HURT IN THE WORLD  BUT KEEPS THE BRIDGE MOST VALIANTLY  WITH EXCELLENT DISCIPLINE</pattern><template>Captain! I thee beseech to do me favors.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL THE DUKE IT IS NOT SO GOOD TO COME TO THE MINES</pattern><template>For look you, the mines is not according to the disciplines of war.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BORROWED GLORIES THAT BY GIFT OF HEAVEN  BY LAW OF NATURE AND OF NATIONS  BELONGS TO HIM AND TO HIS HEIRS</pattern><template>Namely, the crown.</template></category><category><pattern>RECEIVED THE GOLDEN EARNEST OF OUR DEATH WHEREIN</pattern><template>You would have sold your king to slaughter, his princes and his peers to servitude, his subjects to oppression and contempt...</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE MASS  ERE THESE EYES OF MINE TAKE THEMSELVES TO SLUMBER  I'LL DO GOOD SERVICE  OR I'LL LIE IN THE GROUND FOR IT</pattern><template>Captain Macmorris, I think, look you, under your correction, there are not many of your nation.</template></category><category><pattern>BAR HARRY ENGLAND  THAT SWEEPS THROUGH OUR LAND</pattern><template>with pennons painted in the blood of Harflew.</template></category><category><pattern>OR  GUILTY IN DEFENSE  BE THUS DESTROYED</pattern><template>The Dauphin, of whose succor we entreated, returns us that his powers are not yet ready to raise so great a siege.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOSE CONDEMNATION IS PRONOUNCED   SO FAR MY KING AND MASTER  SO MUCH MY OFFICE</pattern><template>What is thy name?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE YOU  MY PRINCES AND MY NOBLE PEERS  THESE ENGLISH MONSTERS</pattern><template>What shall I say to thee, Lord Scroop, thou cruel, ingrateful, savage and inhuman creature?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IT BE  BUT WE HAVE NO GREAT CAUSE TO DESIRE THE APPROACH OF DAY</pattern><template>We see yonder the beginning of the day, but I think we shall never see the end of it.</template></category><category><pattern>COME  YOUR ANSWER IN BROKEN MUSIC  FOR THY VOICE IS MUSIC  AND THY ENGLISH  BROKEN</pattern><template>Therefore, queen of all, Katherine, wilt thou have me?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S FIVE TO ONE</pattern><template>Besides, they are all fresh.</template></category><category><pattern>STEED THREATENS STEED IN HIGH AND BOASTFUL NEIGHS  PIERCING THE NIGHT'S DULL EAR</pattern><template>And from the tents, the armorers, accomplishing the knights, with busy hammers closing rivets up give dreadful note of preparation.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WAS A ROYAL FELLOWSHIP OF DEATH</pattern><template>Where is the number of our English dead?</template></category><category><pattern>AINSI DIS JE: D'ELBOW  DE NICK  ETDE CHIN</pattern><template>Oh.</template></category><category><pattern>HE COULD NEVER ABIDE CARNATION</pattern><template>It was a color he never liked.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THOU CANST LOVE A FELLOW OF THIS TEMPER  KATE  THAT NEVER LOOKS IN HIS GLASS FOR LOVE OF ANYTHING HE SEES THERE  LET THINE EYE BE THY COOK</pattern><template>I speak to thee plain soldier. If thou canst love me for this, take me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MERCY THAT WAS QUICK IN US OF LATE</pattern><template>by your own counsel is suppressed and killed.</template></category><category><pattern>NAY  SURE  HE'S NOT IN HELL</pattern><template>He's in Arthur's bosom, if ever a man went to Arthur's bosom.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  YOU SHOW GREAT MERCY IF YOU GIVE HIM LIFE</pattern><template>after the taste of much correction.</template></category><category><pattern>WE THEREFORE HAVE GREAT CAUSE OF THANKFULNESS</pattern><template>Uncle of Exeter, enlarge the man committed yesterday...</template></category><category><pattern>AND SAY   THESE WOUNDS I HAD ON CRISPIN'S DAY   OLD MEN FORGET  YET ALL SHALL BE FORGOT BUT HE'LL REMEMBER WITH ADVANTAGES</pattern><template>what feats he did that day.</template></category><category><pattern>COME  SHALL WE ABOUT IT</pattern><template>It is now 2:00.</template></category><category><pattern>GO DOWN UPON HIM</pattern><template>You have power enough.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST COME TO MY MASTER  AND YOU  HOSTESS</pattern><template>He's very sick and would to bed.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN CRESSY BATTLE FATALLY WAS STRUCK</pattern><template>and all our princes captived...</template></category><category><pattern>THE FIELD OF AGINCOURT</pattern><template>fought on the day of Crispin Crispianus.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS HIS CLAIM  HIS THREATENING AND MY MESSAGE</pattern><template>Unless the Dauphin be in presence here, to whom expressly I bring greeting to.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SILKEN DALLIANCE IN THE WARDROBE LIES</pattern><template>For now sits expectation in the air...</template></category><category><pattern>UH  OH</pattern><template>Donc, uh, votre est france...</template></category><category><pattern>PISTOL  I WILL PRICK YOUR GUTS A LITTLE IN GOOD TERMS  AS I MAY</pattern><template>That's the humor of it.</template></category><category><pattern>AS GOOD A GENTLEMAN AS THE EMPEROR</pattern><template>Ah, then you are a better than the king.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT NOTHING DO BUT MEDITATE ON BLOOD</pattern><template>to swearing and stern looks, diffused attire, and everything that seems...</template></category><category><pattern>NOW IS IT TIME TO ARM</pattern><template>Come, shall we about it?</template></category><category><pattern>FOR HE IS BRED OUT OF THAT BLOODY STRAIN</pattern><template>that haunted us in our familiar paths.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE COMES THE HERALD OF THE FRENCH  MY LIEGE</pattern><template>What means this, herald?</template></category><category><pattern>OUR BENDING AUTHOR HATH PURSUED THE STORY</pattern><template>in little room confining mighty men...</template></category><category><pattern>COME</pattern><template>Go we in procession to the village...</template></category><category><pattern>THE DAY IS YOURS</pattern><template>Praised be god...</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THE KING IS BUT A MAN AS I AM</pattern><template>The violet smells to him as it doth to me.</template></category><category><pattern>LET HIM CRY   PRAISE AND GLORY ON HIS HEAD   FOR FORTH HE GOES AND VISITS ALL HIS HOST</pattern><template>Bids them good morrow with a modest smile...</template></category><category><pattern>DE CHIN   LE COL  DE NICK</pattern><template>Le menton, de chin.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR WHO IS HE WHOSE CHIN IS BUT ENRICHED WITH ONE APPEARING HAIR</pattern><template>that will not follow these culled and choice drawn cavaliers...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT HE DID NOT</pattern><template>Yeah, that he did.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE UNDERSTAND HIM WELL  HOW HE COMES O'ER US WITH OUR WILDER DAYS  NOT MEASURING WHAT USE WE MADE OF THEM</pattern><template>But tell the Dauphin I will keep my state, be like a king and show my sail of greatness...</template></category><category><pattern>AND BUXOM VALOR  HATH BY CRUEL FATE AND GIDDY FORTUNE'S FURIOUS  FICKLE WHEEL</pattern><template>Touching your patience, Ancient Pistol, fortune is an excellent moral.</template></category><category><pattern>FILLS THE WIDE VESSEL OF THE UNIVERSE</pattern><template>From camp to camp through the foul womb of night...</template></category><category><pattern>AND OF IT LEFT HIS SON IMPERIAL LORD</pattern><template>Henry the sixth, in infant bands crowned king of France and England did this king succeed...</template></category><category><pattern>BROTHERS BOTH  COMMEND ME TO THE PRINCES IN OUR CAMP</pattern><template>Do my good morrow to them, and anon desire them all to my pavilion.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THINGS ARE READY IF OUR MINDS BE SO</pattern><template>Perish the man whose mind is backward now.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS NOW 2:00</pattern><template>But let me see, by 10:00, we shall have each a hundred Englishmen.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I DO BELIEVE YOUR MAJESTY TAKES NO SCORN</pattern><template>to wear the leek upon St. Davy's day.</template></category><category><pattern>I TELL THEE TRULY  HERALD  I KNOW NOT IF THE DAY BE OURS OR NO</pattern><template>The day is yours.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AT HIS HEELS  LEASHED IN LIKE HOUNDS  SHOULD FAMINE  SWORD AND FIRE CROUCH FOR EMPLOYMENT</pattern><template>But pardon, gentles all, the flat, unraised spirits...</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS THINKING OF CIVIL WARS WHEN HE GOT ME</pattern><template>Therefore was I created with a stubborn outside, with an aspect of iron, that when I come to woo ladies, I fright them.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THIS DEAR CONJUNCTION</pattern><template>plant neighborhood...</template></category><category><pattern>MAY CEASE THEIR HATRED</pattern><template>and this dear conjunction...</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID IT WAS A BLACK SOUL BURNING IN HELL</pattern><template>Well, the fuel is gone that maintained that fire.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DAUPHIN  OF WHOSE SUCCOR WE ENTREATED  RETURNS US THAT HIS POWERS ARE NOT YET READY TO RAISE SO GREAT A SIEGE</pattern><template>Therefore, dread king, enter our gates, dispose of us and ours, for we no longer are defensible.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN THIS COCKPIT HOLD THE VASTY FIELDS OF FRANCE OR MAY WE CRAM WITHIN THIS WOODEN  O</pattern><template>the very casques that did affright the air at Agincourt?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  BY THIS HAND  I SWEAR I SCORN THE TERM</pattern><template>Nor shall my Nell keep lodgers!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  MAN</pattern><template>Be of good cheer.  So he cried out,  God, God, God,  Three or four times.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR GAYNESS AND OUR GILT ARE ALL BESMIRCHED</pattern><template>with rainy marching in the painful field, but by the mass, our hearts are in the trim.</template></category><category><pattern>AND CROWNS FOR CONVOY PUT INTO HIS PURSE</pattern><template>We would not die in that man's company...</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE HER  FAIR SON  AND FROM HER BLOOD RAISE UP ISSUE TO ME</pattern><template>that the contending kingdoms of France and England...</template></category><category><pattern>IN ANSWER OF WHICH CLAIM  THE PRINCE  MY MASTER  SAYS THAT YOU SAVOR TOO MUCH OF YOUR YOUTH</pattern><template>He therefore sends you, meeter for your spirit, this tun of treasure.</template></category><category><pattern>AND FROM THE TENTS  THE ARMORERS  ACCOMPLISHING THE KNIGHTS  WITH BUSY HAMMERS CLOSING RIVETS UP GIVE DREADFUL NOTE OF PREPARATION</pattern><template>Proud of their numbers and secure in soul, the confident and over lusty French...</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE FROM THEM NOW THEIR SENSE OF RECKONING</pattern><template>if the opposed numbers pluck their hearts from them.</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN  I THEE BESEECH TO DO ME FAVORS</pattern><template>The duke of Exeter doth love thee well.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEN HE WAS RHEUMATIC AND TALKED OF THE WHORE OF BABYLON</pattern><template>Do you not remember he saw a flea stick upon Bardolph's nose?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE HUMOR OF IT</pattern><template>But...</template></category><category><pattern>STIFFEN THE SINEWS  SUMMON UP THE BLOOD  DISGUISE FAIR NATURE WITH HARD FAVORED RAGE</pattern><template>Then lend the eye a terrible aspect.</template></category><category><pattern>I AND MY BOSOM MUST DEBATE A WHILE  AND THEN I WOULD NO OTHER COMPANY</pattern><template>The lord in heaven bless thee, noble Harry.</template></category><category><pattern>MY LORD  MOST HUMBLY ON MY KNEE  I BEG THE LEADING OF THE VAWARD</pattern><template>Take it, brave York.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR HOW CAN THEY CHARITABLY DISPOSE OF ANYTHING</pattern><template>when blood is their argument?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS THE POINT  IT IS NO TIME TO DISCOURSE  SO CHRIST SAVE ME</pattern><template>The town is besieged, and the trumpet calls us to the breach.</template></category><category><pattern>AMBASSADORS FROM HARRY  KING OF ENGLAND  DO CRAVE ADMITTANCE TO YOUR MAJESTY</pattern><template>Go and bring them.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW SET THE TEETH AND STRETCH THE NOSTRIL WIDE  HOLD HARD THE BREATH AND BEND UP EVERY SPIRIT TO HIS FULL HEIGHT</pattern><template>On, on, you noblest England!</template></category><category><pattern>BY MINE HONOR  IN TRUE ENGLISH  I SWEAR I LOVE THEE  BY WHICH HONOR I DARE NOT SWEAR THOU LOVEST ME</pattern><template>Yet my blood begins to flatter me that thou dost...</template></category><category><pattern>SO TELL YOUR MASTER</pattern><template>I shall deliver so.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THE DUKE HATH LOST NEVER A MAN</pattern><template>but one that is like to be executed for robbing a church.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT TODAY  O GOD  OH  NOT TODAY</pattern><template>Think not upon the fault my father made encompassing the crown.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE NIMBLE GUNNER WITH LINSTOCK NOW THE DEVILISH CANNON TOUCHES  AND DOWN GOES ALL BEFORE THEM</pattern><template>Once more unto the breach, dear friends!</template></category><category><pattern>LES DOIGTS</pattern><template>Je pense qu'ils sont appeles  de fingres.  Le main, de hand.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IT IS MOST LAMENTABLE TO BEHOLD</pattern><template>Sweet men, come to him.</template></category><category><pattern>I SHALL  KING HARRY</pattern><template>And so fare thee well.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DUKE OF EXETER HATH VERY GALLANTLY MAINTAINED THE BRIDGE</pattern><template>What men have you lost?</template></category><category><pattern>MANGLING BY STARTS THE FULL COURSE OF THEIR GLORY</pattern><template>Small time, but in that small most greatly lived...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THOUGH THE TRUTH OF IT STAND OFF AS GROSS AS BLACK AND WHITE  MY EYE WILL SCARCELY SEE IT</pattern><template>So... constant and unspotted didst thou seem...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  BAWD I'LL TURN</pattern><template>and something lean to cutpurse of quick hand.</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE THAT MY OFFICE HATH SO FAR PREVAILED  THAT FACE TO FACE AND ROYAL EYE TO EYE YOU HAVE CONGREETED</pattern><template>let it not disgrace me if I demand before this royal view...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT DIE IN A BATTLE</pattern><template>for how can they charitably dispose of anything...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT    TREASURE  UNCLE</pattern><template>Tennis balls, my liege.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK YOU  IF YOU TAKE THE MATTER OTHERWISE THAN IT IS MEANT  CAPTAIN MACMORRIS  PERADVENTURE I SHALL THINK YOU DO NOT USE ME</pattern><template>with that affability as in discretion you ought to use me, now look you, being as good a man as yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THE FUEL IS GONE THAT MAINTAINED THAT FIRE</pattern><template>That's all the riches I got in his service.</template></category><category><pattern>YET LEAVE OUR COUSIN KATHERINE</pattern><template>here with us.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR ACCEPT AND PEREMPTORY ANSWER</pattern><template>Brother, we shall.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM A HAWK  AND HE IS PURE AIR AND FIRE</pattern><template>The dull elements of earth and water never appear in him, but only impatient stillness while his rider mounts him.</template></category><category><pattern>SWEATS IN THE EYE OF PHOEBUS</pattern><template>and all night sleeps...</template></category><category><pattern>LET IT PRY THROUGH THE PORTAGE OF THE HEAD LIKE THE BRASS CANNON</pattern><template>Let the brow o'erwhelm it as fearfully as doth a galled rock...</template></category><category><pattern>BID THEM MARCH AWAY</pattern><template>Now entertain conjecture of a time...</template></category><category><pattern>BESIDES  THERE IS NO KING  BE HIS CAUSE NEVER SO SPOTLESS  CAN TRY IT OUT WITH ALL UNSPOTTED SOLDIERS</pattern><template>Every subject's duty is the king's, but every subject's soul is his own.</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  QUEEN OF ALL  KATHERINE  WILT THOU HAVE ME</pattern><template>That is as it shall please le roi mon pere.</template></category><category><pattern>AND FIGO FOR THY FRIENDSHIP</pattern><template>How now, Fluellen, comest thou from the bridge?</template></category><category><pattern>UNCLE OF EXETER  ENLARGE THE MAN COMMITTED YESTERDAY</pattern><template>that railed against our person.</template></category><category><pattern>LET THE BROW O'ERWHELM IT AS FEARFULLY AS DOTH A GALLED ROCK</pattern><template>o'erhang and jetty his confounded base, swilled with the wild and wasteful ocean.</template></category><category><pattern>MORE WILL I DO</pattern><template>though all that I can do...</template></category><category><pattern>AYE  CAPTAIN  BUT WITH THIS ACKNOWLEDGEMENT: THAT GOD FOUGHT</pattern><template>for us.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD GOD  WHY SHOULD THEY MOCK POOR FELLOWS THUS</pattern><template>Let me speak proudly.</template></category><category><pattern>ALICE  TU AS ETE EN ANGLETERRE  ET TU PARLES BIEN LE LANGAGE</pattern><template>Un peu, madame.</template></category><category><pattern>DISCIPLINE OUGHT TO BE USED</pattern><template>Then die and be damned...</template></category><category><pattern>DE TOUS LES MOTS QUE VOUS M'AVEZ APPRIS DES A PRESENT</pattern><template>Il est trop difficile, madame, comme je pense.</template></category><category><pattern>OR ART THOU BASE  COMMON AND POPULAR</pattern><template>I am a gentleman of a company.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  MY FAIR COUSIN</pattern><template>If we are marked to die, we are enough to do our country loss.</template></category><category><pattern>OF THE LAST KING'S REIGN WAS LIKE TO HAVE PASSED AGAINST US</pattern><template>But how, my lord, shall we resist it now?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WITH PALE POLICY SEEK TO DIVERT THE ENGLISH PURPOSES</pattern><template>Oh, England, model to thy inward greatness.</template></category><category><pattern>TO BOAST OF THIS</pattern><template>or take that praise from God which is his only.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY THAT THE NAKED  POOR AND MANGLED PEACE</pattern><template>should not in this best garden of the world, our fertile France, put up her lovely visage?</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS  GOOD MY COUNTRYMAN</pattern><template>By jeshu, I am your majesty's countryman!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WOULD ASCEND THE BRIGHTEST HEAVEN OF INVENTION</pattern><template>A kingdom for a stage, princes to act...</template></category><category><pattern>IF NOT  WHY  IN A MOMENT LOOK TO SEE</pattern><template>the blind and bloody soldier with foul hand...</template></category><category><pattern>AND PLAY WITH FLOWERS AND SMILE UPON HIS FINGER'S ENDS  I KNEW THERE WAS BUT ONE WAY</pattern><template>For his nose was as sharp as a pen, and he babbled of green fields.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE FRENCH QUARRELS ENOUGH</pattern><template>Upon the king.</template></category><category><pattern>I THANK YOU</pattern><template>God be with you.</template></category><category><pattern>DE CHIN</pattern><template>De chin.  Le col, de nick.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR US  DEAR UNCLE  THE WINTER COMING ON</pattern><template>and sickness growing upon our soldiers, we will retire to Calais.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HUM OF EITHER ARMY STILLY SOUNDS</pattern><template>that the fixed sentinels almost receive...</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU NOT REMEMBER HE SAW A FLEA STICK UPON BARDOLPH'S NOSE</pattern><template>He said it was a black soul burning in hell.</template></category><category><pattern>OF THE WHICH FIVE HUNDRED</pattern><template>were but yesterday dubbed knights.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SHALL BE APPREHENDED BY AND BY</pattern><template>How smooth and even they do bear themselves, as if allegiance in their bosoms sat crowned with faith and constant loyalty.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  ARE YOU AND ANCIENT PISTOL FRIENDS YET</pattern><template>For my part, I care not.</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS NOT THE BALM  THE SCEPTER AND THE BALL  THE SWORD  THE MACE  THE CROWN IMPERIAL  THE INTERTISSUED ROBE OF GOLD AND PEARL  THE FARCED TITLE RUNNING FORE THE KING  THE THRONE HE SITS ON</pattern><template>nor the tide of pomp...</template></category><category><pattern>THE DUKE OF GLOUCESTER WOULD SPEAK WITH YOU</pattern><template>Tell the duke it is not so good to come to the mines.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT  WHEN THOU ART KING  HANG A THIEF</pattern><template>No, thou shalt.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN SHALL OUR NAMES  FAMILIAR IN THEIR MOUTHS AS HOUSEHOLD WORDS</pattern><template>Harry the king, Bedford and Exeter, Warwick and Talbot, Salisbury and Gloucester...</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS SO STRANGE</pattern><template>that though the truth of it stand off as gross as black and white, my eye will scarcely see it.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE REMAIN AND FORTIFY IT STRONGLY AGAINST THE FRENCH</pattern><template>Use... mercy to them all.</template></category><category><pattern>D'ELBOW</pattern><template>D'elbow.  Je m'en fais la repetition...</template></category><category><pattern>DISCUSS UNTO ME</pattern><template>Art thou officer...</template></category><category><pattern>THE DULL ELEMENTS OF EARTH AND WATER NEVER APPEAR IN HIM  BUT ONLY IMPATIENT STILLNESS WHILE HIS RIDER MOUNTS HIM</pattern><template>Indeed, my lord, it is a most absolute and excellent horse.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR AS I AM A SOLDIER  IF I BEGIN THE BATTERY ONCE AGAIN  I WILL NOT LEAVE THE HALF ACHIEVED HARFLEW</pattern><template>till in her ashes she lie buried.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SELF BILL IS URGED  WHICH  IN THE 11TH YEAR</pattern><template>of the last king's reign was like to have passed against us.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  BE SICK  GREAT GREATNESS  AND BID THY CEREMONY GIVE THEE CURE</pattern><template>Canst thou, when thou commandest the beggar's knee, command the health of it?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT LET ME SEE  BY 10:00  WE SHALL HAVE EACH A HUNDRED ENGLISHMEN</pattern><template>The poor, condemned English, like sacrifices, by their watchful fires sit patiently...</template></category><category><pattern>FAIRLY MET</pattern><template>So are you, princes English, every one.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WE MAY WANDER O'ER THIS BLOODY FIELD TO BOOK OUR DEAD</pattern><template>and then to bury them.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE HE COMES  AND THE SCOTS CAPTAIN  CAPTAIN JAMY  WITH HIM</pattern><template>Oh, no, Captain Jamy is a marvelous, valorous gentleman, that is certain.</template></category><category><pattern>JE NE VOUDRAIS PRONONCER CES MOTS DEVANTS LES SEIGNEURS DE FRANCE POUR TOUT LE MONDE</pattern><template>De footet 'le coun!</template></category><category><pattern>IS THE DUKE OF EXETER SAFE</pattern><template>De is not...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  LET US YET BE MERCIFUL</pattern><template>So may your highness, and yet punish too.</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE HIS ADDICTION WAS TO COURSES VAIN  HIS HOURS FILLED UP WITH RIOTS  BANQUETS  SPORTS AND NEVER NOTED IN HIM ANY STUDY</pattern><template>But, my good lord, how now for the mitigation...</template></category><category><pattern>BETWEEN THE FLOODS OF SALA AND OF ELBE</pattern><template>Then doth it well appear the Salique law...</template></category><category><pattern>USE    MERCY TO THEM ALL</pattern><template>For us, dear uncle, the winter coming on...</template></category><category><pattern>HE HATH PASSED THE RIVER SOMME</pattern><template>And if he be not fought withal, my lord, let us not live in France.</template></category><category><pattern>FAREWELL  HOSTESS</pattern><template>I cannot kiss.</template></category><category><pattern>DEFILE THE LOCKS OF YOUR SHRILL  SHRIEKING DAUGHTERS  YOUR FATHERS TAKEN BY THEIR SILVERED BEARDS</pattern><template>and their most reverend heads dashed to the walls, your naked infants spitted upon pikes...</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM WE COULD HAVE REBUKED HIM AT HARFLEW</pattern><template>Now we speak, and our voice is imperial.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD SPEAK THIS</pattern><template>Amen.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER THE TASTE OF MUCH CORRECTION</pattern><template>Alas, your too much love and care of me...</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  WHEN HE SEES REASON TO FEAR  AS WE DO  HIS FEARS  OUT OF DOUBT  BE OF THE SAME RELISH AS OURS ARE</pattern><template>He may show what outward courage he will, but I believe as cold a night as 'tis...</template></category><category><pattern>MMM  IF TO BE OLD AND MERRY IS A SIN  IF TO BE FAT IS TO BE HATED  THEN NO  MY GOOD LORD  WHEN THOU ART KING  BANISH PISTOL  BANISH BARDOLPH  BANISH NYM</pattern><template>But sweet Jack Falstaff, Aliant Jack Falstaff, and therefore more valiant being as he is, old Jack Falstaff, banish not him thy Harry's company.</template></category><category><pattern>COME THOU NO MORE FOR RANSOM  GENTLE HERALD</pattern><template>They shall have none, I swear, but these my joints!</template></category><category><pattern>KNOWEST THOU FLUELLEN</pattern><template>Aye.</template></category><category><pattern>YET THEIR OWN AUTHORS FAITHFULLY AFFIRM</pattern><template>that the land Salique lies in Germany...</template></category><category><pattern>NORMAN    BASTARDS</pattern><template>Where have they this mettle is not their climate foggy, raw and dull?</template></category><category><pattern>HE THAT OUTLIVES THIS DAY AND COMES SAFE HOME</pattern><template>will stand at tiptoe when this day is named...</template></category><category><pattern>PRAISED BE GOD</pattern><template>and not our strength for it.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAY LITTLE  BUT WHEN TIME SHALL SERVE  THERE SHALL BE SMILES</pattern><template>But that shall be as it may.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  GREAT KING</pattern><template>I come to thee for charitable license...</template></category><category><pattern>COMMENT APPELEZ VOUS LE PIED ET LA ROBE</pattern><template>De foot, madame, et de coun.</template></category><category><pattern>MORE HAPPY MEN</pattern><template>~ Non nobis domine, domine ~ ~ non nobis domine ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ tuo da gloriam ~ ~ Non nobis domine, domine ~ ~ non nobis domine ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ tuo da gloriam ~ ~ non nobis domine, domine ~ ~ non nobis domine ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ tuo da gloriam ~ ~ non nobis domine ~ ~ non nobis domine ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ tuo da gloriam ~ ~ non nobis domine, domine ~ ~ non nobis domine ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ tuo da gloriam ~ ~ non nobis domine, domine ~ ~ non nobis domine ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ tuo da gloriam ~ ~ non nobis domine, domine ~ ~ non nobis domine ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ sed nomeni ~ ~ tuo da gloriam ~ ~ tuo da ~ ~ gloriam ~ Peace to this meeting.</template></category><category><pattern>TO WEAR THE LEEK UPON ST  DAVY'S DAY</pattern><template>I wear it for a memorable honor, for I am Welsh, you know, good my countryman.</template></category><category><pattern>METHINKS I COULD NOT DIE ANYWHERE SO CONTENTED</pattern><template>as in the king's company, his cause being just and his quarrel honorable.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE A SOLDIER  TAKE A KING</pattern><template>And what sayest thou then to my love?</template></category><category><pattern>I SHALL DELIVER SO</pattern><template>Thanks to your majesty.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THE CONTENDING KINGDOMS OF FRANCE AND ENGLAND</pattern><template>whose very shores look pale with envy of each other's happiness...</template></category><category><pattern>IL N'EST PAS LA COUTUME DE FRANCE</pattern><template>Madame my interpreter, what says she?</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS WONDERFUL</pattern><template>Come.</template></category><category><pattern>BID THEM ACHIEVE ME AND THEN SELL MY BONES</pattern><template>Good god, why should they mock poor fellows thus?</template></category><category><pattern>O GOD OF BATTLES  STEEL MY SOLDIERS' HEARTS</pattern><template>Possess them not with fear.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS</pattern><template>The days that we have seen.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT FEARS HIS FELLOWSHIP TO DIE WITH US</pattern><template>This day is called the feast of Crispian.</template></category><category><pattern>MARCH TO THE BRIDGE</pattern><template>It now draws towards night.</template></category><category><pattern>BY FAITH AND HONOR  OUR MADAMS MOCK AT US AND PLAINLY SAY OUR METTLE IS BRED OUT</pattern><template>And they will give their bodies to the lust of English youth...</template></category><category><pattern>AND ON TOMORROW</pattern><template>bid them march away.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HOW  MY LORD  SHALL WE RESIST IT NOW</pattern><template>It must be thought on.</template></category><category><pattern>GO WE IN PROCESSION TO THE VILLAGE</pattern><template>and be it death proclaimed through our host...</template></category><category><pattern>HERE COMES YOUR FATHER</pattern><template>God save your majesty.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ALL THOSE LEGS AND ARMS AND HEADS</pattern><template>chopped off in the battle...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ALL THE RICHES I GOT IN HIS SERVICE</pattern><template>Whall we shog?</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE I MAY SAY   NOW LIE I LIKE A KING   LEND ME THY CLOAK  SIR THOMAS</pattern><template>Brothers both, commend me to the princes in our camp.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS AS IT SHALL PLEASE LE ROI MON PERE</pattern><template>Nay, it shall please him well, Kate.</template></category><category><pattern>COME  'TIS A FOOLISH SAYING</pattern><template>Your reproof is something too round.</template></category><category><pattern>THE VIOLET SMELLS TO HIM AS IT DOTH TO ME</pattern><template>His ceremonies laid by, in his nakedness he appears but a man.</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  LET EVERY MAN NOW TASK HIS THOUGHT</pattern><template>that this fair action may on foot be brought.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR BROTHER KINGS AND MONARCHS OF THE EARTH</pattern><template>do all expect that you should rouse yourself...</template></category><category><pattern>AND A BASTARD AND A KNAVE AND A RASCAL</pattern><template>Look you, if you take the matter otherwise than it is meant, Captain Macmorris, peradventure I shall think you do not use me...</template></category><category><pattern>DO THE LOW RATED ENGLISH PLAY AT DICE</pattern><template>and chide the cripple, tardy gaited night...</template></category><category><pattern>THEN SHOULD THE WARLIKE HARRY  LIKE HIMSELF  ASSUME THE PORT OF MARS</pattern><template>and at his heels, leashed in like hounds, should famine, sword and fire crouch for employment.</template></category><category><pattern>BE HE NE'ER SO VILE  THIS DAY SHALL GENTLE HIS CONDITION</pattern><template>And gentlemen in England now abed...</template></category><category><pattern>HIS CEREMONIES LAID BY  IN HIS NAKEDNESS HE APPEARS BUT A MAN</pattern><template>Therefore, when he sees reason to fear, as we do, his fears, out of doubt, be of the same relish as ours are.</template></category><category><pattern>VIRTUOUS ENOUGH</pattern><template>Swore a little.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR HE HATH STOLEN A PAX AND HANGED MUST HE BE</pattern><template>Therefore, go speak.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THIS FAIR ACTION MAY ON FOOT BE BROUGHT</pattern><template>Now all the youth of England are on fire...</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS NOT A THING TO REJOICE AT</pattern><template>Look you, if he were my brother, I would desire the duke to do his good pleasure...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WILL NOT FOLLOW THESE CULLED AND CHOICE DRAWN CAVALIERS</pattern><template>to France?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOSE VERY SHORES LOOK PALE WITH ENVY OF EACH OTHER'S HAPPINESS</pattern><template>may cease their hatred...</template></category><category><pattern>I PUT MY HAND UNDER THE BED AND FELT THEM  AND THEY WERE AS COLD AS ANY STONE</pattern><template>Then I felt to his knees, and so upward... and upward, and all was as...</template></category><category><pattern>HE LONGS TO EAT THE ENGLISH</pattern><template>I think he will eat all he kills.</template></category><category><pattern>UPON THE KING</pattern><template>Let us our lives, our souls, our debts, our careful wives, our children...</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  GO SPEAK</pattern><template>The duke will hear thy voice.</template></category><category><pattern>AND INLY RUMINATE THE MORNING'S DANGER</pattern><template>And their gesture sad, investing lank, lean cheeks and war worn coats, presenteth them unto the gazing moon...</template></category><category><pattern>SAUF VOTRE HONNEUR  LE FRANCAIS QUE VOUS PARLEZ</pattern><template>Il est meilleur que I'anglais lequel je parle.</template></category><category><pattern>BY THIS SWORD  HE THAT MAKES THE FIRST THRUST  I'LL KILL HIM  BY THIS SWORD  I WILL</pattern><template>If ever you come of women, come in quickly to Sir John.</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  IN FIERCE TEMPEST IS HE COMING  IN THUNDER AND IN EARTHQUAKE  LIKE A JOVE  THAT IF REQUIRING FAIL  HE WILL COMPEL</pattern><template>This is his claim, his threatening and my message.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I COULD WIN A LADY AT LEAPFROG OR BY VAULTING INTO MY SADDLE</pattern><template>with my arm around my back, I should quickly leap into a wife.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW ENTERTAIN CONJECTURE OF A TIME</pattern><template>when creeping murmur and the poring dark...</template></category><category><pattern>AND THOU SHALT WEAR ME</pattern><template>if thou wear me...</template></category><category><pattern>MOUNT THEM AND MAKE INCISION IN THEIR HIDES</pattern><template>that their hot blood may spin in English eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>MY RANSOM IS THIS FRAIL AND WORTHLESS TRUNK  MY ARMY BUT A WEAK AND SICKLY GUARD</pattern><template>Yet, God before, tell him we will come on, though France himself and such another neighbor stand in our way.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ENGLAND</pattern><template>Since that my office hath so far prevailed, that face to face and royal eye to eye you have congreeted...</template></category><category><pattern>NOR THE FATHER OF HIS SON  FOR THEY PURPOSE NOT THEIR DEATHS WHEN THEY PURPOSE THEIR SERVICES</pattern><template>Besides, there is no king, be his cause never so spotless, can try it out with all unspotted soldiers.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR IT IS YOUR THOUGHTS THAT NOW MUST DECK OUR KINGS  CARRY THEM HERE  THERE  JUMPING O'ER TIMES  TURNING THE ACCOMPLISHMENT OF MANY YEARS INTO AN HOURGLASS</pattern><template>For the which supply, admit me, chorus, to this history, who, prologue like, your humble patience pray...</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I WOULD HE WERE HERE ALONE</pattern><template>Methinks I could not die anywhere so contented...</template></category><category><pattern>WHY THE LAW SALIQUE THAT THEY HAVE IN FRANCE  OR SHOULD OR SHOULD NOT BAR US IN OUR CLAIM</pattern><template>And pray, take heed how you impawn our person, how you awake our sleeping sword of war.</template></category><category><pattern>DE NAILS  MADAME     DE ARMA  DE BELBOW</pattern><template>Sauf votre honneur, d'elbow.</template></category><category><pattern>MY LORD  YOUR NOBLES  JEALOUS OF YOUR ABSENCE  SEEK THROUGH THE CAMP TO FIND YOU</pattern><template>Good old knight, Collect them all together at my tent.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE LATEST PARLE WE WILL ADMIT</pattern><template>Therefore, to our best mercy give yourselves, or, like to men proud of destruction, defy us to our worst.</template></category><category><pattern>HERALD  SAVE THOU THY LABOR</pattern><template>Come thou no more for ransom, gentle herald.</template></category><category><pattern>IS NOTHING WORTH</pattern><template>since my penitence comes, after all, imploring pardon.</template></category><category><pattern>ET LES DOIGTS</pattern><template>Les doigts?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE WITCHCRAFT IN YOUR LIPS  KATE</pattern><template>There is more eloquence in a sugar touch of them...</template></category><category><pattern>WHO TALKS OF MY NATION IS A VILLAIN</pattern><template>and a bastard and a knave and a rascal?</template></category><category><pattern>IL EST TROP DIFFICILE  MADAME  COMME JE PENSE</pattern><template>Excusez moi, Alice, ecoutez: De hand, de fingres, de nails, de  arma,  de  bilbow,   d'elbow , madame.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HE COULD WISH HIMSELF IN THAMES UP TO THE NECK</pattern><template>And so I would he were, and I by him.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD DAY TO YOUR WORSHIP  GOOD CAPTAIN JAMES</pattern><template>How now, Captain Macmorris?</template></category><category><pattern>MY LIEGE</pattern><template>My brother Gloucester's voice.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU  MY GENTLE KNIGHT  GIVE ME YOUR THOUGHTS</pattern><template>Think you not that the powers we bear with us...</template></category><category><pattern>I'FAITH  MY WOOING IS FIT FOR THY UNDERSTANDING</pattern><template>I know no ways to mince it in love, but directly to say,  I love you.  Then, if you urge me farther than to say,  Do you in faith?  I wear out my suit.</template></category><category><pattern>PARDONNEZ MOI  I CANNOT TELL WHAT IS  LIKE ME   AN ANGEL IS LIKE YOU  KATE  AND YOU ARE LIKE AN ANGEL</pattern><template>Que dit il? Que je suis semblable a les anges?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOSE HEARTS HAVE LEFT THEIR BODIES HERE IN ENGLAND</pattern><template>and lie pavilioned in the fields of France.</template></category><category><pattern>QUI  VRAIMENT  SAUF VOTRE GRACE  AINSI DIT IL</pattern><template>Mon dieu.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR HE TODAY THAT SHEDS HIS BLOOD WITH ME SHALL BE MY BROTHER</pattern><template>Be he ne'er so vile, this day shall gentle his condition.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD SAVE YOUR MAJESTY</pattern><template>My royal cousin, teach you our princess english?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW ARE WE WELL PREPARED TO KNOW THE PLEASURE OF OUR FAIR COUSIN DAUPHIN</pattern><template>Your highness, lately sending into France did claim some certain dukedoms...</template></category><category><pattern>BEHOLD THE ORDINANCE ON THEIR CARRIAGES  WITH FATAL MOUTHS GAPING ON GIRDED HARFLEW</pattern><template>Suppose the ambassador from the French comes back, tells Harry that the king does offer him Katherine, his daughter, and with her to dowry, some petty and unprofitable dukedoms.</template></category><category><pattern>AND TAKE ME  TAKE A SOLDIER</pattern><template>Take a soldier, take a king.</template></category><category><pattern>EDWARD  THE DUKE OF YORK   THE EARL OF SUFFOLK   SIR RICHARD KETLY  DAVY GAM  ESQUIRE   NONE ELSE OF NAME</pattern><template>and of all other men...</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  ALL OUR RANKS ARE BROKE</pattern><template>O perdurable shame!</template></category><category><pattern>WITH MY ARM AROUND MY BACK  I SHOULD QUICKLY LEAP INTO A WIFE</pattern><template>I could lay on like a butcher and sit like a jackanapes, never off.</template></category><category><pattern>PISH FOR THEE  ICELAND DOG</pattern><template>Good Corporal Nym, show thy valor and put up thy sword.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL NEVER MOVE THEE IN FRENCH UNLESS IT BE TO LAUGH AT ME</pattern><template>Sauf votre honneur, le francais que vous parlez...</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL YET ENLARGE THAT MAN  THOUGH CAMBRIDGE  SCROOP AND GREY  IN THEIR DEAR CARE AND TENDER PRESERVATION</pattern><template>of our person would have him punished.</template></category><category><pattern>COMMENT APPELEZ VOUS LA MAIN EN ANGLAIS</pattern><template>La main?</template></category><category><pattern>AND BEST INDUED WITH SOME SUSPICION</pattern><template>I will weep for thee.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING IS FULL OF GRACE AND FAIR REGARD</pattern><template>And a true lover of the holy church.</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  I SAY 'TIS MEET WE ALL GO FORTH TO VIEW</pattern><template>the sick and feeble parts of France.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE NAME OF JESUS CHRIST  SPEAK LOWER</pattern><template>If you would take the pains but to examine the wars of Pompey the great, you shall find that there is no Tiddle Taddle nor Pibble Babble in Pompey's camp.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT SHALL I SAY TO THEE  LORD SCROOP  THOU CRUEL  INGRATEFUL  SAVAGE AND INHUMAN CREATURE</pattern><template>Thou knave thou!</template></category><category><pattern>I AM A KING THAT FIND THEE  AND I KNOW</pattern><template>'tis not the balm, the scepter and the ball, the sword, the mace, the crown imperial, the intertissued robe of gold and pearl, the farced title running fore the king, the throne he sits on...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT SAY YOU</pattern><template>Will you yield and this avoid?</template></category><category><pattern>PISH</pattern><template>Pish for thee, Iceland dog!</template></category><category><pattern>UPON THAT  I KISS YOUR HAND  AND I CALL YOU MY QUEEN</pattern><template>Laissez, mon seigneur, laissez, laissez.</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE WAS I CREATED WITH A STUBBORN OUTSIDE  WITH AN ASPECT OF IRON  THAT WHEN I COME TO WOO LADIES  I FRIGHT THEM</pattern><template>But, in faith, kate, the elder I wax, the better I shall appear.</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN FLUELLEN  YOU MUST COME PRESENTLY TO THE MINES</pattern><template>The duke of Gloucester would speak with you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF HE BE NOT FOUGHT WITHAL  MY LORD  LET US NOT LIVE IN FRANCE</pattern><template>Normans.</template></category><category><pattern>BY WHICH THE WORLD'S BEST GARDEN HE ACHIEVED</pattern><template>and of it left his son imperial lord.</template></category><category><pattern>HARK HOW OUR STEEDS FOR PRESENT SERVICE NEIGH</pattern><template>Mount them and make incision in their hides...</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE  OH  FOR PITY WE SHALL MUCH DISGRACE</pattern><template>with four or five most vile and ragged foils...</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  DREAD KING  ENTER OUR GATES  DISPOSE OF US AND OURS  FOR WE NO LONGER ARE DEFENSIBLE</pattern><template>Go you and enter Harflew.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  PRINCES  LOOK YOU STRONGLY ARMED TO MEET HIM</pattern><template>For he is bred out of that bloody strain...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HE THAT WISHES SO</pattern><template>My cousin Westmoreland?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU AND I CANNOT BE CONFINED WITHIN THE WEAK LIST OF A COUNTRY'S FASHION</pattern><template>We... are the makers of manners, Kate.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLY TO HEAR  KINDLY TO JUDGE</pattern><template>our play!</template></category><category><pattern>THOU THAT DIDST BEAR THE KEY OF ALL MY COUNSELS  THAT KNEWEST THE VERY BOTTOM OF MY SOUL  THAT ALMOST MIGHTST HAVE COINED ME INTO GOLD  WHICH THOU HAVE PRACTICED ON ME FOR THY USE</pattern><template>May it be possible that foreign hire...</template></category><category><pattern>IF IT PASS AGAINST US  WE LOSE THE BETTER HALF OF OUR POSSESSION</pattern><template>But what prevention?</template></category><category><pattern>THE WORKISH GIVE OVER</pattern><template>The trumpets sound the retreat.</template></category><category><pattern>DEVILS INCARNATE</pattern><template>He could never abide carnation.</template></category><category><pattern>AND KNOW</pattern><template>I know your worthiness.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TO THE THRONG</pattern><template>Let life be short!</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I  WITH RIGHT AND CONSCIENCE  MAKE THIS CLAIM</pattern><template>The sin upon my head, dread sovereign.</template></category><category><pattern>OF THIS BILL URGED BY THE COMMONS</pattern><template>Doth his majesty incline to it or no?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE HAVE HEARD THE CHIMES AT MIDNIGHT  MASTER HARRY</pattern><template>Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS PASSPORT SHALL BE MADE</pattern><template>and crowns for convoy put into his purse.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN DOTH IT WELL APPEAR THE SALIQUE LAW</pattern><template>was not devised for the realm of France, nor did the French possess the Salique land...</template></category><category><pattern>DE NAILS   ECOUTEZ  DITES MOI SI JE PARLE BIEN</pattern><template>De hand, de fingres etde nails.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING IS SET FROM LONDON  AND THE SCENE IS NOW TRANSPORTED  GENTLES  TO SOUTHHAMPTON</pattern><template>Before God, his grace is bold to trust these traitors.</template></category><category><pattern>WHILES THE MAD MOTHERS WITH THEIR HOWLS CONFUSED</pattern><template>do break the clouds!</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN CREEPING MURMUR AND THE PORING DARK</pattern><template>fills the wide vessel of the universe.</template></category><category><pattern>HE NEVER DID HARM THAT I HEARD OF</pattern><template>Nor will do none tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>DOTH HIS MAJESTY INCLINE TO IT OR NO</pattern><template>He seems...</template></category><category><pattern>HE MADE A FINER END AND WENT AWAY AN IT HAD BEEN ANY CHRISTIAN CHILD</pattern><template>He parted even just between 12:00 and 1:00, even at the turning of the tide.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE ARE MARKED TO DIE  WE ARE ENOUGH TO DO OUR COUNTRY LOSS</pattern><template>And if to live, the fewer men, The greater share of honor.</template></category><category><pattern>BROTHER JOHN BATES  IS NOT THAT THE MORNING WHICH BREAKS YONDER</pattern><template>I think it be, but we have no great cause to desire the approach of day.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE TOO MUCH MISTAKEN IN THIS KING</pattern><template>Question, your grace, the late ambassadors.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HIS WHOLE KINGDOM INTO DESOLATION</pattern><template>Get you therefore hence, poor miserable wretches, to your death, the taste whereof God of his mercy give you patience to endure...</template></category><category><pattern>FARE YOU WELL</pattern><template>This was a merry message.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL GO ARM MYSELF</pattern><template>The Dauphin longs for morning.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MONARCHS TO BEHOLD THE SWELLING SCENE</pattern><template>Then should the warlike harry, like himself, assume the port of Mars...</template></category><category><pattern>~ NON NOBIS DOMINE  DOMINE ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ TUO DA GLORIAM ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE  DOMINE ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ TUO DA GLORIAM ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE  DOMINE ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ TUO DA GLORIAM ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ TUO DA GLORIAM ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE  DOMINE ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ TUO DA GLORIAM ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE  DOMINE ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ TUO DA GLORIAM ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE  DOMINE ~ ~ NON NOBIS DOMINE ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ SED NOMENI ~ ~ TUO DA GLORIAM ~ ~ TUO DA ~ ~ GLORIAM ~ PEACE TO THIS MEETING</pattern><template>Unto our brother France, health and fair time of day.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE BEFORE THEE</pattern><template>O God of battles, steel my soldiers' hearts.</template></category><category><pattern>I RICHARD'S BODY HAVE INTERRED NEW</pattern><template>and on it have bestowed more contrite tears...</template></category><category><pattern>DITES MOI I'ANGLAIS POUR LE BRAS</pattern><template>De arm, madame.</template></category><category><pattern>DONC  UH  VOTRE EST FRANCE</pattern><template>et, uh, vous etes mienne.</template></category><category><pattern>AVAUNT  YOU CULLIONS</pattern><template>Captain Fluellen, you must come presently to the mines.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AS OUR VINEYARDS  FALLOWS  MEADS AND HEDGES  DEFECTIVE IN THEIR NATURES  GROW TO WILDNESS  EVEN SO OUR HOUSES AND OURSELVES  OUR CHILDREN HAVE LOST</pattern><template>or do not learn for want of time...</template></category><category><pattern>THE FIGO WITH THEE THEN</pattern><template>I thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE WE THANK YOU</pattern><template>My learned lord, we pray you to proceed...</template></category><category><pattern>MY DUTY TO YOU BOTH  ON EQUAL LOVE  GREAT KINGS OF FRANCE</pattern><template>and England.</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  YOU MEN OF HARFLEW  TAKE PITY OF YOUR TOWN AND OF YOUR PEOPLE</pattern><template>whiles yet my soldiers are in my command, whiles yet the cool and temperate wind of grace...</template></category><category><pattern>AND TRUE REPENTANCE OF ALL YOUR DEAR OFFENSES</pattern><template>Bear them hence.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MUST BE THOUGHT ON</pattern><template>If it pass against us, we lose the better half of our possession.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY WILL GIVE THEIR BODIES TO THE LUST OF ENGLISH YOUTH</pattern><template>to new store France with bastard warriors!</template></category><category><pattern>THAN FROM IT ISSUED FORCED DROPS OF BLOOD</pattern><template>Five hundred poor I have in yearly pay...</template></category><category><pattern>WHY THE DEVIL SHOULD WE KEEP NIVES TO CUT ONE ANOTHER'S THROATS</pattern><template>You'll pay me the eight shillings I won of you at betting?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  IN FAITH  KATE  THE ELDER I WAX  THE BETTER I SHALL APPEAR</pattern><template>My comfort is that old age, that ill layer up of beauty, can do no more spoil upon my face.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT BEFORE GOD  KATE  I CANNOT LOOK GREENLY</pattern><template>Nor gasp out my eloquence nor I have no cunning in protestation.</template></category><category><pattern>COME  I WILL BESTOW A BREAKFAST TO MAKE YOU FRIENDS  AND WE'LL BE ALL THREE SWORN BROTHERS TO FRANCE</pattern><template>Let it be so, good corporal.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  HARRY LE ROY</pattern><template>Le Roy?</template></category><category><pattern>MY NAME IS PISTOL CALLED</pattern><template>It sorts well with your fierceness.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT DO I NOT DWINDLE</pattern><template>My skin hangs about me like an old lady's loose gown.</template></category><category><pattern>AYE  HE SAID SO TO MAKE US FIGHT CHEERFULLY</pattern><template>But when our throats are cut, he may be ransomed, and we ne'er the wiser.</template></category><category><pattern>HE BADE ME PUT MORE CLOTHES ON HIS FEET</pattern><template>I put my hand under the bed and felt them, and they were as cold as any stone.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW NOW  CAPTAIN MACMORRIS</pattern><template>Have you quit the mines? By Christ, la.</template></category><category><pattern>WE FEW  WE HAPPY FEW  WE BAND OF BROTHERS</pattern><template>For he today that sheds his blood with me shall be my brother.</template></category><category><pattern>LE ROY</pattern><template>A... a Cornish name?</template></category><category><pattern>AH  THEN YOU ARE A BETTER THAN THE KING</pattern><template>The king's a bawcock and a heart of gold, a lad of life, an imp of fame, of parents good, of fist most valiant.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH PROFITABLE LABOR TO HIS GRAVE</pattern><template>And but for ceremony...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AFEARED THERE ARE FEW DIE WELL</pattern><template>that die in a battle...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS THE PRINCESS</pattern><template>I'faith, my wooing is fit for thy understanding.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE CONSPIRED AGAINST OUR ROYAL PERSON  JOINED WITH AN ENEMY PROCLAIMED AND FROM HIS COFFERS</pattern><template>received the golden earnest of our death wherein.</template></category><category><pattern>SO MAY YOUR HIGHNESS  AND YET PUNISH TOO</pattern><template>Sir, you show great mercy if you give him life...</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S CAPTAIN MACMORRIS  IS IT NOT</pattern><template>I think it be.</template></category><category><pattern>IF ANY ORDER MIGHT BE THOUGHT UPON</pattern><template>The devil take order now!</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING HATH NOTE OF ALL THEY INTEND BY INTERCEPTION WHICH THEY DREAM NOT OF</pattern><template>Nay, but the man that was his bedfellow, whom he hath dulled and cloyed with gracious favors...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NOW  WHO WILL BEHOLD THE ROYAL CAPTAIN OF THIS RUINED BAND  WALKING FROM WATCH TO WATCH  FROM TENT TO TENT</pattern><template>Let him cry,  Praise and glory on his head,  For forth he goes and visits all his host.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW YOUR PLACES</pattern><template>God be with you all!</template></category><category><pattern>BETTER AND BETTER</pattern><template>And, therefore, tell me, most fair Katherine, Will you have me?</template></category><category><pattern>DE ARM  MADAME</pattern><template>Et le coude?</template></category><category><pattern>ADDED TO THESE  OF KNIGHTS  ESQUIRES AND GALLANT GENTLEMEN  EIGHT THOUSAND AND FOUR HUNDRED</pattern><template>of the which five hundred...</template></category><category><pattern>THE DAY  MY FRIENDS  AND ALL THINGS</pattern><template>stay...</template></category><category><pattern>IF I LIVE TO SEE IT  I'LL NEVER TRUST HIS WORD AFTER</pattern><template>You pay him then!</template></category><category><pattern>HE THAT SHALL SEE THIS DAY AND LIVE OLD AGE</pattern><template>will yearly, on the vigil, feast his neighbors...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THE TONGUES OF MEN ARE FULL OF DECEITS</pattern><template>Oui. That the tongues of the mens is be full of deceits.</template></category><category><pattern>SPEAK  MY FAIR  AND FAIRLY  TOO  I PRAY THEE</pattern><template>Is it possible that I should love the enemy of France?</template></category><category><pattern>WE WOULD NOT DIE IN THAT MAN'S COMPANY</pattern><template>that fears his fellowship to die with us.</template></category><category><pattern>ART THOU HIS FRIEND</pattern><template>And his kinsman too.</template></category><category><pattern>SHAME AND ETERNAL SHAME</pattern><template>Nothing but shame.</template></category><category><pattern>I SPEAK TO THEE PLAIN SOLDIER  IF THOU CANST LOVE ME FOR THIS  TAKE ME</pattern><template>If not, to say to thee that I shall die, 'tis true, but for thy love, by the lord, no.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THIS IS NOT SO</pattern><template>The king is not bound to answer the particular endings of his soldiers...</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD HAVE HER LEARN  MY FAIR COUSIN  HOW PERFECTLY I LOVE HER  AND THAT IS GOOD ENGLISH</pattern><template>We have consented to all terms of reason.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL STAND AT TIPTOE WHEN THIS DAY IS NAMED</pattern><template>and rouse him at the name of Crispian.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT RAILED AGAINST OUR PERSON</pattern><template>We consider it was excess of wine that set him on, And on his more advice we pardon him.</template></category><category><pattern>TO ENGLAND WILL I STEAL  AND THERE I'LL    STEAL</pattern><template>herald, are the dead numbered?</template></category><category><pattern>O SEIGNEUR DIEU</pattern><template>Ce sont mots de son mauvais corruptible, Gros, et impudique et non pour les dames d'honneur d'user.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YIELDING</pattern><template>You have witchcraft in your lips, Kate.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THEE NOT  OLD MAN</pattern><template>The king hath run bad humors on the knight.</template></category><category><pattern>SHALL YOU KNOW OUR MIND AT FULL</pattern><template>Thus with imagined wing our swift scene flies, in motion of no less celerity than that of thought!</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT NOT LAWFUL  AN'T PLEASE YOUR MAJESTY  TO TELL HOW MANY IS KILLED</pattern><template>Aye, captain, but with this acknowledgement: That God fought...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MAY GIVE FURTHERANCE TO OUR EXPEDITION</pattern><template>For we have now no thought in us but France, save those to God that run before our business.</template></category><category><pattern>O  SEIGNEUR DIEU  JE M'EN OUBLIE  D'ELBOW</pattern><template>Comment appelez vous le col?</template></category><category><pattern>NORMANS</pattern><template>But bastard Normans!</template></category><category><pattern>WHOO</pattern><template>Hey! Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>THERE YOURS  LORD SCROOP OF MASHAM  AND SIR KNIGHT  GREY OF NORTHUMBERLAND  THIS SAME IS YOURS</pattern><template>Read them...</template></category><category><pattern>NOW WE SPEAK  AND OUR VOICE IS IMPERIAL</pattern><template>England shall repent his folly.</template></category><category><pattern>LAISSEZ  MON SEIGNEUR  LAISSEZ  LAISSEZ</pattern><template>Ma foi, je ne veux point que vous abaissiez votre grandeur...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF THE CAUSE BE NOT GOOD  THE KING HIMSELF HATH A HEAVY RECKONING TO MAKE</pattern><template>And all those legs and arms and heads...</template></category><category><pattern>C'EST BIEN DIT  MADAME</pattern><template>Il est fort bon anglais.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH FOUR OR FIVE MOST VILE AND RAGGED FOILS</pattern><template>right ill disposed in brawl ridiculous...</template></category><category><pattern>IF HIS CAUSE BE WRONG  OUR OBEDIENCE TO THE KING</pattern><template>wipes the crime of it out of us.</template></category><category><pattern>BY MY TROTH  THE KING HAS KILLED HIS HEART</pattern><template>Good husband, come home presently.</template></category><category><pattern>ELSE SHAME WILL BE TOO LONG</pattern><template>Well have we done, thrice valiant countrymen!</template></category><category><pattern>SHALL THINK THEMSELVES ACCURSED THEY WERE NOT HERE</pattern><template>and hold their manhoods cheap...</template></category><category><pattern>THEN HEAR ME  GRACIOUS SOVEREIGN</pattern><template>There is no bar to make against your highness' claim to France...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  FOR A MUSE OF FIRE</pattern><template>that would ascend the brightest heaven of invention.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES BLUE  SOMETIMES RED</pattern><template>But his nose is executed and his fire's out.</template></category><category><pattern>EN BAISANT LA MAIN D'UNE DE VOTRE SEIGNEURIE INDIGNE SERVITEUR</pattern><template>Excusez moi, je vous supplie, mon tres puissant seigneur.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH PENNONS PAINTED IN THE BLOOD OF HARFLEW</pattern><template>Go down upon him.</template></category><category><pattern>THOU DOST THY OFFICE FAIRLY</pattern><template>Turn thee back, and tell thy king I do not seek him now, but could be willing to march on to Calais without impeachment.</template></category><category><pattern>FOUGHT ON THE DAY OF CRISPIN CRISPIANUS</pattern><template>Your grandfather of famous memory, an't please your majesty, and your great uncle, Edward, the black prince of Wales, as I have read in the Chronicles, fought a most brave battle here in France.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO GOES THERE</pattern><template>A friend.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  FAITH  IT IS NOT</pattern><template>But tell me, Kate, Canst thou understand thus much English?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOSE WANT GIVES GROWTH TO THE IMPERFECTIONS WHICH YOU HAVE CITED  THEN YOU MUST BUY THAT PEACE</pattern><template>with full accord to all our just demands.</template></category><category><pattern>LET IT BE SO  GOOD CORPORAL</pattern><template>I will do as I may.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS DAY IS CALLED THE FEAST OF CRISPIAN</pattern><template>He that outlives this day and comes safe home...</template></category><category><pattern>ALL APPEAR TO HOLD IN RIGHT AND TITLE OF THE FEMALE</pattern><template>So do the kings of France...</template></category><category><pattern>FOR MANY OF OUR PRINCES</pattern><template>woe the while...</template></category><category><pattern>FOR I HAVE MADE AN OFFER TO HIS MAJESTY  AS TOUCHING FRANCE</pattern><template>Where is my gracious lord of Canterbury?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS BECOMES THE GREAT</pattern><template>Sorry am I his numbers are so few, his soldiers sick and famished in their march.</template></category><category><pattern>THRUST IN BETWEEN THE PACTION OF THESE KINGDOMS</pattern><template>to make divorce of their incorporate league...</template></category><category><pattern>AND CHRISTIAN LIKE ACCORD IN THEIR SWEET BOSOMS</pattern><template>that never war advance...</template></category><category><pattern>YET MY BLOOD BEGINS TO FLATTER ME THAT THOU DOST</pattern><template>withstanding the poor and untempering effect of my vis Now beshrew my father's ambition!</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING HIMSELF HAS RODE TO VIEW THEIR BATTLE</pattern><template>Of fighting men, they have full threescore thousand.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT ENGLAND SHALL CROUCH DOWN IN FEAR    AND YIELD</pattern><template>Where is the king?</template></category><category><pattern>AND PUT HIM TO EXECUTION</pattern><template>Discipline ought to be used.</template></category><category><pattern>I KISS HIS DIRTY SHOE  AND FROM HEARTSTRING  I LOVE THE LOVELY BULLY</pattern><template>What is thy name?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GIVE EXPRESS CHARGE THAT IN OUR MARCHES</pattern><template>through the country there be nothing compelled from the villages, nothing taken but paid for, none of the French upbraided or abused in disdainful language.</template></category><category><pattern>FAIR KATHERINE  AND MOST FAIR  WILL YOU VOUCHSAFE TO TEACH A SOLDIER</pattern><template>terms such as will enter at a lady's ear...</template></category><category><pattern>AS TO SPEAK SO MUCH MORE FRENCH</pattern><template>I will never move thee in French unless it be to laugh at me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MY SPEECH ENTREATS THAT I MAY KNOW</pattern><template>the let why gentle peace...</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS A COLOR HE NEVER LIKED</pattern><template>He said once the devil would have him about women.</template></category><category><pattern>SHH</pattern><template>In the name of Jesus Christ, speak lower.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY</pattern><template>for me.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL CUT THEIR PASSAGE THROUGH THE FORCE OF FRANCE</pattern><template>No doubt, my liege, if each man do his best. I doubt not that.</template></category><category><pattern>IT NOW DRAWS TOWARDS NIGHT</pattern><template>Beyond the river we'll encamp ourselves...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THIS THY FALL HATH LEFT A KIND OF BLOT</pattern><template>to mark the full fraught man...</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY AM I HIS NUMBERS ARE SO FEW  HIS SOLDIERS SICK AND FAMISHED IN THEIR MARCH</pattern><template>For I am sure when he shall see our army, he'll drop his heart into the sink of fear...</template></category><category><pattern>UNDER WHAT CAPTAIN SERVE YA</pattern><template>Under Sir Thomas Erpingham.</template></category><category><pattern>OR BREAK IT ALL TO PIECES</pattern><template>Now are we well prepared to know the pleasure of our fair cousin Dauphin.</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL THIS INSTANT</pattern><template>Here comes the herald of the French, my liege.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL NOT SAY SO  FOR FEAR I SHOULD BE FACED OUT OF MY WAY</pattern><template>I'll go arm myself.</template></category><category><pattern>BE FRIENDS  YOU ENGLISH FOOLS  BE FRIENDS</pattern><template>We have French quarrels enough!</template></category><category><pattern>DOTH FORTUNE PLAY THE HOUSEWIFE WITH ME NOW</pattern><template>News I have that my Nell is dead.</template></category><category><pattern>WE KNOW ENOUGH IF WE KNOW WE ARE THE KING'S SUBJECT</pattern><template>If his cause be wrong, our obedience to the king...</template></category><category><pattern>I SAY    GOOD DAY  CAPTAIN FLUELLEN</pattern><template>Good day to your worship, good Captain James.</template></category><category><pattern>READY</pattern><template>Fire!</template></category><category><pattern>UP TO THE BREACH  YOU DOGS</pattern><template>Avaunt, you cullions!</template></category><category><pattern>DO BUT BEHOLD YON POOR AND STARVED BAND</pattern><template>Your fair show shall suck away their souls, leaving them but the shales and husks of men.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DO YOU STAY SO LONG  MY LORDS OF FRANCE</pattern><template>Yon island carrions, desperate of their bones, ill favoredly become the morning field.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT SAYEST THOU THEN TO MY LOVE</pattern><template>Speak, my fair, and fairly, too, I pray thee.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  HEAR ME WHEN I SAY  HE THAT STRIKES THE FIRST STROKE  I'LL RUN HIM UP TO THE HILTS  AS I'M A SOLDIER</pattern><template>An oath of mickle might, and fury shall abate.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL TROT TOMORROW A MILE  AND MY WAY SHALL BE PAVED WITH ENGLISH FACES</pattern><template>I will not say so, for fear I should be faced out of my way.</template></category><category><pattern>FAITH  HE'S VERY ILL</pattern><template>By my troth, the king has killed his heart.</template></category><category><pattern>O'ERGLANCED THE ARTICLES</pattern><template>Pleaseth your grace to appoint some of your council...</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD CORPORAL NYM  SHOW THY VALOR AND PUT UP THY SWORD</pattern><template>Will you shog off?</template></category><category><pattern>LET US SWEAR THAT YOU ARE WORTH YOUR BREEDING  WHICH I DOUBT NOT</pattern><template>For there is none of you so mean and base that hath not noble luster in your eyes!</template></category><category><pattern>JE TE PRIE  M'ENSEIGNEZ</pattern><template>Il faut que j'apprenne a parler.</template></category><category><pattern>INDEED  MY LORD  IT IS A MOST ABSOLUTE AND EXCELLENT HORSE</pattern><template>My lord constable, the armor in your tent tonight...</template></category><category><pattern>HE WILLS YOU  IN THE NAME OF GOD ALMIGHTY  THAT YOU DIVEST YOURSELF AND LAY APART</pattern><template>the borrowed glories that by gift of heaven, by law of nature and of nations, belongs to him and to his heirs.</template></category><category><pattern>OF A KING</pattern><template>My lord, your nobles, jealous of your absence, seek through the camp to find you.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DID  FLUELLEN</pattern><template>Y your majesty says very true.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW YOUR WORTHINESS</pattern><template>My Lord of Westmoreland, uncle Exeter, we will aboard tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>F FOOTET 'LE COUN</pattern><template>Mmm.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WITH NO MORE THAN IF WE HEARD THAT ENGLAND WERE BUSIED WITH  UH  A WHITSUN MORRIS DANCE</pattern><template>For, my good liege, she is so idly kinged by a vain, giddy, shallow, humorous youth, that fear attends her not.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS NOT BE THE FASHION FOR THE LADIES OF FRANCE</pattern><template>Oh, I cannot tell what Isbaiserin English.</template></category><category><pattern>AND BLESS US WITH HER FORMER QUALITIES</pattern><template>If, duke of Burgundy, you would the peace...</template></category><category><pattern>MY COMFORT IS THAT OLD AGE  THAT ILL LAYER UP OF BEAUTY  CAN DO NO MORE SPOIL UPON MY FACE</pattern><template>Thou hast me... if thou hast me... at the worst.</template></category><category><pattern>'TWIXT ENGLAND AND FAIR FRANCE</pattern><template>Amen.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THOU PROUD DREAM  THAT PLAYEST SO SUBTLY WITH A KING'S REPOSE</pattern><template>I am a king that find thee, and I know...</template></category><category><pattern>TO BE THE REALM OF FRANCE</pattern><template>Yet their own authors faithfully affirm...</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS NOT WORK ENOUGH FOR ALL OUR HANDS</pattern><template>Why do you stay so long, my lords of france?</template></category><category><pattern>DO WE ALL HOLY RITES</pattern><template>Let there be sung non nobisandte deum.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE HAVE THEY THIS METTLE IS NOT THEIR CLIMATE FOGGY  RAW AND DULL</pattern><template>O, for honor of our land.</template></category><category><pattern>A KINGDOM FOR A STAGE  PRINCES TO ACT</pattern><template>and monarchs to behold the swelling scene.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSEZ MOI  ALICE  ECOUTEZ: DE HAND  DE FINGRES  DE NAILS  DE  ARMA   DE  BILBOW    D'ELBOW   MADAME</pattern><template>O, seigneur dieu, je m'en oublie! D'elbow.</template></category><category><pattern>OF THE SIEGE IS GIVEN  IS ALTOGETHER DIRECTED BY AN IRISHMAN</pattern><template>It's Captain Macmorris, is it not?</template></category><category><pattern>HEAR YOUR SENTENCE</pattern><template>You have conspired against our royal person, joined with an enemy proclaimed and from his coffers...</template></category><category><pattern>UNTO OUR BROTHER FRANCE  HEALTH AND FAIR TIME OF DAY</pattern><template>Joy and good wishes to our most fair and princely cousin Katherine.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH TROUBLES OFT THE BED OF BLESSED MARRIAGE</pattern><template>thrust in between the paction of these kingdoms...</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THOUSANDS WEEP MORE THAN DID LAUGH AT IT</pattern><template>Convey them with safe conduct.</template></category><category><pattern>SELF LOVE  MY LIEGE  IS NOT SO VILE A SIN AS SELF NEGLECTING</pattern><template>From our brother England?</template></category><category><pattern>MON DIEU</pattern><template>Les langues des hommes sont pleines de tromperies.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD BE WITH YOU ALL</pattern><template>Once more I come to know of thee, if for they ransom, thou wilt now compound before thy most assured overthrow.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SICK AND FEEBLE PARTS OF FRANCE</pattern><template>And let us do it with no show of fear!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW ALL THE YOUTH OF ENGLAND ARE ON FIRE</pattern><template>and silken dalliance in the wardrobe lies.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HE DID</pattern><template>And of women.</template></category><category><pattern>I CANNOT SPEAK YOUR ENGLAND</pattern><template>Oh.</template></category><category><pattern>TURN THEE BACK  AND TELL THY KING I DO NOT SEEK HIM NOW  BUT COULD BE WILLING TO MARCH ON TO CALAIS WITHOUT IMPEACHMENT</pattern><template>Go, therefore, tell thy master here I am.</template></category><category><pattern>BY MY HAND  'TIS ILL DONE</pattern><template>Captain Macmorris, I beseech you now, a few disputations as partly touching the disciplines of the war, partly to satisfy my opinion...</template></category><category><pattern>MY LORD CONSTABLE  THE ARMOR IN YOUR TENT TONIGHT</pattern><template>Are those suns or stars on it?</template></category><category><pattern>I MYSELF HEARD THE KING SAY HE WOULD NOT BE RANSOMED</pattern><template>Aye, he said so to make us fight cheerfully.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SHALL HAVE CAUSE TO CURSE THE DAUPHIN'S SCORN</pattern><template>So get you hence in peace, and tell the Dauphin...</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT ART THOU  THOU IDLE CEREMONY</pattern><template>What drinks thou oft instead of homage sweet but poison flattery?</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL WEEP FOR THEE</pattern><template>For this revolt of thine, methinks, is like another fall of man.</template></category><category><pattern>LET HIM GREET ENGLAND WITH OUR SHARP DEFIANCE</pattern><template>Up, princes, and with spirit of honor edged more sharper than your swords, hie to the field.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MADE HIS ENGLAND BLEED</pattern><template>which oft our stage hath shown, and, for their sake, in your fair minds let this acceptance take.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE BUT WITH A CURSORARY EYE</pattern><template>o'erglanced the articles.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM A GENTLEMAN OF A COMPANY</pattern><template>Trailest thou the puissant pike? Even so.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE IS THE NUMBER OF THE SLAUGHTERED FRENCH</pattern><template>This note doth tell me of...</template></category><category><pattern>MONTJOY</pattern><template>Thou dost thy office fairly.</template></category><category><pattern>I SHALL CONFESS IT TO ALL THE WORLD</pattern><template>And I need not be ashamed of your majesty, praised be god, so long as your majesty is an honest man.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SIGNS OF WAR ADVANCE</pattern><template>No king of England if not king of France.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WOULD HAVE ALL SUCH OFFENDERS SO CUT OFF</pattern><template>We give express charge that in our marches...</template></category><category><pattern>BY CHESHU  HE IS AN ASS IN THE WORLD</pattern><template>He has no more directions...</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAS NO MORE DIRECTIONS</pattern><template>in the true disciplines of the wars than is a puppy dog.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HE DID IN SOME SORT</pattern><template>handle women.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEREUPON GIVE ME YOUR DAUGHTER</pattern><template>Take her, fair son, and from her blood raise up issue to me...</template></category><category><pattern>JE PENSE QU'ILS SONT APPELES  DE FINGRES   LE MAIN  DE HAND</pattern><template>Le doigts, de fingres.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I DO ROUSE ME IN MY THRONE OF FRANCE</pattern><template>And tell the pleasant prince this mock of his...</template></category><category><pattern>OF THIS MOST DREADFUL PREPARATION  SHAKE IN THEIR FEAR</pattern><template>and with pale policy seek to divert the English purposes.</template></category><category><pattern>FAIR KATHERINE  IF YOU WILL LOVE ME SOUNDLY WITH YOUR FRENCH HEART  GLAD TO HEAR YOU CONFESS IT BROKENLY WITH YOUR ENGLISH DO YOU LIKE ME  KATE</pattern><template>Pardonnez moi. I cannot tell what is  like me.  An angel is like you, Kate, and you are like an angel.</template></category><category><pattern>PERISH THE MAN WHOSE MIND IS BACKWARD NOW</pattern><template>Thou dost not wish more help from England, coz?</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  THE DUKES OF BERRI</pattern><template>and of Bretagne, of Brabant and of Orleans shall make forth.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  SOLDIERS  MARCH AWAY  AND HOW THOU PLEASEST  GOD  DISPOSE THE DAY</pattern><template>And so our scene must to the battle fly...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT FIVE AND TWENTY</pattern><template>'Tis wonderful.</template></category><category><pattern>LES DAMES ET DEMOISELLES POUR ETRE BAISEES DEVANT LEUR NOCES</pattern><template>Il n'est pas la coutume de France.</template></category><category><pattern>DE FOOTET 'LE COUN</pattern><template>Neanmoins, je reciterai une autre fois ma lecon ensemble.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL NOT CHANGE MY HORSE</pattern><template>for any that treads but on four hooves.</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS LIKE A COAL OF FIRE</pattern><template>sometimes blue, sometimes red.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YEARLY  ON THE VIGIL  FEAST HIS NEIGHBORS</pattern><template>and say,  tomorrow is Saint Crispin's.  Then will he strip his sleeve and show his scars...</template></category><category><pattern>FOR NEVER TWO SUCH KINGDOMS DID CONTEND WITHOUT MUCH FALL OF BLOOD</pattern><template>Then hear me, gracious sovereign.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MORROW  LIEUTENANT BARDOLPH</pattern><template>What, are you and Ancient Pistol friends yet?</template></category><category><pattern>AND OF ALL OTHER MEN</pattern><template>but five and twenty.</template></category><category><pattern>HAD THE FOREHAND AND VANTAGE</pattern><template>of a king.</template></category><category><pattern>AND CHIDE THE CRIPPLE  TARDY GAITED NIGHT</pattern><template>who, like a foul and ugly witch, doth limp so tediously away.</template></category><category><pattern>BE OF GOOD CHEER   SO HE CRIED OUT   GOD  GOD  GOD   THREE OR FOUR TIMES</pattern><template>Now I, to comfort him, bid him he should not think of God.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN BLOOD IS THEIR ARGUMENT</pattern><template>Now if these men do not die well, it will be a black matter for the king that led them to it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IN LIEU OF THIS  DESIRES YOU LET THOSE DUKEDOMS</pattern><template>that you claim hear no more of you.</template></category><category><pattern>YET ALL'S NOT DONE</pattern><template>Yet keep the French the field!</template></category><category><pattern>BESIDES  THEY ARE ALL FRESH</pattern><template>'Tis a fearful odds.</template></category><category><pattern>TO SIT WITH US ONCE MORE</pattern><template>we will suddenly pass...</template></category><category><pattern>FROM HIS MOST FAMED OF FAMOUS ANCESTORS  EDWARD THE III  HE BIDS YOU THEN RESIGN YOUR CROWN AND KINGDOM  INDIRECTLY HELD FROM HIM  THE NATIVE AND TRUE CHALLENGER</pattern><template>Or else what follows?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SO  MY LIEGE</pattern><template>This lodging likes me better...</template></category><category><pattern>MADAME MY INTERPRETER  WHAT SAYS SHE</pattern><template>That is not be the fashion for the ladies of France...</template></category><category><pattern>AS THE WRETCHED SLAVE  WHO  WITH A BODY FILLED AND VACANT MIND  GETS HIM TO REST  CRAMMED WITH DISTRESSFUL BREAD  NEVER SEES HORRID NIGHT  THE CHILD OF HELL  BUT LIKE A LACKEY  FROM THE RISE TO THE SET</pattern><template>sweats in the eye of Phoebus...</template></category><category><pattern>THINK NOT UPON THE FAULT MY FATHER MADE ENCOMPASSING THE CROWN</pattern><template>I Richard's body have interred new...</template></category><category><pattern>SUCH A WRETCH  WINDING UP DAYS OF TOIL</pattern><template>and nights with sleep...</template></category><category><pattern>WIPES THE CRIME OF IT OUT OF US</pattern><template>But if the cause be not good, the king himself hath a heavy reckoning to make.</template></category><category><pattern>MA FOI  JE NE VEUX POINT QUE VOUS ABAISSIEZ VOTRE GRANDEUR</pattern><template>En baisant la main d'une de votre seigneurie indigne serviteur.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS NOT POSSIBLE THAT YOU SHOULD LOVE THE ENEMY OF FRANCE</pattern><template>But in loving me, you should love the friend of France, for I love France so well that I will not part with a village of it.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS NO BAR TO MAKE AGAINST YOUR HIGHNESS' CLAIM TO FRANCE</pattern><template>but this, which they produce from Pharamond.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LONGS NOT FOR THE DAWNING AS WE DO</pattern><template>If the English had any apprehension, they would run away.</template></category><category><pattern>CALL IN THE MESSENGERS SENT FROM THE DAUPHIN</pattern><template>Now are we well resolved, and by God's help and yours, the noble sinews of our power, France being ours, we'll bend it to our all...</template></category><category><pattern>HIS FACE IS ALL BUBUKLES AND WHELKS AND KNOBS AND FLAMES OF FIRE</pattern><template>His lips blows at his nose.</template></category><category><pattern>TO SORT OUR NOBLES FROM OUR COMMON MEN</pattern><template>For many of our princes...</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  THEN  REJOICE THEREFORE</pattern><template>'Tis not a thing to rejoice at.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO HAST SENT THEE NOW</pattern><template>The constable of France.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD KEEP ME SO</pattern><template>Doth fortune play the housewife with me now?</template></category><category><pattern>UPON SAINT CISPIN'S DAY</pattern><template>My sovereign lord!</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL SUDDENLY PASS</pattern><template>our accept and peremptory answer.</template></category><category><pattern>ON  ON  YOU NOBLEST ENGLAND</pattern><template>Now attest that those whom you called fathers did beget you.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE BARDOLPH  IF YOUR MAJESTY KNOW THE MAN</pattern><template>His face is all bubukles and whelks and knobs and flames of fire.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH RAINY MARCHING IN THE PAINFUL FIELD  BUT BY THE MASS  OUR HEARTS ARE IN THE TRIM</pattern><template>Herald, save thou thy labor.</template></category><category><pattern>SO MANY HORRID GHOSTS</pattern><template>Ahh.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR NOW SITS EXPECTATION IN THE AIR</pattern><template>and hides a sword, from hilts unto the point, with crowns imperial, crowns and coronets...</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE TRUE DISCIPLINES OF THE WARS THAN IS A PUPPY DOG</pattern><template>Here he comes, and the Scots captain, Captain Jamy, with him.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR YOUR OWN REASONS TURN INTO YOUR BOSOMS AS DOGS UPON THEIR MASTERS WORRYING YOU</pattern><template>See you, my princes and my noble peers, these English monsters.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  KATE  WHEN FRANCE IS MINE  AND I AM YOURS  THEN YOURS IS FRANCE  AND YOU ARE MINE</pattern><template>I cannot tell what is that.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING BUT SHAME</pattern><template>Let us die in arms.</template></category><category><pattern>EEVERY MAN THAT DIES ILL  THE ILL UPON HIS OWN HEAD</pattern><template>The king is not to answer it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE CONSENTED TO ALL TERMS OF REASON</pattern><template>And thereupon give me your daughter.</template></category><category><pattern>AND A MOST NOBLE CARRIAGE</pattern><template>But do I not dwindle?</template></category><category><pattern>THE GAME'S AFOOT</pattern><template>Follow your spirit, and upon this charge, cry,  God for Harry, England and Saint George!  God for harry, England and Saint George!</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO OUR SCENE MUST TO THE BATTLE FLY</pattern><template>where, oh, for pity we shall much disgrace...</template></category><category><pattern>AND AS A BRANCH AND MEMBER OF THIS ROYALTY</pattern><template>by whom this great assembly is contrived, we do salute you, duke of Burgundy.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOT OUR STRENGTH FOR IT</pattern><template>What is this castle called...</template></category><category><pattern>THOU NEVER SHALT HEAR HERALD ANYMORE</pattern><template>My lord, most humbly on my knee, I beg the leading of the vaward.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT HE DID</pattern><template>He said they were...</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD IT WERE DAY</pattern><template>Alas, poor Harry of England.</template></category><category><pattern>ALAS  POOR HARRY OF ENGLAND</pattern><template>He longs not for the dawning as we do.</template></category><category><pattern>BY WHOM THIS GREAT ASSEMBLY IS CONTRIVED  WE DO SALUTE YOU  DUKE OF BURGUNDY</pattern><template>And, princes French and peers, health to you all.</template></category><category><pattern>DO MY GOOD MORROW TO THEM  AND ANON DESIRE THEM ALL TO MY PAVILION</pattern><template>We shall, my liege.</template></category><category><pattern>SHALL I ATTEND YOUR GRACE</pattern><template>No, my good knight.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT MEANS THIS  HERALD</pattern><template>Huh? Com'st thou again for ransom?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOSE STATE SO MANY HAD THE MANAGING</pattern><template>that they lost France...</template></category><category><pattern>AND ROUSE HIM AT THE NAME OF CRISPIAN</pattern><template>He that shall see this day and live old age...</template></category><category><pattern>AND CALLS THEM  BROTHERS  FRIENDS AND COUNTRYMEN   A LARGESSE UNIVERSAL  LIKE THE SUN</pattern><template>his liberal eye doth give to everyone, thawing cold fear...</template></category><category><pattern>I PRAY YOU AND BESEECH YOU THAT YOU WILL</pattern><template>Brother John Bates, Is not that the morning which breaks yonder?</template></category><category><pattern>SWEET MEN  COME TO HIM</pattern><template>Poor Sir John.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT BASTARD NORMANS</pattern><template>Norman... bastards!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  HOW NOW  GENTLEMEN WHAT SEE YOU IN THOSE PAPERS THAT YOU LOSE SO MUCH COMPLEXION</pattern><template>I do confess my fault and do submit me to your highness' mercy.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THEIR HOT BLOOD MAY SPIN IN ENGLISH EYES</pattern><template>Do but behold yon poor and starved band.</template></category><category><pattern>RATHER  PROCLAIM IT  WESTMORELAND  THROUGH MY HOST  THAT HE WHICH HATH NO STOMACH TO THIS FIGHT</pattern><template>let him depart.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO CONFESS MY FAULT AND DO SUBMIT ME TO YOUR HIGHNESS' MERCY</pattern><template>To which we all appeal.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR THERE IS NONE OF YOU SO MEAN AND BASE THAT HATH NOT NOBLE LUSTER IN YOUR EYES</pattern><template>I see you stand like greyhounds in the slips, straining upon the start.</template></category><category><pattern>TOMORROW    FOR THE MARCH ARE WE ADDRESSED</pattern><template>Alice.</template></category><category><pattern>HATH TURNED HIS BALLS TO GUNSTONES  AND HIS SOUL SHALL STAND SORE CHARGED</pattern><template>for the wasteful vengeance that shall fly with them.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'LL MAKE YOUR PARIS LOUVRE SHAKE FOR IT</pattern><template>And be assured you'll find a difference, as we, his subjects, have in wonder found, between the promise of his greener days and these he masters now.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT STANDS HARD BY</pattern><template>They call it Agincourt.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD OLD KNIGHT  COLLECT THEM ALL TOGETHER AT MY TENT</pattern><template>I'll be before thee.</template></category><category><pattern>J'AI GAGNE DEUX MOTS D'ANGLAIS VITEMENT</pattern><template>Comment appelez vous les ongles?</template></category><category><pattern>ART THOU OFFICER</pattern><template>or art thou base, common and popular?</template></category><category><pattern>COMPANY  VILLAINOUS COMPANY HAVE BEEN THE SPOIL OF ME</pattern><template>Whoo!</template></category><category><pattern>OF HEADY MURDER  SPOIL AND VILLAINY</pattern><template>If not, why, in a moment look to see...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HE SHOULD  FOR A FOREIGN PURSE  SO SELL HIS SOVEREIGN'S LIFE TO DEATH AND TREACHERY</pattern><template>Now sits the wind fair, and we will aboard.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT KNOW YOU SO GOOD A MAN AS MYSELF</pattern><template>So Christ save me, I will cut off your head!</template></category><category><pattern>DE  NICK   MADAME</pattern><template>De nick.    Mmm.</template></category><category><pattern>CHOPPED OFF IN THE BATTLE</pattern><template>will join together at the latter day and cry all,  we died at such a place.  Some swearing, some crying for a surgeon, some upon their wives left poor behind them, some upon the debts they owe, some upon their children rawly left.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  LET THEIR BODIES FOLLOW  MY DEAR LIEGE  WITH BLOOD AND SWORD AND FIRE TO WIN YOUR RIGHT</pattern><template>In aid whereof, we of the spirituality will raise your highness...</template></category><category><pattern>WITH THAT AFFABILITY AS IN DISCRETION YOU OUGHT TO USE ME  NOW LOOK YOU  BEING AS GOOD A MAN AS YOURSELF</pattern><template>I do not know you so good a man as myself.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THE FIXED SENTINELS ALMOST RECEIVE</pattern><template>the secret whispers of each other's watch.</template></category><category><pattern>BID HIM  THEREFORE  CONSIDER OF HIS RANSOM</pattern><template>which must proportion the losses we have borne...</template></category><category><pattern>SPEED HIM HENCE</pattern><template>Let him greet England with our sharp defiance.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS PRESENT AND YOUR PAINS WE THANK YOU FOR</pattern><template>When we have matched our rackets to these balls, we will in France, by God's grace, play a set shall strike his father's crown into the hazard.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOUR MAJESTY IS REMEMBERED OF IT  THE WELSHMEN DID GOOD SERVICE IN A GARDEN WHERE LEEKS DID GROW  WEARING LEEKS IN THEIR MONMOUTH CAPS  WHICH  AS YOUR MAJESTY KNOW  TO THIS HOUR IS AN HONORABLE BADGE OF SERVICE</pattern><template>And I do believe your majesty takes no scorn...</template></category><category><pattern>I ONE  MY LORD</pattern><template>Your highness bade me ask for it today. So did you me.</template></category><category><pattern>TO BAR YOUR HIGHNESS CLAIMING FROM THE FEMALE</pattern><template>May I, with right and conscience, make this claim?</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU QUIT THE MINES  BY CHRIST  LA</pattern><template>The workish give over.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING HATH RUN BAD HUMORS ON THE KNIGHT</pattern><template>Nym, thou hast spoke the right.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN IT SHALL ALSO CONTENT ME</pattern><template>Upon that, I kiss your hand, and I call you my queen.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HOLD THEIR MANHOODS CHEAP</pattern><template>whiles any speaks that fought with us...</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT DESIRE HE SHOULD ANSWER FOR ME</pattern><template>Yet I determine to fight lustily for him.</template></category><category><pattern>UNTO THIS DAY</pattern><template>Howbeit, they would hold up this salique law...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT MEN HAVE YOU LOST</pattern><template>I think the duke hath lost never a man...</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU WOULD TAKE THE PAINS BUT TO EXAMINE THE WARS OF POMPEY THE GREAT  YOU SHALL FIND THAT THERE IS NO TIDDLE TADDLE NOR PIBBLE BABBLE IN POMPEY'S CAMP</pattern><template>The enemy is loud.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR WE HAVE NOW NO THOUGHT IN US BUT FRANCE  SAVE THOSE TO GOD THAT RUN BEFORE OUR BUSINESS</pattern><template>Therefore, let every man now task his thought...</template></category><category><pattern>THE BLIND AND BLOODY SOLDIER WITH FOUL HAND</pattern><template>defile the locks of your shrill, shrieking daughters, your fathers taken by their silvered beards...</template></category><category><pattern>NEANMOINS  JE RECITERAI UNE AUTRE FOIS MA LECON ENSEMBLE</pattern><template>De hand, de fingres, De nails, de arma, de...</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH I AM SURE WILL HANG ABOUT MY TONGUE</pattern><template>like a new married wife about her husband's neck, hardly to be shook off.</template></category><category><pattern>NEWS I HAVE THAT MY NELL IS DEAD</pattern><template>Tsk!</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS CERTAIN  CORPORAL  THAT ANCIENT PISTOL IS MARRIED TO NELL QUICKLY</pattern><template>For certainly she did you wrong, for you were betrothed to her.</template></category><category><pattern>I ARREST THEE OF HIGH TREASON BY THE NAME OF THOMAS GREY  KNIGHT OF NORTHUMBERLAND</pattern><template>I arrest thee of high treason by the name of Henry Lord Scroop of Masham.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT JOYOUS ARE WE TO BEHOLD YOUR FACE  MOST WORTHY BROTHER ENGLAND</pattern><template>Fairly met.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO  CAPTAIN JAMY IS A MARVELOUS  VALOROUS GENTLEMAN  THAT IS CERTAIN</pattern><template>I say... good day, Captain Fluellen.</template></category><category><pattern>LIE DROWNED AND SOAKED IN MERCENARY BLOOD</pattern><template>O, give us leave, great king, to view the field in safety...</template></category><category><pattern>WE SEE YONDER THE BEGINNING OF THE DAY  BUT I THINK WE SHALL NEVER SEE THE END OF IT</pattern><template>Who goes there?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW SMOOTH AND EVEN THEY DO BEAR THEMSELVES  AS IF ALLEGIANCE IN THEIR BOSOMS SAT CROWNED WITH FAITH AND CONSTANT LOYALTY</pattern><template>The king hath note of all they intend by interception which they dream not of.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DAYS THAT WE HAVE SEEN</pattern><template>I know thee not, old man.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A NEW MARRIED WIFE ABOUT HER HUSBAND'S NECK  HARDLY TO BE SHOOK OFF</pattern><template>Je quand sur le possession de France...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  'TIS NOT SO  MY LORD HIGH CONSTABLE</pattern><template>Though we think it so, 'tis no matter.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR HIGHNESS  LATELY SENDING INTO FRANCE DID CLAIM SOME CERTAIN DUKEDOMS</pattern><template>in the right of your great predecessor, king Edward III.</template></category><category><pattern>JE NE DOUTE POINT D'APPRENDRE PAR LA GRACE DE DIEU  ET EN PEU DE TEMPS</pattern><template>N'avez vous pas deja oublie ce que je vous ai enseigne?</template></category><category><pattern>AND SOMETHING LEAN TO CUTPURSE OF QUICK HAND</pattern><template>To England will I steal, and there I'll... steal.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DRINKS THOU OFT INSTEAD OF HOMAGE SWEET BUT POISON FLATTERY</pattern><template>Oh, be sick, great greatness, and bid thy ceremony give thee cure.</template></category><category><pattern>BEHOLD  AS MAY UNWORTHINESS DEFINE  A LITTLE TOUCH OF HARRY IN THE NIGHT</pattern><template>Good morrow, old sir Thomas Erpingham.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO FARE THEE WELL</pattern><template>Thou never shalt hear herald anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>IF EVER YOU COME OF WOMEN  COME IN QUICKLY TO SIR JOHN</pattern><template>He is so shaked with a burning quotidian fever...</template></category><category><pattern>WE MUST TO FRANCE TOGETHER</pattern><template>Why the devil should we keep nives to cut one another's throats?</template></category><category><pattern>AYE  TO A CHEERFUL LOOK  A PLEASING EYE</pattern><template>and a most noble carriage.</template></category><category><pattern>A FRIEND</pattern><template>Under what captain serve ya?</template></category><category><pattern>THEREFORE  PATIENTLY</pattern><template>and yielding.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL HAVE WE DONE  THRICE VALIANT COUNTRYMEN</pattern><template>Yet all's not done!</template></category><category><pattern>AND LIE PAVILIONED IN THE FIELDS OF FRANCE</pattern><template>Oh, let their bodies follow, my dear liege, with blood and sword and fire to win your right.</template></category><category><pattern>NOUS LES APPELONS DE NAILS</pattern><template>De nails.  Ecoutez, dites moi si je parle bien.</template></category><category><pattern>NAY  BUT THE MAN THAT WAS HIS BEDFELLOW  WHOM HE HATH DULLED AND CLOYED WITH GRACIOUS FAVORS</pattern><template>That he should, for a foreign purse, so sell his sovereign's life to death and treachery.</template></category><category><pattern>TOUCHING YOUR PATIENCE  ANCIENT PISTOL  FORTUNE IS AN EXCELLENT MORAL</pattern><template>Fortune is Bardolph's foe and frowns on him...</template></category><category><pattern>THINK WE KING HARRY STRONG</pattern><template>And, princes, look you strongly armed to meet him.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THAT WE NOW HAD HERE BUT ONE TEN THOUSAND OF THOSE MEN IN ENGLAND</pattern><template>That do no work today.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW NOW  MINE HOST PISTOL</pattern><template>Base tyke!</template></category><category><pattern>NON  JE RECITERAI A VOUS PROMPTEMENT: DE HAND  DE FINGRES</pattern><template>Tsk. Mmm.</template></category><category><pattern>THUS SAYS MY KING   SAY THOU TO HARRY OF ENGLAND   THOUGH WE SEEMED DEAD  WE DID BUT SLEEP</pattern><template>Tell him we could have rebuked him at Harflew.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW I  TO COMFORT HIM  BID HIM HE SHOULD NOT THINK OF GOD</pattern><template>I hoped there was no need to trouble himself with any such thoughts yet.</template></category><category><pattern>BEYOND THE RIVER WE'LL ENCAMP OURSELVES</pattern><template>and on tomorrow...</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASETH YOUR GRACE TO APPOINT SOME OF YOUR COUNCIL</pattern><template>to sit with us once more...</template></category><category><pattern>OF OUR PERSON WOULD HAVE HIM PUNISHED</pattern><template>And now to our French causes.</template></category><category><pattern>COME  SHALL I MAKE YOU TWO FRIENDS</pattern><template>We must to France together.</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE HUNDRED POOR I HAVE IN YEARLY PAY</pattern><template>who twice a day their withered hands...</template></category><category><pattern>THE TRUMPETS SOUND THE RETREAT</pattern><template>By my hand, 'tis ill done.</template></category><category><pattern>WHALL WE SHOG</pattern><template>The king will be gone from Southampton.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HATH NOT TOLD HIS THOUGHT TO THE KING</pattern><template>No, nor it is not meet he should.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TRAITORS ARE AGREED</pattern><template>The king is set from London, and the scene is now transported, gentles, to Southhampton.</template></category><category><pattern>YET I DETERMINE TO FIGHT LUSTILY FOR HIM</pattern><template>I myself heard the king say he would not be ransomed.</template></category><category><pattern>NOR WILL DO NONE TOMORROW</pattern><template>Would it were day.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPED THERE WAS NO NEED TO TROUBLE HIMSELF WITH ANY SUCH THOUGHTS YET</pattern><template>He bade me put more clothes on his feet.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS JEST    WILL SAVOR BUT OF SHALLOW WIT</pattern><template>when thousands weep more than did laugh at it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE MUST BEAR ALL</pattern><template>Oh, hard condition.</template></category><category><pattern>HE THEREFORE SENDS YOU  MEETER FOR YOUR SPIRIT  THIS TUN OF TREASURE</pattern><template>And in lieu of this, desires you let those dukedoms...</template></category><category><pattern>THOUGH WE THINK IT SO  'TIS NO MATTER</pattern><template>In matters of defense, 'tis best to weigh the enemy more mighty than he seems.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I</pattern><template>Then, Richard Earl of cambridge, there is yours.</template></category><category><pattern>MM HMM</pattern><template>Je pense que je suis le bon ecolier.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  IT IS NOT A FASHION FOR THE MAIDS IN FRANCE TO KISS BEFORE THEY ARE MARRIED</pattern><template>Oui, vraiment.</template></category><category><pattern>LES LANGUES DES HOMMES SONT PLEINES DE TROMPERIES</pattern><template>What says she, fair one?</template></category><category><pattern>NOR THE TIDE OF POMP</pattern><template>that beats upon the high shore of this world.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR HIS NOSE WAS AS SHARP AS A PEN  AND HE BABBLED OF GREEN FIELDS</pattern><template>How now, Sir John,  quoth I.</template></category><category><pattern>LET US DIE IN ARMS</pattern><template>Once more back again.</template></category><category><pattern>BESTOW YOURSELF WITH SPEED</pattern><template>The French are bravely in their battle set...</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL GO WITH THEE</pattern><template>The day, my friends, and all things...</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU  GOOD YEOMAN  WHOSE LIMBS WERE MADE IN ENGLAND  SHOW US HERE THE METTLE OF YOUR PASTURE</pattern><template>Let us swear that you are worth your breeding, which I doubt not!</template></category><category><pattern>THE SIN UPON MY HEAD  DREAD SOVEREIGN</pattern><template>Stand for your own.</template></category><category><pattern>O  GIVE US LEAVE  GREAT KING  TO VIEW THE FIELD IN SAFETY</pattern><template>and to dispose of their dead bodies.</template></category><category><pattern>THOU HAST ME    IF THOU HAST ME    AT THE WORST</pattern><template>And thou shalt wear me...</template></category><category><pattern>MY LEARNED LORD  WE PRAY YOU TO PROCEED</pattern><template>and justly and religiously unfold...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE AN EXCELLENT ARMOR  BUT LET MY HORSE HAVE HIS DUE</pattern><template>It is the best horse of Europe.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN WE HAVE MATCHED OUR RACKETS TO THESE BALLS  WE WILL IN FRANCE  BY GOD'S GRACE  PLAY A SET SHALL STRIKE HIS FATHER'S CROWN INTO THE HAZARD</pattern><template>And we understand him well, how he comes o'er us with our wilder days, not measuring what use we made of them.</template></category><category><pattern>THOU KNAVE THOU</pattern><template>Thou that didst bear the key of all my counsels, that knewest the very bottom of my soul, that almost mightst have coined me into gold, which thou have practiced on me for thy use.</template></category><category><pattern>THUS WITH IMAGINED WING OUR SWIFT SCENE FLIES  IN MOTION OF NO LESS CELERITY THAN THAT OF THOUGHT</pattern><template>Work, work your thoughts, and in them see a siege!</template></category><category><pattern>AND TO DISPOSE OF THEIR DEAD BODIES</pattern><template>I tell thee truly, herald, I know not if the day be ours or no.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAY HE CRIED OUT FOR SACK</pattern><template>That he did.</template></category><category><pattern>AYE  AND MORE THAN WE SHOULD SEEK AFTER</pattern><template>We know enough if we know we are the king's subject.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE RIGHT OF YOUR GREAT PREDECESSOR  KING EDWARD III</pattern><template>In answer of which claim, the prince, my master, says that you savor too much of your youth.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT DO NO WORK TODAY</pattern><template>What's he that wishes so?</template></category><category><pattern>HUH  COM'ST THOU AGAIN FOR RANSOM</pattern><template>No! Great king!</template></category><category><pattern>AND  FOR ACHIEVEMENT  OFFER US HIS RANSOM</pattern><template>Therefore, lord constable, haste on montjoy.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAS A MERRY MESSAGE</pattern><template>We hope to make the sender blush at it.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THEY LOST FRANCE</pattern><template>and made his England bleed...</template></category><category><pattern>TSK  MMM</pattern><template>De  mails ?</template></category><category><pattern>DE HAND  DE FINGRES  DE NAILS  DE ARMA  DE</pattern><template>De nick, de chin, de foot et 'le coun!</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK YOU  IF HE WERE MY BROTHER  I WOULD DESIRE THE DUKE TO DO HIS GOOD PLEASURE</pattern><template>and put him to execution.</template></category><category><pattern>JOY AND GOOD WISHES TO OUR MOST FAIR AND PRINCELY COUSIN KATHERINE</pattern><template>And as a branch and member of this royalty...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS THE DAUPHIN SPEAKS</pattern><template>What... treasure, uncle?</template></category><category><pattern>THUS FAR  WITH ROUGH AND ALL UNABLE PEN</pattern><template>our bending author hath pursued the story...</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IN WEIGHT TO RE ANSWER HIS PETTINESS WOULD BOW UNDER</pattern><template>To this add defiance, and tell him, for conclusion,  he hath betrayed his followers...</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT WEAR YOUR DAGGER IN YOUR CAP THAT DAY  LEST HE KNOCK THAT ABOUT YOURS</pattern><template>Art thou his friend?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT HAVE KINGS THAT PRIVATES HAVE NOT TOO</pattern><template>save ceremony?</template></category><category><pattern>QUI VA LA</pattern><template>A friend.</template></category><category><pattern>IN PEACE THERE'S NOTHING SO BECOMES A MAN AS MODEST STILLNESS AND HUMILITY</pattern><template>But when the blast of war blows in our ears, then imitate the action of the tiger!</template></category><category><pattern>YET I LOVE THEE TOO</pattern><template>If thou would have such a one, take me.</template></category><category><pattern>UNWIND YOUR BLOODY FLAG</pattern><template>Your brother kings and monarchs of the earth...</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MORROW  OLD SIR THOMAS ERPINGHAM</pattern><template>A good soft pillow for that good white head were better than a churlish turf of France.</template></category><category><pattern>AND FOLLOWS SO THE EVER RUNNING YEAR</pattern><template>with profitable labor to his grave.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR FALSTAFF IS DEAD  AND WE MUST YEARN THEREFORE</pattern><template>Would I were with him, wheresome'er he is, either in heaven or in hell.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS NOT DEVISED FOR THE REALM OF FRANCE  NOR DID THE FRENCH POSSESS THE SALIQUE LAND</pattern><template>until 421 years after defunction of king Pharamond, idly supposed the founder of this law.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEIR GESTURE SAD  INVESTING LANK  LEAN CHEEKS AND WAR WORN COATS  PRESENTETH THEM UNTO THE GAZING MOON</pattern><template>so many horrid ghosts.</template></category><category><pattern>READ THEM</pattern><template>and know...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  ENGLAND  MODEL TO THY INWARD GREATNESS</pattern><template>Like a little body with a mighty heart.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY</pattern><template>I was as virtuous as a gentleman need to be.</template></category><category><pattern>CANST THOU  WHEN THOU COMMANDEST THE BEGGAR'S KNEE  COMMAND THE HEALTH OF IT</pattern><template>No, thou proud dream, that playest so subtly with a king's repose.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I AM A WELSHMAN</pattern><template>Knowest thou Fluellen?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS MORE ELOQUENCE IN A SUGAR TOUCH OF THEM</pattern><template>than in the tongues of the French council.</template></category><category><pattern>TO WHICH WE ALL APPEAL</pattern><template>The mercy that was quick in us of late...</template></category><category><pattern>KING PEPIN  WHICH DEPOSED CHILDERIC  DID  AS HEIR GENERAL  BEING DESCENDED OF BLITHILD  WHICH WAS THE DAUGHTER TO KING CLOTHAIR  MAKE CLAIM AND TITLE TO THE CROWN OF FRANCE</pattern><template>Hugh Capet, also, who usurped the crown of Charles, the duke of Lorraine, sole heir male of the true line and stock of Charles the great, could not keep quiet in his conscience wearing the crown of France...</template></category></AIML>