<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>BESIDES YOU  WE KNOW THERE'S ANOTHER KRAUT PATROL FUCKING AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE</pattern><template>If that patrol were to have any crack shots, that orchard would be a goddamn sniper's delight.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  THAT I CAN'T ABIDE</pattern><template>How about you, Utivich, can you abide it?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YEAH</pattern><template>Now, that leaves two ways we can play this out.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TOWER STANDS</pattern><template>Psst! Psst!</template></category><category><pattern>IF FRAU VON HAMMERSMARK'S COVER IS COMPROMISED  THE MISSION IS KAPUT</pattern><template>Speaking of Frau von Hammersmark, whose idea was it for the deathtrap rendezvous?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IN THE PAGES OF HISTORY  EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE  FATE REACHES OUT AND EXTENDS ITS HAND</pattern><template>What shall the history books read?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOLE POINT OF THE SECRET SERVICE  OLD BOY  YOU NOT HEARING OF THEM</pattern><template>But the Jerries have heard of them, because these Yanks have been them the devil.</template></category><category><pattern>FACTS COULD BE SO MISLEADING  WHERE RUMORS  TRUE OR FALSE  ARE OFTEN REVEALING</pattern><template>So, monsieur LaPadite, what rumors have you heard regarding the Dreyfuses?</template></category><category><pattern>AND  YES  SOME GERMANS WILL DIE</pattern><template>Yes, it will ruin the evening.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL BE DROPPED INTO FRANCE  ABOUT 24 KILOMETERS OUTSIDE OF PARIS</pattern><template>The Basterds will be waiting for you.</template></category><category><pattern>EITHER KILL YOU OR LET YOU GO</pattern><template>Whether or not you're going to leave this ditch alive depends entirely on you.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME  ALDO  IF I WERE SITTING WHERE YOU'RE SITTING  WOULD YOU SHOW ME MERCY</pattern><template>Nope.</template></category><category><pattern>LIEUTENANT ALDO  IF YOU DON'T THINK I WOULDN'T INTERROGATE EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOUR SWASTIKA MARKED SURVIVORS  WE SIMPLY AREN'T OPERATING ON THE LEVEL OF MUTUAL RESPECT I ASSUMED</pattern><template>No, I guess not.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A PRETTY EXCITING STORY</pattern><template>What's next? Eliza on Ice?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  THAT LEAVES TWO WAYS WE CAN PLAY THIS OUT</pattern><template>Either kill you or let you go.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  WE'RE NOT LOOKING FOR TROUBLE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Simply making contact with our agent.</template></category><category><pattern>MY NAME IS LIEUTENANT ALDO RAINE</pattern><template>And I'm putting together a special team, and I need me eight soldiers.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU  GO</pattern><template>Sergeant Werner Rachtman.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'S HE DOING</pattern><template>Frightfully sorry, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT SOUNDS GOOD</pattern><template>If you don't blow it, with that, I can get you in the building.</template></category><category><pattern>EVER HEARD OF US</pattern><template>We just want to say we're a big fan of your work.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  ABOUT THIS PICKLE WE FIND OURSELVES IN</pattern><template>It would appear there's only one thing left for you to do.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WILLI  WHAT'S WITH THE MACHINE GUN  I THOUGHT WE HAD US A DEAL</pattern><template>We still have a deal.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ALIVE</pattern><template>Who's that?</template></category><category><pattern>UP THERE  IF YOU ENGAGE IN WHAT THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT CALLS ILLEGAL ACTIVITY  BUT WHAT WE CALL JUST A MAN TRYING TO MAKE A LIVING FOR HIS FAMILY SELLING MOONSHINE LIQUOR  IT BEHOOVES ONESELF TO KEEP HIS WITS</pattern><template>Long story short, we hear a story too good to be true, it ain't.</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE WAY  THAT LAST PART IS ACTUALLY TRUE</pattern><template>I want my full military pension and benefits under my proper rank.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ENGLISHMAN GAVE HIMSELF AWAY</pattern><template>How'd he do that?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE AMERICAN</pattern><template>What are you?</template></category><category><pattern>BRIEF HIM</pattern><template>Lieutenant Hicox, at this point and time I'd like to brief you on Operation Kino.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO DO YOU THINK</pattern><template>Von Hammersmark.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW WILL I KNOW HER</pattern><template>I suspect that won't be too much trouble for you.</template></category><category><pattern>BYE BYE  ACTING CAREER</pattern><template>Fun while it lasted.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THIS LITTLE ESCAPADE OF OURS REQUIRES A KNOWLEDGE OF THE GERMAN FILM INDUSTRY UNDER THE THIRD REICH</pattern><template>Explain to me UFA under Goebbels.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THAT ENGLISH EXPRESSION ABOUT SHOES AND FEET</pattern><template>Looks like the shoe is on the other foot.    Yeah, I was just thinking that.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S CALLED SUSPICIOUS</pattern><template>Everybody needs to calm down.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  ACCORDING TO THESE PAPERS  ALL THE JEWISH FAMILIES IN THIS AREA HAVE BEEN ACCOUNTED FOR EXCEPT THE DREYFUSES</pattern><template>Somewhere in the last year it would appear they've vanished.</template></category><category><pattern>OR YOU WILL DIE TRYING</pattern><template>Hey, Hirschberg.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF THERE ARE ANY IRREGULARITIES TO BE FOUND  REST ASSURED THEY WILL BE</pattern><template>That is unless you have something to tell me that makes the conducting of a search unnecessary.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO</pattern><template>Champagne?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU</pattern><template>Damn it, Hirschberg!</template></category><category><pattern>WOULDN'T YOU AGREE</pattern><template>I guess so.</template></category><category><pattern>VON HAMMERSMARK</pattern><template>Yeah, she's ours.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S ALSO MADE ALL THE OTHER ARRANGEMENTS YOU'RE GOING TO NEED</pattern><template>How will I know her?</template></category><category><pattern>IT SOUNDS LIKE SHIT  WHAT ELSE ARE WE GOING TO DO  GO HOME</pattern><template>No, that sounds good.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU CAN ASSIST ME WITH ANSWERS  MY DEPARTMENT CAN CLOSE THE FILE ON YOUR FAMILY</pattern><template>Now, before the occupation, there were four Jewish families in this area, all dairy farmers like yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THE SHOE FITS  YOU MUST WEAR IT   FUCKING SHITHEAD</pattern><template>Faggot fuck. Fuck you!</template></category><category><pattern>IN FACT  I WANT ALL THE MEMBERS OF OPERATION KINO TO RECEIVE THE CONGRESSIONAL MEDAL OF HONOR</pattern><template>Full citizenship for myself.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU SAY WE MAKE US A DEAL</pattern><template>What's your name?</template></category><category><pattern>AND  YES  SOME OF THEM WERE JEWS</pattern><template>But Jew Hunter?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  I'M THE DIRECT DESCENDENT OF THE MOUNTAIN MAN JIM BRIDGER</pattern><template>That means I got a little Indian in me.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKS LIKE THE SHOE IS ON THE OTHER FOOT     YEAH  I WAS JUST THINKING THAT</pattern><template>So you're Aldo the Apache.</template></category><category><pattern>THREE DAYS FROM NOW JOSEPH GOEBBELS IS THROWING A GALA PREMIERE OF ONE OF HIS NEW MOVIES IN PARIS</pattern><template>What film, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I ASSUME YOU KNOW WHO WE ARE</pattern><template>You're Aldo the Apache.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU DO HAVE TO ADMIT  IT IS CATCHY</pattern><template>Do you control the nicknames your enemies bestow on you?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  AIN'T THAT NICE</pattern><template>Ask if he's going to take off his uniform.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR</pattern><template>Over and out.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  I HAVE NO INTENTION OF KILLING HITLER AND KILLING GOEBBELS AND KILLING GORING AND KILLING BORMANN  NOT TO MENTION WINNING THE WAR SINGLE HANDEDLY FOR THE ALLIES  ONLY LATER TO FIND MYSELF STANDING BEFORE A JEWISH TRIBUNAL</pattern><template>If you want to win the war tonight, we have to make a deal.</template></category><category><pattern>EXPLOSIVES STILL AROUND THEIR ANKLES  STILL READY TO EXPLODE</pattern><template>And your mission, some would call a terrorist plot, as of this moment, is still a go.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT</pattern><template>But how can I?</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU ALL GET IN TROUBLE IN THERE  WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO</pattern><template>Make bets on how it all comes out?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF YOU'RE WILLING TO BARBECUE THE WHOLE HIGH COMMAND  I SUPPOSE THAT'S WORTH CERTAIN CONSIDERATIONS</pattern><template>But I do have one question.</template></category><category><pattern>SAY AUF WIEDERSEHEN TO YOUR NAZI BALLS</pattern><template>You outside.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  FOR THE LAST TWO YEARS NOW</pattern><template>One could even say that Operation Kino was her brainchild.</template></category><category><pattern>ISN'T THAT JUST DANDY</pattern><template>Look, she's not a military strategist.</template></category><category><pattern>WE MUST DESTROY THAT TOWER</pattern><template>Sarge, that tower...</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT YOU  LIEUTENANT</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU AWARE OF</pattern><template>That they call you  The Jew Hunter.  Precisely.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU FAMILIAR WITH GERMAN CINEMA UNDER THE THIRD REICH</pattern><template>Yes. Obviously, I haven't seen any of the films made in the last three years, but I'm familiar with it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT LOUIS B  MAYER WOULDN'T BE GOEBBELS' PROPER OPPOSITE NUMBER</pattern><template>I believe Goebbels sees himself closer to David O. Selznick.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT MY KNIFE</pattern><template>Thank you very much, Colonel.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BASTERDS WILL BE WAITING FOR YOU</pattern><template>First thing, you'll go to a little village called Nadine.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT GOING AS MEMBERS OF THE GERMAN FILM INDUSTRY  THEY WEAR TUXEDOS AND FIT IN WITH EVERYBODY ELSE</pattern><template>I arranged for the tailor to fit three tuxedos tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOULD BE UNEVENTFUL</pattern><template>However, the off chance I'm wrong, things prove eventful, I need to know we can all remain calm.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M HERE  WILLI</pattern><template>I want to trust you.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT YOU  UTIVICH</pattern><template>You make that deal?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  IS THERE ANYBODY ALIVE ON OUR SIDE</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>LIEUTENANT HICOX WAS GOING AS MY ESCORT</pattern><template>The other two were going as a German cameraman and his assistant.</template></category><category><pattern>DONNY</pattern><template>Yeah, Donny!</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU NEED ALL FOUR TO END THE WAR</pattern><template>But if I don't pick up this phone right here, you may very well get all four.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S MY MEN</pattern><template>Where's Bridget von Hammersmark?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU SHOW GREAT TALENT</pattern><template>And I pride myself for having an eye for that kind of talent.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT DO YOU SAY  WILLI</pattern><template>We got us a deal?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE I SAID  THIRD BEST  JUST KEEP YOUR FUCKING MOUTH SHUT</pattern><template>In fact, why don't you start practicing right now?</template></category><category><pattern>WE STILL HAVE A DEAL</pattern><template>Now, get the girl and go.</template></category><category><pattern>AN ALTERNATIVE TO WHAT HE CONSIDERS THE JEWISH GERMAN INTELLECTUAL CINEMA OF THE '20S  AND THE JEWISH CONTROLLED DOGMA OF HOLLYWOOD</pattern><template>How's he doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T LOOK CALM TO YOU</pattern><template>Well, now that you put it like that, I guess you do.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS UNLESS YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO TELL ME THAT MAKES THE CONDUCTING OF A SEARCH UNNECESSARY</pattern><template>I might add, also, that any information that makes the performance of my duty easier will not be met with punishment.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  ARE YOU AWARE OF THE JOB I'VE BEEN ORDERED TO CARRY OUT IN FRANCE</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>AN AMERICAN SECRET SERVICE OUTFIT THAT LIVES DEEP BEHIND ENEMY LINES WILL BE YOUR ASSIST</pattern><template>The Germans call them the Basterds.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN THE LITTLE MAN</pattern><template>Germans' nickname for you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SHOSANNA WAS 18 OR 19</pattern><template>I'm not really sure.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY IN THE GERMAN ARMY HAS HEARD OF HUGO STIGLITZ</pattern><template>The reason for Hugo Stiglitz's celebrity among German soldiers is simple.</template></category><category><pattern>POINT OUT TO ME THE AREAS WHERE THEY'RE HIDING</pattern><template>Since I haven't heard any disturbance, I assume, while they're listening, they don't speak English.</template></category><category><pattern>LIEUTENANT RAINE</pattern><template>Right here.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MAKE A DEAL</pattern><template>Over there is a very capable two way radio and sitting behind it is a more than capable radio operator named Hermann.</template></category><category><pattern>SARGE  THAT TOWER</pattern><template>The tower stands!</template></category><category><pattern>FINE</pattern><template>Just take that fucking traitor, and get her out of my sight.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ORDERED THREE GLASSES</pattern><template>We order three glasses.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE GIRL</pattern><template>Au revoir, Shosanna!</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR CONTACT IS BRIDGET VON HAMMERSMARK</pattern><template>Bridget von Hammersmark?</template></category><category><pattern>LIST YOUR ACCOMPLISHMENTS</pattern><template>Well, sir, such as they are, I write reviews and articles for a publication called Films and Filmmakers, and I've had two books published.</template></category><category><pattern>IN ATTENDANCE AT THIS JOYOUS GERMATIC OCCASION WILL BE GOEBBELS  GORING  BORMANN  AND MOST OF THE GERMAN HIGH COMMAND INCLUDING ALL HIGH RANKING OFFICERS OF BOTH THE SS AND THE GESTAPO  AS WELL AS LUMINARIES OF THE NAZI PROPAGANDA FILM INDUSTRY</pattern><template>The master race at play?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I'M AWARE WHAT TREMENDOUS FEATS HUMAN BEINGS ARE CAPABLE OF ONCE THEY ABANDON DIGNITY</pattern><template>May I smoke my pipe as well?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO INTEREST IN SUCH THINGS</pattern><template>But you are aware of what they call me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE YOU</pattern><template>British? American?</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF YOU GET ALL FOUR  YOU END THE WAR TONIGHT</pattern><template>So, gentlemen, let's discuss the prospect of ending the war tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  LIEUTENANT  YOU'RE GETTING PRETTY GOOD AT THAT</pattern><template>You know how you get to Carnegie Hall, don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>QUITE FRANKLY  WATCHING DONNY BEAT NAZIS TO DEATH IS THE CLOSEST WE EVER GET TO GOING TO THE MOVIES  DONNY</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  DONNY</pattern><template>About now I'd be shitting my pants if I was you.</template></category><category><pattern>NUMBER ONE BEING  YOU'RE FIGHTING IN A BASEMENT</pattern><template>What if we go in there and she's not even there?</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IS</pattern><template>Der Fuhrer is attending the premiere.</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD OF THE BEAR JEW</pattern><template>What did you hear?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT MY FULL MILITARY PENSION AND BENEFITS UNDER MY PROPER RANK</pattern><template>I want to receive the Congressional Medal of Honor for my invaluable assistance in the toppling of the Third Reich.</template></category><category><pattern>LIEUTENANT ALDO RAINE</pattern><template>These are the Basterds.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS SO  TOO</pattern><template>Gentlemen, I have no intention of killing Hitler and killing Goebbels and killing Goring and killing Bormann, not to mention winning the war single handedly for the Allies, only later to find myself standing before a Jewish tribunal.</template></category><category><pattern>HMM</pattern><template>You Jerry banging, Limburg smelling...</template></category><category><pattern>SEND THAT KRAUT SARGE OVER</pattern><template>You. Go.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT YOU ARE ALL GOING TO DIE</pattern><template>And I want you to look deep into the face of the Jew who's going to do it!</template></category><category><pattern>HAVING NEVER MET THE DREYFUSES  WOULD YOU CONFIRM FOR ME THE EXACT MEMBERS OF THE HOUSEHOLD AND THEIR NAMES</pattern><template>There were five of them.</template></category><category><pattern>I BELIEVE GOEBBELS SEES HIMSELF CLOSER TO DAVID O  SELZNICK</pattern><template>Brief him.</template></category><category><pattern>PARIS WHEN IT SIZZLES</pattern><template>You didn't say the goddamn rendezvous is in a fucking basement.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHERE OUR CONCLUSIONS DIFFER  IS I DON'T CONSIDER THE COMPARISON AN INSULT</pattern><template>Consider for a moment the world a rat lives in.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN HE AND HIS RADIO OPERATOR WILL GET IN THE TRUCK AND DRIVE TO OUR LINES</pattern><template>Upon crossing our lines, Colonel Landa and his man will surrender to you.</template></category><category><pattern>GET ME SOMEONE ON THE OTHER END OF THAT RADIO WITH THE POWER OF THE PEN TO AUTHORIZE MY  LET'S CALL IT  THE TERMS OF MY CONDITIONAL SURRENDER</pattern><template>If that tastes better going down.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A HOSTILE WORLD  INDEED</pattern><template>If a rat were to scamper through your front door, right now, would you greet it with hostility?</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT I GOT THREE MEN DEAD BACK THERE</pattern><template>Why don't you try telling us what the fuck happened?</template></category><category><pattern>HIS COMMANDING OFFICER GAVE HIM AND HIS MATES THE NIGHT OFF TO CELEBRATE</pattern><template>The Germans being there was either a trap set by me or a tragic coincidence.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THAT SIMPLE  WILLI</pattern><template>You go your way, we go ours.</template></category><category><pattern>RATS WERE THE CAUSE OF THE BUBONIC PLAGUE  BUT THAT'S SOME TIME AGO</pattern><template>I propose to you any disease a rat could spread, a squirrel could equally carry.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BETTING FOR</pattern><template>OSS would be my guess.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYNARDVILLE  TENNESSEE</pattern><template>I've done my share of bootlegging.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WILL THEN TAKE OVER DRIVING OF THE TRUCK AND BRING THEM STRAIGHT TO ME FOR DEBRIEFING  IS THAT CLEAR  LIEUTENANT</pattern><template>Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  WHEN YOU REPORT WHAT HAPPENED HERE  YOU CAN'T TELL THEM YOU TOLD US WHAT YOU TOLD US  THEY'LL SHOOT YOU</pattern><template>They're going to want to know why you so special, we let you live.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAME AMERICAN  GOT DRAFTED  COME BACK TO GIVE Y'ALL WHAT FOR</pattern><template>Another one up there you might be familiar with.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS NAME IS MAX</pattern><template>We were in here drinking, celebrating.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE IT YOURSELF LIKE A GOOD CHAP  WILL YOU</pattern><template>The bar is in the globe.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE THE JEW HUNTER</pattern><template>I'm a detective.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN IT COMES TO KILLING NAZIS</pattern><template>...I think you show great talent.</template></category><category><pattern>OMAR  THIRD MOST</pattern><template>He'll be Donny's assistant.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE TELL ME WHAT YOU'VE HEARD</pattern><template>I've heard that the F�hrer has put you in charge of rounding up the Jews left in France who are either hiding or passing for Gentile.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU</pattern><template>And your Jew dogs.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO</pattern><template>Donny!</template></category><category><pattern>FRIGHTFULLY SORRY  SIR</pattern><template>Once again?</template></category><category><pattern>IS SHE OKAY</pattern><template>Wilhelm!</template></category><category><pattern>BUNCH OF SHITHEAD FUCK</pattern><template>Fuck you, too!</template></category><category><pattern>AND THROUGH OUR CRUELTY  THEY WILL KNOW WHO WE ARE</pattern><template>And they will find the evidence of our cruelty in the disemboweled, dismembered and disfigured bodies of their brothers we leave behind us.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER  I'M SURE THIS MISSION OF YOURS HAS A COMMANDING OFFICER</pattern><template>A general.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST THING  YOU'LL GO TO A LITTLE VILLAGE CALLED NADINE</pattern><template>In Nadine, there's a tavern called La Louisiane.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU GET THAT FOR KILLING JEWS</pattern><template>Bravery.</template></category><category><pattern>AS A GERMAN ENLISTED MAN  HE KILLED 13 GESTAPO OFFICERS</pattern><template>Instead of putting him up against a wall, the High Command decided to send him back to Berlin to be made an example of.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT I LIKE TO HEAR</pattern><template>But I got a word of warning for all you would be warriors.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOING TO HUG HIS MOTHER</pattern><template>Well, ain't that nice?</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAD JUST BECOME A FATHER</pattern><template>His commanding officer gave him and his mates the night off to celebrate.</template></category><category><pattern>MY NAME IS SHOSANNA DREYFUS  AND THIS IS THE FACE OF JEWISH VENGEANCE</pattern><template>Hermann, uncuff them.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  WERNER  WE'RE ALL TICKLED TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT</pattern><template>Quite frankly, watching Donny beat Nazis to death is the closest we ever get to going to the movies. Donny!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S BRIDGET VON HAMMERSMARK</pattern><template>Well, let's just say, she got what she deserved.</template></category><category><pattern>TOUCH ME AGAIN  KRAUT BURGER</pattern><template>Utivich?</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE WE GET INTO WHO SHOT JOHN  WHY'D YOU INVITE MY MEN TO A RENDEZVOUS IN A BASEMENT WITH A BUNCH OF NAZIS</pattern><template>I can see since you didn't see what happened inside, that the Nazis being there must look odd.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT LIKE ANY ENTERPRISE  WHEN UNDER NEW MANAGEMENT  THERE IS ALWAYS A SLIGHT DUPLICATION OF EFFORTS  MOST OF IT BEING A COMPLETE WASTE OF TIME  BUT NEEDS TO BE DONE NEVERTHELESS</pattern><template>I just have a few questions, monsieur LaPadite.</template></category><category><pattern>UP THE ROAD A PIECE  THERE'S AN ORCHARD</pattern><template>Besides you, we know there's another Kraut patrol fucking around here somewhere.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THAT GOES WITHOUT SAYING</pattern><template>And I would like the United States of America to purchase property for me on Nantucket Island as a reward for all the countless lives I've saved by bringing the tyranny of the National Socialist Party to a swifter than imagined end.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU CONTROL THE NICKNAMES YOUR ENEMIES BESTOW ON YOU</pattern><template>Aldo the Apache and the Little Man?</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THE WAY I SEE IT  SINCE HITLER'S DEATH OR POSSIBLE RESCUE RESTS SOLELY ON MY REACTION  IF I DO NOTHING  IT'S AS IF I'M CAUSING HIS DEATH EVEN MORE THAN YOURSELVES</pattern><template>Wouldn't you agree?</template></category><category><pattern>AND AS IF TO MAKE MY POINT  I'M A LITTLE SURPRISED HOW TALL YOU WERE IN REAL LIFE</pattern><template>I mean, you're a little fellow, but not circus midget little, as your reputation would suggest.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GERMANS BEING THERE WAS EITHER A TRAP SET BY ME OR A TRAGIC COINCIDENCE</pattern><template>It couldn't be both.</template></category><category><pattern>GERMANS DON'T HAVE A GOOD EAR FOR ITALIAN</pattern><template>So you mumble Italian and brazen through it. Is that the plan?</template></category><category><pattern>GET THE FUCK UP</pattern><template>Batter up. You're on deck!</template></category><category><pattern>UTIVICH</pattern><template>Is that you, Lieutenant?</template></category><category><pattern>ENGLISH</pattern><template>Wicki.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WOMAN</pattern><template>No, I do not.</template></category><category><pattern>BRITISH  AMERICAN</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>AIN'T YOU</pattern><template>That's what I thought.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I GUESS NOT</pattern><template>Well, back to the whereabouts of your two Italian saboteurs.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOUR JEW DOGS</pattern><template>Actually, Werner, we're all tickled to hear you say that.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU TAKE OFF THAT UNIFORM  AIN'T NOBODY GOING TO KNOW YOU'S A NAZI</pattern><template>And that don't sit well with us.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WENT YARD ON THAT ONE  ON TO FUCKING LANSDOWNE STREET</pattern><template>You!</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU DO IT</pattern><template>I have to.</template></category><category><pattern>SEEING AS I MAY BE RAPPING ON THE DOOR MOMENTARILY  I MUST SAY  DAMN GOOD STUFF  SIR</pattern><template>Now, about this pickle we find ourselves in.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>Gorlomi?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE GERMAN THREE</pattern><template>The other looks odd.</template></category><category><pattern>FAGGOT FUCK  FUCK YOU</pattern><template>Bunch of shithead fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT DON'T SIT WELL WITH US</pattern><template>So I'm going to give you a little something you can't take off.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  SHE'S NOT A MILITARY STRATEGIST</pattern><template>She's just an actress.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING FOR YOURSELF  SIR</pattern><template>Whiskey. Straight.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHEN THE MILITARY HISTORY OF THIS NIGHT IS WRITTEN  IT WILL BE RECORDED THAT I WAS PART OF OPERATION KINO FROM THE VERY BEGINNING AS A DOUBLE AGENT</pattern><template>Anything I've done in my guise as an SS Colonel was sanctioned by the OSS as a necessary evil to establish my cover with the Germans.</template></category><category><pattern>I PROPOSE TO YOU ANY DISEASE A RAT COULD SPREAD  A SQUIRREL COULD EQUALLY CARRY</pattern><template>Would you agree?</template></category><category><pattern>SO LET'S TALK</pattern><template>Okay, talk.</template></category><category><pattern>A DAMN GOOD DETECTIVE</pattern><template>Finding people is my specialty, so naturally, I worked for the Nazis finding people.</template></category><category><pattern>ASK HIM HOW MANY GERMANS</pattern><template>Around about 12.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T SAY THE GODDAMN RENDEZVOUS IS IN A FUCKING BASEMENT</pattern><template>I didn't know.</template></category><category><pattern>A DEBIT YOU OWE ME  PERSONALLY</pattern><template>Each and every man under my command owes me 100 Nazi scalps.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE GERMAN WILL BE SICKENED BY US</pattern><template>And the German will talk about us.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  YOU ALL MIGHT'VE HEARD RUMORS ABOUT THE ARMADA HAPPENING SOON</pattern><template>Well, we'll be leaving a little earlier.</template></category><category><pattern>BATTER UP  YOU'RE ON DECK</pattern><template>Two hits. I hit you, you hit the ground.</template></category><category><pattern>BEATS GERMAN SOLDIERS WITH A CLUB</pattern><template>He bashes their brains in with a baseball bat, what he does.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN THEY'RE FLAMMABLE</pattern><template>Go on, hop off.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER  THE OFF CHANCE I'M WRONG  THINGS PROVE EVENTFUL  I NEED TO KNOW WE CAN ALL REMAIN CALM</pattern><template>I don't look calm to you?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY'VE BEEN WAITING A LONG TIME TO TOUCH YOU</pattern><template>Caught you flinching.</template></category><category><pattern>I MADE A DEAL WITH YOUR GENERAL FOR THAT MAN'S LIFE</pattern><template>Yeah, they made that deal. But they don't give a fuck about him. They need you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T LIKE THAT</pattern><template>See, we like our Nazis in uniforms.</template></category><category><pattern>IF A RAT WERE TO WALK IN HERE  RIGHT NOW  AS I'M TALKING WOULD YOU GREET IT WITH A SAUCER OF YOUR DELICIOUS MILK</pattern><template>Probably not.</template></category><category><pattern>AND LITTLE MAX GETS TO GROW UP PLAYING CATCH WITH HIS DADDY</pattern><template>So what do you say, Willi?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T EXPECT ME TO DIVULGE INFORMATION THAT WOULD PUT GERMAN LIVES IN DANGER</pattern><template>Well, now, Werner, that's where you're wrong, because that's exactly what I expect.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MEANS YOU GETTING US IN THAT PREMIERE</pattern><template>I'm probably going to end up losing this leg.</template></category><category><pattern>SIMPLY MAKING CONTACT WITH OUR AGENT</pattern><template>Should be uneventful.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF ARTILLERY</pattern><template>Now, when you report what happened here, you can't tell them you told us what you told us. They'll shoot you.</template></category><category><pattern>THE F�HRER COULDN'T HAVE SAID IT BETTER HIMSELF</pattern><template>But the meaning of your visit, pleasant though it is, is mysterious to me.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE THE ONES THAT CAME IN SHOOTING AND KILLING  IT'S NOT MY FAULT</pattern><template>Okay!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S NEXT  ELIZA ON ICE</pattern><template>However, all I have to do is pick up this phone right here, inform the cinema, and your plan is kaput.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  TAKE YOUR WIENER SCHNITZEL LICKING FINGER  AND POINT OUT ON THIS MAP WHAT I WANT TO KNOW</pattern><template>Fuck you.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT THIS WAY  LIEUTENANT</pattern><template>Lieutenant Archie Hicox reporting, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>SCALP HERMANN</pattern><template>Are you mad?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU WON'T GET HITLER  YOU WON'T GET GOEBBELS  YOU WON'T GET GORING  AND YOU WON'T GET BORMANN</pattern><template>And you need all four to end the war.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A KATZENJAMMER KID</pattern><template>And your occupation before the war?</template></category><category><pattern>FAIR POINT  LIEUTENANT</pattern><template>So you all get in trouble in there, what are we supposed to do?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF WE GO IN THERE AND SHE'S NOT EVEN THERE</pattern><template>We wait.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE LETTING YOUR IMAGINATION GET THE BETTER OF YOU</pattern><template>You met the sergeant yourself. Willi.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE SECOND ONE WAS CALLED TWENTY FOUR FRAME DA VINCI</pattern><template>It's a subtextual film criticism study of the work of German director G.W. Pabst.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SAYS HERE THAT YOU SPEAK GERMAN FLUENTLY</pattern><template>Like a Katzenjammer Kid.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WAIT</pattern><template>Don't worry. She's a British spy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT SHOULD WE DRINK TO  SIR</pattern><template>Well...</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I KILL THAT GUY  YOU GOT 30 FEET TO GET TO THAT GUARD</pattern><template>Can you do it?</template></category><category><pattern>LIEUTENANT ARCHIE HICOX REPORTING  SIR</pattern><template>General Ed Fenech.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE HEARD THAT THE F�HRER HAS PUT YOU IN CHARGE OF ROUNDING UP THE JEWS LEFT IN FRANCE WHO ARE EITHER HIDING OR PASSING FOR GENTILE</pattern><template>The F�hrer couldn't have said it better himself.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOOK FORWARD TO SEEING YOU FACE TO FACE AS WELL  SIR</pattern><template>Lieutenant Raine?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE  THE VENUE HAS BEEN CHANGED FROM THE RITZ TO A MUCH SMALLER VENUE</pattern><template>Enormous change at the last minute?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE ALL THAT  SIR</pattern><template>I look forward to seeing you face to face as well, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>I'm alive!</template></category><category><pattern>THE OBJECTIVE OF OPERATION KINO  BLOW UP THE BASKET</pattern><template>And like the snows of yesteryear, gone from this earth.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF THIS IS IT  OLD BOY  I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND IF I GO OUT SPEAKING THE KING'S</pattern><template>By all means, Captain.</template></category><category><pattern>EXPLAIN IT TO ME</pattern><template>Pardon, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>THE MOTION PICTURE IS CALLED NATION'S PRIDE</pattern><template>In attendance at this joyous Germatic occasion will be Goebbels, Goring, Bormann, and most of the German High Command including all high ranking officers of both the SS and the Gestapo, as well as luminaries of the Nazi propaganda film industry.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AN INTERESTING THOUGHT  HERR COLONEL</pattern><template>However interesting as the thought may be, it makes not one bit of difference to how you feel.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THAT YOU'VE SURVIVED THE WAR  WHEN YOU GET HOME  WHAT YOU GOING TO DO</pattern><template>He's going to hug his mother.</template></category><category><pattern>WICKI</pattern><template>Ask him if he wants to live.</template></category><category><pattern>WE JUST WANT TO SAY WE'RE A BIG FAN OF YOUR WORK</pattern><template>When it comes to killing Nazis...</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE NITRATE FILM BURNS THREE TIMES FASTER THAN PAPER</pattern><template>Shosanna has a collection of over 350 nitrate film prints.</template></category><category><pattern>SPEAKING OF FRAU VON HAMMERSMARK  WHOSE IDEA WAS IT FOR THE DEATHTRAP RENDEZVOUS</pattern><template>She chose the spot.</template></category><category><pattern>FULL CITIZENSHIP FOR MYSELF</pattern><template>Well, that goes without saying.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I PRIDE MYSELF FOR HAVING AN EYE FOR THAT KIND OF TALENT</pattern><template>But your status as a Nazi killer is still amateur.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  MONSIEUR LAPADITE  THIS IS YOUR HOUSE  MAKE YOURSELF COMFORTABLE</pattern><template>Now, according to these papers, all the Jewish families in this area have been accounted for except the Dreyfuses.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE COULD EVEN SAY THAT OPERATION KINO WAS HER BRAINCHILD</pattern><template>Indeed.</template></category><category><pattern>HEAR THAT</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WANT MY SCALPS</pattern><template>And all y'all will get me 100 Nazi scalps taken from the heads of 100 dead Nazis.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A SUBTEXTUAL FILM CRITICISM STUDY OF THE WORK OF GERMAN DIRECTOR G W  PABST</pattern><template>What should we drink to, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE GOEBBELS HAS TAKEN OVER  FILM ATTENDANCE HAS STEADILY RISEN IN GERMANY OVER THE LAST EIGHT YEARS</pattern><template>But Louis B. Mayer wouldn't be Goebbels' proper opposite number.</template></category><category><pattern>BRIDGET VON HAMMERSMARK</pattern><template>The German movie star is working for England?</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON  HOP OFF</pattern><template>Because nitrate film burns three times faster than paper.</template></category><category><pattern>AU REVOIR  SHOSANNA</pattern><template>At that time, 35 millimeter nitrate film was so flammable that you couldn't even bring a reel onto a streetcar.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU ALL  BUT I SURE AS HELL DIDN'T COME DOWN FROM THE GODDAMN SMOKY MOUNTAINS  CROSS 5  000 MILES OF WATER  FIGHT MY WAY THROUGH HALF OF SICILY AND JUMP OUT OF A FUCKING AIRPLANE TO TEACH THE NAZIS LESSONS IN HUMANITY</pattern><template>Nazi ain't got no humanity.</template></category><category><pattern>BRAVERY</pattern><template>Yeah!</template></category><category><pattern>SERGEANT WERNER RACHTMAN</pattern><template>Lieutenant Aldo Raine.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AWARE OF THAT</pattern><template>I've read the reports of this area.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THEY CALL YOU  THE JEW HUNTER   PRECISELY</pattern><template>I understand your trepidation in repeating it.</template></category><category><pattern>EXPLAIN TO ME UFA UNDER GOEBBELS</pattern><template>Goebbels considers the films he's making to be the beginning of a new era in German cinema.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY  SHE'S A BRITISH SPY</pattern><template>She'll make the rendezvous.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  BACK TO THE WHEREABOUTS OF YOUR TWO ITALIAN SABOTEURS</pattern><template>As of this moment, both Omar and Donowitz should be sitting in the very seats we left them in.</template></category><category><pattern>GERMANS' NICKNAME FOR YOU</pattern><template>The Germans' nickname for me is the Little Man?</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE GET INTO TROUBLE  WE CAN HANDLE IT</pattern><template>But if trouble does happen, we need you to make damn sure no Germans, or French, for that matter, escape from that basement.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU THINKING</pattern><template>I'm thinking getting a whack at planting old Uncle Adolf makes this horse a different color.</template></category><category><pattern>I HEAR YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD WITH THAT</pattern><template>You know, we're not looking for trouble right now.</template></category><category><pattern>AND LIKE THE SNOWS OF YESTERYEAR  GONE FROM THIS EARTH</pattern><template>Jolly good, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID YOU HEAR</pattern><template>Beats German soldiers with a club.</template></category><category><pattern>PARDON  SIR</pattern><template>Well, this little escapade of ours requires a knowledge of the German film industry under the Third Reich.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  COMPARED TO  SAY  LOUIS B  MAYER  HOW'S HE DOING</pattern><template>Quite well, actually.</template></category><category><pattern>DOGGY DOC'S GOING TO DIG THAT SLUG OUT YOUR GAM</pattern><template>He's going to wrap it up in a cast, and you got a good how l broke my leg  mountain climbing story.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LET ME AND ONE OF MY MEN COME DOWN THERE AND TAKE THE GIRL AWAY</pattern><template>No guns. No guns me, no guns you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I GOT A WORD OF WARNING FOR ALL YOU WOULD BE WARRIORS</pattern><template>When you join my command, you take on debit.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY THE HELL IS GOEBBELS DOING STUFF SO DAMN PECULIAR</pattern><template>It probably has something to do with the second development.</template></category><category><pattern>HERR COLONEL  WOULD IT DISTURB YOU IF I SMOKED MY PIPE</pattern><template>Please, monsieur LaPadite, this is your house, make yourself comfortable.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OTHER TWO WERE GOING AS A GERMAN CAMERAMAN AND HIS ASSISTANT</pattern><template>You still get us in that premiere?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE GERMAN WON'T BE ABLE TO HELP THEMSELVES BUT IMAGINE THE CRUELTY THEIR BROTHERS ENDURED AT OUR HANDS  AND OUR BOOT HEELS AND THE EDGE OF OUR KNIVES</pattern><template>And the German will be sickened by us.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Where is that exactly?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHEN THE GERMAN CLOSES THEIR EYES AT NIGHT AND THEY'RE TORTURED BY THEIR SUBCONSCIOUS FOR THE EVIL THEY HAVE DONE  IT WILL BE WITH THOUGHTS OF US THAT THEY ARE TORTURED WITH</pattern><template>Sound good?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WERE FIVE OF THEM</pattern><template>The father, Jacob.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'LL BE DONNY'S ASSISTANT</pattern><template>I don't speak Italian.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW AS FAR AS YOUR PAESANOS  SERGEANT DONOWITZ AND PRIVATE OMAR</pattern><template>How you know our names?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A FATHER</pattern><template>My baby was born today.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I GUESS THAT SHOULD DO IT</pattern><template>However, before I go, could I have another glass of your delicious milk?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE TAKE THE GIRL AND LEAVE</pattern><template>It's that simple, Willi.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S SERGEANT DONNY DONOWITZ</pattern><template>You might know him better by his nickname.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ORDER THREE GLASSES</pattern><template>That's the German three.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  WHERE I'M FROM</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>SITTING IN YOUR CHAIR  I WOULD PROBABLY SAY THE SAME THING  AND 999  999 TIMES OUT OF A MILLION  YOU WOULD BE CORRECT</pattern><template>But in the pages of history, every once in a while, fate reaches out and extends its hand.</template></category><category><pattern>SOUND GOOD</pattern><template>Yes, sir!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT  SIR</pattern><template>I hear you're pretty good with that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN</pattern><template>It means you getting us in that premiere.</template></category><category><pattern>OVER THERE IS A VERY CAPABLE TWO WAY RADIO AND SITTING BEHIND IT IS A MORE THAN CAPABLE RADIO OPERATOR NAMED HERMANN</pattern><template>Get me someone on the other end of that radio with the power of the pen to authorize my, let's call it, the terms of my conditional surrender.</template></category><category><pattern>COME DOWN</pattern><template>Hey, Willi, what's with the machine gun? I thought we had us a deal?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S THE ONE WHO IS GOING TO GET YOU INTO THE PREMIERE</pattern><template>It'll be you, her, and two German born members of the Basterds.</template></category><category><pattern>DOMINICK DECOCCO</pattern><template>What's that American expression?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TO KNOW ABOUT GERMANS HIDING IN TREES</pattern><template>And you need to tell me. And you need to tell me right now.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  TALK</pattern><template>I'm a father.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MEANS I GOT A LITTLE INDIAN IN ME</pattern><template>And our battle plan will be that of an Apache resistance.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REMEMBER HIM  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>Yeah, I remember him.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU DON'T BLOW IT  WITH THAT  I CAN GET YOU IN THE BUILDING</pattern><template>Who does what?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE YOUR PRISONERS</pattern><template>How about my knife?</template></category><category><pattern>MARCEL  BURN IT DOWN</pattern><template>Oui, Shosanna.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  LET'S PRETEND THERE WERE NO GERMANS AND EVERYTHING WENT EXACTLY THE WAY IT WAS SUPPOSED TO</pattern><template>What was the next step?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A MEXICAN STANDOFF  AND THAT WAS NOT THE DEAL</pattern><template>No trust, no deal.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SO FAST</pattern><template>We only got a deal, we trust each other.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A GERMAN  YOU IDIOT</pattern><template>Speak English pretty good for a German.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S BEEN SHOT</pattern><template>But she's alive.</template></category><category><pattern>CAUGHT YOU FLINCHING</pattern><template>Touch me again, Kraut burger.</template></category><category><pattern>ANOTHER ONE UP THERE YOU MIGHT BE FAMILIAR WITH</pattern><template>Sergeant Hugo Stiglitz.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  IF ONE WERE TO DETERMINE WHAT ATTRIBUTE THE GERMAN PEOPLE SHARE WITH A BEAST  IT WOULD BE THE CUNNING AND THE PREDATORY INSTINCT OF A HAWK</pattern><template>But if one were to determine what attributes the Jews share with a beast, it would be that of the rat.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM TO POINT OUT ON THIS MAP THE GERMAN POSITION</pattern><template>Ask him how many Germans.</template></category><category><pattern>NO GUNS  NO GUNS ME  NO GUNS YOU</pattern><template>And we take the girl and leave.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D YOU INTEND TO GET THEM IN THAT PREMIERE</pattern><template>Hand me my purse.</template></category><category><pattern>MONSIEUR LAPADITE  ARE YOU AWARE OF THE NICKNAME THE PEOPLE OF FRANCE HAVE GIVEN ME</pattern><template>I have no interest in such things.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS A TAVERN</pattern><template>Yeah, in a basement.</template></category><category><pattern>OVER AND OUT</pattern><template>When I kill that guy, you got 30 feet to get to that guard.</template></category><category><pattern>A GENERAL</pattern><template>I'm betting for...</template></category><category><pattern>I RESPECTFULLY REFUSE  SIR</pattern><template>Hear that?</template></category><category><pattern>HAND ME MY PURSE</pattern><template>Lieutenant Hicox was going as my escort.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  OKAY</pattern><template>Aldo, I'm going to trust you.</template></category><category><pattern>AS OF THIS MOMENT  BOTH OMAR AND DONOWITZ SHOULD BE SITTING IN THE VERY SEATS WE LEFT THEM IN</pattern><template>Double zero 23 and double zero 24, if my memory serves.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ONLY GOT A DEAL  WE TRUST EACH OTHER</pattern><template>And a Mexican standoff ain't trust.</template></category><category><pattern>PRACTICE</pattern><template>Au revoir, Shosanna!</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER  BEFORE I GO  COULD I HAVE ANOTHER GLASS OF YOUR DELICIOUS MILK</pattern><template>But of course.</template></category><category><pattern>I SUPPOSE I WOULD</pattern><template>Has a rat ever done anything to you to create this animosity you feel toward them?</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU AGREE</pattern><template>Yet, I assume you don't share the same animosity with squirrels that you do with rats, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>KILLING NAZIS</pattern><template>I don't know about you all, but I sure as hell didn't come down from the goddamn Smoky Mountains, cross 5, 000 miles of water, fight my way through half of Sicily and jump out of a fucking airplane to teach the Nazis lessons in humanity.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  WHY HE WOULD HATE THE NAME  THE HANGMAN  IS BAFFLING TO ME</pattern><template>It would appear he has done everything in his power to earn it.</template></category><category><pattern>AROUND ABOUT 12</pattern><template>What kind of artillery?</template></category><category><pattern>WE FILL YOU UP WITH MORPHINE TILL IT'S COMING OUT YOUR EARS AND JUST LIMP YOUR LITTLE ASS UP THAT REUGE CARPET</pattern><template>I know this is a silly question before I ask it, but can you Americans speak any other language than English?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOING TO WRAP IT UP IN A CAST  AND YOU GOT A GOOD HOW L BROKE MY LEG  MOUNTAIN CLIMBING STORY</pattern><template>That's German, ain't it?</template></category><category><pattern>THE GERMAN MOVIE STAR IS WORKING FOR ENGLAND</pattern><template>Yes, for the last two years now.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WANTS TO SEND A MESSAGE TO GERMANY</pattern><template>I have a message for Germany.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MASTER RACE AT PLAY</pattern><template>Basically, we have all our rotten eggs in one basket.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO DOES WHAT</pattern><template>Well, I speak the most Italian, so I'll be your escort.</template></category><category><pattern>TEN HUT</pattern><template>My name is Lieutenant Aldo Raine.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF DEAL</pattern><template>The kind you wouldn't have the authority to make.</template></category><category><pattern>CONSIDER FOR A MOMENT THE WORLD A RAT LIVES IN</pattern><template>It's a hostile world, indeed.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MET THE SERGEANT YOURSELF  WILLI</pattern><template>You remember him, don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T GOT TO BE STONEWALL JACKSON TO KNOW YOU DON'T WANT TO FIGHT IN A BASEMENT</pattern><template>She wasn't picking a place to fight.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DO NOT</pattern><template>Tell me, Aldo, if I were sitting where you're sitting, would you show me mercy?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  FIGHTING IN A BASEMENT OFFERS A LOT OF DIFFICULTIES</pattern><template>Number one being, you're fighting in a basement.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST LIKE THAT</pattern><template>But you take off that uniform, ain't nobody going to know you's a Nazi.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GERMANS' NICKNAME FOR ME IS THE LITTLE MAN</pattern><template>And as if to make my point, I'm a little surprised how tall you were in real life.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM TO GO PLAY WITH HIS DOGS</pattern><template>Before we yank that slug out you, you need to answer a few questions.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FEATURE THAT MAKES ME SUCH AN EFFECTIVE HUNTER OF THE JEWS IS  AS OPPOSED TO MOST GERMAN SOLDIERS  I CAN THINK LIKE A JEW WHERE THEY CAN ONLY THINK LIKE A GERMAN</pattern><template>More precisely, a German soldier.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A FILM CRITIC</pattern><template>List your accomplishments.</template></category><category><pattern>QUITE WELL  ACTUALLY</pattern><template>Since Goebbels has taken over, film attendance has steadily risen in Germany over the last eight years.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D HE DO THAT</pattern><template>He ordered three glasses.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHEN YOU PURCHASE FRIENDS LIKE BRIDGET VON HAMMERSMARK  YOU GET WHAT YOU PAY FOR</pattern><template>Now as far as your paesanos, Sergeant Donowitz and Private Omar...</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HIRSCHBERG</pattern><template>Send that Kraut sarge over.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  AT SOME POINT  YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE IT OFF</pattern><template>So, I'm going to give you a little something you can't take off.</template></category><category><pattern>AGES OF THE CHILDREN</pattern><template>Amos was nine or 10.</template></category><category><pattern>NAZI AIN'T GOT NO HUMANITY</pattern><template>They're the foot soldiers of a Jew hating, mass murdering maniac and they need to be destroyed.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>AND EXCEPT FOR THE TAIL  THEY EVEN RATHER LOOK ALIKE  DON'T THEY</pattern><template>It's an interesting thought, Herr Colonel.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THEY'RE STILL HERE  AND IF THEY'RE STILL ALIVE  AND THAT'S ONE BIG IF  THERE AIN'T NO WAY YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE THEM BOYS WITHOUT SETTING OFF THEM BOMBS</pattern><template>I have no doubt.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S YOUR NAME</pattern><template>Aldo.</template></category><category><pattern>GENERAL ED FENECH</pattern><template>At ease, Hicox.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL YOU KNOW IS YOU FIND THEM REPULSIVE</pattern><template>Consequently, a German soldier conducts a search of a house suspected of hiding Jews.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  IF I HAD MY WAY  YOU'D WEAR THAT GODDAMN UNIFORM FOR THE REST OF YOUR PECKER SUCKING LIFE</pattern><template>But I'm aware that ain't practical.</template></category><category><pattern>WE BOTH SPEAK A LITTLE ITALIAN</pattern><template>With an atrocious accent, no doubt.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SPEAK GERMAN BETTER THAN YOUR FRIENDS  NO</pattern><template>Have I been shot? Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU  TOO</pattern><template>Goddamn Nazi farts, sons of bitches!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT'S WHAT WE THOUGHT</pattern><template>We don't like that.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT REALLY NECESSARY</pattern><template>I'm a slave to appearances.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE READ THE REPORTS OF THIS AREA</pattern><template>But like any enterprise, when under new management, there is always a slight duplication of efforts, most of it being a complete waste of time, but needs to be done nevertheless.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT NOW I'D BE SHITTING MY PANTS IF I WAS YOU</pattern><template>Teddy Fucking Williams knocks it out of the park!</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO DOUBT</pattern><template>And, yes, some Germans will die.</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE</pattern><template>What is that English expression about shoes and feet?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DROP THEM DOWN HERE  YOU'RE DEAD</pattern><template>That's a Mexican standoff, and that was not the deal.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW IS YOUR ENGLISH  WERNER</pattern><template>Because if need be, we got a couple of fellows who can translate.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A SLAVE TO APPEARANCES</pattern><template>Scalp Hermann.</template></category><category><pattern>CONSEQUENTLY  A GERMAN SOLDIER CONDUCTS A SEARCH OF A HOUSE SUSPECTED OF HIDING JEWS</pattern><template>Where does the hawk look?</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN IT  HIRSCHBERG</pattern><template>Donny, bring that other one over here. Alive!</template></category><category><pattern>NO JUNK IN IT</pattern><template>It says here that you speak German fluently.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D MAKE THAT DEAL</pattern><template>I don't blame you.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SHE'S OURS</pattern><template>Is she okay?</template></category><category><pattern>AND A MEXICAN STANDOFF AIN'T TRUST</pattern><template>You need guns on me for it to be a Mexican standoff.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE BETS ON HOW IT ALL COMES OUT</pattern><template>If we get into trouble, we can handle it.</template></category><category><pattern>GOEBBELS CONSIDERS THE FILMS HE'S MAKING TO BE THE BEGINNING OF A NEW ERA IN GERMAN CINEMA</pattern><template>An alternative to what he considers the Jewish German intellectual cinema of the '20s, and the Jewish controlled dogma of Hollywood.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT TO TELL ME HOW MANY THEY ARE  AND YOU GOT TO TELL ME WHAT KIND OF ARTILLERY THEY'RE CARRYING WITH THEM</pattern><template>You can't expect me to divulge information that would put German lives in danger.</template></category><category><pattern>FENWAY PARK IS ON ITS FEET FOR TEDDY FUCKING BALLGAME</pattern><template>He went yard on that one, on to fucking Lansdowne Street!</template></category><category><pattern>MMM</pattern><template>Well, if this is it, old boy, I hope you don't mind if I go out speaking the King's.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A SPECIAL RUNG IN HELL RESERVED FOR PEOPLE WHO WASTE GOOD SCOTCH</pattern><template>Seeing as I may be rapping on the door momentarily, I must say, damn good stuff, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>GERMANS WOULD AND DID NOTICE IT</pattern><template>Okay, let's pretend there were no Germans and everything went exactly the way it was supposed to.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU VERY MUCH  COLONEL</pattern><template>Utivich, cuff the Colonel's hands behind his back.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THAT</pattern><template>Is the girl on your side?</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE RUMORS</pattern><template>Facts could be so misleading, where rumors, true or false, are often revealing.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING I'VE DONE IN MY GUISE AS AN SS COLONEL WAS SANCTIONED BY THE OSS AS A NECESSARY EVIL TO ESTABLISH MY COVER WITH THE GERMANS</pattern><template>And it was my placement of Lieutenant Raine's dynamite in Hitler and Goebbels' opera box that assured their demise.</template></category><category><pattern>BY ALL MEANS  CAPTAIN</pattern><template>There's a special rung in hell reserved for people who waste good Scotch.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FUCKING BRATWURST SMELLING</pattern><template>Goddamn you! Get off!</template></category><category><pattern>UP TOP  THEY GOT GRENADES</pattern><template>They drop them down here, you're dead.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  BEFORE THE OCCUPATION  THERE WERE FOUR JEWISH FAMILIES IN THIS AREA  ALL DAIRY FARMERS LIKE YOURSELF</pattern><template>Doleracs, Rollins, the Loveitts and the Dreyfuses.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU OFFER ME A SCOTCH AND PLAIN WATER  I COULD DRINK A SCOTCH AND PLAIN WATER</pattern><template>That a boy, Lieutenant.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU</pattern><template>I'm a German, you idiot.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JERRY BANGING  LIMBURG SMELLING</pattern><template>As Stanley said to Livingstone, Lieutenant Aldo Raine, I presume?</template></category><category><pattern>AT EASE  HICOX</pattern><template>Drink?</template></category><category><pattern>SERGEANT HUGO STIGLITZ</pattern><template>Lieutenant Aldo Raine.</template></category><category><pattern>MY BABY WAS BORN TODAY</pattern><template>In Frankfurt.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ABOUT IT</pattern><template>That sounds good.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S JUST AN ACTRESS</pattern><template>You don't got to be Stonewall Jackson to know you don't want to fight in a basement.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KIND YOU WOULDN'T HAVE THE AUTHORITY TO MAKE</pattern><template>However, I'm sure this mission of yours has a commanding officer.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OTHER LOOKS ODD</pattern><template>Germans would and did notice it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU TRY TELLING US WHAT THE FUCK HAPPENED</pattern><template>The British officer blew his German act and the Gestapo major saw it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MAKE THAT DEAL</pattern><template>I'd make that deal.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'VE BEEN TWO RECENT DEVELOPMENTS REGARDING OPERATION KINO</pattern><template>One, the venue has been changed from The Ritz to a much smaller venue.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOUR MISSION  SOME WOULD CALL A TERRORIST PLOT  AS OF THIS MOMENT  IS STILL A GO</pattern><template>That's a pretty exciting story.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  YOU'RE A LITTLE FELLOW  BUT NOT CIRCUS MIDGET LITTLE  AS YOUR REPUTATION WOULD SUGGEST</pattern><template>Where's my men?</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T THINK SO</pattern><template>You don't like them.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST A NAME THAT STUCK</pattern><template>Well, you do have to admit, it is catchy.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU MUMBLE ITALIAN AND BRAZEN THROUGH IT  IS THAT THE PLAN</pattern><template>That's about it.</template></category><category><pattern>GODDAMN NAZI FARTS  SONS OF BITCHES</pattern><template>Get your hands off me.</template></category><category><pattern>TO MY KNOWLEDGE  THOSE WERE THE JEWISH FAMILIES AMONG THE DAIRY FARMERS</pattern><template>Herr Colonel, would it disturb you if I smoked my pipe?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW YOU KNOW OUR NAMES</pattern><template>Lieutenant Aldo, if you don't think I wouldn't interrogate every single one of your swastika marked survivors, we simply aren't operating on the level of mutual respect I assumed.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOSANNA HAS A COLLECTION OF OVER 350 NITRATE FILM PRINTS</pattern><template>Right this way, Lieutenant.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT GUNS ON US</pattern><template>You decide to shoot, we're dead.</template></category><category><pattern>ALDO</pattern><template>I'm here, Willi.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I DO HAVE ONE QUESTION</pattern><template>When you get to your little place on Nantucket Island, I imagine you are going to take off that handsome looking SS uniform of yours.</template></category><category><pattern>LONG STORY SHORT  WE HEAR A STORY TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE  IT AIN'T</pattern><template>Sitting in your chair, I would probably say the same thing, and 999. 999 times out of a million, you would be correct.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU MAD</pattern><template>What have you done?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GERMAN  AIN'T IT</pattern><template>You all like climbing mountains, don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAVE YOU DONE</pattern><template>I made a deal with your general for that man's life!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SOUNDS GOOD</pattern><template>It sounds like shit. What else are we going to do? Go home?</template></category><category><pattern>AND OUR BATTLE PLAN WILL BE THAT OF AN APACHE RESISTANCE</pattern><template>We will be cruel to the Germans.</template></category><category><pattern>OBLIGE HIM</pattern><template>Did you get that for killing Jews?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIGHT KNOW HIM BETTER BY HIS NICKNAME</pattern><template>The Bear Jew.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FIRST BOOK WAS CALLED ART OF THE EYES  THE HEART AND THE MIND: A STUDY OF GERMAN CINEMA IN THE '20S</pattern><template>And the second one was called Twenty Four Frame da Vinci.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  YES  GOEBBELS WILL BE VERY  VERY  VERY MAD AT YOU FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE TO HIS BIG NIGHT</pattern><template>But you won't get Hitler, you won't get Goebbels, you won't get Goring, and you won't get Bormann.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AWARE</pattern><template>What are you aware of?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU EXPECT ME TO WALK THE RED CARPET</pattern><template>Doggy doc's going to dig that slug out your gam.</template></category><category><pattern>LIEUTENANT HICOX  AT THIS POINT AND TIME I'D LIKE TO BRIEF YOU ON OPERATION KINO</pattern><template>Three days from now Joseph Goebbels is throwing a gala premiere of one of his new movies in Paris.</template></category><category><pattern>UTIVICH  CUFF THE COLONEL'S HANDS BEHIND HIS BACK</pattern><template>Is that really necessary?</template></category><category><pattern>I ARRANGED FOR THE TAILOR TO FIT THREE TUXEDOS TONIGHT</pattern><template>How'd you intend to get them in that premiere?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  GET THE GIRL AND GO</pattern><template>Not so fast.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT THE WAY YOU SAY IT</pattern><template>That's a bingo.  You just say,  Bingo.  Bingo! How fun.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH GIRL</pattern><template>Who do you think?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT REALLY SURE</pattern><template>Well, I guess that should do it.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THEY MADE THAT DEAL  BUT THEY DON'T GIVE A FUCK ABOUT HIM  THEY NEED YOU</pattern><template>You'll be shot for this!</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A MESSAGE FOR GERMANY</pattern><template>That you are all going to die.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT REWARD WILL BE  YOUR FAMILY WILL CEASE TO BE HARASSED IN ANY WAY BY THE GERMAN MILITARY DURING THE REST OF OUR OCCUPATION OF YOUR COUNTRY</pattern><template>You're sheltering enemies of the state, are you not?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS THAT EXACTLY</pattern><template>Maynardville, Tennessee.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BAR IS IN THE GLOBE</pattern><template>Something for yourself, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>AMOS WAS NINE OR 10</pattern><template>And Shosanna?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  MY JOB DICTATES THAT I MUST HAVE MY MEN ENTER YOUR HOME AND CONDUCT A THOROUGH SEARCH BEFORE I CAN OFFICIALLY CROSS YOUR FAMILY'S NAME OFF MY LIST</pattern><template>And if there are any irregularities to be found, rest assured they will be.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT FILM  SIR</pattern><template>The motion picture is called Nation's Pride.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I'M AWARE THAT AIN'T PRACTICAL</pattern><template>I mean, at some point, you're going to have to take it off.</template></category><category><pattern>IN NADINE  THERE'S A TAVERN CALLED LA LOUISIANE</pattern><template>There you'll rendezvous with our double agent. She'll take it from there.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GERMANS CALL THEM THE BASTERDS</pattern><template>The Basterds.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOING TO BURN IT</pattern><template>Yeah, that's what we thought.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAY YOU CAN SPOT THEM</pattern><template>Just like that.</template></category><category><pattern>I UNDERSTAND YOUR TREPIDATION IN REPEATING IT</pattern><template>Heydrich apparently hates the moniker the good people of Prague have bestowed on him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHISKEY  STRAIGHT</pattern><template>No junk in it.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT TO RECEIVE THE CONGRESSIONAL MEDAL OF HONOR FOR MY INVALUABLE ASSISTANCE IN THE TOPPLING OF THE THIRD REICH</pattern><template>In fact, I want all the members of Operation Kino to receive the Congressional Medal of Honor.</template></category><category><pattern>WICKI HERE  AN AUSTRIAN JEW  GOT THE FUCK OUT OF MUNICH WHILE THE GETTING WAS GOOD</pattern><template>Became American, got drafted, come back to give y'all what for.</template></category><category><pattern>ALDO THE APACHE AND THE LITTLE MAN</pattern><template>What do you mean the Little Man?</template></category><category><pattern>THE FATHER  JACOB</pattern><template>Wife, Miram.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT</pattern><template>Now, that I can't abide.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE IF NEED BE  WE GOT A COUPLE OF FELLOWS WHO CAN TRANSLATE</pattern><template>Wicki here, an Austrian Jew, got the fuck out of Munich while the getting was good.</template></category><category><pattern>AGAIN  THIS IS JUST A RUMOR  BUT WE HEARD THE DREYFUSES HAD MADE THEIR WAY INTO SPAIN</pattern><template>So, the rumors you've heard have been of escape?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THE GIRL ON YOUR SIDE</pattern><template>Which girl?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE FILMS  AIN'T THEY</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK SO  SIR</pattern><template>Paris when it sizzles.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T KNOW</pattern><template>You said it was in a tavern.</template></category><category><pattern>INSTEAD OF PUTTING HIM UP AGAINST A WALL  THE HIGH COMMAND DECIDED TO SEND HIM BACK TO BERLIN TO BE MADE AN EXAMPLE OF</pattern><template>Needless to say, once the Basterds heard about him, he never got there.</template></category><category><pattern>EACH AND EVERY MAN UNDER MY COMMAND OWES ME 100 NAZI SCALPS</pattern><template>And I want my scalps.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ALL LIKE CLIMBING MOUNTAINS  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>I don't. I like smoking, drinking and ordering in restaurants.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WANT YOU TO LOOK DEEP INTO THE FACE OF THE JEW WHO'S GOING TO DO IT</pattern><template>Marcel, burn it down.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS THE NEXT STEP</pattern><template>Tuxedos.</template></category><category><pattern>LEAST OF ALL  BY TOMORROW NIGHT</pattern><template>However, there's something you don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT SHE'S ALIVE</pattern><template>Okay, Wilhelm.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU GET TO YOUR LITTLE PLACE ON NANTUCKET ISLAND  I IMAGINE YOU ARE GOING TO TAKE OFF THAT HANDSOME LOOKING SS UNIFORM OF YOURS</pattern><template>Ain't you?</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER HEARD OF THEM</pattern><template>Whole point of the Secret Service, old boy, you not hearing of them.</template></category><category><pattern>TO GET THEM INTO THE PREMIERE WEARING MILITARY UNIFORMS WITH ALL THE MILITARY THERE WOULD'VE BEEN SUICIDE</pattern><template>But going as members of the German film industry, they wear tuxedos and fit in with everybody else.</template></category><category><pattern>IN FRANKFURT</pattern><template>Five hours ago.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'LL MAKE THE RENDEZVOUS</pattern><template>Stiglitz, right?</template></category><category><pattern>ENORMOUS CHANGE AT THE LAST MINUTE</pattern><template>That's not very Germatic.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IF YOU EVER WANT TO EAT A SAUERKRAUT SANDWICH AGAIN  YOU GOT TO SHOW ME ON THIS HERE MAP WHERE THEY ARE</pattern><template>You got to tell me how many they are, and you got to tell me what kind of artillery they're carrying with them.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  SIT DOWN  MEANS  WERNER</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DOES THE HAWK LOOK</pattern><template>He looks in the barn, he looks in the attic, he looks in the cellar, he looks everywhere he would hide.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THERE ARE SO MANY PLACES IT WOULD NEVER OCCUR TO A HAWK TO HIDE</pattern><template>However, the reason the F�hrer has brought me off my Alps in Austria and placed me in French cow country today is because it does occur to me.</template></category><category><pattern>OUI  SHOSANNA</pattern><template>My name is Shosanna Dreyfus, and this is the face of Jewish vengeance.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF I DON'T PICK UP THIS PHONE RIGHT HERE  YOU MAY VERY WELL GET ALL FOUR</pattern><template>And if you get all four, you end the war tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER INTERESTING AS THE THOUGHT MAY BE  IT MAKES NOT ONE BIT OF DIFFERENCE TO HOW YOU FEEL</pattern><template>If a rat were to walk in here, right now, as I'm talking would you greet it with a saucer of your delicious milk?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S YOUR NAME  SOLDIER</pattern><template>Wilhelm.</template></category><category><pattern>DRINK</pattern><template>If you offer me a scotch and plain water, I could drink a scotch and plain water.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THAT TASTES BETTER GOING DOWN</pattern><template>You know, where I'm from...</template></category><category><pattern>ALAS  YOU'RE NOW IN THE HANDS OF THE SS</pattern><template>My hands to be exact.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAD JUST BECOME A</pattern><template>He had just become a father!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT CHOICE YOU GOT  SON</pattern><template>Okay, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL</pattern><template>Down with Hitler.</template></category><category><pattern>BASICALLY  WE HAVE ALL OUR ROTTEN EGGS IN ONE BASKET</pattern><template>The objective of Operation Kino, blow up the basket.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH AN ATROCIOUS ACCENT  NO DOUBT</pattern><template>But that doesn't exactly kill us in the crib.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T BLAME YOU</pattern><template>Damn good deal.</template></category><category><pattern>YET  I ASSUME YOU DON'T SHARE THE SAME ANIMOSITY WITH SQUIRRELS THAT YOU DO WITH RATS  DO YOU</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>MORE PRECISELY  A GERMAN SOLDIER</pattern><template>Now, if one were to determine what attribute the German people share with a beast, it would be the cunning and the predatory instinct of a hawk.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT VERY GERMATIC</pattern><template>Why the hell is Goebbels doing stuff so damn peculiar?</template></category><category><pattern>THE BASTERDS</pattern><template>Never heard of them.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE JERRIES HAVE HEARD OF THEM  BECAUSE THESE YANKS HAVE BEEN THEM THE DEVIL</pattern><template>You'll be dropped into France, about 24 kilometers outside of Paris.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M OFFICIALLY SURRENDERING MYSELF OVER TO YOU  LIEUTENANT RAINE</pattern><template>We're your prisoners.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT WAS MY PLACEMENT OF LIEUTENANT RAINE'S DYNAMITE IN HITLER AND GOEBBELS' OPERA BOX THAT ASSURED THEIR DEMISE</pattern><template>By the way, that last part is actually true.</template></category><category><pattern>EIGHT JEWISH AMERICAN SOLDIERS</pattern><template>Now, you all might've heard rumors about the armada happening soon.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT AMERICAN EXPRESSION</pattern><template>If the shoe fits, you must wear it.  Fucking shithead.</template></category><category><pattern>NO TRUST  NO DEAL</pattern><template>All right, Aldo.</template></category><category><pattern>NEEDLESS TO SAY  ONCE THE BASTERDS HEARD ABOUT HIM  HE NEVER GOT THERE</pattern><template>Sergeant Hugo Stiglitz?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW I  ON THE OTHER HAND  LOVE MY UNOFFICIAL TITLE PRECISELY BECAUSE I'VE EARNED IT</pattern><template>The feature that makes me such an effective hunter of the Jews is, as opposed to most German soldiers, I can think like a Jew where they can only think like a German.</template></category><category><pattern>IMPRESSIVE  DON'T BE MODEST  LIEUTENANT  WHAT ARE THEIR TITLES</pattern><template>The first book was called Art of the Eyes, the Heart and the Mind: A Study of German Cinema in the '20s.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE THE FOOT SOLDIERS OF A JEW HATING  MASS MURDERING MANIAC AND THEY NEED TO BE DESTROYED</pattern><template>That's why any and every son of a bitch we find wearing a Nazi uniform, they're going to die.</template></category><category><pattern>UPON CROSSING OUR LINES  COLONEL LANDA AND HIS MAN WILL SURRENDER TO YOU</pattern><template>You will then take over driving of the truck and bring them straight to me for debriefing. Is that clear, Lieutenant?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING TO BE DROPPED INTO FRANCE DRESSED AS CIVILIANS</pattern><template>Once we're in enemy territory, as a bushwhacking guerrilla army, we're going to be doing one thing and one thing only.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT OF COURSE</pattern><template>Monsieur LaPadite, are you aware of the nickname the people of France have given me?</template></category><category><pattern>I MIGHT ADD  ALSO  THAT ANY INFORMATION THAT MAKES THE PERFORMANCE OF MY DUTY EASIER WILL NOT BE MET WITH PUNISHMENT</pattern><template>Actually, quite the contrary.</template></category><category><pattern>RATS SPREAD DISEASE</pattern><template>They bite people.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL BE CRUEL TO THE GERMANS</pattern><template>And through our cruelty, they will know who we are.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  HERR COLONEL  MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME</pattern><template>Now, my job dictates that I must have my men enter your home and conduct a thorough search before I can officially cross your family's name off my list.</template></category><category><pattern>I SUSPECT THAT WON'T BE TOO MUCH TROUBLE FOR YOU</pattern><template>Your contact is Bridget von Hammersmark.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU CAN'T BRING THOSE HERE ON A PUBLIC VEHICLE</pattern><template>They're films, ain't they?</template></category><category><pattern>THIRTY  31</pattern><template>Continue.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER  THERE'S SOMETHING YOU DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>There've been two recent developments regarding Operation Kino.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ALDO THE APACHE</pattern><template>Werner, if you heard of us, you probably heard we ain't in the prisoner taking business.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE ARE THE BASTERDS</pattern><template>Ever heard of us?</template></category><category><pattern>HEARD OF HIM</pattern><template>Everybody in the German Army has heard of Hugo Stiglitz.</template></category><category><pattern>COLONEL LANDA WILL PUT YOU AND PRIVATE UTIVICH IN A TRUCK AS PRISONERS</pattern><template>Then he and his radio operator will get in the truck and drive to our lines.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A LITTLE SOMETHING YOU CAN'T TAKE OFF</pattern><template>You know, Lieutenant, you're getting pretty good at that.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALL COME HERE TO SEE IF YOU WANT TO GO PRO</pattern><template>Can I assume you know who we are?</template></category><category><pattern>YET  THEY'RE BOTH RODENTS  ARE THEY NOT</pattern><template>And except for the tail, they even rather look alike, don't they?</template></category><category><pattern>DOWN WITH HITLER</pattern><template>All the way down, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT JEW HUNTER</pattern><template>Just a name that stuck.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT A BOY  LIEUTENANT</pattern><template>Make it yourself like a good chap, will you?</template></category><category><pattern>ASK IF HE'S GOING TO TAKE OFF HIS UNIFORM</pattern><template>He's going to burn it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHILE I'M VERY FAMILIAR WITH YOU AND YOUR FAMILY  I HAVE NO WAY OF KNOWING IF YOU ARE FAMILIAR WITH WHO I AM</pattern><template>Are you aware of my existence?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A DETECTIVE</pattern><template>A damn good detective.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  SIR  SUCH AS THEY ARE  I WRITE REVIEWS AND ARTICLES FOR A PUBLICATION CALLED FILMS AND FILMMAKERS  AND I'VE HAD TWO BOOKS PUBLISHED</pattern><template>Impressive. Don't be modest, Lieutenant. What are their titles?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  NOW  WERNER  THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE WRONG  BECAUSE THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I EXPECT</pattern><template>I need to know about Germans hiding in trees.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE I BEEN SHOT  YES</pattern><template>I don't see me tripping the light fantastique up a red carpet anytime soon.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO SWITCH BACK TO FRENCH NOW  AND I WANT YOU TO FOLLOW MY MASQUERADE</pattern><template>Is that clear?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HOW CAN I</pattern><template>What choice you got, son?</template></category><category><pattern>END THE WAR TONIGHT</pattern><template>I'd make that deal.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I SEE YOUR POINT</pattern><template>We fill you up with morphine till it's coming out your ears and just limp your little ass up that reuge carpet.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>We're American.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WILL BE MET WITH REWARD</pattern><template>And that reward will be, your family will cease to be harassed in any way by the German military during the rest of our occupation of your country.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SO GODDAMN FAST  DOC</pattern><template>Tell him to go play with his dogs.</template></category><category><pattern>HE BASHES THEIR BRAINS IN WITH A BASEBALL BAT  WHAT HE DOES</pattern><template>And, Werner, I'm going to ask you one last goddamn time, and if you still respectfully refuse, I'm calling The Bear Jew over.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M THINKING GETTING A WHACK AT PLANTING OLD UNCLE ADOLF MAKES THIS HORSE A DIFFERENT COLOR</pattern><template>What is that supposed to mean?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT CLEAR</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  GENTLEMEN  LET'S DISCUSS THE PROSPECT OF ENDING THE WAR TONIGHT</pattern><template>So, the way I see it, since Hitler's death or possible rescue rests solely on my reaction, if I do nothing, it's as if I'm causing his death even more than yourselves.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  LET'S JUST SAY  SHE GOT WHAT SHE DESERVED</pattern><template>And when you purchase friends like Bridget von Hammersmark, you get what you pay for.</template></category><category><pattern>FINDING PEOPLE IS MY SPECIALTY  SO NATURALLY  I WORKED FOR THE NAZIS FINDING PEOPLE</pattern><template>And, yes, some of them were Jews.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN SIT DOWN</pattern><template>How is your English, Werner?</template></category><category><pattern>TWO HITS  I HIT YOU  YOU HIT THE GROUND</pattern><template>English?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL BE SHOT FOR THIS</pattern><template>Nah, I don't think so. More like chewed out. I've been chewed out before.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT CORRECT</pattern><template>To my knowledge, those were the Jewish families among the dairy farmers.</template></category><category><pattern>HAS A RAT EVER DONE ANYTHING TO YOU TO CREATE THIS ANIMOSITY YOU FEEL TOWARD THEM</pattern><template>Rats spread disease.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY NEEDS TO CALM DOWN</pattern><template>You're letting your imagination get the better of you.</template></category><category><pattern>DOUBLE ZERO 23 AND DOUBLE ZERO 24  IF MY MEMORY SERVES</pattern><template>Explosives still around their ankles, still ready to explode.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED GUNS ON ME FOR IT TO BE A MEXICAN STANDOFF</pattern><template>You got guns on us.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE WE YANK THAT SLUG OUT YOU  YOU NEED TO ANSWER A FEW QUESTIONS</pattern><template>Few questions about what?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE YOU'LL RENDEZVOUS WITH OUR DOUBLE AGENT  SHE'LL TAKE IT FROM THERE</pattern><template>She's the one who is going to get you into the premiere.</template></category><category><pattern>DOLERACS  ROLLINS  THE LOVEITTS AND THE DREYFUSES</pattern><template>Is that correct?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT PRETTY LITTLE NEST YOU FEATHERED FOR YOURSELF</pattern><template>Well, if you're willing to barbecue the whole High Command, I suppose that's worth certain considerations.</template></category><category><pattern>WIFE  MIRAM</pattern><template>And her brother, Bob.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE MEANING OF YOUR VISIT  PLEASANT THOUGH IT IS  IS MYSTERIOUS TO ME</pattern><template>The Germans looked through my house nine months ago for hiding Jews and found nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>IN FACT  WHY DON'T YOU START PRACTICING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOUR OCCUPATION BEFORE THE WAR</pattern><template>I'm a film critic.</template></category><category><pattern>HERMANN  UNCUFF THEM</pattern><template>I'm officially surrendering myself over to you, Lieutenant Raine.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T SEE ME TRIPPING THE LIGHT FANTASTIQUE UP A RED CARPET ANYTIME SOON</pattern><template>Least of all, by tomorrow night.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY BITE PEOPLE</pattern><template>Rats were the cause of the bubonic plague, but that's some time ago.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER  THE REASON THE F�HRER HAS BROUGHT ME OFF MY ALPS IN AUSTRIA AND PLACED ME IN FRENCH COW COUNTRY TODAY IS BECAUSE IT DOES OCCUR TO ME</pattern><template>Because I'm aware what tremendous feats human beings are capable of once they abandon dignity.</template></category><category><pattern>ASK HIM IF HE WANTS TO LIVE</pattern><template>Tell him to point out on this map the German position.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW SOMETHING  UTIVICH</pattern><template>I think this just might be my masterpiece.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SHELTERING ENEMIES OF THE STATE  ARE YOU NOT</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH LEADS ME TO THE CONCLUSION THAT THEY'VE EITHER MADE GOOD THEIR ESCAPE OR SOMEONE IS VERY SUCCESSFULLY HIDING THEM</pattern><template>What have you heard about the Dreyfuses, monsieur LaPadite?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL BE YOU  HER  AND TWO GERMAN BORN MEMBERS OF THE BASTERDS</pattern><template>She's also made all the other arrangements you're going to need.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT THE KIND OF MAN YOU NEED  LOQUACIOUS TYPE</pattern><template>Fair point, Lieutenant.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE ALDO THE APACHE</pattern><template>So you're The Jew Hunter.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I SMOKE MY PIPE AS WELL</pattern><template>Please, Herr Colonel, make yourself at home.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  IF YOU HEARD OF ALDO THE APACHE  YOU GOT TO HAVE HEARD ABOUT THE BEAR JEW</pattern><template>I heard of The Bear Jew.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T LIKE THEM</pattern><template>You don't really know why you don't like them.</template></category><category><pattern>AT THAT TIME  35 MILLIMETER NITRATE FILM WAS SO FLAMMABLE THAT YOU COULDN'T EVEN BRING A REEL ONTO A STREETCAR</pattern><template>Hey, you can't bring those here on a public vehicle.</template></category><category><pattern>MY HANDS TO BE EXACT</pattern><template>And they've been waiting a long time to touch you.</template></category><category><pattern>CHAMPAGNE</pattern><template>Who wants to send a message to Germany?</template></category><category><pattern>AND ALL Y'ALL WILL GET ME 100 NAZI SCALPS TAKEN FROM THE HEADS OF 100 DEAD NAZIS</pattern><template>Or you will die trying!</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE AGAIN</pattern><template>You say he wants to take on the Jews at their own game.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST TAKE THAT FUCKING TRAITOR  AND GET HER OUT OF MY SIGHT</pattern><template>Not so goddamn fast, doc.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU AWARE OF MY EXISTENCE</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SHELTERING THEM UNDERNEATH YOUR FLOORBOARDS  AREN'T YOU</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THE F�HRER AND GOEBBELS' PROPAGANDA HAVE SAID PRETTY MUCH THE SAME THING</pattern><template>But where our conclusions differ, is I don't consider the comparison an insult.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DECIDE TO SHOOT  WE'RE DEAD</pattern><template>Up top, they got grenades.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT US A GERMAN HERE WHO WANTS TO DIE FOR COUNTRY</pattern><template>Oblige him.</template></category><category><pattern>ANTONIO MARGHERITI</pattern><template>Margheriti.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STILL GET US IN THAT PREMIERE</pattern><template>You speak German better than your friends? No.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT THE GIST</pattern><template>I think so, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS JERRY OF YOURS  STIGLITZ  NOT EXACTLY THE LOQUACIOUS TYPE  IS HE</pattern><template>Is that the kind of man you need? Loquacious type?</template></category><category><pattern>PSST  PSST</pattern><template>So when the military history of this night is written, it will be recorded that I was part of Operation Kino from the very beginning as a double agent.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF ONE WERE TO DETERMINE WHAT ATTRIBUTES THE JEWS SHARE WITH A BEAST  IT WOULD BE THAT OF THE RAT</pattern><template>The F�hrer and Goebbels' propaganda have said pretty much the same thing.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WASN'T PICKING A PLACE TO FIGHT</pattern><template>She was picking a place isolated and without Germans.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OUTSIDE</pattern><template>Who are you?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T  I LIKE SMOKING  DRINKING AND ORDERING IN RESTAURANTS</pattern><template>But I see your point.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE CHOSE THE SPOT</pattern><template>Isn't that just dandy?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A BINGO   YOU JUST SAY   BINGO   BINGO  HOW FUN</pattern><template>But I digress. Where were we?</template></category><category><pattern>MARGHERITI</pattern><template>Dominick Decocco.</template></category><category><pattern>IT COULDN'T BE BOTH</pattern><template>How'd the shooting start?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY ANY AND EVERY SON OF A BITCH WE FIND WEARING A NAZI UNIFORM  THEY'RE GOING TO DIE</pattern><template>Now, I'm the direct descendent of the mountain man Jim Bridger.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE DONE MY SHARE OF BOOTLEGGING</pattern><template>Up there, if you engage in what the federal government calls illegal activity, but what we call just a man trying to make a living for his family selling moonshine liquor, it behooves oneself to keep his wits.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST HAVE A FEW QUESTIONS  MONSIEUR LAPADITE</pattern><template>If you can assist me with answers, my department can close the file on your family.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE WAY DOWN  SIR</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY WILL FIND THE EVIDENCE OF OUR CRUELTY IN THE DISEMBOWELED  DISMEMBERED AND DISFIGURED BODIES OF THEIR BROTHERS WE LEAVE BEHIND US</pattern><template>And the German won't be able to help themselves but imagine the cruelty their brothers endured at our hands, and our boot heels and the edge of our knives.</template></category><category><pattern>GODDAMN YOU  GET OFF</pattern><template>Hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>NAH  I DON'T THINK SO  MORE LIKE CHEWED OUT  I'VE BEEN CHEWED OUT BEFORE</pattern><template>You know, Utivich and myself heard that deal you made with the brass.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  QUITE THE CONTRARY</pattern><template>It will be met with reward.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A LITTLE SOMETHING YOU CAN'T TAKE OFF</pattern><template>You know something, Utivich?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT TO TRUST YOU</pattern><template>But...</template></category><category><pattern>THE BEAR JEW</pattern><template>Now, if you heard of Aldo the Apache, you got to have heard about The Bear Jew.</template></category><category><pattern>IF A RAT WERE TO SCAMPER THROUGH YOUR FRONT DOOR  RIGHT NOW  WOULD YOU GREET IT WITH HOSTILITY</pattern><template>I suppose I would.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU NEED TO TELL ME  AND YOU NEED TO TELL ME RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Now, just take that finger of yours and point out on this here map where this party is being held, how many is coming and what they brought to play with.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THAT PATROL WERE TO HAVE ANY CRACK SHOTS  THAT ORCHARD WOULD BE A GODDAMN SNIPER'S DELIGHT</pattern><template>So if you ever want to eat a sauerkraut sandwich again, you got to show me on this here map where they are.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  UTIVICH AND MYSELF HEARD THAT DEAL YOU MADE WITH THE BRASS</pattern><template>End the war tonight?</template></category><category><pattern>HANS LANDA</pattern><template>You've had a nice long run, Aldo.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T REALLY KNOW WHY YOU DON'T LIKE THEM</pattern><template>All you know is you find them repulsive.</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE WE'RE IN ENEMY TERRITORY  AS A BUSHWHACKING GUERRILLA ARMY  WE'RE GOING TO BE DOING ONE THING AND ONE THING ONLY</pattern><template>Killing Nazis.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT YOU  UTIVICH  CAN YOU ABIDE IT</pattern><template>Not one damn bit, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE CHILDREN  AMOS AND SHOSANNA</pattern><template>Ages of the children?</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN GOOD DEAL</pattern><template>And that pretty little nest you feathered for yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>ALDO  I'M GOING TO TRUST YOU</pattern><template>Come down.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WILHELM</pattern><template>What do you say we make us a deal?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  OBVIOUSLY  I HAVEN'T SEEN ANY OF THE FILMS MADE IN THE LAST THREE YEARS  BUT I'M FAMILIAR WITH IT</pattern><template>Explain it to me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT SHALL THE HISTORY BOOKS READ</pattern><template>I implore you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE IN HERE DRINKING  CELEBRATING</pattern><template>They're the ones that came in shooting and killing. It's not my fault!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I REMEMBER HIM</pattern><template>His wife had a baby tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>DER FUHRER IS ATTENDING THE PREMIERE</pattern><template>Fuck a duck!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A BINGO</pattern><template>Is that the way you say it?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN SEE SINCE YOU DIDN'T SEE WHAT HAPPENED INSIDE  THAT THE NAZIS BEING THERE MUST LOOK ODD</pattern><template>Yeah, we got a word for that kind of odd in English.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  ALDO</pattern><template>Fine.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SHOSANNA</pattern><template>And Shosanna was 18 or 19.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE GOT A WORD FOR THAT KIND OF ODD IN ENGLISH</pattern><template>It's called suspicious.</template></category><category><pattern>STIGLITZ</pattern><template>Say auf Wiedersehen to your Nazi balls.</template></category><category><pattern>DONOWITZ SPEAKS SECOND MOST  SO HE'LL BE YOUR ITALIAN CAMERAMAN</pattern><template>Omar, third most.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  NOW THAT YOU PUT IT LIKE THAT  I GUESS YOU DO</pattern><template>This Jerry of yours, Stiglitz, not exactly the loquacious type, is he?</template></category><category><pattern>IT PROBABLY HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH THE SECOND DEVELOPMENT</pattern><template>Which is?</template></category><category><pattern>HEYDRICH APPARENTLY HATES THE MONIKER THE GOOD PEOPLE OF PRAGUE HAVE BESTOWED ON HIM</pattern><template>Actually, why he would hate the name  the Hangman  is baffling to me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE GERMAN WILL FEAR US</pattern><template>And when the German closes their eyes at night and they're tortured by their subconscious for the evil they have done, it will be with thoughts of us that they are tortured with.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASED TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>You know what  sit down  means, Werner?</template></category><category><pattern>I IMPLORE YOU</pattern><template>We must destroy that tower.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER  ALL I HAVE TO DO IS PICK UP THIS PHONE RIGHT HERE  INFORM THE CINEMA  AND YOUR PLAN IS KAPUT</pattern><template>If they're still here, and if they're still alive, and that's one big if, there ain't no way you're going to take them boys without setting off them bombs.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE GOING TO WANT TO KNOW WHY YOU SO SPECIAL  WE LET YOU LIVE</pattern><template>So tell them, we let you live so you could spread the word through the ranks what's going to happen to every Nazi we find.</template></category><category><pattern>JOLLY GOOD  SIR</pattern><template>An American Secret Service outfit that lives deep behind enemy lines will be your assist.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE GERMAN WILL TALK ABOUT US</pattern><template>And the German will fear us.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M PROBABLY GOING TO END UP LOSING THIS LEG</pattern><template>Bye bye, acting career.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I DIGRESS  WHERE WERE WE</pattern><template>Yeah! Make a deal.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS WIFE HAD A BABY TONIGHT</pattern><template>He had just become a...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GO YOUR WAY  WE GO OURS</pattern><template>And little Max gets to grow up playing catch with his daddy.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT WOULD THAT BE</pattern><template>Stiglitz.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT</pattern><template>What's your name, soldier?</template></category><category><pattern>CONTINUE</pattern><template>And the children, Amos and Shosanna.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU WANT TO WIN THE WAR TONIGHT  WE HAVE TO MAKE A DEAL</pattern><template>What kind of deal?</template></category><category><pattern>SO TELL THEM  WE LET YOU LIVE SO YOU COULD SPREAD THE WORD THROUGH THE RANKS WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN TO EVERY NAZI WE FIND</pattern><template>Now that you've survived the war, when you get home, what you going to do?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU ARE AWARE OF WHAT THEY CALL ME</pattern><template>I'm aware.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW HOW YOU GET TO CARNEGIE HALL  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>Practice.</template></category><category><pattern>TUXEDOS</pattern><template>To get them into the premiere wearing military uniforms with all the military there would've been suicide.</template></category><category><pattern>FEW QUESTIONS ABOUT WHAT</pattern><template>About I got three men dead back there.</template></category><category><pattern>DONNY  BRING THAT OTHER ONE OVER HERE  ALIVE</pattern><template>Get the fuck up!</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED TO DONNY</pattern><template>Omar?</template></category><category><pattern>WE IN THE KILLING NAZI BUSINESS  AND  COUSIN  BUSINESS IS A BOOMING</pattern><template>Oh, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THE RUMORS YOU'VE HEARD HAVE BEEN OF ESCAPE</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOING TO TAKE THAT BIG BAT OF HIS  AND HE'S GOING TO BEAT YOUR ASS TO DEATH WITH IT</pattern><template>Now, take your Wiener schnitzel licking finger, and point out on this map what I want to know.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU JOIN MY COMMAND  YOU TAKE ON DEBIT</pattern><template>A debit you owe me, personally.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID IT WAS IN A TAVERN</pattern><template>It is a tavern.</template></category><category><pattern>WILHELM</pattern><template>She's been shot.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK A DUCK</pattern><template>What are you thinking?</template></category><category><pattern>AS STANLEY SAID TO LIVINGSTONE  LIEUTENANT ALDO RAINE  I PRESUME</pattern><template>Hans Landa.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>It wasn't your fault.</template></category><category><pattern>THE REASON FOR HUGO STIGLITZ'S CELEBRITY AMONG GERMAN SOLDIERS IS SIMPLE</pattern><template>As a German enlisted man, he killed 13 Gestapo officers.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LOOKS IN THE BARN  HE LOOKS IN THE ATTIC  HE LOOKS IN THE CELLAR  HE LOOKS EVERYWHERE HE WOULD HIDE</pattern><template>But there are so many places it would never occur to a hawk to hide.</template></category><category><pattern>STIGLITZ  RIGHT</pattern><template>That's right, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THIS IS A SILLY QUESTION BEFORE I ASK IT  BUT CAN YOU AMERICANS SPEAK ANY OTHER LANGUAGE THAN ENGLISH</pattern><template>We both speak a little Italian.</template></category><category><pattern>WERNER  IF YOU HEARD OF US  YOU PROBABLY HEARD WE AIN'T IN THE PRISONER TAKING BUSINESS</pattern><template>We in the killing Nazi business, and, cousin, business is a booming.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT THE DREYFUSES  MONSIEUR LAPADITE</pattern><template>Only rumors.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WOULD LIKE THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA TO PURCHASE PROPERTY FOR ME ON NANTUCKET ISLAND AS A REWARD FOR ALL THE COUNTLESS LIVES I'VE SAVED BY BRINGING THE TYRANNY OF THE NATIONAL SOCIALIST PARTY TO A SWIFTER THAN IMAGINED END</pattern><template>Do you have all that, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD APPEAR HE HAS DONE EVERYTHING IN HIS POWER TO EARN IT</pattern><template>Now I, on the other hand, love my unofficial title precisely because I've earned it.</template></category><category><pattern>INDEED</pattern><template>Got the gist?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D THE SHOOTING START</pattern><template>The Englishman gave himself away.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  WERNER  I'M GOING TO ASK YOU ONE LAST GODDAMN TIME  AND IF YOU STILL RESPECTFULLY REFUSE  I'M CALLING THE BEAR JEW OVER</pattern><template>He's going to take that big bat of his, and he's going to beat your ass to death with it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF TROUBLE DOES HAPPEN  WE NEED YOU TO MAKE DAMN SURE NO GERMANS  OR FRENCH  FOR THAT MATTER  ESCAPE FROM THAT BASEMENT</pattern><template>If Frau von Hammersmark's cover is compromised, the mission is kaput.</template></category><category><pattern>FUN WHILE IT LASTED</pattern><template>How do you expect me to walk the red carpet?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  WE LIKE OUR NAZIS IN UNIFORMS</pattern><template>That way you can spot them.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T SPEAK ITALIAN</pattern><template>Like I said, third best. Just keep your fucking mouth shut.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS PICKING A PLACE ISOLATED AND WITHOUT GERMANS</pattern><template>Mmm.</template></category><category><pattern>WHETHER OR NOT YOU'RE GOING TO LEAVE THIS DITCH ALIVE DEPENDS ENTIRELY ON YOU</pattern><template>Up the road a piece, there's an orchard.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE'LL BE LEAVING A LITTLE EARLIER</pattern><template>We're going to be dropped into France dressed as civilians.</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY RUMORS</pattern><template>I love rumors!</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD APPEAR THERE'S ONLY ONE THING LEFT FOR YOU TO DO</pattern><template>And what would that be?</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE I HAVEN'T HEARD ANY DISTURBANCE  I ASSUME  WHILE THEY'RE LISTENING  THEY DON'T SPEAK ENGLISH</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME</pattern><template>You fucking bratwurst smelling...</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE HOURS AGO</pattern><template>His name is Max.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I SPEAK THE MOST ITALIAN  SO I'LL BE YOUR ESCORT</pattern><template>Donowitz speaks second most, so he'll be your Italian cameraman.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GERMANS LOOKED THROUGH MY HOUSE NINE MONTHS AGO FOR HIDING JEWS AND FOUND NOTHING</pattern><template>I'm aware of that.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS GOOD</pattern><template>Now, are you aware of the job I've been ordered to carry out in France?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT DOESN'T EXACTLY KILL US IN THE CRIB</pattern><template>Germans don't have a good ear for Italian.</template></category><category><pattern>SPEAK ENGLISH PRETTY GOOD FOR A GERMAN</pattern><template>I agree.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'M PUTTING TOGETHER A SPECIAL TEAM  AND I NEED ME EIGHT SOLDIERS</pattern><template>Eight Jewish American soldiers.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  MONSIEUR LAPADITE  WHAT RUMORS HAVE YOU HEARD REGARDING THE DREYFUSES</pattern><template>Again, this is just a rumor, but we heard the Dreyfuses had made their way into Spain.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEWHERE IN THE LAST YEAR IT WOULD APPEAR THEY'VE VANISHED</pattern><template>Which leads me to the conclusion that they've either made good their escape or someone is very successfully hiding them.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WILHELM  HERE'S MY DEAL</pattern><template>You let me and one of my men come down there and take the girl away.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IN A BASEMENT</pattern><template>You know, fighting in a basement offers a lot of difficulties.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS SO</pattern><template>How about you, Utivich?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT WILL RUIN THE EVENING</pattern><template>And, yes, Goebbels will be very, very, very mad at you for what you've done to his big night.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  JUST TAKE THAT FINGER OF YOURS AND POINT OUT ON THIS HERE MAP WHERE THIS PARTY IS BEING HELD  HOW MANY IS COMING AND WHAT THEY BROUGHT TO PLAY WITH</pattern><template>I respectfully refuse, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I AGREE</pattern><template>So let's talk.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BRITISH OFFICER BLEW HIS GERMAN ACT AND THE GESTAPO MAJOR SAW IT</pattern><template>Before we get into who shot John, why'd you invite my men to a rendezvous in a basement with a bunch of Nazis?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW OLD IS BOB</pattern><template>Thirty, 31.</template></category><category><pattern>TEDDY FUCKING WILLIAMS KNOCKS IT OUT OF THE PARK</pattern><template>Fenway Park is on its feet for Teddy Fucking Ballgame!</template></category><category><pattern>OMAR</pattern><template>The woman?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT US A DEAL</pattern><template>Aldo.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HER BROTHER  BOB</pattern><template>How old is Bob?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAY HE WANTS TO TAKE ON THE JEWS AT THEIR OWN GAME</pattern><template>Well, compared to, say, Louis B. Mayer, how's he doing?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOUR STATUS AS A NAZI KILLER IS STILL AMATEUR</pattern><template>We all come here to see if you want to go pro.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT ONE DAMN BIT  SIR</pattern><template>I mean, if I had my way, you'd wear that goddamn uniform for the rest of your pecker sucking life.</template></category><category><pattern>OSS WOULD BE MY GUESS</pattern><template>That's a bingo!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE HAD A NICE LONG RUN  ALDO</pattern><template>Alas, you're now in the hands of the SS.</template></category><category><pattern>GORLOMI</pattern><template>Antonio Margheriti.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY NOT</pattern><template>I didn't think so.</template></category></AIML>