<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>MAKE ONE OF THEM DIRTY  WILL YOU</pattern><template>Wow. Tony Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  COME ON</pattern><template>You get me one of those?</template></category><category><pattern>CHRISTINE EVERHART  VANITY FAIR MAGAZINE</pattern><template>Can I ask you a couple of questions?</template></category><category><pattern>I LAY LOW  AND YOU TAKE CARE OF ALL</pattern><template>Hey, come on. In public. The press.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUY FROM THE</pattern><template>Strategic Homeland Intervention, Enforcement and Logistics Division.</template></category><category><pattern>JIMMY  STAY WITH STARK</pattern><template>Stay down!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAS ALWAYS THE PLAN  STARK</pattern><template>Come on, you're gonna go see your family. Get up.</template></category><category><pattern>GET ME COLONEL RHODES FROM WEAPONS DEVELOPMENT DOWN HERE NOW</pattern><template>We ran an ID check and cross referenced with all known databases.</template></category><category><pattern>PRESS CONTROL  L</pattern><template>I.  Got it.</template></category><category><pattern>YES AND NO</pattern><template>March and I had a scheduling conflict, but fortunately, the Christmas cover was twins.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL GIVE ME A BONE TO THROW THE BOYS   IN NEW YORK</pattern><template>This one stays with me.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE  AT LEAST THREE OLIVES</pattern><template>Two vodka martinis, extra dry, extra olives, extra fast.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE A VERY RARE WOMAN</pattern><template>Tony doesn't know how lucky he is.</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE    BOGEY SPOTTED</pattern><template>Whiplash, come in hot.</template></category><category><pattern>SAY SOMETHING BACK TO HIM</pattern><template>He's speaking Hungarian. I don't...</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT SHOULD BE FINE</pattern><template>It's like Operation.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  SIR</pattern><template>Speaking of manned or unmanned, you gotta get him to tell you about the time he guessed wrong at spring break.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THOSE BULLET HOLES</pattern><template>Welcome.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE MAKING THE CASE THAT YOU AND YOUR NEW DIRECTION   ISN'T IN THE COMPANY'S BEST INTEREST</pattern><template>I'm being responsible!</template></category><category><pattern>I    ENTER    L  AND  ENTER   COME OVER HERE AND BUTTON ME UP</pattern><template>Okay. All right.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME KNOW AND I'LL GET YOU A BOTTLE  OKAY</pattern><template>Hey! Heat up the sake, will you?</template></category><category><pattern>DIDN'T  WELL  GOOD  BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE OUTLANDISH AND FANTASTIC  I'M JUST NOT THE HERO TYPE  CLEARLY  WITH THIS LAUNDRY LIST OF CHARACTER DEFECTS  ALL THE MISTAKES I'VE MADE    LARGELY PUBLIC    JUST STICK TO THE CARDS  MAN</pattern><template>Yeah, okay. Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIGHT WANT TO TAKE A FEW STEPS BACK</pattern><template>That's the coolest thing I've ever seen.</template></category><category><pattern>SAME DRILL</pattern><template>They've been dealing under the table, and I'm going to stop them.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU GOT A LOT OF MY WEAPONS</pattern><template>He says they have everything you need to build the Jericho missile.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T AFFORD TO BE THIS NAIVE</pattern><template>You know what? I was naive before, when they said,  Here's the line. We don't cross it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I SAW THAT I HAD BECOME PART OF A SYSTEM THAT IS COMFORTABLE WITH ZERO ACCOUNTABILITY</pattern><template>Mr. Stark!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURPRISED</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>STARK HAS PERFECTED HIS DESIGN</pattern><template>He has made a masterpiece of death.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE GOING TO BE ALL OVER THIS</pattern><template>Get those monitors up!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OKAY</pattern><template>Don't ever, ever, ever, ever ask me to do anything like that ever again.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE WE</pattern><template>Tony, your picture, please!</template></category><category><pattern>TALK TO ME  TELL ME WHEN YOU SEE IT</pattern><template>I have it.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T EVER  EVER  EVER  EVER ASK ME TO DO ANYTHING LIKE THAT EVER AGAIN</pattern><template>I don't have anyone but you.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE WON'T</pattern><template>I'm sure they're looking for you, Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS VERY NICE</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>START LISTENING IN ON GROUND CONTROL</pattern><template>Sir, there are still terabytes of calculations needed before an actual flight is... Jarvis! Sometimes you got to run before you can walk.</template></category><category><pattern>SAY SOMETHING</pattern><template>Say something back to him.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS WHAT YOU CALL ACCOUNTABILITY</pattern><template>It's a town called Gulmira. Heard of it?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THAT WILL BE ALL  MISS POTTS</pattern><template>And now, Mr. Stark has prepared a statement. He will not be taking any questions. Thank you. Been a while since I was in front of you. I figure I'll stick to the cards this time. There's been speculation that I was involved in the events that occurred on the freeway and the rooftop... I'm sorry, Mr. Stark, but do you honestly expect us to believe that that was a bodyguard in a suit that conveniently appeared,   despite the fact that you...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHERE I EXIT</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IN THE HELL IS THAT NOISE</pattern><template>Oh, yeah, I'm driving with the top down.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WANT IT  YES OR NO</pattern><template>Is it a good representation of his spring period?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST DON'T KNOW IT YET</pattern><template>Who the hell are you?</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE IN MINE  IT CAN ACTUALLY DO SOME GOOD</pattern><template>Next. Up.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BUY YOU SOME TIME</pattern><template>This looks important! I never had a taste for this sort of thing, but I must admit, I'm deeply enjoying the suit!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE YOU TRYING TO HUSTLE ME OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Your flight was scheduled to leave an hour and a half ago.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  I NEED TO SPEAK TO YOU ABOUT A COUPLE THINGS BEFORE I GET YOU OUT OF THE DOOR</pattern><template>Doesn't it kind of defeat the whole purpose of having your own plane if it departs before you arrive?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I NEED SOME AIR</pattern><template>That was totally weird.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOING TO FRY EVERYTHING UP HERE</pattern><template>Okay. I'm going in now.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU WERE DONE MAKING WEAPONS</pattern><template>It is.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  SUIT YOURSELF</pattern><template>You know, if I were Iron Man, I'd have this girlfriend who knew my true identity.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST CLICK IT  DON'T CHANGE ANY SETTINGS</pattern><template>What's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS LIKE WE GOT HIM BACK FROM THE DEAD</pattern><template>Now I realize, well, Tony never really did come home, did he?</template></category><category><pattern>I SAW YOUNG AMERICANS KILLED BY THE VERY WEAPONS I CREATED TO DEFEND THEM AND PROTECT THEM</pattern><template>And I saw that I had become part of a system that is comfortable with zero accountability.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN I DON'T THINK I'M IRON MAN</pattern><template>You're not Iron Man.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE GOING TO KILL ME  YOU  EITHER WAY</pattern><template>And if they don't, I'll probably be dead in a week.</template></category><category><pattern>IT DOESN'T MATTER</pattern><template>We own the controlling interest in the company.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU MIND</pattern><template>Not at all.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME  TONY  WE'RE A TEAM</pattern><template>Do you understand?</template></category><category><pattern>THOUGHT SO</pattern><template>Will that be all, Mr. Stark?</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHEN DO WE DO IT</pattern><template>It's right here.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A TOWN CALLED GULMIRA  HEARD OF IT</pattern><template>When were these taken?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT DOES</pattern><template>The copper wire.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THOSE MONITORS UP</pattern><template>We got a bogey!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SERIOUS</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE'VE BEEN WORKING OUR BEST TO DO IT</pattern><template>Absolutely, we're...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T RESPECT YOURSELF    SO I KNOW YOU DON'T RESPECT ME</pattern><template>I respect you.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FAMILY IS DEAD</pattern><template>I'm going to see them now, Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  FORREST</pattern><template>We can talk, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S SOMETHING ELSE</pattern><template>I don't have any of those floating around.</template></category><category><pattern>TRAINING EXERCISE  ISN'T THAT THE USUAL BS  IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE  AN UNFORTUNATE TRAINING EXERCISE INVOLVING AN F 22 RAPTOR OCCURRED YESTERDAY</pattern><template>I am pleased to report that the pilot was not injured.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOODNESS</pattern><template>It worked all right.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S INSIDE</pattern><template>Well, that... That went well.</template></category><category><pattern>REHEARSE THAT MUCH</pattern><template>Every night in front of the mirror before bedtime.</template></category><category><pattern>LARRY CALLED  HE'S GOT ANOTHER BUYER FOR THE JACKSON POLLOCK IN THE WINGS</pattern><template>Do you want it? Yes or no.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  IT IS ME  YOU ASKED  WHAT YOU WERE ASKING ABOUT IS ME  NO  SEE  THIS ISN'T A GAME</pattern><template>You do not send civilian equipment into my active war zone.</template></category><category><pattern>WE MET ONCE  YOU KNOW  AT A TECHNICAL CONFERENCE IN BERN</pattern><template>I don't remember.</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME HOME  SIR   I AM IRON MAN   YOU THINK YOU'RE THE ONLY SUPERHERO IN THE WORLD</pattern><template>Mr. Stark, you've become part of a bigger universe.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR LACK OF A BETTER OPTION  DUMMY IS STILL ON FIRE SAFETY</pattern><template>If you douse me again, and I'm not on fire, I'm donating you to a city college.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE WORLD COMING TO WHEN A GUY'S GOT TO CRASH HIS OWN PARTY</pattern><template>Look at you. Hey, what a surprise.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO ACCESS THIS AREA    JESUS</pattern><template>That's Jarvis. He runs the house.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  HONEY BEAR</pattern><template>There it is.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SOON  IT WILL BE MY TURN</pattern><template>What does he want?</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME A LITTLE SOMETHING SOMETHING</pattern><template>Okay, you, too.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  WE'RE A WEAPONS MANUFACTURER</pattern><template>Obie, I just don't want a body count to be our only legacy.</template></category><category><pattern>RELAX  I HAVE STEADY HANDS</pattern><template>Why do you think you're still alive?</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME AN EXPLODED VIEW</pattern><template>The compression in cylinder three appears to be low. Log that.</template></category><category><pattern>HIGHER</pattern><template>We iced up, Jarvis!</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO BE A PART OF IT</pattern><template>You're about to make a whole lot of people around here real happy, 'cause that little stunt at the press conference, that was a doozy.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN IN CAPTIVITY FOR THREE MONTHS</pattern><template>There are two things I want to do.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS NOTHING EXCEPT THIS</pattern><template>There's no art opening.</template></category><category><pattern>AS YOU WISH  TEST COMPLETE  PREPARING TO POWER DOWN AND BEGIN DIAGNOSTICS  YEAH  TELL YOU WHAT</pattern><template>Do a weather and ATC check.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO BE HALFWAY AROUND THE WORLD RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>How'd she take it?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SHALL I RENDER USING PROPOSED SPECIFICATIONS  THRILL ME</pattern><template>Tonight's red hot red carpet is right here at the Disney Concert Hall, where Tony Stark's third annual benefit for the Firefighter's Family Fund has become the place to be for L.A.'s high society. Jarvis, we get an invite for that?</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE TWO</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  GOOD  'CAUSE I'M STARING AT ONE RIGHT NOW  AND IT'S ABOUT TO BE BLOWN TO KINGDOM COME</pattern><template>That's my exit.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST YOUR BABYSITTER</pattern><template>So, when you need your diaper changed... Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT  UP</pattern><template>Not in the boot, Dummy. Right here.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D BETTER GET BACK THERE</pattern><template>Is that today's paper?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GREAT</pattern><template>From you, actually.</template></category><category><pattern>SCREW IT  DON'T EVEN MOVE</pattern><template>You are a tragedy.</template></category><category><pattern>I SHOULDN'T BE ALIVE  UNLESS IT WAS FOR A REASON</pattern><template>I'm not crazy, Pepper.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GET ME ONE OF THOSE</pattern><template>There's only one left. I need it.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I HAD BEEN THAT DRUNK  I WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN ABLE TO STAND  MUCH LESS GIVE A LECTURE ON INTEGRATED CIRCUITS</pattern><template>Where are we?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK WHO FELL OUT OF THE SKY</pattern><template>Mr. Tony Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD ROLL  GOOD ROLL</pattern><template>You still haven't told me where you're from.</template></category><category><pattern>COMMENCING AUTOMATED ASSEMBLY  ESTIMATED COMPLETION TIME IS FIVE HOURS  DON'T WAIT UP FOR ME  HONEY</pattern><template>Weapons manufacturing is only one small part of what Stark Industries is all about, and our partnership with the fire and rescue community...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  SIR  IT'S TINY</pattern><template>We think it's an unmanned aerial vehicle.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S BEING HANDLED  HE'S ON VACATION</pattern><template>Small aircraft have such a poor safety record.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW IRONIC  TONY</pattern><template>Trying to rid the world of weapons, you gave it its best one ever!</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT</pattern><template>Let's get this show on the road.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THIS</pattern><template>Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  WE'RE WORKING ON IT</pattern><template>You know, we've been approached already by the DOD, the FBI, the CIA...</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE IN THE SHOP</pattern><template>Hey, hey! Hey, Tony. Listen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  IF I WERE IRON MAN  I'D HAVE THIS GIRLFRIEND WHO KNEW MY TRUE IDENTITY</pattern><template>She'd be a wreck, 'cause she'd always be worrying that I was going to die, yet so proud of the man I'd become.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S SO MANY APPLICATIONS FOR CAUSING SHORT TERM PARALYSIS</pattern><template>Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY SHOULD I DO ANYTHING</pattern><template>They're going to kill me, you, either way.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME A SCOTCH  I'M STARVING</pattern><template>Mr. Stark?</template></category><category><pattern>FUNCTION 11</pattern><template>Tell me when you see a progress bar.</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK  IMPORT ALL PREFERENCES FROM HOME INTERFACE</pattern><template>Will do, sir. All right, what do you say?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  CAN YOU MOVE</pattern><template>Okay, say it again.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S ONLY ONE LEFT  I NEED IT</pattern><template>Hey, look who's here! Yeah!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE BEEN REENGAGED  EXECUTE EVASIVE MANEUVER  KEEP GOING</pattern><template>Good chute! Good chute!   Tony, you still there?</template></category><category><pattern>I'D BE OUT OF A JOB WITH PEACE</pattern><template>Come on. Hurry up.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO SEE THEM NOW  STARK</pattern><template>It's okay.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A NEW DIRECTION FOR ME  FOR THE COMPANY</pattern><template>I mean, me on the company's behalf being responsible for the way that...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GOING TO BE A PART OF IT</pattern><template>I shouldn't be alive, unless it was for a reason.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  PEACE  I LOVE PEACE</pattern><template>I'd be out of a job with peace.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  EVERYTHING'S    WHAT</pattern><template>Obadiah's upstairs.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE COMING</pattern><template>Make sure the checkpoints are clear before you follow me out, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT YOU  I GOT YOU</pattern><template>What's wrong with you?</template></category><category><pattern>I DESIGNED THIS TO COME OFF  SO    HEY</pattern><template>I really should be able to...</template></category><category><pattern>INITIALIZE THE POWER SEQUENCE</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>MY OLD MAN HAD A PHILOSOPHY   PEACE MEANS HAVING A BIGGER STICK THAN THE OTHER GUY   THAT'S A GREAT LINE COMING FROM THE GUY SELLING THE STICKS</pattern><template>My father helped defeat the Nazis.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'LL BELIEVE IT  DON'T DO THAT</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  I WAS DRIVING TO THE CANYON  WHERE I'M GOING TO JOG  YOU SURE YOU DON'T HAVE ANY TECH IN THAT AREA I SHOULD KNOW ABOUT</pattern><template>Nope!   Bogey spotted!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU'RE GONNA ATTACH THAT TO THE BASE PLATE  MAKE SURE YOU</pattern><template>Was that so hard? That was fun, right?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT OPENING THE DOOR</pattern><template>Oh, wow! What's that?</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR EYES ARE RED</pattern><template>A few tears for your long lost boss?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO GO TO MY OFFICE</pattern><template>You're going to hack into the mainframe and you're going to retrieve all the recent shipping manifests.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THAT</pattern><template>Absolutely ridiculous. I don't paint.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THIS THING JUST APPEARED OUT OF NOWHERE</pattern><template>How come it didn't show up on the radar?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHAT COULD IT GENERATE</pattern><template>If my math is right, and it always is, three gigajoules per second.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  TONY</pattern><template>You can't afford to be this naive.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH THAT IN MIND  I HUMBLY PRESENT THE CROWN JEWEL OF STARK INDUSTRIES' FREEDOM LINE</pattern><template>It's the first missile system to incorporate our proprietary repulsor technology.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I DID</pattern><template>What I did is to save your life.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE DON'T FOLLOW ME AROUND WITH IT  EITHER  'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA CATCH ON FIRE SPONTANEOUSLY</pattern><template>Just stand down!</template></category><category><pattern>SECTOR 16</pattern><template>What are you up to, Obadiah?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WILL BE ALL  MISS POTTS</pattern><template>Hey, Butterfingers, come here.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO VODKA MARTINIS  EXTRA DRY  EXTRA OLIVES  EXTRA FAST</pattern><template>Make one of them dirty, will you?</template></category><category><pattern>PUSH IT</pattern><template>Tony!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT WE DO</pattern><template>You'll be hearing from us.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THE NIGHT THAT WE DANCED AND WENT UP ON THE ROOF  AND THEN YOU WENT DOWNSTAIRS TO GET ME A DRINK  AND YOU LEFT ME THERE  BY MYSELF</pattern><template>Is that the night you're talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>YEP</pattern><template>Tony, we're a weapons manufacturer.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT IT'D BE BIGGER</pattern><template>How do you think the Mark One chest piece is going to hold up?</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>Do you mind?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M INDIFFERENT  OKAY</pattern><template>I said I was sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ABOUT TO MAKE A WHOLE LOT OF PEOPLE AROUND HERE REAL HAPPY  'CAUSE THAT LITTLE STUNT AT THE PRESS CONFERENCE  THAT WAS A DOOZY</pattern><template>This is not for the military. I'm not...</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S BEEN THROUGH A LOT</pattern><template>I think he'll be all right.</template></category><category><pattern>INCINERATE IT</pattern><template>You don't want to keep it?</template></category><category><pattern>NOSTALGIC  IS NOT ONE OF THEM</pattern><template>Will that be all, Mr. Stark?</template></category><category><pattern>WILL THAT BE ALL  MR  STARK</pattern><template>Yes, that will be all, Miss Potts.</template></category><category><pattern>VERY PETITE  INDEED</pattern><template>I just need your help for a sec.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T HAVE ANY OF THOSE FLOATING AROUND</pattern><template>We're gonna let it ride!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WHAT DO I DO</pattern><template>What's wrong?</template></category><category><pattern>IMPORTING PREFERENCES AND CALIBRATING VIRTUAL ENVIRONMENT  DO A CHECK ON CONTROL SURFACES</pattern><template>As you wish. Test complete. Preparing to power down and begin diagnostics. Yeah. Tell you what.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A LOCK CHIP</pattern><template>This'll get you in.</template></category><category><pattern>STARK INDUSTRIES  I'VE GOT ONE RECOMMENDATION  READY  READY  SELL  SELL  SELL  ABANDON SHIP  DOES THE HINDENBURG RING ANY BELLS  LET ME SHOW YOU THE NEW STARK INDUSTRIES BUSINESS PLAN  LOOK  THAT'S A WEAPONS COMPANY THAT DOESN'T MAKE WEAPONS  PEPPER  HOW BIG ARE YOUR HANDS    WHAT</pattern><template>How big are your hands?   I don't understand why...</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU DREAM OF STARK'S THRONE</pattern><template>We have a common enemy.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  YOU NEED A NEW NAME FOR THAT</pattern><template>Yeah, I hear that a lot.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S SR 71'S RECORD</pattern><template>The altitude record for fixed wing flight is 85,000 feet, sir. Records are made to be broken!</template></category><category><pattern>I ALREADY DID</pattern><template>And?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  TONY</pattern><template>You are not authorized to access this area.   Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>MY KEY'S NOT WORKING</pattern><template>It's not opening the door.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  YOU UP</pattern><template>For you, sir, always. I'd like to open a new project file, index as Mark Two.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  DO YOU MIND</pattern><template>Have you seen these pictures?</template></category><category><pattern>FROM THE STRATEGIC HOMELAND</pattern><template>Just call us S.H.I.E.L.D.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ISN'T THAT STRANGE</pattern><template>It's the same day as last year.</template></category><category><pattern>SPEED BUMP  WHAT DOES THAT MEAN</pattern><template>It's nothing. It's just a little snag.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE HARANGUING ME  SO I'M GONNA SAY YES</pattern><template>Deflect it and absorb it.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM YOU  ACTUALLY</pattern><template>Well, I got great taste.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  I KNOW THIS MUST BE A TRYING TIME FOR YOU  BUT WE NEED TO DEBRIEF YOU</pattern><template>There's still a lot of unanswered questions, and time can be a factor with these things.</template></category><category><pattern>DO A WEATHER AND ATC CHECK</pattern><template>Start listening in on ground control.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  THE BOARD HAS RIGHTS  TOO</pattern><template>They're making the case that you and your new direction   isn't in the company's best interest.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THROW IT UP  I'M KIDDING</pattern><template>Yeah, peace. I love peace.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST INDIFFERENT RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Hot towel?</template></category><category><pattern>WILLIAM  HERE IS THE TECHNOLOGY</pattern><template>I've asked you to simply make it smaller.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY DOESN'T KNOW HOW LUCKY HE IS</pattern><template>Thank you. Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>Yeah, I can fly.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK GREAT  HEF</pattern><template>We're going to have a great quarter.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  WHAT KIND OF WORLD WOULD IT BE TODAY IF HE WAS AS SELFISH AS YOU</pattern><template>Oh, it's beautiful.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO</pattern><template>Tony?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S READY  TONY  GET OFF THE ROOF</pattern><template>Tony!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST NEED YOUR HELP FOR A SEC</pattern><template>Oh, my God, is that the thing that's keeping you alive?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  COME ON</pattern><template>Thank you. No.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW THAT I'M TRYING TO PROTECT THE PEOPLE THAT I PUT IN HARM'S WAY  YOU'RE GOING TO WALK OUT</pattern><template>You're going to kill yourself, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T EXPECT THAT</pattern><template>How'd it go?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>We're going to have it right now.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST STICK TO THE OFFICIAL STATEMENT  AND SOON  THIS WILL ALL BE BEHIND YOU</pattern><template>You've got 90 seconds.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT BAD  HUH  LET'S DO IT</pattern><template>You need me to do anything else?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S LIKE OPERATION</pattern><template>You just don't let it touch the socket wall or it goes  beep.    What do you mean,  Operation ?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU WANT  A DELIVERY DATE</pattern><template>I need him.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STOOD BY MY SIDE ALL THESE YEARS WHILE I REAPED THE BENEFITS OF DESTRUCTION</pattern><template>And now that I'm trying to protect the people that I put in harm's way, you're going to walk out?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  WELL  THIS STAYS WITH ME  THEN</pattern><template>Go on, here, you can have a piece.</template></category><category><pattern>WHIPLASH TWO  IF YOU HAVE A CLEAR SHOT  TAKE IT</pattern><template>You've been reengaged. Execute evasive maneuver. Keep going!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BUTTERFINGERS  COME HERE</pattern><template>What's all this stuff doing on top of my desk?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THIS IS WHERE I DON'T WANT TO BE</pattern><template>Not the car, not the car!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS IT  YOU JUST PULLED IT OUT</pattern><template>Oh, God!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANTED TO SAY THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR ALL OF YOUR HELP</pattern><template>That's what we do.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  THANKS  OH  MY GOD  YOU CRAZY SON OF A BITCH</pattern><template>You owe me a plane.</template></category><category><pattern>TEARS OF JOY  I HATE JOB HUNTING</pattern><template>Yeah, vacation's over.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE IT</pattern><template>Press Control  l .</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT AN AMERICAN CHEESEBURGER    AND THE OTHER</pattern><template>That's enough of that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S UP WITH THE LOVE IN</pattern><template>Don't look at me.</template></category><category><pattern>WE RAN AN ID CHECK AND CROSS REFERENCED WITH ALL KNOWN DATABASES</pattern><template>We have nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  AND I WILL SEE THEM WHEN I LEAVE HERE</pattern><template>And you, Stark?</template></category><category><pattern>HI</pattern><template>Yeah. Okay, go.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS</pattern><template>That is an electromagnet, hooked up to a car battery, and it's keeping the shrapnel from entering your heart.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT WE DO  WE'RE IRON MONGERS</pattern><template>We make weapons.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>We have port papers that put you in Avalon all night, and sworn statements from 50 of your guests.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SUIT'S AT 48% POWER AND FALLING  SIR  THAT CHEST PIECE WAS NEVER DESIGNED FOR SUSTAINED FLIGHT  KEEP ME POSTED</pattern><template>Pepper!   Tony! Tony, are you okay?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD BE IRRESPONSIBLE NOT TO DRINK</pattern><template>I'm just talking about a nightcap.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SWAPPING IT UP FOR AN UPGRADED UNIT  AND I JUST RAN INTO A LITTLE SPEED BUMP</pattern><template>Speed bump, what does that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT TIME  BABY</pattern><template>Looks like you were right.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU THE MEETING OF YOUR LIFE  YOUR OFFICE</pattern><template>Yeah, we've been working our best to do it.</template></category><category><pattern>A MAN WITH A DOZEN OF THESE CAN RULE ALL OF ASIA</pattern><template>And you dream of Stark's throne.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY WHO I WORK WITH</pattern><template>No, you know why?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  OKAY  GO</pattern><template>It's okay?</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I GET UP IN THE MORNING AND I'M PUTTING ON MY UNIFORM  YOU KNOW WHAT I RECOGNIZE</pattern><template>I see in that mirror that every person that's got this uniform on got my back!</template></category><category><pattern>PUT THAT ON THE TABLE OVER THERE</pattern><template>That is irrelevant.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD BOY</pattern><template>Tony?</template></category><category><pattern>I RESPECTFULLY DISAGREE</pattern><template>I prefer the weapon you only have to fire once.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF THERE RIGHT NOW  WHERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING  YOUR SERVICES ARE NO LONGER REQUIRED  STANE  I LOVE THIS SUIT    PUT THEM DOWN    COLLATERAL DAMAGE  TONY  DIVERT POWER TO CHEST RT</pattern><template>Power reduced to 19%. Lady! No, no, no, no, no, no! For 30 years, I've been holding you up! I built this company from nothing! Nothing is going to stand in my way. Least of all you! Impressive! You've upgraded your armor! I've made some upgrades of my own! Sir, it appears that his suit can fly. Duly noted.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WAY TO GO  MY BOY  I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW  YEAH  WHY AREN'T YOU WEARING THOSE PAJAMAS I GOT YOU</pattern><template>Good night, Tony.   Hey, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  STANE  SIR  WE'VE EXPLORED WHAT YOU'VE ASKED US  AND IT SEEMS AS THOUGH THERE'S A LITTLE HICCUP</pattern><template>Actually...</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU BY YOURSELF</pattern><template>Yes. Where'd you get that dress?</template></category><category><pattern>WILL DO  SIR  ALL RIGHT  WHAT DO YOU SAY</pattern><template>I have indeed been uploaded, sir. We're online and ready. Can we start the virtual walk around?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHAT ABOUT THE WHOLE COVER STORY THAT IT'S A BODYGUARD</pattern><template>He's my... I mean, is that...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE COOLEST THING I'VE EVER SEEN</pattern><template>Not bad, huh? Let's do it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FLIGHT WAS SCHEDULED TO LEAVE AN HOUR AND A HALF AGO</pattern><template>That's funny, I thought with it being my plane and all, that it would just wait for me to get there.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I PLEASE GET EYES ON TARGET</pattern><template>Negative, negative.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S PEPPER</pattern><template>She's fine. She's with five agents.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S QUESTIONS THAT I WOULD HAVE ASKED HIM</pattern><template>I would have asked him how he felt about what this company did.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  DON'T LET IT TOUCH THE SIDES WHEN YOU'RE COMING OUT</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE WAS CONFLICTED  IF HE EVER HAD DOUBTS</pattern><template>Or maybe he was every inch the man we all remember from the newsreels.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE GOT YOUR CLOTHES HERE</pattern><template>They've been dry cleaned and pressed, and there's a car waiting for you outside that will take you anywhere you'd like to go.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT MANNED OR UNMANNED</pattern><template>I'll tell you, in my experience, no unmanned aerial vehicle will ever trump a pilot's instinct, his insight, that ability to look into a situation beyond the obvious and discern its outcome, or a pilot's judgment.</template></category><category><pattern>NEGATIVE  NO CHUTE  NO CHUTE  MY CHUTE'S JAMMED  SIR  I'VE GOT A VISUAL ON THE BOGEY  WHIPLASH TWO  REENGAGE</pattern><template>If you get a clear shot, you take it.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT'S OKAY</pattern><template>Wow! Would you look at that?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL DIE</pattern><template>Push it!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  DRAW UP SOME SPECS</pattern><template>No. No, absolutely not.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MORNING  MR  STARK</pattern><template>You don't need to apologize to me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OTHER EIGHT</pattern><template>So I got you for the other eight.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT I DO</pattern><template>Let me finish this.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HE'S A COMPLICATED PERSON</pattern><template>He's been through a lot.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NICE SEEING YOU  TONY</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>AS A MATTER OF FACT  I DO</pattern><template>I don't like it when you have plans.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT THE CAR  NOT THE CAR</pattern><template>Table!</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE</pattern><template>Take care.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAVE WE GOT</pattern><template>Jimmy, stay with Stark!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  OKAY</pattern><template>Tony? It's going to be okay.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT PUS  IT'S AN INORGANIC PLASMIC DISCHARGE FROM THE DEVICE    NOT FROM MY BODY</pattern><template>It smells!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS AN EXCELLENT QUESTION</pattern><template>Yes and no.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>I swear, I didn't expect to see you walking around so soon.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT DRINKING</pattern><template>We're working right now.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL DID YOU DO TO ME</pattern><template>What I did?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD MY EYES OPENED</pattern><template>I came to realize that I have more to offer this world than just making things that blow up.</template></category><category><pattern>'CAUSE I WAS REFERRING TO YOUR COMPANY'S INVOLVEMENT IN THIS LATEST ATROCITY</pattern><template>Yeah. They just put my name on the invitation. I don't know what to tell you.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS ISN'T MY FIRST RODEO  MR  STARK</pattern><template>Just stick to the official statement, and soon, this will all be behind you.</template></category><category><pattern>'CAUSE I'M</pattern><template>Okay, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>TRYING TO RID THE WORLD OF WEAPONS  YOU GAVE IT ITS BEST ONE EVER</pattern><template>Pepper!</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOTTA HURRY  TAKE THIS  TAKE THIS</pattern><template>You gotta switch it out really quick.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE ARE STILL IN BUSINESS  I WILL GIVE YOU THESE DESIGNS AS A GIFT</pattern><template>And in turn, I hope you'll repay me with a gift of iron soldiers.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT THIS  I WANT THIS</pattern><template>Thank you for saving me.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS THE LAST ACT OF DEFIANCE OF THE GREAT TONY STARK</pattern><template>Or are you going to do something about it?</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU HEAR THE INTERCOM</pattern><template>Yeah, everything's... What?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THING IS BACK</pattern><template>Get me Major Allen. Scramble the jets!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S FUNNY  I THOUGHT WITH IT BEING MY PLANE AND ALL  THAT IT WOULD JUST WAIT FOR ME TO GET THERE</pattern><template>Tony, I need to speak to you about a couple things before I get you out of the door.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I DON'T THINK THAT I'M QUALIFIED TO DO THIS</pattern><template>No, you're fine.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  I HAVE A QUESTION TO ASK</pattern><template>Yes, please.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M KIND OF HAVING A HARD TIME NOT LOOKING AT YOU NOW</pattern><template>Is that weird? Come on, it's okay, laugh.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D BE PREPARED TO LOSE A FEW WITH YOU</pattern><template>Good morning. It's 7:00 a.m. The weather in Malibu is 72 degrees with scattered clouds. The surf conditions are fair with waist to shoulder high lines. High tide will be at 10:52 a.m. Tony?</template></category><category><pattern>THE MIT COMMENCEMENT SPEECH</pattern><template>Is in June. Please, don't harangue me about stuff that's way, way, down...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS YOUR LEGACY</pattern><template>A new generation of weapons with this at its heart.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GONNA BE OKAY</pattern><template>I'm gonna make this okay.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT ANSWERING HIS PHONE</pattern><template>Please go over there and make sure everything's okay.</template></category><category><pattern>I PREFER THE WEAPON YOU ONLY HAVE TO FIRE ONCE</pattern><template>That's how Dad did it.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  YOU OKAY</pattern><template>Where's Pepper?</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER IT WAS  IT JUST BOUGHT THE FARM  I THINK BOGEY'S BEEN HANDLED  SIR    HELLO</pattern><template>Hi, Rhodey, it's me.   It's who?</template></category><category><pattern>MISS POTTS</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE A JERICHO MISSILE</pattern><template>That's because it's a miniaturized arc reactor.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THAT IT'S CONFUSING  IT IS ONE THING TO QUESTION THE OFFICIAL STORY  AND ANOTHER THING ENTIRELY TO MAKE WILD ACCUSATIONS  OR INSINUATE THAT I'M A SUPERHERO  I NEVER SAID YOU WERE A SUPERHERO</pattern><template>Didn't? Well, good, because that would be outlandish and fantastic. I'm just not the hero type. Clearly. With this laundry list of character defects, all the mistakes I've made,   largely public.   Just stick to the cards, man.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT IF EVERYONE SAT DOWN</pattern><template>Why don't you just sit down?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HEY</pattern><template>Fancy seeing you here.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S HOPE</pattern><template>Okay, you're gonna attach that to the base plate. Make sure you...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FINALLY OUTDID YOURSELF  TONY</pattern><template>You'd have made your father proud!</template></category><category><pattern>STAY DOWN</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE WHAT</pattern><template>You want us to make baby bottles?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT DO YOU PLAN TO DO WITH THIS INFORMATION IF I BRING IT BACK HERE</pattern><template>Same drill.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE GO OVER THERE AND MAKE SURE EVERYTHING'S OKAY</pattern><template>Thank you, Rhodey. I know a shortcut.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT THE 24TH AT 7:00 P M</pattern><template>at Stark Industries?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WOW  THEY ARE SMALL</pattern><template>Very petite, indeed.</template></category><category><pattern>MAJOR  WE DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT WE'RE SHOOTING AT</pattern><template>Call off the Raptors.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL JUST BE A MINUTE</pattern><template>Give me a Scotch. I'm starving.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT I WAS TRYING TO TELL YOU BEFORE</pattern><template>Okay, now make sure that when you pull it out, you don't...</template></category><category><pattern>WE KNEW THAT BEFORE WE BUILT IT</pattern><template>Arc reactor technology, that's a dead end, right?</template></category><category><pattern>FOR YOUR CONSIDERATION  THE JERICHO</pattern><template>I'll be throwing one of these in with every purchase of 500 million or more.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  OH  MY GOD  ARE YOU OKAY</pattern><template>I'm almost out of power. I've got to get out of this thing. I'll be right there.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE THIS</pattern><template>That thing is back.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU BUSY</pattern><template>You mind if I send you on an errand?</template></category><category><pattern>DEPLOY FLAPS  JARVIS</pattern><template>Come on, we got to break the ice!</template></category><category><pattern>UP</pattern><template>Screw it. Don't even move.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN TALK  SIR</pattern><template>Oh, I see. So it's personal?</template></category><category><pattern>FANCY SEEING YOU HERE</pattern><template>Carrie.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT IT</pattern><template>Yes. Shall I render using proposed specifications? Thrill me.</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME</pattern><template>Compliments of Tony Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M IN IT  IT'S A SUIT  IT'S ME</pattern><template>Rhodey, you got anything for me?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AN AIRMAN</pattern><template>You have, actually, excellent bone structure, there.</template></category><category><pattern>IT ALLOWED THE GREAT GENGHIS KHAN TO RULE FROM THE PACIFIC TO THE UKRAINE</pattern><template>An empire twice the size of Alexander the Great and four times the size of the Roman Empire.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BOARD IS CLAIMING YOU HAVE POSTTRAUMATIC STRESS</pattern><template>They're filing an injunction.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING PRETTY  JUST GET IT DONE</pattern><template>Just get it done.</template></category><category><pattern>PEPPER    TONY  TONY  ARE YOU OKAY</pattern><template>I'm fine. How are...   Obadiah, he's gone insane!</template></category><category><pattern>THE JERICHO MISSILE THAT YOU DEMONSTRATED</pattern><template>This one.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THAT</pattern><template>That's palladium, 0.15 grams.</template></category><category><pattern>NEGATIVE  NEGATIVE</pattern><template>Cannot identify.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CALL THEM THE WALKING DEAD BECAUSE IT TAKES ABOUT A WEEK FOR THE BARBS TO REACH THE VITAL ORGANS</pattern><template>What is this?</template></category><category><pattern>PEPPER</pattern><template>And now I'm going to kill you with it!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS CRAZY  WHAT DID I DO</pattern><template>I feel like you're going to pull over and snuff me.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WHERE'S TONY NOW</pattern><template>I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY CALL THEMSELVES THE TEN RINGS</pattern><template>You know, we might be more productive if you include me in the planning process.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  WANT TO SEE</pattern><template>I have a souvenir. Take a look.</template></category><category><pattern>HULL PRESSURIZATION IS PROBLEMATIC</pattern><template>I'm thinking icing is the probable factor.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  NICE AND EASY  SERIOUSLY  JUST GONNA START OFF WITH 1% THRUST CAPACITY  AND THREE  TWO  ONE  OKAY</pattern><template>Please don't follow me around with it, either, 'cause I feel like I'm gonna catch on fire spontaneously.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY HIGH ALTITUDE SURVEILLANCE IN THE REGION</pattern><template>We got an AWAC and a Global Hawk in the area.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE GOING TO MEET AT THE HOSPITAL</pattern><template>No, I'm fine.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  AS A SCIENCE PROJECT</pattern><template>The arc was never cost effective.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS ONE STAYS WITH ME</pattern><template>That's it, Obie. Forget it.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL I WANT IS A SERIOUS ANSWER</pattern><template>Okay, here's serious.</template></category><category><pattern>OR ARE YOU GOING TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Why should I do anything?</template></category><category><pattern>FIND AN EXCUSE TO LET ONE OF THESE OFF THE CHAIN  AND I PERSONALLY GUARANTEE YOU THE BAD GUYS WON'T EVEN WANT TO COME OUT OF THEIR CAVES</pattern><template>For your consideration, the Jericho.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THING JUST JUMPED OFF THE RADAR  SIR</pattern><template>The sat visual has been lost.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT'S YOU  THAT'S GREAT</pattern><template>So when do we do it?</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU GET A CLEAR SHOT  YOU TAKE IT</pattern><template>Major, we don't even know what we're shooting at.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  WE'VE BEEN APPROACHED ALREADY BY THE DOD  THE FBI  THE CIA</pattern><template>We're a separate division with a more specific focus.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  I WAS THINKING MAYBE WE SHOULD SAY IT WAS JUST PEPPER AND ME ALONE ON THE ISLAND</pattern><template>That's what happened.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LET'S FINISH UP HERE</pattern><template>Set up Sector 16 underneath the arc reactor, and I'm going to want this data masked.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE DOESN'T  OH  BOY</pattern><template>It would have gone better if you were there.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA DO SOMETHING ELSE</pattern><template>Like what?</template></category><category><pattern>AND IN TURN  I HOPE YOU'LL REPAY ME WITH A GIFT OF IRON SOLDIERS</pattern><template>Technology.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT</pattern><template>What would you like me to tell him?</template></category><category><pattern>YINSEN  NICE TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>Nice to meet you, too.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT</pattern><template>It's gonna be okay.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT YOU  HEY  WHAT A SURPRISE</pattern><template>I'll see you inside.</template></category><category><pattern>GET ME MAJOR ALLEN  SCRAMBLE THE JETS</pattern><template>Not necessary, people.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  TONY STARK</pattern><template>Oh, hey.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST DO AS I DO</pattern><template>Come on, put your hands up.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S BECAUSE IT'S A MINIATURIZED ARC REACTOR</pattern><template>I got a big one powering my factory at home.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE A LOT OF HEAT</pattern><template>I want you to promise me that you're gonna lay low.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE WE</pattern><template>Come on, stand up. Stand up!</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TWO SETS OF PRECISION TOOLS</pattern><template>How many languages do you speak?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LET'S SEE WHAT THIS THING CAN DO</pattern><template>What's SR 71's record?</template></category><category><pattern>MY TURN</pattern><template>Not bad.</template></category><category><pattern>TOO BAD YOU HAD TO INVOLVE PEPPER IN THIS</pattern><template>I would have preferred that she lived.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT  WAIT  THE TECHNOLOGY</pattern><template>William, here is the technology.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT IT  YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT</pattern><template>Well, I'm going to go to my assistant, and we'll make a date.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU'D KILLED HIM WHEN YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO  YOU'D STILL HAVE A FACE</pattern><template>You paid us trinkets to kill a prince.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP THE SKIES CLEAR  DAMN</pattern><template>Next time, baby.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD NIGHT  OBIE</pattern><template>Day 11, test 37, configuration 2.0.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THOSE BREAKTHROUGHS  MILITARY FUNDING  HONEY</pattern><template>You ever lose an hour of sleep your whole life?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE OF NO BENEFIT AT ALL</pattern><template>Move down to the toe. I got this.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  HE WANTS TO KNOW WHAT YOU THINK</pattern><template>I think you got a lot of my weapons.</template></category><category><pattern>AT MINIMUM</pattern><template>Yep.</template></category><category><pattern>WASN'T MARINES</pattern><template>I need answers!</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A MAGNET AT THE END OF IT</pattern><template>That was it. You just pulled it out.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  OKAY  YEAH</pattern><template>The truth is I am Iron Man. Jarvis!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BEING RESPONSIBLE</pattern><template>That's a new direction for me, for the company.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS ESCAPE BORE UNEXPECTED FRUIT</pattern><template>So this is how he did it.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BOW AND ARROW ONCE WAS THE PINNACLE OF WEAPONS TECHNOLOGY</pattern><template>It allowed the great Genghis Khan to rule from the Pacific to the Ukraine.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DO NOT SEND CIVILIAN EQUIPMENT INTO MY ACTIVE WAR ZONE</pattern><template>You understand that?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST FINALLY KNOW WHAT I HAVE TO DO</pattern><template>And I know in my heart that it's right.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SUIT'S A GOLD TITANIUM ALLOY  BUT IT'S KIND OF EVOCATIVE  THE IMAGERY  ANYWAY</pattern><template>Here's your alibi.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEY TOLD ME THAT IF I PRESENTED YOU WITH AN AWARD  YOU'D BE DEEPLY HONORED</pattern><template>Of course I'd be deeply honored.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WENT THAT BAD  HUH</pattern><template>Just because I brought pizza back from New York   doesn't mean it went bad.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  TONY  YOU HAVE TO   GO TO THE HOSPITAL</pattern><template>No is a complete answer.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW    LISTEN  YOU'D BETTER GET OUT OF THERE    HE BUILT A SUIT</pattern><template>Get out of there right now! Where do you think you're going? Your services are no longer required. Stane! I love this suit!   Put them down!   Collateral damage, Tony. Divert power to chest RT.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS</pattern><template>Jarvis, you up?</template></category><category><pattern>ARC REACTOR TECHNOLOGY  THAT'S A DEAD END  RIGHT</pattern><template>Maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HOW ARE YOU GOING TO DO THAT</pattern><template>You're going to do it.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL YOU WHAT</pattern><template>You got it. You're absolutely right.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTES  MAIN TRANSDUCER FEELS SLUGGISH AT PLUS 40 ALTITUDE</pattern><template>Hull pressurization is problematic.</template></category><category><pattern>THREE  TWO  ONE</pattern><template>Okay, this is where I don't want to be!</template></category><category><pattern>I ACTUALLY ALMOST BOUGHT IT  HOOK  LINE AND SINKER</pattern><template>I was out of town for a couple months, in case you didn't hear.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST CALL US S H I E L D</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T HAVE ANYONE BUT YOU</pattern><template>Anyway...</template></category><category><pattern>CRATE UP THE ARMOR AND THE REST OF IT</pattern><template>All right, let's finish up here.</template></category><category><pattern>GET DOWN HERE  I NEED YOU  HEY</pattern><template>Let's see them. Show me your hands.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU LOST OBJECTIVITY  I THINK THEY JUST    PEOPLE    WE JUST DANCED</pattern><template>No, it was not just a dance. You don't understand because you're you.</template></category><category><pattern>SIMPLE FARMERS AND HERDERS FROM PEACEFUL VILLAGES HAVE BEEN DRIVEN FROM THEIR HOMES  DISPLACED FROM THEIR LANDS BY WARLORDS EMBOLDENED BY A NEW FOUND POWER  VILLAGERS HAVE BEEN FORCED TO TAKE SHELTER IN WHATEVER CRUDE DWELLINGS THEY CAN FIND IN THE RUINS OF OTHER VILLAGES  OR HERE IN THE REMNANTS OF AN OLD SOVIET SMELTING PLANT  RECENT VIOLENCE HAS BEEN ATTRIBUTED TO A GROUP OF FOREIGN FIGHTERS REFERRED TO BY LOCALS AS THE TEN RINGS  AS YOU CAN SEE  THESE MEN ARE HEAVILY ARMED AND ON A MISSION  A MISSION THAT COULD PROVE FATAL TO ANYONE WHO STANDS IN THEIR WAY  WITH NO POLITICAL WILL OR INTERNATIONAL PRESSURE  THERE'S VERY LITTLE HOPE FOR THESE REFUGEES  AROUND ME  A WOMAN BEGGING FOR NEWS ON HER HUSBAND  WHO WAS KIDNAPPED BY INSURGENTS  EITHER FORCED TO JOIN THEIR MILITIA    DESPERATE REFUGEES CLUTCH YELLOWED PHOTOGRAPHS  HOLDING THEM UP TO ANYONE WHO WILL STOP  A CHILD'S SIMPLE QUESTION   WHERE ARE MY MOTHER AND FATHER   THERE'S VERY LITTLE HOPE FOR THESE REFUGEES  REFUGEES WHO CAN ONLY WONDER WHO  IF ANYONE  WILL HELP  HE'S ALL YOURS  WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT</pattern><template>Were we cleared to go in there?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A FLIGHT STABILIZER</pattern><template>It's completely harmless.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALLY SHOULD BE ABLE TO</pattern><template>Please, try not to move, sir. What's going on here?</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU  STARK</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I SPEAK TO YOU FOR A MOMENT</pattern><template>I'm not part of the press conference, but it's about to begin right now.</template></category><category><pattern>CHRISTINE</pattern><template>That's right.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID  SIR</pattern><template>I had to cut across Mulholland.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST STAND DOWN</pattern><template>If something happens, then come in.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU KIDDING ME WITH THIS</pattern><template>Get rid of them.</template></category><category><pattern>THE COPPER WIRE  YOU GOT IT</pattern><template>Okay, I got it! I got it!</template></category><category><pattern>IT WORKS</pattern><template>Listen to me, Tony. We're a team.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  YOU KNOW THAT I WOULD HELP YOU WITH ANYTHING  BUT I CANNOT HELP YOU IF YOU'RE GOING TO START ALL OF THIS AGAIN</pattern><template>There is nothing except this.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOOD</pattern><template>I thought I lost you back there.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT DO YOU SAY TO YOUR OTHER NICKNAME</pattern><template>The Merchant of Death ?</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS</pattern><template>This is a flight stabilizer.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  NO</pattern><template>Am I making you uncomfortable?</template></category><category><pattern>SO</pattern><template>I think it's a fair example.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE US A COUPLE MINUTES  YOU GUYS</pattern><template>I'm surprised.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS SO HAPPY WHEN HE CAME HOME</pattern><template>It was like we got him back from the dead.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME HAVE THE ENGINEERS ANALYZE THAT</pattern><template>You know, draw up some specs.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY  HEY  TONY  LISTEN</pattern><template>I'm trying to turn this thing around, but you gotta give me something.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I ORDERED THE HIT ON YOU  I WORRIED THAT I WAS KILLING THE GOLDEN GOOSE</pattern><template>But, you see, it was just fate that you survived that.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD</pattern><template>I want you to reach in, and you're just gonna gently lift the wire out.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MY PHONE  THAT'S A PICTURE OF ME AND MY DAD</pattern><template>Right there. In the garbage.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD LIKE A DRINK  PLEASE</pattern><template>Got it, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WANTS YOU TO MAKE THE LIST OF MATERIALS</pattern><template>He says for you to start working immediately, and when you're done, he will set you free.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT BAD</pattern><template>Let me guess. Berkeley?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM PLEASED TO REPORT THAT THE PILOT WAS NOT INJURED</pattern><template>As for the unexpected turn of events on the ground in Gulmira, it is still unclear who or what intervened, but I can assure you that the United States government was not involved. Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD OBADIAH</pattern><template>Okay, where's Tony now?</template></category><category><pattern>ABSOLUTELY  WE'RE</pattern><template>I'm going to have to call you back.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY</pattern><template>What do you want me to do with this?</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  WHO DO YOU THINK LOCKED YOU OUT</pattern><template>I was the one who filed the injunction against you.</template></category><category><pattern>AM SO</pattern><template>You're not.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>Is it?</template></category><category><pattern>TONY</pattern><template>You've all received the official statement of what occurred at Stark Industries last night. There have been unconfirmed reports that a robotic prototype malfunctioned and caused damage to the arc reactor. Fortunately, a member of Tony Stark's personal security staff...  Iron Man.  That's kind of catchy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY NOT A PILOT WITHOUT THE PLANE</pattern><template>Look who fell out of the sky.</template></category><category><pattern>NOBODY ROPED ME INTO ANYTHING</pattern><template>I'm so sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>DEFLECT IT AND ABSORB IT</pattern><template>Don't transmit it back to me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ARC REACTOR  THAT'S A PUBLICITY STUNT</pattern><template>Tony, come on. We built that thing to shut the hippies up!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TILL TOMORROW TO ASSEMBLE MY MISSILE</pattern><template>Okay? Can you move?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT A BIG ONE POWERING MY FACTORY AT HOME</pattern><template>It should keep the shrapnel out of my heart.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE TWO THINGS I WANT TO DO</pattern><template>I want an American cheeseburger,   and the other...</template></category><category><pattern>DESTROY IT</pattern><template>Incinerate it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SHOULD KEEP THE SHRAPNEL OUT OF MY HEART</pattern><template>But what could it generate?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REMEMBER THIS ONE  RIGHT</pattern><template>It's a shame the government didn't approve it.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME MAKE A CALL</pattern><template>Sergeant, clear a hole.</template></category><category><pattern>A VERY ASTUTE OBSERVATION  SIR  PERHAPS  IF YOU INTEND TO VISIT OTHER PLANETS  WE SHOULD IMPROVE THE EXOSYSTEMS  CONNECT TO THE SYS  CO</pattern><template>Have it reconfigure the shell metals.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WOW  WHAT'S THAT</pattern><template>It's, like, a little device?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S PALLADIUM  0 15 GRAMS</pattern><template>We need at least 1.6, so why don't you go break down the other 11?</template></category><category><pattern>PEPPER  I'VE BEEN CALLED MANY THINGS</pattern><template>Nostalgic  is not one of them.</template></category><category><pattern>I RESPECT YOU</pattern><template>I'm just your babysitter.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD YOU HAVE A LOUSIER POKER FACE</pattern><template>Just tell me, who told you?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST A GAME  NEVER MIND</pattern><template>Just gently lift the wire. Okay? Great.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS OUR TICKET OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>What is it?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST TELL ME  WHO TOLD YOU</pattern><template>Never mind who told me. Show me.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD HAVE GONE BETTER IF YOU WERE THERE</pattern><template>You told me to lay low.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT</pattern><template>That's something else.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I AT LEAST GET A REACTION FROM YOU</pattern><template>Panic. I would say panic is my reaction.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD NIGHT  TONY    HEY  TONY</pattern><template>I'm sorry, this is the  fun vee.  The  hum drum vee  is back there.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HOW AMERICA DOES IT</pattern><template>And it's worked out pretty well so far.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT THE CIA ON THE LINE</pattern><template>I've got Langley on the line.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LEFT A PART OF HIMSELF IN THAT CAVE</pattern><template>Breaks my heart.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW  MR  STARK HAS PREPARED A STATEMENT  HE WILL NOT BE TAKING ANY QUESTIONS  THANK YOU  BEEN A WHILE SINCE I WAS IN FRONT OF YOU  I FIGURE I'LL STICK TO THE CARDS THIS TIME  THERE'S BEEN SPECULATION THAT I WAS INVOLVED IN THE EVENTS THAT OCCURRED ON THE FREEWAY AND THE ROOFTOP    I'M SORRY  MR  STARK  BUT DO YOU HONESTLY EXPECT US TO BELIEVE THAT THAT WAS A BODYGUARD IN A SUIT THAT CONVENIENTLY APPEARED    DESPITE THE FACT THAT YOU</pattern><template>I know that it's confusing. It is one thing to question the official story, and another thing entirely to make wild accusations, or insinuate that I'm a superhero. I never said you were a superhero.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE</pattern><template>They are your loyal customers, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'VE BEEN DEALING UNDER THE TABLE  AND I'M GOING TO STOP THEM</pattern><template>I'm going to find my weapons and destroy them.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THEN  THIS IS A VERY IMPORTANT WEEK FOR YOU  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>If this is going to be my work station, I want it well lit. I want these up.</template></category><category><pattern>I HONESTLY    I COULDN'T HAVE CALLED THAT</pattern><template>I mean, I'd apologize, but isn't that what we're going for here?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED ANSWERS</pattern><template>Can I please get eyes on target?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>He's not answering his phone.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU OKAY</pattern><template>Yeah, I feel great.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THING JUST TOOK OUT AN F 22 INSIDE A LEGAL NO FLY ZONE</pattern><template>Whiplash Two, if you have a clear shot, take it!</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF THEY DON'T  I'LL PROBABLY BE DEAD IN A WEEK</pattern><template>Well, then, this is a very important week for you, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED HIM</pattern><template>Good assistant.</template></category><category><pattern>THE COPPER WIRE</pattern><template>The copper wire, you got it?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST THINK YOU'RE OVERSTATING IT</pattern><template>You know, and we're here, and then I'm wearing this ridiculous dress, and then we were dancing like that and...</template></category><category><pattern>I CAME TO REALIZE THAT I HAVE MORE TO OFFER THIS WORLD THAN JUST MAKING THINGS THAT BLOW UP</pattern><template>And that is why, effective immediately, I am shutting down the weapons manufacturing division of Stark International until such a time as I can decide what the future of the company will be. I think we're gonna be selling a lot of newspapers. What direction it should take, one that I'm comfortable with and is consistent with the highest good for this country, as well. What we should take away from this is that Tony's back! And he's healthier than ever. We're going to have a little internal discussion and we'll get back to you with the follow up.   Where is he?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE FIRST MISSILE SYSTEM TO INCORPORATE OUR PROPRIETARY REPULSOR TECHNOLOGY</pattern><template>They say the best weapon is one you never have to fire.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I DID IS TO SAVE YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>I removed all the shrapnel I could, but there's a lot left, and it's headed into your atrial septum.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD GOD  YOU'RE A WOMAN</pattern><template>I honestly... I couldn't have called that.</template></category><category><pattern>RHODEY  I'M WORKING ON SOMETHING BIG</pattern><template>I came to talk to you.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID IT'S RHODES    SPEAK UP  PLEASE</pattern><template>What in the hell is that noise?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Just read it, word for word.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WANTS YOU TO BUILD THE MISSILE</pattern><template>The Jericho missile that you demonstrated.</template></category><category><pattern>OBIE  I JUST DON'T WANT A BODY COUNT TO BE OUR ONLY LEGACY</pattern><template>That's what we do. We're iron mongers.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T REMEMBER</pattern><template>No, you wouldn't.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASURE MEETING YOU</pattern><template>Give us a couple minutes, you guys.</template></category><category><pattern>KILL POWER</pattern><template>Notes. Main transducer feels sluggish at plus 40 altitude.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW I REALIZE  WELL  TONY NEVER REALLY DID COME HOME  DID HE</pattern><template>He left a part of himself in that cave.</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE  RIGHT NOW  COME WITH ME</pattern><template>Right now?</template></category><category><pattern>BROWN  ACTUALLY</pattern><template>Well, Ms. Brown, it's an imperfect world, but it's the only one we've got.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S IT  OBIE  FORGET IT</pattern><template>All right, well, this stays with me, then.</template></category><category><pattern>SHALL I STORE THIS ON THE STARK INDUSTRIES CENTRAL DATABASE  ACTUALLY  I DON'T KNOW WHO TO TRUST RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Till further notice, why don't we just keep everything on my private server?</template></category><category><pattern>A HICCUP</pattern><template>Yes, to power the suit, sir, the technology actually doesn't exist.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WEIRD  COME ON  IT'S OKAY  LAUGH</pattern><template>Sir, I have a question to ask.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  HE ALWAYS GETS THE GOOD STUFF  DOESN'T HE</pattern><template>I was so happy when he came home.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE TRY    WEAPONS STATUS</pattern><template>Repulsors offline. Missiles offline. Flares!</template></category><category><pattern>I'D LIKE TO SHOW YOU FIRST HAND</pattern><template>All I want is a serious answer.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TELL YOU  IN MY EXPERIENCE  NO UNMANNED AERIAL VEHICLE WILL EVER TRUMP A PILOT'S INSTINCT  HIS INSIGHT  THAT ABILITY TO LOOK INTO A SITUATION BEYOND THE OBVIOUS AND DISCERN ITS OUTCOME  OR A PILOT'S JUDGMENT</pattern><template>Colonel?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY OTHER HEX BOLT</pattern><template>They're coming!</template></category><category><pattern>FLATTEN THEM OUT AND LOOK</pattern><template>Oh, wow.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY I DIDN'T GIVE YOU A HEADS UP  OKAY</pattern><template>But if I had...</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE FINE  OKAY</pattern><template>No!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>When I get up in the morning and I'm putting on my uniform, you know what I recognize?</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  NO GANG SIGNS</pattern><template>No, throw it up. I'm kidding.</template></category><category><pattern>CALL FOR A PRESS CONFERENCE</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID NOT TELL US THAT THE TARGET YOU PAID US TO KILL WAS THE GREAT TONY STARK    AS YOU CAN SEE  OBADIAH STANE      OH  MY GOD</pattern><template>... your deception and lies will cost you dearly. The price to kill Tony Stark has just gone up. So, what are we going to do about this?</template></category><category><pattern>NICK FURY  DIRECTOR OF S H I E L D</pattern><template>I'm here to talk to you about the Avenger Initiative.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOING TO KILL YOURSELF  TONY</pattern><template>I'm not going to be a part of it.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU'RE FINE</pattern><template>You're the most capable, qualified, trustworthy person I've ever met.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS FOR THE SAVE</pattern><template>This is beautiful. Thank you. Thank you all very much. This is wonderful. Well, I'm not Tony Stark. But if I were Tony, I would tell you how honored I feel and what a joy it is to receive this very prestigious award. Tony, you know... The best thing about Tony is also the worst thing. He's always working. Work it! Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU UNDERSTAND ME</pattern><template>That was Dad's line.</template></category><category><pattern>A WHAT</pattern><template>They want to lock you out.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FUNNY HOW THAT WORKS  HUH  YEAH  SPEAKING OF FUNNY  WE'VE GOT A WEAPONS DEPOT THAT WAS JUST BLOWN UP A FEW CLICKS FROM WHERE YOU WERE BEING HELD CAPTIVE</pattern><template>Well, that's a hot spot. Sounds like someone stepped in and did your job for you, huh? Why do you sound out of breath, Tony?</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER HELPED DEFEAT THE NAZIS</pattern><template>He worked on the Manhattan Project.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED OVER THERE</pattern><template>I had my eyes opened.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TRYING TO TURN THIS THING AROUND  BUT YOU GOTTA GIVE ME SOMETHING</pattern><template>Something to pitch them.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A MASTERPIECE  LOOK AT THAT</pattern><template>This is your legacy.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT CAUGHT DOING A PIECE FOR VANITY FAIR  FOR THREE HOURS  FOR THREE HOURS YOU GOT ME STANDING HERE</pattern><template>Waiting on you now. Let's go. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M YOUR MAN</pattern><template>Hi. I told him I was sorry, but he...</template></category><category><pattern>AND</pattern><template>It was very nice.</template></category><category><pattern>GET RID OF THEM</pattern><template>Your eyes are red.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS'LL GET YOU IN</pattern><template>It's probably under Executive Files.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY HERE</pattern><template>Whoa!</template></category><category><pattern>SET UP SECTOR 16 UNDERNEATH THE ARC REACTOR  AND I'M GOING TO WANT THIS DATA MASKED</pattern><template>Recruit our top engineers.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A COMMON ENEMY</pattern><template>If we are still in business, I will give you these designs as a gift.</template></category><category><pattern>THE COMPRESSION IN CYLINDER THREE APPEARS TO BE LOW  LOG THAT</pattern><template>I'm gonna try again, right now.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE CARE</pattern><template>Ms. Potts? We had an appointment.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO DANCE</pattern><template>Oh, no.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TRUTH IS I AM IRON MAN  JARVIS</pattern><template>Welcome home, sir.  I am Iron Man.  You think you're the only superhero in the world?</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME YOU NEVER THINK ABOUT THAT NIGHT</pattern><template>What night?</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>AT STARK INDUSTRIES</pattern><template>Tell you what.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT NECESSARY  PEOPLE</pattern><template>Just a training exercise.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M FINE  HOW ARE      OBADIAH  HE'S GONE INSANE</pattern><template>I know.   Listen, you'd better get out of there.   He built a suit.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SHOULD BE UP RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR YOU  SIR  ALWAYS  I'D LIKE TO OPEN A NEW PROJECT FILE  INDEX AS MARK TWO</pattern><template>Shall I store this on the Stark Industries Central Database? Actually, I don't know who to trust right now.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THAT'S A HOT SPOT  SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE STEPPED IN AND DID YOUR JOB FOR YOU  HUH  WHY DO YOU SOUND OUT OF BREATH  TONY</pattern><template>I'm not, I was just jogging in the canyon.   I thought you were driving.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS THE ONLY WAY I COULD PROTECT YOU</pattern><template>No. No.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WOW</pattern><template>Impressive.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING ELSE  YOU'RE KIDDING ME WITH THE HAND UP  RIGHT</pattern><template>Is it cool if I take a picture with you?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>You were on your yacht.</template></category><category><pattern>DAY 11  TEST 37  CONFIGURATION 2 0</pattern><template>For lack of a better option, Dummy is still on fire safety.</template></category><category><pattern>READY  IN THREE  TWO  ONE</pattern><template>Handles like a dream.</template></category><category><pattern>A FEW TEARS FOR YOUR LONG LOST BOSS</pattern><template>Tears of joy. I hate job hunting.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MERCHANT OF DEATH</pattern><template>That's not bad.</template></category><category><pattern>LIEUTENANT COLONEL RHODES ROLLS  AND</pattern><template>Two craps. Line away.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU FORGET ABOUT OUR APPOINTMENT</pattern><template>Nope, right now. Come with me.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW ARE YOU GOING TO COME BY AND SEE WHAT I'M WORKING ON  NO  NO  NO  NO  NO  NO  THE LESS I KNOW  THE BETTER</pattern><template>Now, what am I supposed to tell the press?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING</pattern><template>I've been in captivity for three months.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS HIS NAME</pattern><template>Don't do that.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NOTHING ABOUT STANE HERE</pattern><template>That's being handled. He's on vacation.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  TONY  ARE YOU THERE  HELLO  BREATHE</pattern><template>Easy, easy.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS FOR YOU TO START WORKING IMMEDIATELY  AND WHEN YOU'RE DONE  HE WILL SET YOU FREE</pattern><template>No, he won't.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT SO</pattern><template>Well, then, I quit.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS ONE</pattern><template>I refuse.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT TODAY'S PAPER</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO SIGN THIS BEFORE YOU GET ON THE PLANE</pattern><template>What are you trying to get rid of me for?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  AND WE'RE HERE  AND THEN I'M WEARING THIS RIDICULOUS DRESS  AND THEN WE WERE DANCING LIKE THAT AND</pattern><template>I would like a drink, please.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD STILL  YOU LITTLE PRICK</pattern><template>Just do it!</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE NOTHING</pattern><template>Any high altitude surveillance in the region?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I HEAR THAT A LOT</pattern><template>Listen, I know this must be a trying time for you, but we need to debrief you.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD CHUTE  GOOD CHUTE    TONY  YOU STILL THERE</pattern><template>Hey, thanks. Oh, my God, you crazy son of a bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THIS IS GOING TO BE MY WORK STATION  I WANT IT WELL LIT  I WANT THESE UP</pattern><template>I need welding gear.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK IT WAS TAKEN THAT WAY</pattern><template>Because it makes me look like the one who's trying to...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STILL HAVEN'T TOLD ME WHERE YOU'RE FROM</pattern><template>I'm from a small town called Gulmira.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS TOTALLY WEIRD</pattern><template>Totally harmless.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T HAVE SASHIMI WITHOUT SAKE</pattern><template>You are constitutionally incapable of being responsible.</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT COULSON</pattern><template>I just wanted to say thank you very much for all of your help.</template></category><category><pattern>WAITING ON YOU NOW  LET'S GO  COME ON</pattern><template>Wheels up! Rock and roll!</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT TO SEE IT</pattern><template>Okay, Rhodey.</template></category><category><pattern>INDEED I AM</pattern><template>After all these years, Tony still has you picking up the dry cleaning.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT YOU</pattern><template>You had to have a burger, yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST A TRAINING EXERCISE</pattern><template>Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>You mind if I come down there and see what you're doing?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU'RE MORE THAN WHAT YOU ARE</pattern><template>Can you excuse me if I'm a bit distracted here?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FINE</pattern><template>What do you want me to do?</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME  TELL ME</pattern><template>Function 11.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT ME</pattern><template>Stay put. Nice.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'D HAVE MADE YOUR FATHER PROUD</pattern><template>It's ready, Tony! Get off the roof!</template></category><category><pattern>THREE HOURS</pattern><template>I got caught doing a piece for Vanity Fair. For three hours. For three hours you got me standing here.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  IT'S BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>Tony, this is your Ninth Symphony.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY</pattern><template>That thing just jumped off the radar, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  NOT AS CONSERVATIVE AS YOURS</pattern><template>Too bad you had to involve Pepper in this.</template></category><category><pattern>NON RESPONSIVE  SIR  THEN YOU ARE CLEAR TO ENGAGE</pattern><template>Hit it. That bogey just went supersonic. I got a lock!   Inbound missile.   Flares!</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS BUILDING A SUIT</pattern><template>I thought it'd be bigger.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT THE NIGHT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>Thought so.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT AT ALL</pattern><template>Puzzle.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE A TRAGEDY</pattern><template>Okay, let's do this right. Start mark, half a meter, and back and center. Dummy, look alive. You're on standby for fire safety. You, roll it.</template></category><category><pattern>TO PEACE</pattern><template>Tony.   Obie, what are you doing up?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  ME ON THE COMPANY'S BEHALF BEING RESPONSIBLE FOR THE WAY THAT</pattern><template>This is great.</template></category><category><pattern>A LITTLE LESS FORMAL AND</pattern><template>What's up with the love in?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  RHODEY  I KNOW A SHORTCUT</pattern><template>Good boy.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT A PROTOTYPE RIGHT AWAY</pattern><template>Hey. You busy?</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME  MR  STARK  WE LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR WEAPONS PRESENTATION</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>I'm not like you. I'm not cut out...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE ALL RECEIVED THE OFFICIAL STATEMENT OF WHAT OCCURRED AT STARK INDUSTRIES LAST NIGHT  THERE HAVE BEEN UNCONFIRMED REPORTS THAT A ROBOTIC PROTOTYPE MALFUNCTIONED AND CAUSED DAMAGE TO THE ARC REACTOR  FORTUNATELY  A MEMBER OF TONY STARK'S PERSONAL SECURITY STAFF     IRON MAN   THAT'S KIND OF CATCHY</pattern><template>It's got a nice ring to it.</template></category><category><pattern>AN EMPIRE TWICE THE SIZE OF ALEXANDER THE GREAT AND FOUR TIMES THE SIZE OF THE ROMAN EMPIRE</pattern><template>But today, whoever holds the latest Stark weapons rules these lands.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  I TOLD HIM I WAS SORRY  BUT HE</pattern><template>I'm just indifferent right now.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GOD</pattern><template>But I could fire you if that would take the edge off.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN SEE THAT</pattern><template>I'd like to show you first hand.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE THE MOST CAPABLE  QUALIFIED  TRUSTWORTHY PERSON I'VE EVER MET</pattern><template>You're gonna do great.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THAT  RIGHT</pattern><template>Yeah, well, technically, he hit me.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE DON'T</pattern><template>You look great, Hef.</template></category><category><pattern>AM I RIGHT  WE HAVEN'T HAD A BREAKTHROUGH IN THAT IN WHAT</pattern><template>Thirty years.</template></category><category><pattern>WEAPONS THAT WILL HELP STEER THE WORLD BACK ON COURSE  PUT THE BALANCE OF POWER IN OUR HANDS</pattern><template>The right hands.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO HAVE TO CALL YOU BACK</pattern><template>Mr. Stane? Sir, we've explored what you've asked us, and it seems as though there's a little hiccup.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHEN YOU NEED YOUR DIAPER CHANGED    THANK YOU</pattern><template>Let me know and I'll get you a bottle, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME  DO YOU PLAN TO REPORT ON THE MILLIONS WE'VE SAVED BY ADVANCING MEDICAL TECHNOLOGY OR KEPT FROM STARVATION WITH OUR INTELLI CROPS</pattern><template>All those breakthroughs, military funding, honey.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW I'M GOING TO KILL YOU WITH IT</pattern><template>You ripped out my targeting system!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST BE THE FAMOUS PEPPER POTTS</pattern><template>Indeed I am.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THAT    THAT WENT WELL</pattern><template>Did I just paint a target on the back of my head?</template></category><category><pattern>WE THINK IT'S AN UNMANNED AERIAL VEHICLE</pattern><template>Colonel, what are we dealing with here?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  COME ON  IN PUBLIC  THE PRESS</pattern><template>This was a board of directors meeting.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU EXCUSE ME IF I'M A BIT DISTRACTED HERE</pattern><template>No! You can't be distracted right now!</template></category><category><pattern>HERE'S YOUR ALIBI</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WORSE THINGS HAVE HAPPENED</pattern><template>I think we're gonna be fine.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WORKED ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>That's what I do.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEY WILL NEVER FIND YOU IN THESE MOUNTAINS</pattern><template>Look, what you just saw, that is your legacy, Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU WOULDN'T</pattern><template>If I had been that drunk, I wouldn't have been able to stand, much less give a lecture on integrated circuits.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T WANT TO KEEP IT</pattern><template>Pepper, I've been called many things.</template></category><category><pattern>MARCH AND I HAD A SCHEDULING CONFLICT  BUT FORTUNATELY  THE CHRISTMAS COVER WAS TWINS</pattern><template>Anything else? You're kidding me with the hand up, right?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>You are a very rare woman.</template></category><category><pattern>SMALL AIRCRAFT HAVE SUCH A POOR SAFETY RECORD</pattern><template>But what about the whole cover story that it's a bodyguard?</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH YOU COULD'VE SEEN MY PROTOTYPE</pattern><template>It's not as...</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THAT STUFF</pattern><template>The future of air combat.</template></category><category><pattern>I REMOVED ALL THE SHRAPNEL I COULD  BUT THERE'S A LOT LEFT  AND IT'S HEADED INTO YOUR ATRIAL SEPTUM</pattern><template>Here, want to see?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR</pattern><template>Thirteen percent power, sir.   Climb!</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT OF PEOPLE  INCLUDING YOUR PROFESSORS AT BROWN  WOULD CALL THAT BEING A HERO</pattern><template>And a lot of people would also call that war profiteering.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S OKAY</pattern><template>I want this. I want this.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S AN EXPOSED WIRE UNDER THIS DEVICE</pattern><template>And it's contacting the socket wall and causing a little bit of a short.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD LIKE A VODKA MARTINI  PLEASE</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>OR MAYBE HE WAS EVERY INCH THE MAN WE ALL REMEMBER FROM THE NEWSREELS</pattern><template>I saw young Americans killed by the very weapons I created to defend them and protect them.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT APPARENTLY  NOT ENOUGH FOR THIS PLACE</pattern><template>They speak Arabic, Urdu, Dari, Pashto, Mongolian, Farsi, Russian.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ALLOWED TO HAVE PLANS ON MY BIRTHDAY</pattern><template>It's your birthday?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I'M GOING IN NOW</pattern><template>Make sure you wait till I clear the roof.</template></category><category><pattern>41 STEPS STRAIGHT AHEAD  THEN 16 STEPS  THAT'S FROM THE DOOR  FORK RIGHT  33 STEPS  TURN RIGHT</pattern><template>Yinsen! Yinsen! Stark!</template></category><category><pattern>GENERAL</pattern><template>Welcome, Mr. Stark. We look forward to your weapons presentation.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT  WAIT  GIVE ME A GUN</pattern><template>Stay here!</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  THANKS</pattern><template>I'd better get back there.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YEAH  I'M DRIVING WITH THE TOP DOWN</pattern><template>Yeah, well, I need your help right now.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S COMPLETELY HARMLESS</pattern><template>I didn't expect that.</template></category><category><pattern>HANDLES LIKE A DREAM</pattern><template>All right, let's see what this thing can do.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT AS</pattern><template>Well, not as conservative as yours.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEAT UP THE SAKE  WILL YOU</pattern><template>Thanks for reminding me.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  TRY NOT TO MOVE  SIR  WHAT'S GOING ON HERE</pattern><template>Let's face it. This is not the worst thing you've caught me doing.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  LET'S DO THIS RIGHT  START MARK  HALF A METER  AND BACK AND CENTER  DUMMY  LOOK ALIVE  YOU'RE ON STANDBY FOR FIRE SAFETY  YOU  ROLL IT</pattern><template>Okay. Activate hand controls. We're gonna start off nice and easy. We're gonna see if 10% thrust capacity achieves lift. And three, two, one. Up two. All right, set that.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING</pattern><template>Whatever it was, it just bought the farm. I think bogey's been handled, sir.   Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT'S CONTACTING THE SOCKET WALL AND CAUSING A LITTLE BIT OF A SHORT</pattern><template>It's fine.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE ABOUT TO ARREST OBADIAH</pattern><template>That's not going to be enough.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T NAVY</pattern><template>Wasn't Marines.</template></category><category><pattern>YINSEN</pattern><template>Watch out!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THEY WERE USING HUMAN SHIELDS</pattern><template>We never got the green light.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE THROWING ONE OF THESE IN WITH EVERY PURCHASE OF 500 MILLION OR MORE</pattern><template>To peace!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT LOVELY LADY YOU WOKE UP WITH</pattern><template>Don't do that!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE BEEN CALLED THE DA VINCI OF OUR TIME</pattern><template>What do you say to that?</template></category><category><pattern>CAREFUL</pattern><template>Careful, we only get one shot at this.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  TO POWER THE SUIT  SIR  THE TECHNOLOGY ACTUALLY DOESN'T EXIST</pattern><template>So it's...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M GOING TO GO TO MY ASSISTANT  AND WE'LL MAKE A DATE</pattern><template>You look fantastic!</template></category><category><pattern>CONTACT LEFT</pattern><template>What have we got?</template></category><category><pattern>WE OWN THE CONTROLLING INTEREST IN THE COMPANY</pattern><template>Tony, the board has rights, too.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  THIS IS THE  FUN VEE   THE  HUM DRUM VEE  IS BACK THERE</pattern><template>Nice job.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  MS  BROWN  IT'S AN IMPERFECT WORLD  BUT IT'S THE ONLY ONE WE'VE GOT</pattern><template>I guarantee you, the day weapons are no longer needed to keep the peace, I'll start making bricks and beams for baby hospitals.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AGENT PHIL COULSON  WITH THE STRATEGIC HOMELAND INTERVENTION  ENFORCEMENT AND LOGISTICS DIVISION</pattern><template>That's quite a mouthful.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO WITH THIS</pattern><template>That?</template></category><category><pattern>TABLE</pattern><template>Could be worse! Could be worse!</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH IT  COMING UP HERE</pattern><template>Are you kidding me with this?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE YOU BACK AT BASE</pattern><template>I wouldn't do that if I were you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW</pattern><template>How'd that work?</template></category><category><pattern>THIRTY YEARS</pattern><template>That's what they say.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT'S WORKED OUT PRETTY WELL SO FAR</pattern><template>Find an excuse to let one of these off the chain, and I personally guarantee you the bad guys won't even want to come out of their caves.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOLD ME TO LAY LOW</pattern><template>That's what I've been doing.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S PROBABLY UNDER EXECUTIVE FILES</pattern><template>If not, they put it on a ghost drive, in which case you need to look for the lowest numeric heading.</template></category><category><pattern>TIME TO HIT THE BUTTON</pattern><template>You told me not to!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW COME IT DIDN'T SHOW UP ON THE RADAR</pattern><template>Got a minimal radar cross section, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WE MAKE WEAPONS</pattern><template>It's my name on the side of the building.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>Flatten them out and look.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SO SORRY</pattern><template>Yeah, it's okay.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SHOULD ENSURE A FUSELAGE INTEGRITY WHILE MAINTAINING POWER TO WEIGHT RATIO</pattern><template>Got it?</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T RECOGNIZE YOU</pattern><template>What are you doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THE SPRINGS WAS ACTUALLY THE NEIGHBORHOOD IN EAST HAMPTON WHERE HE LIVED AND WORKED    NOT  SPRING  LIKE THE SEASON</pattern><template>So?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  STAND UP  STAND UP</pattern><template>Just do as I do.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW BIG ARE YOUR HANDS    I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY</pattern><template>Get down here. I need you. Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>WEAPONS MANUFACTURING IS ONLY ONE SMALL PART OF WHAT STARK INDUSTRIES IS ALL ABOUT  AND OUR PARTNERSHIP WITH THE FIRE AND RESCUE COMMUNITY</pattern><template>Hey, Tony, remember me?</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN WERE THESE TAKEN</pattern><template>Yesterday.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME</pattern><template>Don't waste it. Don't waste your life.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS THEY HAVE EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO BUILD THE JERICHO MISSILE</pattern><template>He wants you to make the list of materials.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  HERE'S SERIOUS</pattern><template>My old man had a philosophy,  Peace means having a bigger stick than the other guy.  That's a great line coming from the guy selling the sticks.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GONNA DO GREAT</pattern><template>Is it too much of a problem to ask?</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON  HERE  YOU CAN HAVE A PIECE</pattern><template>Take two.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO</pattern><template>Put that on the table over there.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  WHAT YOU JUST SAW  THAT IS YOUR LEGACY  STARK</pattern><template>Your life's work, in the hands of those murderers.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY    OBIE  WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP</pattern><template>I couldn't sleep till I found out how it went. How'd it go? It went great. Looks like it's gonna be an early Christmas.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES HE WANT</pattern><template>What do you want? A delivery date?</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT A GOOD REPRESENTATION OF HIS SPRING PERIOD</pattern><template>No. The Springs was actually the neighborhood in East Hampton where he lived and worked,   not  spring  like the season.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY NIGHT IN FRONT OF THE MIRROR BEFORE BEDTIME</pattern><template>I can see that.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOTHING  IT'S JUST A LITTLE SNAG</pattern><template>There's an exposed wire under this device.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW THAT  ALREADY</pattern><template>Yeah. Isn't that strange?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT PART OF THE PRESS CONFERENCE  BUT IT'S ABOUT TO BEGIN RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>I'm not a reporter.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE CONSTITUTIONALLY INCAPABLE OF BEING RESPONSIBLE</pattern><template>It would be irresponsible not to drink.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER ALL THESE YEARS  TONY STILL HAS YOU PICKING UP THE DRY CLEANING</pattern><template>I do anything and everything that Mr. Stark requires, including, occasionally, taking out the trash.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A CHAMP</pattern><template>Why are you trying to hustle me out of here?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE SAME DAY AS LAST YEAR</pattern><template>Get yourself something nice from me.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT I LOST YOU BACK THERE</pattern><template>You did, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED IT  BUY IT  STORE IT</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO PROMISE ME THAT YOU'RE GONNA LAY LOW</pattern><template>Stark Industries! I've got one recommendation! Ready? Ready? Sell, sell, sell! Abandon ship! Does the Hindenburg ring any bells? Let me show you the new Stark Industries business plan! Look, that's a weapons company that doesn't make weapons! Pepper. How big are your hands?   What?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S KIND OF FLIMSY  DON'T YOU THINK</pattern><template>This isn't my first rodeo, Mr. Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I GET CLEAR OF THE ROOF  I'LL LET YOU KNOW</pattern><template>You're going to hit the master bypass button.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ALL I HAVE  TOO  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Sector 16?</template></category><category><pattern>SPEAKING OF MANNED OR UNMANNED  YOU GOTTA GET HIM TO TELL YOU ABOUT THE TIME HE GUESSED WRONG AT SPRING BREAK</pattern><template>Just remember that, spring break, 1987.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT A REPORTER</pattern><template>I'm agent Phil Coulson, with the Strategic Homeland Intervention, Enforcement and Logistics Division.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS TOTALLY NOT HARMLESS  BY THE WAY</pattern><template>We're dancing. No one's even watching.</template></category><category><pattern>RENDER UNTO CAESAR THAT WHICH IS CAESAR'S  THERE YOU GO</pattern><template>Mr. Stark! Excuse me, Mr. Stark!</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR LIFE'S WORK  IN THE HANDS OF THOSE MURDERERS</pattern><template>Is that how you want to go out?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A GREAT QUARTER</pattern><template>What's the world coming to when a guy's got to crash his own party?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOING TO HIT THE MASTER BYPASS BUTTON</pattern><template>It's going to fry everything up here.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE</pattern><template>Are you okay?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO</pattern><template>All right, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  YOUR PICTURE  PLEASE</pattern><template>Let's take a picture. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  IT WAS A BIRTHDAY PRESENT</pattern><template>That's great.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE IT MAKES ME LOOK LIKE THE ONE WHO'S TRYING TO</pattern><template>I just think you're overstating it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAD TO HAVE A BURGER  YEAH</pattern><template>Well, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING TO PITCH THEM</pattern><template>Let me have the engineers analyze that.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  IT'S NOT TECHNICALLY ACCURATE</pattern><template>The suit's a gold titanium alloy, but it's kind of evocative, the imagery, anyway.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>That's what I was trying to tell you before.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA MAKE THIS OKAY</pattern><template>Let's hope.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT GOING TO BE ENOUGH</pattern><template>Section 16. Section 16. There it is.</template></category><category><pattern>OPTIMISTICALLY  40 POINTS</pattern><template>At minimum.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I'M SORRY  AM I IN YOUR WAY</pattern><template>Up.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL THAT BE ALL</pattern><template>Give me an exploded view.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT BASED ON WHAT I SAW</pattern><template>We're not doing a good enough job.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS   WELCOME  TONY STARK  THE MOST FAMOUS MASS MURDERER  IN THE HISTORY OF AMERICA   HE IS HONORED</pattern><template>He wants you to build the missile.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME GUESS  BERKELEY</pattern><template>Brown, actually.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WANT TO LOCK YOU OUT</pattern><template>Why, 'cause the stocks dipped 40 points?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT A LITTLE AIR</pattern><template>Yes, I need some air.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU READING  PLATYPUS</pattern><template>Nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS  IT IS NOW AN ANTIQUE</pattern><template>This is what will be keeping me alive for the foreseeable future.</template></category><category><pattern>I REFUSE</pattern><template>Tony! He wants to know what you think.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  HELLO</pattern><template>I said it's Rhodes.   Speak up, please.</template></category><category><pattern>RELAX</pattern><template>The bow and arrow once was the pinnacle of weapons technology.</template></category><category><pattern>TECHNOLOGY</pattern><template>It's always been your Achilles' heel in this part of the world.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOUR COMPANY DID</pattern><template>Well, I'm not my company.</template></category><category><pattern>WERE WE CLEARED TO GO IN THERE</pattern><template>No, they were using human shields.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK THE OVER UNDER ON THE STOCK DROP IS GONNA BE TOMORROW</pattern><template>Optimistically, 40 points.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED AT LEAST 1 6  SO WHY DON'T YOU GO BREAK DOWN THE OTHER 11</pattern><template>Careful.</template></category><category><pattern>WORKING ON A SECRET PROJECT  ARE WE  SIR  I DON'T WANT THIS WINDING UP IN THE WRONG HANDS</pattern><template>Maybe in mine, it can actually do some good.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU GOT PLANS</pattern><template>As a matter of fact, I do.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  ACTIVATE HAND CONTROLS  WE'RE GONNA START OFF NICE AND EASY  WE'RE GONNA SEE IF 10% THRUST CAPACITY ACHIEVES LIFT  AND THREE  TWO  ONE  UP TWO  ALL RIGHT  SET THAT</pattern><template>I've been buzzing you.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST READ IT  WORD FOR WORD</pattern><template>There's nothing about Stane here.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT DEFINITELY IS NOT US  SIR</pattern><template>It wasn't Navy.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS FOR REMINDING ME</pattern><template>No, I'm not talking...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS NOT FOR THE MILITARY  I'M NOT</pattern><template>It's different.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OWE ME A PLANE</pattern><template>You know that, right?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU INTIMIDATE THEM</pattern><template>Good God, you're a woman.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT IS WHY  EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY  I AM SHUTTING DOWN THE WEAPONS MANUFACTURING DIVISION OF STARK INTERNATIONAL UNTIL SUCH A TIME AS I CAN DECIDE WHAT THE FUTURE OF THE COMPANY WILL BE  I THINK WE'RE GONNA BE SELLING A LOT OF NEWSPAPERS  WHAT DIRECTION IT SHOULD TAKE  ONE THAT I'M COMFORTABLE WITH AND IS CONSISTENT WITH THE HIGHEST GOOD FOR THIS COUNTRY  AS WELL  WHAT WE SHOULD TAKE AWAY FROM THIS IS THAT TONY'S BACK  AND HE'S HEALTHIER THAN EVER  WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A LITTLE INTERNAL DISCUSSION AND WE'LL GET BACK TO YOU WITH THE FOLLOW UP    WHERE IS HE</pattern><template>He's inside.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DO YOU THINK YOU'RE STILL ALIVE</pattern><template>What do I call you?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BEN</pattern><template>What happened over there?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU REALLY THINK THAT JUST BECAUSE YOU HAVE AN IDEA  IT BELONGS TO YOU</pattern><template>Your father, he helped give us the atomic bomb.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAY YOU CAN SEE ME  AND I CAN</pattern><template>A little less formal and...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS BEAUTIFUL  THANK YOU  THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH  THIS IS WONDERFUL  WELL  I'M NOT TONY STARK  BUT IF I WERE TONY  I WOULD TELL YOU HOW HONORED I FEEL AND WHAT A JOY IT IS TO RECEIVE THIS VERY PRESTIGIOUS AWARD  TONY  YOU KNOW    THE BEST THING ABOUT TONY IS ALSO THE WORST THING  HE'S ALWAYS WORKING  WORK IT  COME ON</pattern><template>We should just stay till the morning.</template></category><category><pattern>AND A LOT OF PEOPLE WOULD ALSO CALL THAT WAR PROFITEERING</pattern><template>Tell me, do you plan to report on the millions we've saved by advancing medical technology or kept from starvation with our intelli crops?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO TELL HIM</pattern><template>Great. I'll be right up.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT  SMILE</pattern><template>We met once, you know, at a technical conference in Bern.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  ARE YOU THERE</pattern><template>At your service, sir.   Engage Heads Up Display.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIND IF I SEND YOU ON AN ERRAND</pattern><template>I need you to go to my office.</template></category><category><pattern>I   GOT IT</pattern><template>I.   Enter.   l  and  Enter.  Come over here and button me up.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT</pattern><template>Destroy it.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT COOL IF I TAKE A PICTURE WITH YOU</pattern><template>Yes. It's very cool.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  PLEASE</pattern><template>Is it true you went 12 for 12 with last year's Maxim cover models?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO  DID THEY ROPE YOU INTO THIS</pattern><template>Nobody roped me into anything!</template></category><category><pattern>SEVEN PERCENT POWER    JUST LEAVE IT ON THE SCREEN</pattern><template>Stop telling me!</template></category><category><pattern>WAS THAT SO HARD  THAT WAS FUN  RIGHT</pattern><template>Here, I got it. I got it. Here.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU KNOW WHY</pattern><template>I think you lost objectivity. I think they just... People... We just danced.</template></category><category><pattern>COLONEL</pattern><template>Why not a pilot without the plane?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  COME ON  TONY  TONY</pattern><template>I'll be in the shop.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WORKED ON THE MANHATTAN PROJECT</pattern><template>A lot of people, including your professors at Brown, would call that being a hero.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THEN  I QUIT</pattern><template>You stood by my side all these years while I reaped the benefits of destruction.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  TECHNICALLY  HE HIT ME</pattern><template>Now are you going to come by and see what I'm working on? No, no, no, no, no, no, the less I know, the better.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SPEAK ARABIC  URDU  DARI  PASHTO  MONGOLIAN  FARSI  RUSSIAN</pattern><template>Who are these people?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT LIKE YOU  I'M NOT CUT OUT</pattern><template>No, no. You don't have to be like me!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL BE HEARING FROM US</pattern><template>From the Strategic Homeland...</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO OVERLOAD THE REACTOR AND BLAST THE ROOF</pattern><template>Well, how are you going to do that?</template></category><category><pattern>I ACTUALLY DON'T THINK THAT YOU COULD TIE YOUR SHOES WITHOUT ME</pattern><template>I'd make it a week. Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S TAKE A PICTURE  COME ON</pattern><template>Picture time!</template></category><category><pattern>WHO THE HELL ARE YOU</pattern><template>Nick Fury, Director of S.H.I.E.L.D.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS THE NEXT MISSION AND NOTHING ELSE</pattern><template>Is that so?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M NOT MY COMPANY</pattern><template>Please, do you mind?</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T APPROVE ANY SHIPMENT</pattern><template>Well, your company did.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING TO HAVE IT RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Yeah, walk with me.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA TRY AGAIN  RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Please don't turn down my music.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE IT RECONFIGURE THE SHELL METALS</pattern><template>Use the gold titanium alloy from the seraphim tactical satellite.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT  I WAS JUST JOGGING IN THE CANYON    I THOUGHT YOU WERE DRIVING</pattern><template>Right, I was driving to the canyon, where I'm going to jog. You sure you don't have any tech in that area I should know about?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST BECAUSE I BROUGHT PIZZA BACK FROM NEW YORK   DOESN'T MEAN IT WENT BAD</pattern><template>Sure doesn't. Oh, boy.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S MY    I MEAN  IS THAT</pattern><template>That's kind of flimsy, don't you think?</template></category><category><pattern>GOT A MINIMAL RADAR CROSS SECTION  SIR</pattern><template>Is it stealth?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT'S VERY COOL</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>GET YOURSELF SOMETHING NICE FROM ME</pattern><template>I already did.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAD A GREAT IDEA  TONY  BUT MY SUIT IS MORE ADVANCED IN EVERY WAY  HOW'D YOU SOLVE THE ICING PROBLEM  ICING PROBLEM  MIGHT WANT TO LOOK INTO IT  TWO PERCENT  WE ARE NOW RUNNING ON EMERGENCY BACKUP POWER    POTTS</pattern><template>Tony! Oh, my God, are you okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO LISTEN TO ME</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE A SEPARATE DIVISION WITH A MORE SPECIFIC FOCUS</pattern><template>We need to debrief Mr. Stark about the circumstances of his escape.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE SURE THE CHECKPOINTS ARE CLEAR BEFORE YOU FOLLOW ME OUT  OKAY</pattern><template>We need more time.</template></category><category><pattern>EASY  EASY</pattern><template>You remember this one, right?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT AN AWAC AND A GLOBAL HAWK IN THE AREA</pattern><template>So this thing just appeared out of nowhere?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN DOING</pattern><template>I lay low, and you take care of all...</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T LIKE IT WHEN YOU HAVE PLANS</pattern><template>I'm allowed to have plans on my birthday.</template></category><category><pattern>MARK YOUR POSITION AND RETURN TO BASE    ROGER THAT  BALLROOM  ON YOUR BELLY  IT LOOKS LIKE A MAN  SHAKE HIM OFF  ROLL  ROLL  I'M HIT  I'M HIT  IT'S CONFIRMED  HE HAS BEEN HIT</pattern><template>Punch out! Punch out! Whiplash One down. Whiplash Two, do you see a chute?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIND IF I COME DOWN THERE AND SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING</pattern><template>Good night, Obie.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THIS    IT'S RHODES</pattern><template>Sorry, hello?</template></category><category><pattern>MR  TONY STARK</pattern><template>Hello, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK GREAT AND YOU SMELL GREAT</pattern><template>Oh, God.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST AVOIDING GOVERNMENT AGENTS</pattern><template>Are you by yourself?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Contact left!</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IT IS  THAT WAS EASY</pattern><template>I'm so sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>PEPPER  SLOW DOWN</pattern><template>Why would Obadiah...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THERE'S PUS</pattern><template>It's not pus. It's an inorganic plasmic discharge from the device,   not from my body.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU NEED IS TIME TO GET YOUR MIND RIGHT</pattern><template>I'm serious.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S QUITE A MOUTHFUL</pattern><template>I know. We're working on it.</template></category><category><pattern>FIFTY SIX AND A HALF</pattern><template>It doesn't matter.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT BETTER TO BE FEARED OR RESPECTED</pattern><template>I say, is it too much to ask for both?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN SPEAK HUNGARIAN</pattern><template>Okay. I know.</template></category><category><pattern>NO IS A COMPLETE ANSWER</pattern><template>The doctor has to look at you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE TO  SIR</pattern><template>Take us to the hospital, please, Happy.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER MIND WHO TOLD ME  SHOW ME</pattern><template>It's Rhodey or Pepper.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOW ME THE WEAPON</pattern><template>Come. Leave your guards outside.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A SOUVENIR  TAKE A LOOK</pattern><template>I've seen many wounds like that in my village.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL KEEP YOU POSTED</pattern><template>You are supposed to be halfway around the world right now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE UNBELIEVABLE</pattern><template>Oh, no! Did they rope you into this?</template></category><category><pattern>IF MY MATH IS RIGHT  AND IT ALWAYS IS  THREE GIGAJOULES PER SECOND</pattern><template>That could run your heart for 50 lifetimes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE MISSING JUST A COUPLE OF DIGITS THERE</pattern><template>The other eight?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT IN THE BOOT  DUMMY  RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>You got me?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO ART OPENING</pattern><template>There is no benefit.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  RHODEY</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>HOGAN  DRIVE  CHEESEBURGER FIRST</pattern><template>Look at this!</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHOULD JUST STAY TILL THE MORNING</pattern><template>You are unbelievable.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN BUZZING YOU</pattern><template>Did you hear the intercom?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  WE GOT TO GO</pattern><template>Move for me, come on. We got a plan.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DOCTOR HAS TO LOOK AT YOU</pattern><template>I don't have to do anything.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO REACH IN  AND YOU'RE JUST GONNA GENTLY LIFT THE WIRE OUT</pattern><template>Is it safe?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL PUT SOMETHING IN THE BOOK  SHALL I</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  COME ON  WE BUILT THAT THING TO SHUT THE HIPPIES UP</pattern><template>It works.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE FOR ME  COME ON  WE GOT A PLAN</pattern><template>We're gonna stick to it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A SHAME THE GOVERNMENT DIDN'T APPROVE IT</pattern><template>There's so many applications for causing short term paralysis.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS LOOKS IMPORTANT  I NEVER HAD A TASTE FOR THIS SORT OF THING  BUT I MUST ADMIT  I'M DEEPLY ENJOYING THE SUIT</pattern><template>You finally outdid yourself, Tony!</template></category><category><pattern>AT YOUR SERVICE  SIR    ENGAGE HEADS UP DISPLAY</pattern><template>Check. Import all preferences from home interface.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S WRONG</pattern><template>Nothing, I'm just going into cardiac arrest 'cause you yanked it out like a trout...</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE ME TO MAXIMUM ALTITUDE</pattern><template>With only 15% power, the odds of reaching that... I know the math! Do it!</template></category><category><pattern>WASN'T AIR FORCE</pattern><template>We got the CIA on the line?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D IT GO</pattern><template>It went that bad, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>RECRUIT OUR TOP ENGINEERS</pattern><template>I want a prototype right away.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED WELDING GEAR</pattern><template>I don't care if it's acetylene or propane.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT THEY SAY</pattern><template>Could you have a lousier poker face?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I KNOW IN MY HEART THAT IT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>You're all I have, too, you know.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY PUT  NICE</pattern><template>You're of no benefit at all.</template></category><category><pattern>CAREFUL  WE ONLY GET ONE SHOT AT THIS</pattern><template>Relax. I have steady hands.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU GOT IT</pattern><template>Now, don't let it touch the sides when you're coming out!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  WHERE'D YOU GET THAT DRESS</pattern><template>Oh, it was a birthday present.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU  I'M NOT MAD</pattern><template>I'm indifferent, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>Sir, there is a potentially fatal buildup of ice occurring. Keep going!</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE'RE GONNA BE FINE</pattern><template>Color me up, William.</template></category><category><pattern>DID I JUST PAINT A TARGET ON THE BACK OF MY HEAD</pattern><template>Your head? What about my head?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>How was the  fun vee ?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU CAN COUNT ON IT</pattern><template>I'm serious!</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING</pattern><template>Come on, sour patch. Don't be mad.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALLY NEED YOUR HELP HERE</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU CAN'T BE DISTRACTED RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Listen to me!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE GOT 90 SECONDS</pattern><template>Agent Coulson?</template></category><category><pattern>I'D MAKE IT A WEEK  SURE</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  YOU SEE  IT WAS JUST FATE THAT YOU SURVIVED THAT</pattern><template>You had one last golden egg to give.</template></category><category><pattern>COLONEL  WHAT ARE WE DEALING WITH HERE</pattern><template>Let me make a call.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE TO MEET YOU  TOO</pattern><template>That doesn't look like a Jericho missile.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GENTLY LIFT THE WIRE  OKAY  GREAT</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAY  IS IT TOO MUCH TO ASK FOR BOTH</pattern><template>With that in mind, I humbly present the crown jewel of Stark Industries' Freedom Line.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT TO SEE THIS ON YOUR MYSPACE PAGE</pattern><template>Please, no gang signs.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S SPEAKING HUNGARIAN  I DON'T</pattern><template>Then speak Hungarian.</template></category><category><pattern>COLOR ME UP  WILLIAM</pattern><template>This is where I exit.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA</pattern><template>Tony Stark. Visionary. Genius. American patriot. Even from an early age, the son of legendary weapons developer Howard Stark quickly stole the spotlight with his brilliant and unique mind. At age four, he built his first circuit board. At age six, his first engine. And at 17, he graduated summa cum laude from MIT. Then, the passing of a titan. Howard Stark's lifelong friend and ally, Obadiah Stane, steps in to help fill the gap left by the legendary founder, until, at age 21, the prodigal son returns and is anointed the new CEO of Stark Industries. With the keys to the kingdom, Tony ushers in a new era for his father's legacy, creating smarter weapons, advanced robotics, satellite targeting. Today, Tony Stark has changed the face of the weapons industry by ensuring freedom and protecting America and her interests around the globe. As liaison to Stark Industries, I've had the unique privilege of serving with a real patriot. He is my friend and he is my great mentor. Ladies and gentlemen, it is my honor to present this year's Apogee Award to Mr. Tony Stark. Tony?   Thank you, Colonel.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE</pattern><template>Am I right? We haven't had a breakthrough in that in what?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU UNDERSTAND THAT</pattern><template>This is not a piece of equipment.</template></category><category><pattern>SECTION 16  SECTION 16  THERE IT IS</pattern><template>My key's not working.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD ASSISTANT</pattern><template>You have till tomorrow to assemble my missile.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WANT TO KNOW IF IT'S US</pattern><template>No, it definitely is not us, sir!</template></category><category><pattern>WHEELS UP  ROCK AND ROLL</pattern><template>What you reading, platypus?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT</pattern><template>All right, suit yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I COULD FIRE YOU IF THAT WOULD TAKE THE EDGE OFF</pattern><template>I actually don't think that you could tie your shoes without me.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURE THEY'RE LOOKING FOR YOU  STARK</pattern><template>But they will never find you in these mountains.</template></category><category><pattern>ELEVEN PERCENT    KEEP GOING</pattern><template>Seven percent power.   Just leave it on the screen!</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR DECEPTION AND LIES WILL COST YOU DEARLY  THE PRICE TO KILL TONY STARK HAS JUST GONE UP  SO  WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO ABOUT THIS</pattern><template>I know what you're going through, Pepper.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT COULD RUN YOUR HEART FOR 50 LIFETIMES</pattern><template>Yeah. Or something big for 15 minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUARANTEE YOU  THE DAY WEAPONS ARE NO LONGER NEEDED TO KEEP THE PEACE  I'LL START MAKING BRICKS AND BEAMS FOR BABY HOSPITALS</pattern><template>Rehearse that much?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ICED UP  JARVIS</pattern><template>Deploy flaps! Jarvis!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU THINK THE MARK ONE CHEST PIECE IS GOING TO HOLD UP</pattern><template>The suit's at 48% power and falling, sir. That chest piece was never designed for sustained flight. Keep me posted.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU SEEN THESE PICTURES</pattern><template>What's going on in Gulmira?</template></category><category><pattern>CANNOT IDENTIFY</pattern><template>Get me Colonel Rhodes from Weapons Development down here now!</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR HEAD  WHAT ABOUT MY HEAD</pattern><template>What do you think the over under on the stock drop is gonna be tomorrow?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS DAD'S LINE</pattern><template>You gotta let me handle this.</template></category><category><pattern>YINSEN  YINSEN  STARK</pattern><template>Say something.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE A MAN WHO HAS EVERYTHING AND NOTHING</pattern><template>Relax.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE ON YOUR YACHT</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>IF SOMETHING HAPPENS  THEN COME IN</pattern><template>And again, let's bring it up to 2.5.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GET IT DONE</pattern><template>They're coming.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT SAFE</pattern><template>Yeah, it should be fine.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S UP TO</pattern><template>Good to see you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO DEBRIEF MR  STARK ABOUT THE CIRCUMSTANCES OF HIS ESCAPE</pattern><template>I'll put something in the book, shall I?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M FROM A SMALL TOWN CALLED GULMIRA</pattern><template>It's actually a nice place.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A BOGEY</pattern><template>Wasn't Air Force!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE LEAST OF YOUR PROBLEMS</pattern><template>Crate up the armor and the rest of it.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO CRAPS  LINE AWAY</pattern><template>That's what happens.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME FINISH THIS</pattern><template>Initialize the power sequence.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU DOUSE ME AGAIN  AND I'M NOT ON FIRE  I'M DONATING YOU TO A CITY COLLEGE</pattern><template>All right, nice and easy. Seriously, just gonna start off with 1% thrust capacity. And three, two, one. Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>BALLROOM  THIS IS WHIPLASH ONE  I'VE GOT THE BOGEY IN MY SIGHTS  WHIPLASH ONE  WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>I've got no idea.   You have radio contact?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MORNING  IT'S 7:00 A M  THE WEATHER IN MALIBU IS 72 DEGREES WITH SCATTERED CLOUDS  THE SURF CONDITIONS ARE FAIR WITH WAIST TO SHOULDER HIGH LINES  HIGH TIDE WILL BE AT 10:52 A M  TONY</pattern><template>Hey, Tony?</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>What's your Social Security number?</template></category><category><pattern>PICTURE TIME</pattern><template>Tony. Who do you think locked you out?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS AN ELECTROMAGNET  HOOKED UP TO A CAR BATTERY  AND IT'S KEEPING THE SHRAPNEL FROM ENTERING YOUR HEART</pattern><template>That's right. Smile.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  STARK  YOU'VE BECOME PART OF A BIGGER UNIVERSE</pattern><template>You just don't know it yet.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SAT VISUAL HAS BEEN LOST</pattern><template>No way that's a UAV. What is it?</template></category><category><pattern>GOT IT  OKAY</pattern><template>I would like a vodka martini, please.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE SURE YOU WAIT TILL I CLEAR THE ROOF</pattern><template>I'll buy you some time.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST REMEMBER THAT  SPRING BREAK  1987</pattern><template>That lovely lady you woke up with.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW WAS THE  FUN VEE</pattern><template>Next time, you ride with me, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>NO WAY THAT'S A UAV  WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>I can't see anything.</template></category><category><pattern>HIT IT  THAT BOGEY JUST WENT SUPERSONIC  I GOT A LOCK    INBOUND MISSILE    FLARES</pattern><template>Wait a second. Bogey deployed flares! Deploy flaps!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS I THINKING  YOU'RE USUALLY SO DISCREET  TELL YOU WHAT</pattern><template>Throw a little hot rod red in there.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE YOU GO</pattern><template>There it is. That was easy.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW</pattern><template>Tell me. Tell me.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD  IS THAT THE THING THAT'S KEEPING YOU ALIVE</pattern><template>It was. It is now an antique.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  LISTEN  TAKE IT SLOW  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>I think I got the board right where we want them.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID THEY GET MY GUNS</pattern><template>Do you understand me? Do as I do.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU UP TO  OBADIAH</pattern><template>You did not tell us that the target you paid us to kill was the great Tony Stark.   As you can see, Obadiah Stane...   Oh, my God.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>There's nothing we can't do if we stick together, like your father and I.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED MORE TIME</pattern><template>Hey,   I'm gonna go buy you some time.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU'RE A HUMANITARIAN NOW OR SOMETHING</pattern><template>I need you to listen to me.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME  DO AS I DO</pattern><template>He says,  Welcome, Tony Stark, the most famous mass murderer  in the history of America.  He is honored.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  PUT YOUR HANDS UP</pattern><template>Those are my guns.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  SOUR PATCH  DON'T BE MAD</pattern><template>I told you, I'm not mad.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO RECORD OF AN INVITATION  SIR      HASN'T BEEN SEEN IN PUBLIC SINCE HIS BIZARRE AND HIGHLY CONTROVERSIAL PRESS CONFERENCE  SOME CLAIM HE'S SUFFERING FROM POSTTRAUMATIC STRESS AND HAS BEEN BEDRIDDEN FOR WEEKS  WHATEVER THE CASE MAY BE  NO ONE EXPECTS AN APPEARANCE FROM HIM TONIGHT  THE RENDER IS COMPLETE  A LITTLE OSTENTATIOUS  DON'T YOU THINK</pattern><template>What was I thinking? You're usually so discreet. Tell you what.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TRANSMIT IT BACK TO ME</pattern><template>I need you to sign this before you get on the plane.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'VE BEEN DRY CLEANED AND PRESSED  AND THERE'S A CAR WAITING FOR YOU OUTSIDE THAT WILL TAKE YOU ANYWHERE YOU'D LIKE TO GO</pattern><template>You must be the famous Pepper Potts.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO ANYTHING AND EVERYTHING THAT MR  STARK REQUIRES  INCLUDING  OCCASIONALLY  TAKING OUT THE TRASH</pattern><template>Will that be all?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I GOT IT  I GOT IT</pattern><template>Okay, you got it?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE GOT LANGLEY ON THE LINE</pattern><template>They want to know if it's us.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ALMOST OUT OF POWER  I'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF THIS THING  I'LL BE RIGHT THERE</pattern><template>Nice try!   Weapons status?</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD HAVE ASKED HIM HOW HE FELT ABOUT WHAT THIS COMPANY DID</pattern><template>If he was conflicted, if he ever had doubts.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULDN'T SLEEP TILL I FOUND OUT HOW IT WENT  HOW'D IT GO  IT WENT GREAT  LOOKS LIKE IT'S GONNA BE AN EARLY CHRISTMAS</pattern><template>Hey! Way to go, my boy! I'll see you tomorrow, yeah? Why aren't you wearing those pajamas I got you?</template></category><category><pattern>SO THIS IS HOW HE DID IT</pattern><template>This is only a first, crude effort.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS IRRELEVANT</pattern><template>Oh, my God!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA LET IT RIDE</pattern><template>Give me a hand, will you?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE YOU INSIDE</pattern><template>Hey. Listen, take it slow, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I WAS NOT EXPECTING</pattern><template>Don't put it back in! Don't put it back in!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO TELL THE PRESS</pattern><template>Training exercise. Isn't that the usual BS? It's not that simple. An unfortunate training exercise involving an F 22 Raptor occurred yesterday.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOING TO HACK INTO THE MAINFRAME AND YOU'RE GOING TO RETRIEVE ALL THE RECENT SHIPPING MANIFESTS</pattern><template>This is a lock chip.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS ONLY A FIRST  CRUDE EFFORT</pattern><template>Stark has perfected his design.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T CARE IF IT'S ACETYLENE OR PROPANE</pattern><template>I need a soldering station. I need helmets. I'm gonna need goggles.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA SWITCH IT OUT REALLY QUICK</pattern><template>Okay. Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>PUNCH OUT  PUNCH OUT  WHIPLASH ONE DOWN  WHIPLASH TWO  DO YOU SEE A CHUTE</pattern><template>Negative! No chute, no chute! My chute's jammed! Sir, I've got a visual on the bogey. Whiplash Two, reengage.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU EVER LOSE AN HOUR OF SLEEP YOUR WHOLE LIFE</pattern><template>I'd be prepared to lose a few with you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO GET RID OF ME FOR</pattern><template>What, you got plans?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YEAH  YEAH  YEAH</pattern><template>The guy from the...</template></category><category><pattern>HOT SAKE</pattern><template>Yes, two, please.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  IT'S ACTUALLY NOT THAT BAD</pattern><template>Even I don't think I'm Iron Man.</template></category><category><pattern>BREAKS MY HEART</pattern><template>Well, he's a complicated person.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED A SOLDERING STATION  I NEED HELMETS  I'M GONNA NEED GOGGLES</pattern><template>I would like a smelting cup.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT OF YOU AS A SOLDIER FIRST</pattern><template>I'm an airman.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S SEE THEM  SHOW ME YOUR HANDS</pattern><template>Let's see them.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU  TOO</pattern><template>I don't blow on a man's dice.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAME TO TALK TO YOU</pattern><template>I want you to be a part of it.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT  I'LL BE RIGHT UP</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  'CAUSE THE STOCKS DIPPED 40 POINTS</pattern><template>We knew that was gonna happen.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT WAS NOT JUST A DANCE  YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND BECAUSE YOU'RE YOU</pattern><template>And everybody knows exactly who you are and how you are with girls and all of that, which is completely fine.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GET THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD</pattern><template>You know, it's actually not that bad.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE FILING AN INJUNCTION</pattern><template>A what?</template></category><category><pattern>TONY STARK WAS ABLE TO BUILD THIS IN A CAVE  WITH A BOX OF SCRAPS</pattern><template>Well, I'm sorry. I'm not Tony Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>AND EVERYBODY KNOWS EXACTLY WHO YOU ARE AND HOW YOU ARE WITH GIRLS AND ALL OF THAT  WHICH IS COMPLETELY FINE</pattern><template>But, you know, then me, you're my boss,   and I'm dancing with you.</template></category><category><pattern>TILL FURTHER NOTICE  WHY DON'T WE JUST KEEP EVERYTHING ON MY PRIVATE SERVER</pattern><template>Working on a secret project, are we, sir? I don't want this winding up in the wrong hands.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN'T DO IF WE STICK TOGETHER  LIKE YOUR FATHER AND I</pattern><template>I'm sorry I didn't give you a heads up, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>THIRTEEN PERCENT POWER  SIR    CLIMB</pattern><template>Eleven percent.   Keep going!</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO CUT ACROSS MULHOLLAND</pattern><template>I got you. I got you.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST DO IT</pattern><template>You'll die!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE WORKING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>You can't have sashimi without sake.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SIR  AND THAT'S WHAT WE'RE TRYING TO DO  BUT HONESTLY  IT'S IMPOSSIBLE</pattern><template>Tony Stark was able to build this in a cave! With a box of scraps!</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S SEE THEM</pattern><template>Oh, wow. They are small.</template></category><category><pattern>HOT TOWEL</pattern><template>You don't respect yourself,   so I know you don't respect me.</template></category><category><pattern>VERY TASTEFUL  THANK YOU  MR  STARK</pattern><template>You're welcome, Miss Potts.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  RHODEY  IT'S ME    IT'S WHO</pattern><template>I'm sorry, it is me. You asked. What you were asking about is me. No, see, this isn't a game.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  NO MORE OF THIS  READY  FIRE  AIM  BUSINESS</pattern><template>You understand me?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ALTITUDE RECORD FOR FIXED WING FLIGHT IS 85 000 FEET  SIR  RECORDS ARE MADE TO BE BROKEN</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ENOUGH OF THAT</pattern><template>...is not what you think. I want you to call for a press conference now.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE JOB</pattern><template>See you back at base.</template></category><category><pattern>STARK</pattern><template>Come on. We got to go.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  THIS IS YOUR NINTH SYMPHONY</pattern><template>What a masterpiece. Look at that.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT HOW YOU WANT TO GO OUT</pattern><template>Is this the last act of defiance of the great Tony Stark?</template></category><category><pattern>SO I GOT YOU FOR THE OTHER EIGHT</pattern><template>How about a little air?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WALK WITH ME</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>OBADIAH'S UPSTAIRS</pattern><template>Great!</template></category><category><pattern>IMPRESSIVE</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER GOT TO SAY GOODBYE TO DAD</pattern><template>I never got to say goodbye to my father.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  STARK</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT THERE  IN THE GARBAGE</pattern><template>All that stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA LET ME HANDLE THIS</pattern><template>We're gonna have to play a whole different kind of ball now.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEVER GOT THE GREEN LIGHT</pattern><template>Put me through to State.</template></category><category><pattern>USE THE GOLD TITANIUM ALLOY FROM THE SERAPHIM TACTICAL SATELLITE</pattern><template>That should ensure a fuselage integrity while maintaining power to weight ratio.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  I ALWAYS FORGET TO WEAR DEODORANT AND DANCE WITH MY BOSS IN FRONT OF EVERYONE THAT I WORK WITH IN A DRESS WITH NO BACK</pattern><template>You look great and you smell great.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN  HE PAID TO HAVE TONY KILLED</pattern><template>Pepper, slow down.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME WHEN YOU SEE A PROGRESS BAR</pattern><template>It should be up right now.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  I'D APOLOGIZE  BUT ISN'T THAT WHAT WE'RE GOING FOR HERE</pattern><template>I thought of you as a soldier first.</template></category><category><pattern>STICK TO THE PLAN</pattern><template>Yinsen!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU JUST SIT DOWN</pattern><template>That way you can see me, and I can...</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I ASK YOU A COUPLE OF QUESTIONS</pattern><template>She's cute.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  TWO  PLEASE</pattern><template>No. I'm not drinking. I don't want any.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA STICK TO IT</pattern><template>This was always the plan, Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME</pattern><template>General.</template></category><category><pattern>AS FOR THE UNEXPECTED TURN OF EVENTS ON THE GROUND IN GULMIRA  IT IS STILL UNCLEAR WHO OR WHAT INTERVENED  BUT I CAN ASSURE YOU THAT THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT WAS NOT INVOLVED  HEY</pattern><template>It is a tight fit, sir. Sir, the more you struggle, the more this is going to hurt. Be gentle. This is my first time.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID I WAS SORRY</pattern><template>Good morning, Mr. Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING  I'M JUST GOING INTO CARDIAC ARREST 'CAUSE YOU YANKED IT OUT LIKE A TROUT</pattern><template>What? You said it was safe!</template></category><category><pattern>IS NOT WHAT YOU THINK  I WANT YOU TO CALL FOR A PRESS CONFERENCE NOW</pattern><template>Call for a press conference?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT TODAY  WHOEVER HOLDS THE LATEST STARK WEAPONS RULES THESE LANDS</pattern><template>And soon, it will be my turn.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAS MADE A MASTERPIECE OF DEATH</pattern><template>A man with a dozen of these can rule all of Asia.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT US TO MAKE BABY BOTTLES</pattern><template>I think we should take another look into arc reactor technology.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THEY JUST PUT MY NAME ON THE INVITATION  I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO TELL YOU</pattern><template>I actually almost bought it, hook, line and sinker.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD TO SEE YOU</pattern><template>I never got to say goodbye to Dad.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  I GOT IT  I GOT IT  HERE</pattern><template>Nice.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ACTUALLY A NICE PLACE</pattern><template>Got a family?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D SHE TAKE IT</pattern><template>Like a champ.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT BAD</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOLD ME NOT TO</pattern><template>Hold still, you little prick!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAS A BOARD OF DIRECTORS MEETING</pattern><template>The board is claiming you have posttraumatic stress.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  THERE IS A POTENTIALLY FATAL BUILDUP OF ICE OCCURRING  KEEP GOING</pattern><template>Higher!</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD LIKE A SMELTING CUP</pattern><template>I need two sets of precision tools.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY</pattern><template>A hiccup?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  OR SOMETHING BIG FOR 15 MINUTES</pattern><template>This is our ticket out of here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT IRON MAN</pattern><template>Am so.</template></category><category><pattern>IF NOT  THEY PUT IT ON A GHOST DRIVE  IN WHICH CASE YOU NEED TO LOOK FOR THE LOWEST NUMERIC HEADING</pattern><template>And what do you plan to do with this information if I bring it back here?</template></category><category><pattern>CALL OFF THE RAPTORS</pattern><template>That thing just took out an F 22 inside a legal no fly zone!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'D BE WILDLY CONFLICTED  WHICH WOULD ONLY MAKE HER MORE CRAZY ABOUT ME</pattern><template>Tell me you never think about that night.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE SEEN MANY WOUNDS LIKE THAT IN MY VILLAGE</pattern><template>We call them the walking dead because it takes about a week for the barbs to reach the vital organs.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT STEALTH</pattern><template>No, sir, it's tiny.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS</pattern><template>Worse things have happened.</template></category><category><pattern>PUZZLE</pattern><template>Of course.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS OUT OF TOWN FOR A COUPLE MONTHS  IN CASE YOU DIDN'T HEAR</pattern><template>Is this what you call accountability?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I FEEL GREAT</pattern><template>You okay?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY    I'M GONNA GO BUY YOU SOME TIME</pattern><template>Stick to the plan!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'D BE A WRECK  'CAUSE SHE'D ALWAYS BE WORRYING THAT I WAS GOING TO DIE  YET SO PROUD OF THE MAN I'D BECOME</pattern><template>She'd be wildly conflicted, which would only make her more crazy about me.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I KNOW</pattern><template>What do you know?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT CRAZY  PEPPER</pattern><template>I just finally know what I have to do.</template></category><category><pattern>YESTERDAY</pattern><template>I didn't approve any shipment.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD HAVE PREFERRED THAT SHE LIVED</pattern><template>What do you mean, he paid to have Tony killed?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU RIPPED OUT MY TARGETING SYSTEM</pattern><template>Time to hit the button!</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT</pattern><template>But apparently, not enough for this place.</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE ARE MY GUNS</pattern><template>How did they get my guns?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ARC WAS NEVER COST EFFECTIVE</pattern><template>We knew that before we built it.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE ASKED YOU TO SIMPLY MAKE IT SMALLER</pattern><template>Okay, sir, and that's what we're trying to do, but honestly, it's impossible.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M SORRY  I'M NOT TONY STARK</pattern><template>Tony? Tony, are you there? Hello? Breathe.</template></category><category><pattern>THE RIGHT HANDS</pattern><template>I wish you could've seen my prototype.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Are you talking about the night that we danced and went up on the roof, and then you went downstairs to get me a drink, and you left me there, by myself?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Every other hex bolt.</template></category><category><pattern>CARRIE</pattern><template>Christine.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE DANCING  NO ONE'S EVEN WATCHING</pattern><template>Everybody who I work with...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T NEED TO APOLOGIZE TO ME</pattern><template>I'm your man.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU SAID IT WAS SAFE</pattern><template>We gotta hurry. Take this. Take this.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T DO THAT</pattern><template>Pleasure meeting you.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S RHODEY OR PEPPER</pattern><template>I want to see it.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS GREAT</pattern><template>Oh, come on. Tony. Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I GOT THE BOARD RIGHT WHERE WE WANT THEM</pattern><template>You got it. Just cabin fever.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Here you go.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOU'RE GONNA GO SEE YOUR FAMILY  GET UP</pattern><template>My family is dead.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  WE GOT TO BREAK THE ICE</pattern><template>Kill power.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S CUTE</pattern><template>She's all right?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKS LIKE YOU WERE RIGHT</pattern><template>He was building a suit.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAD ONE LAST GOLDEN EGG TO GIVE</pattern><template>Do you really think that just because you have an idea, it belongs to you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOING TO DO IT</pattern><template>Go to the central console, open up all the circuits.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED TO TALK</pattern><template>Hey, Forrest!</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULDN'T DO THAT IF I WERE YOU</pattern><template>What the hell did you do to me?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO FIND MY WEAPONS AND DESTROY THEM</pattern><template>Tony, you know that I would help you with anything, but I cannot help you if you're going to start all of this again.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S JARVIS  HE RUNS THE HOUSE</pattern><template>I've got your clothes here.</template></category><category><pattern>ABSOLUTELY RIDICULOUS  I DON'T PAINT</pattern><template>And what do you say to your other nickname?</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR  I DIDN'T EXPECT TO SEE YOU WALKING AROUND SO SOON</pattern><template>I'm doing a little better than walking.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S JUST PUT SOMETHING ON THE BOOKS</pattern><template>How about the 24th at 7:00 p.m.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  WE MIGHT BE MORE PRODUCTIVE IF YOU INCLUDE ME IN THE PLANNING PROCESS</pattern><template>Okay, we don't need this.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT A FAMILY</pattern><template>Yes, and I will see them when I leave here.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I SEE  SO IT'S PERSONAL</pattern><template>No, you intimidate them.</template></category><category><pattern>I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE GOING TO PULL OVER AND SNUFF ME</pattern><template>What, you're not allowed to talk?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S  LIKE  A LITTLE DEVICE</pattern><template>It's, like, a thing that's going to pick the lock?</template></category><category><pattern>MS  POTTS  WE HAD AN APPOINTMENT</pattern><template>Did you forget about our appointment?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S STILL A LOT OF UNANSWERED QUESTIONS  AND TIME CAN BE A FACTOR WITH THESE THINGS</pattern><template>Let's just put something on the books.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU PAID US TRINKETS TO KILL A PRINCE</pattern><template>Show me the weapon.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAY THE BEST WEAPON IS ONE YOU NEVER HAVE TO FIRE</pattern><template>I respectfully disagree.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HOW DAD DID IT</pattern><template>That's how America does it.</template></category><category><pattern>TOMORROW  DON'T BE LATE</pattern><template>Yeah, you can count on it.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME A HAND  WILL YOU</pattern><template>Give me a little something something.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  HURRY UP</pattern><template>Just click it. Don't change any settings.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S FACE IT  THIS IS NOT THE WORST THING YOU'VE CAUGHT ME DOING</pattern><template>Are those bullet holes?</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FATHER  HE HELPED GIVE US THE ATOMIC BOMB</pattern><template>Now, what kind of world would it be today if he was as selfish as you?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M NOT DRINKING  I DON'T WANT ANY</pattern><template>That's what I'm talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE DON'T TURN DOWN MY MUSIC</pattern><template>I'll keep you posted.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS HOW WE DO BUSINESS   IF WE'RE DOUBLE DEALING UNDER THE TABLE</pattern><template>Are we?</template></category><category><pattern>TOTALLY HARMLESS</pattern><template>It was totally not harmless, by the way.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE US TO THE HOSPITAL  PLEASE  HAPPY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS THE ONE WHO FILED THE INJUNCTION AGAINST YOU</pattern><template>It was the only way I could protect you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  YOU KNOW  THEN ME  YOU'RE MY BOSS    AND I'M DANCING WITH YOU</pattern><template>I don't think it was taken that way.</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN'T IT KIND OF DEFEAT THE WHOLE PURPOSE OF HAVING YOUR OWN PLANE IF IT DEPARTS BEFORE YOU ARRIVE</pattern><template>Larry called. He's got another buyer for the Jackson Pollock in the wings.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IT IS</pattern><template>Lieutenant Colonel Rhodes rolls! And...</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SAY IT AGAIN</pattern><template>41 steps straight ahead. Then 16 steps, that's from the door, fork right, 33 steps, turn right.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S DIFFERENT</pattern><template>What? You're a humanitarian now or something?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE</pattern><template>Just avoiding government agents.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WASTE IT  DON'T WASTE YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>My turn.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF I HAD</pattern><template>Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>COME  LEAVE YOUR GUARDS OUTSIDE</pattern><template>His escape bore unexpected fruit.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THAT SHOULD HELP YOU KEEP A LOW PROFILE  THE RENDER IS COMPLETE  HEY  I LIKE IT  FABRICATE IT  PAINT IT</pattern><template>Commencing automated assembly. Estimated completion time is five hours. Don't wait up for me, honey.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  I KNOW</pattern><template>Render unto Caesar that which is Caesar's. There you go.</template></category><category><pattern>REPULSORS OFFLINE  MISSILES OFFLINE  FLARES</pattern><template>Very clever, Tony.   Potts?</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT TOO MUCH OF A PROBLEM TO ASK</pattern><template>'Cause I'm...</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T PUT IT BACK IN  DON'T PUT IT BACK IN</pattern><template>Okay, what do I do?</template></category><category><pattern>AM I MAKING YOU UNCOMFORTABLE</pattern><template>No. No. I always forget to wear deodorant and dance with my boss in front of everyone that I work with in a dress with no back.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT WE DO KEEPS THE WORLD FROM FALLING INTO CHAOS</pattern><template>Not based on what I saw.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  THERE ARE STILL TERABYTES OF CALCULATIONS NEEDED BEFORE AN ACTUAL FLIGHT IS    JARVIS  SOMETIMES YOU GOT TO RUN BEFORE YOU CAN WALK</pattern><template>Ready? In three, two, one.</template></category><category><pattern>WE KNEW THAT WAS GONNA HAPPEN</pattern><template>Fifty six and a half.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M FINE</pattern><template>Look at you!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  NOW MAKE SURE THAT WHEN YOU PULL IT OUT  YOU DON'T</pattern><template>There's a magnet at the end of it!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT DOING A GOOD ENOUGH JOB</pattern><template>We can do better.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  ABSOLUTELY NOT</pattern><template>It'll give me a bone to throw the boys   in New York!</template></category><category><pattern>TONY STARK  VISIONARY  GENIUS  AMERICAN PATRIOT  EVEN FROM AN EARLY AGE  THE SON OF LEGENDARY WEAPONS DEVELOPER HOWARD STARK QUICKLY STOLE THE SPOTLIGHT WITH HIS BRILLIANT AND UNIQUE MIND  AT AGE FOUR  HE BUILT HIS FIRST CIRCUIT BOARD  AT AGE SIX  HIS FIRST ENGINE  AND AT 17  HE GRADUATED SUMMA CUM LAUDE FROM MIT  THEN  THE PASSING OF A TITAN  HOWARD STARK'S LIFELONG FRIEND AND ALLY  OBADIAH STANE  STEPS IN TO HELP FILL THE GAP LEFT BY THE LEGENDARY FOUNDER  UNTIL  AT AGE 21  THE PRODIGAL SON RETURNS AND IS ANOINTED THE NEW CEO OF STARK INDUSTRIES  WITH THE KEYS TO THE KINGDOM  TONY USHERS IN A NEW ERA FOR HIS FATHER'S LEGACY  CREATING SMARTER WEAPONS  ADVANCED ROBOTICS  SATELLITE TARGETING  TODAY  TONY STARK HAS CHANGED THE FACE OF THE WEAPONS INDUSTRY BY ENSURING FREEDOM AND PROTECTING AMERICA AND HER INTERESTS AROUND THE GLOBE  AS LIAISON TO STARK INDUSTRIES  I'VE HAD THE UNIQUE PRIVILEGE OF SERVING WITH A REAL PATRIOT  HE IS MY FRIEND AND HE IS MY GREAT MENTOR  LADIES AND GENTLEMEN  IT IS MY HONOR TO PRESENT THIS YEAR'S APOGEE AWARD TO MR  TONY STARK  TONY    THANK YOU  COLONEL</pattern><template>Thanks for the save.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN DO BETTER</pattern><template>We're gonna do something else.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE SHOULD TAKE ANOTHER LOOK INTO ARC REACTOR TECHNOLOGY</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M NOT TALKING</pattern><template>We're not drinking.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS IT IVAN</pattern><template>Don't do that.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I GOT GREAT TASTE</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS NOT A PIECE OF EQUIPMENT</pattern><template>I'm in it. It's a suit. It's me!</template></category><category><pattern>STRATEGIC HOMELAND INTERVENTION  ENFORCEMENT AND LOGISTICS DIVISION</pattern><template>God, you need a new name for that.</template></category><category><pattern>POWER REDUCED TO 19%  LADY  NO  NO  NO  NO  NO  NO  FOR 30 YEARS  I'VE BEEN HOLDING YOU UP  I BUILT THIS COMPANY FROM NOTHING  NOTHING IS GOING TO STAND IN MY WAY  LEAST OF ALL YOU  IMPRESSIVE  YOU'VE UPGRADED YOUR ARMOR  I'VE MADE SOME UPGRADES OF MY OWN  SIR  IT APPEARS THAT HIS SUIT CAN FLY  DULY NOTED</pattern><template>Take me to maximum altitude.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH ONLY 15% POWER  THE ODDS OF REACHING THAT    I KNOW THE MATH  DO IT</pattern><template>Sir, you're not going to believe this.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE I'D BE DEEPLY HONORED</pattern><template>And it's you, that's great.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AGAIN  LET'S BRING IT UP TO 2 5</pattern><template>Three, two, one.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS NOTHING TO SIGN</pattern><template>There is the next mission and nothing else.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHAT WILL BE KEEPING ME ALIVE FOR THE FORESEEABLE FUTURE</pattern><template>I'm swapping it up for an upgraded unit, and I just ran into a little speed bump.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  TONY  REMEMBER ME</pattern><template>Sure don't.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP TELLING ME</pattern><template>You had a great idea, Tony, but my suit is more advanced in every way! How'd you solve the icing problem? Icing problem? Might want to look into it. Two percent. We are now running on emergency backup power.   Potts!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S FINE  SHE'S WITH FIVE AGENTS</pattern><template>They're about to arrest Obadiah.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS ISN'T WORKING</pattern><template>We're going to have to overload the reactor and blast the roof.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE IN THAT MIRROR THAT EVERY PERSON THAT'S GOT THIS UNIFORM ON GOT MY BACK</pattern><template>Hey, you know what?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOT A NICE RING TO IT</pattern><template>I mean, it's not technically accurate.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A SECOND  BOGEY DEPLOYED FLARES  DEPLOY FLAPS</pattern><template>Holy!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  LOOK WHO'S HERE  YEAH</pattern><template>Miss Potts?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I CAN FLY</pattern><template>Jarvis, are you there?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER</pattern><template>Five.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER GOT TO SAY GOODBYE TO MY FATHER</pattern><template>There's questions that I would have asked him.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT ME THROUGH TO STATE</pattern><template>They're going to be all over this.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M DOING A LITTLE BETTER THAN WALKING</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY NAME ON THE SIDE OF THE BUILDING</pattern><template>And what we do keeps the world from falling into chaos.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING THROUGH  PEPPER</pattern><template>Tony. He always gets the good stuff, doesn't he?</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH OUT</pattern><template>Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE DOWN TO THE TOE  I GOT THIS</pattern><template>Okay, I'm sorry, am I in your way?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALWAYS BEEN YOUR ACHILLES' HEEL IN THIS PART OF THE WORLD</pattern><template>Don't worry. It'll only last for 15 minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>You have a lot of nerve showing up here tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>THROW A LITTLE HOT ROD RED IN THERE</pattern><template>Yes, that should help you keep a low profile. The render is complete. Hey, I like it. Fabricate it. Paint it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT NIGHT</pattern><template>You know.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT TRUE YOU WENT 12 FOR 12 WITH LAST YEAR'S MAXIM COVER MODELS</pattern><template>That is an excellent question.</template></category><category><pattern>RHODEY  YOU GOT ANYTHING FOR ME</pattern><template>Mark your position and return to base.   Roger that, Ballroom. On your belly! It looks like a man! Shake him off! Roll! Roll! I'm hit! I'm hit! It's confirmed. He has been hit.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE INDEED BEEN UPLOADED  SIR  WE'RE ONLINE AND READY  CAN WE START THE VIRTUAL WALK AROUND</pattern><template>Importing preferences and calibrating virtual environment. Do a check on control surfaces.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  I NEED YOUR HELP RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>It's funny how that works, huh? Yeah. Speaking of funny, we've got a weapons depot that was just blown up a few clicks from where you were being held captive.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON IN GULMIRA</pattern><template>Tony, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK FANTASTIC</pattern><template>I didn't recognize you.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  STARK  EXCUSE ME  MR  STARK</pattern><template>Christine Everhart, Vanity Fair magazine.</template></category><category><pattern>VERY CLEVER  TONY    POTTS</pattern><template>Tony!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE  ACTUALLY  EXCELLENT BONE STRUCTURE  THERE</pattern><template>I'm kind of having a hard time not looking at you now.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D THAT WORK</pattern><template>Oh, my goodness.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S ALL THIS STUFF DOING ON TOP OF MY DESK</pattern><template>That's my phone, that's a picture of me and my dad.</template></category><category><pattern>A NEW GENERATION OF WEAPONS WITH THIS AT ITS HEART</pattern><template>Weapons that will help steer the world back on course, put the balance of power in our hands.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS A TIGHT FIT  SIR  SIR  THE MORE YOU STRUGGLE  THE MORE THIS IS GOING TO HURT  BE GENTLE  THIS IS MY FIRST TIME</pattern><template>I designed this to come off, so... Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T BLOW ON A MAN'S DICE</pattern><template>Come on, honey bear.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST DON'T LET IT TOUCH THE SOCKET WALL OR IT GOES  BEEP     WHAT DO YOU MEAN   OPERATION</pattern><template>It's just a game, never mind.</template></category><category><pattern>PANIC  I WOULD SAY PANIC IS MY REACTION</pattern><template>'Cause I was referring to your company's involvement in this latest atrocity.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO I CALL YOU</pattern><template>My name is Yinsen.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE GOT NO IDEA    YOU HAVE RADIO CONTACT</pattern><template>Non responsive, sir. Then you are clear to engage.</template></category><category><pattern>TONIGHT'S RED HOT RED CARPET IS RIGHT HERE AT THE DISNEY CONCERT HALL  WHERE TONY STARK'S THIRD ANNUAL BENEFIT FOR THE FIREFIGHTER'S FAMILY FUND HAS BECOME THE PLACE TO BE FOR L A 'S HIGH SOCIETY  JARVIS  WE GET AN INVITE FOR THAT</pattern><template>I have no record of an invitation, sir. ... hasn't been seen in public since his bizarre and highly controversial press conference. Some claim he's suffering from posttraumatic stress and has been bedridden for weeks. Whatever the case may be, no one expects an appearance from him tonight. The render is complete. A little ostentatious, don't you think?</template></category><category><pattern>WHIPLASH  COME IN HOT</pattern><template>Okay, good, 'cause I'm staring at one right now, and it's about to be blown to kingdom come.</template></category><category><pattern>SERGEANT  CLEAR A HOLE</pattern><template>Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  VACATION'S OVER</pattern><template>Where to, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED ME TO DO ANYTHING ELSE</pattern><template>Keep the skies clear. Damn!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WELCOME  MISS POTTS</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>MY NAME IS YINSEN</pattern><template>Yinsen. Nice to meet you.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD BE WORSE  COULD BE WORSE</pattern><template>We're fine! Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>GO TO THE CENTRAL CONSOLE  OPEN UP ALL THE CIRCUITS</pattern><template>When I get clear of the roof, I'll let you know.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY LANGUAGES DO YOU SPEAK</pattern><template>A lot.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S  LIKE  A THING THAT'S GOING TO PICK THE LOCK</pattern><template>You might want to take a few steps back.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MY EXIT</pattern><template>Ballroom, this is Whiplash One. I've got the bogey in my sights. Whiplash One, what is it?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IT'S INCREDIBLY OVERPRICED</pattern><template>I need it. Buy it. Store it.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IN JUNE  PLEASE  DON'T HARANGUE ME ABOUT STUFF THAT'S WAY  WAY  DOWN</pattern><template>They're haranguing me, so I'm gonna say yes.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IT'S A FAIR EXAMPLE</pattern><template>I think it's incredibly overpriced.</template></category><category><pattern>THE 15 MILE HIKE TO THE OUTSKIRTS OF GULMIRA CAN ONLY BE DESCRIBED AS A DESCENT INTO HELL  INTO A MODERN DAY HEART OF DARKNESS</pattern><template>Simple farmers and herders from peaceful villages have been driven from their homes, displaced from their lands by warlords emboldened by a new found power. Villagers have been forced to take shelter in whatever crude dwellings they can find in the ruins of other villages, or here in the remnants of an old Soviet smelting plant. Recent violence has been attributed to a group of foreign fighters referred to by locals as the Ten Rings. As you can see, these men are heavily armed and on a mission. A mission that could prove fatal to anyone who stands in their way. With no political will or international pressure, there's very little hope for these refugees. Around me, a woman begging for news on her husband, who was kidnapped by insurgents, either forced to join their militia... Desperate refugees clutch yellowed photographs, holding them up to anyone who will stop. A child's simple question,  Where are my mother and father?  There's very little hope for these refugees, refugees who can only wonder who, if anyone, will help. He's all yours. What the hell was that?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ON EARTH FOR</pattern><template>Hogan, drive. Cheeseburger first.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO PLAY A WHOLE DIFFERENT KIND OF BALL NOW</pattern><template>We're going to have to take a lot of heat.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SMELLS</pattern><template>Yeah, it does.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IT'S</pattern><template>Wait, wait, wait. The technology?</template></category><category><pattern>COMPLIMENTS OF TONY STARK</pattern><template>If you'd killed him when you were supposed to, you'd still have a face.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT IT  JUST CABIN FEVER</pattern><template>I'll just be a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T LOOK AT ME</pattern><template>I don't know what he's up to.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M THINKING ICING IS THE PROBABLE FACTOR</pattern><template>A very astute observation, sir. Perhaps, if you intend to visit other planets, we should improve the exosystems. Connect to the sys. co.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY  IT'LL ONLY LAST FOR 15 MINUTES</pattern><template>That's the least of your problems.</template></category><category><pattern>SON OF A BITCH</pattern><template>Wait, wait, wait! Give me a gun!</template></category><category><pattern>I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE DRIVING ME TO A COURT MARTIAL</pattern><template>This is crazy. What did I do?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  I WAS NAIVE BEFORE  WHEN THEY SAID   HERE'S THE LINE  WE DON'T CROSS IT</pattern><template>This is how we do business.  If we're double dealing under the table...</template></category><category><pattern>VERY DRY WITH OLIVES  A LOT OF OLIVES</pattern><template>Like, at least three olives.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE A LOT OF NERVE SHOWING UP HERE TONIGHT</pattern><template>Can I at least get a reaction from you?</template></category><category><pattern>THE FUTURE OF AIR COMBAT</pattern><template>Is it manned or unmanned?</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE PORT PAPERS THAT PUT YOU IN AVALON ALL NIGHT  AND SWORN STATEMENTS FROM 50 OF YOUR GUESTS</pattern><template>See, I was thinking maybe we should say it was just Pepper and me alone on the island.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD</pattern><template>Good roll. Good roll.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT TIME  YOU RIDE WITH ME  OKAY</pattern><template>Watch it, coming up here.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO</pattern><template>The 15 mile hike to the outskirts of Gulmira can only be described as a descent into hell, into a modern day Heart of Darkness.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WE DON'T NEED THIS</pattern><template>What is that?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE YOUR LOYAL CUSTOMERS  SIR</pattern><template>They call themselves the Ten Rings.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE LIKE ME</pattern><template>But you're more than what you are.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST TALKING ABOUT A NIGHTCAP</pattern><template>Hot sake?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS NO BENEFIT</pattern><template>There is nothing to sign.</template></category></AIML>