<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>IS IT GONNA FIT THROUGH THE DOOR    WELL ACTUALLY  UH  THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION  I GOT A TEAM OF GUYS COMING TOMORROW  THEY'RE GONNA BLOW OUT THAT WALL</pattern><template>So, uh, tense? Good day?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF PERK PACKAGE ARE YOU THINKING OF</pattern><template>Let him go.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY SUBJECTS WITHIN 12 5 YARDS WERE VAPORIZED INSTANTLY</pattern><template>No bomb parts found in a 3 mile radius of the Chinese theatre.   No, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU NEED A PLASTIC BAG TO BREATHE INTO</pattern><template>Do you have medication?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO FOLLOW THIS GUY</pattern><template>I'm going to run his plates and if it gets rough, so be it.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE</pattern><template>Is everything all right, Colonel?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD THEY</pattern><template>Hey Tony!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  I FINALLY MET A MAN CALLED HOPE</pattern><template>I'd like to introduce you to our guest, Doctor Wu.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YOU'RE FREE  IF YOU WEREN'T BEFORE  YES MA'AM IRON PATRIOT ON THE JOB  HAPPY TO HELP  NO NEED TO THANK ME  IT'S MY PLEASURE</pattern><template>Savin, I've acquired the Patriot armor.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL RHODES  FIND THIS LUNATIC RIGHT NOW   SIR  WE TRACKED THE BROADCAST SIGNAL</pattern><template>We have a possible point of origin in Pakistan and the Patriot is ready to strike.   Right now!   Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAW HIM ON THE STREET  PEOPLE ARE GOING 'BANG'  THEY'RE PAINTING THE WALLS  MAYA  YOU'RE KIDDING YOURSELF</pattern><template>Then help me fix it.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD EVENING  COLONEL  CAN I GIVE YOU A LIFT</pattern><template>Very funny.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN IS A BOMB NOT A BOMB</pattern><template>Any military victims?</template></category><category><pattern>ELLEN BRANDT</pattern><template>Okay, so, the injections are administered periodically.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT AS I LOOKED OUT OVER THAT CITY  NOBODY KNEW I WAS THERE  NOBODY COULD SEE ME  NO ONE WAS EVEN LOOKING I HAD A THOUGHT THAT WOULD GUIDE ME FOR YEARS TO COME</pattern><template>Anonymity, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  I'M GONNA SHAVE THEM DOWN A LITTLE BIT</pattern><template>Jarvis, hey.</template></category><category><pattern>A VALID POINT    WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM</pattern><template>Life. I built him; I take care of him.</template></category><category><pattern>STARK SECURE SERVER   RETINAL SCAN VERIFIED</pattern><template>Pepper, it's me.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  YOU LOOK GREAT  I    I    I CAN'T</pattern><template>what on Earth have you been doing?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE I SAID  WE CAN'T STAY HERE</pattern><template>Move! I'm right behind  Get her, I'm going to find a way around.</template></category><category><pattern>MY NAME IS TONY STARK AND I'M NOT AFRAID OF YOU I KNOW THAT YOU'RE A COWARD SO I'VE DECIDED THAT YOU JUST DIED  PAL</pattern><template>I'm gonna come get the body.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I'M RIGHT  WE CAN ACCESS THE AREA OF THE BRAIN THAT GOVERNS REPAIR AND CHEMICALLY RECODE IT</pattern><template>That's incredible.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY</pattern><template>Do you have PTSD?</template></category><category><pattern>BERN  SWITZERLAND 1999 THE OLD DAYS  I NEVER THOUGHT THEY'D COME BACK TO BITE ME</pattern><template>Why would they?</template></category><category><pattern>ADVANCED IDEA MECHANICS  OR AIM FOR SHORT  YOU GET IT</pattern><template>I see that 'cause it's on your t shirt.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY NEEDS GARY AND GARY NEEDS TONY   BE QUIET ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Go.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S HERE  HE'S HERE</pattern><template>But he's not here. He's here but he's not here.</template></category><category><pattern>SCREW IT  IT'S CHRISTMAS  YES  YES</pattern><template>Okay so far? You like it?</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  JARVIS  BUT IT'S ONLY HALF DONE  WE STILL GOTTA GET PEPP  THAT CAME OUT OF NOWHERE</pattern><template>Gimme some good news man.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR    ALRIGHT  KILL THE ALARM</pattern><template>That's the emergency alert triggered by the power dropping below 5 %.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK SO</pattern><template>Are you going completely mental?</template></category><category><pattern>UM  WELL  UH  I HAVE A LITTLE PROBLEM WITH  UM  SUBSTANCES  AND I ENDED UP DOING THINGS    NO TWO WAYS ABOUT IT IN THE STREET THAT A MAN SHOULDN'T DO   NEXT</pattern><template>Then, they approached me about the role and they knew about the drugs What'd they say they'd get you off them?</template></category><category><pattern>EXTREMIS IS PRATICALLY STABLE    I'M TELLING YOU IT ISN'T</pattern><template>I saw him on the street, people are going 'bang', they're painting the walls. Maya, you're kidding yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>YUP  WHAT DO I DO    STAY ON MY SIX  COVER HIGH  AND DON'T SHOOT ME IN THE BACK    SIX  HIGH  BACK  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>You see that? Nailed it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'VE YOU COME AS</pattern><template>Make a move and I'll break your face.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  LOOK AROUND YOU  COSTUMES  GREEN SCREEN HONESTLY  I WASN'T ON LOCATION FOR HALF THIS STUFF  AND WHEN I WAS  MOVIE MAGIC  LOVE I'M SORRY BUT I GOT A BEST FRIEND WHO'S IN A COMA AND HE MIGHT NOT WAKE UP SO YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO ANSWER FOR THAT</pattern><template>You're still going down, pal.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  GIVE ME A SUIT RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Aw, come on!</template></category><category><pattern>TONY  THIS IS HOW NORMAL PEOPLE BEHAVE</pattern><template>I can't protect you out there. I challenged  Is this normal?   Sadly, that   Yes, this is normal!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW LAST TIME I WENT MISSING  IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY  YOU WENT LOOKING FOR ME</pattern><template>What are you doing? A little talking, making friends in Pakistan.   What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>CLOSE YOUR EYES; YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE THIS</pattern><template>Yeah, you take a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  AND YOU HAVE TO WEAR YOUR HOBBY IN THE LIVING ROOM  JUST BREAKING IT IN  YOU KNOW  IT'S ALWAYS A LITTLE PINCHY IN THE GUI BAGGER AT FIRST</pattern><template>Oh hey, did you see your Christmas present?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL GET YOU OUT OF THERE  DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>You'll damage the armor.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IT'S ME  I'LL THINK OF SOMETHING</pattern><template>Don't touch me. No, I'm gonna burn you!   No, no You're not hot.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>With Happy in the hospital, I didn't know we were expecting guests.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE THE SECOND YOU GIVE EVIL A FACE BIN LADEN  GADDAFI  THE MANDARIN YOU HAND THE PEOPLE A TARGET   YOU'RE SOMETHING ELSE YOU HAVE MET HIM  I ASSUME</pattern><template>Yeah, Sir Lawrence Oblivion.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAPPY NOW</pattern><template>Freeze!</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE'S RIGHT ABOUT THE LOCATION  WE'RE 20 MINUTES FROM WHERE PEPPER IS    BUT WE ALSO HAVE TO FIGURE OUT THIS VICE PRESIDENT THING  RIGHT</pattern><template>I wonder who I'm calling right now.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  THE PENTAGON IS SCARED</pattern><template>After what happened in New York... aliens, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO  AS CHRISTMAS MORNING BEGAN  MY JOURNEY HAD REACHED ITS END</pattern><template>You start with something pure, something exciting Then come the mistakes The compromises We create our own demons.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY  WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT OF THE CORNER</pattern><template>You know what you did.</template></category><category><pattern>I INTEND TO FINISH THIS BEFORE CHRISTMAS MORNING</pattern><template>Meet Thomas Richards.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID HE HACK MY PHONE</pattern><template>We can't allow terrorists to dictate  I have to make this call.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU WANT SOMETHING  TAKE IT  ALTHOUGH THE GUNS ARE ALL FAKE BECAUSE THOSE WANKERS WOULDN'T TRUST ME WITH THE REAL ONES</pattern><template>What?   Hey, do you fancy either of the birds?</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU'RE GOING TO JOIN ME    BETTER</pattern><template>Tony!</template></category><category><pattern>NICE POTATO GUN</pattern><template>Barrel's a little long.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO BOMB CASINGS   YOU KNOW I CAN HELP JUST ASK  I GOT A TON OF NEW TECH</pattern><template>I got a prehensile suit. I got Bomb disposal Catches explosions mid air When's the last time you got a good night's sleep?</template></category><category><pattern>CLOSE YOUR EYES</pattern><template>Close your eyes; you don't want to see this.</template></category><category><pattern>GO</pattern><template>What would you regard as the defining moment of your life?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THOSE WERE GOOD TIMES</pattern><template>Then I moved on.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT TO CLIP YOUR WINGS HERE; WE'RE BOTH A LITTLE OVER EXCITED</pattern><template>I have an issue. I'm chasing bad guys, trying to grapple with something from some hard crypt data files.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW I GOT A REAL JOB; I'M WATCHING PEPPER</pattern><template>What's going on? Fill me in.</template></category><category><pattern>A: SAVED YOU FIRST  B: THANKS  SORT OF AND C: IF YOU DO SOMEONE A SOLID  DON'T BE A YUTZ ALRIGHT  JUST PLAY IT COOL OTHERWISE YOU COME OFF GRANDIOSE UNLIKE YOU</pattern><template>Admit it: you need me. We're connected.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVING YOU HERE IS NOT JUST TO MOTIVATE TONY STARK; IT'S ACTUALLY MORE EMBARRASSING THAN THAT</pattern><template>You're here as my, um   Trophy.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I MAY BE MALFUNCTIONING  SIR    OPEN EJECT</pattern><template>That's brisk!</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE 5 MILES OUTSIDE OF ROSE HILLS  TENNESSEE</pattern><template>Why?!</template></category><category><pattern>HAPPY WAS CONCERNED   NO  YOU'RE SPYING ON ME</pattern><template>I'm going to bed.   Hold on. Come on. Pep  Hey, I admit it! My fault. Sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  I'M SORRY  BUDDY</pattern><template>What're ya doing, buddy?</template></category><category><pattern>THE HEAT SIGNATURE IS REMARKABLY SIMILAR</pattern><template>That's two military guys...</template></category><category><pattern>THEN HOW DID YOU GET HERE  TREVOR</pattern><template>Um, well, uh, I have a little problem with, um, substances, and I ended up doing things... no two ways about it In the street that a man shouldn't do   Next!</template></category><category><pattern>3  4 SHUT UP    54321 I TOLD YOU</pattern><template>Where's the rest?</template></category><category><pattern>OLD BOTANIST PAL THAT I USED TO KNOW  BARELY</pattern><template>Please don't tell me that there is a 12 year old kid waiting in the car that I've never met.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THAT'S GREAT  NOW GIVE ME CAMERAS A THROUGH E AND DO A FULL TECH REHEARSAL</pattern><template>Is your gun up?</template></category><category><pattern>WALK AWAY FROM THAT  YOU SON OF A BITCH</pattern><template>How many in the air?   Thirteen, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I CAN GET YOU BETTER</pattern><template>That's what I do. I fix things.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THAT'S THE VICE PRESIDENT</pattern><template>Hello.   Sir, this is Tony Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT THERE'S FINE  I GET A LOT OF THIS  IT'S OKAY</pattern><template>Can I just say?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  OF COURSE  BUT MISS HANSEN  MY ORGANIZATION HAS BEEN TRACKING YOUR RESEARCH SINCE YEAR TWO OF M I T</pattern><template>Oh wow, he made it. He made the cut.</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT'S HAPPENED TONY AND I'M CLOSE</pattern><template>Extremis is pratically stable.   I'm telling you it isn't.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE HERE AS MY  UM   TROPHY</pattern><template>Good evening, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>STARK SECURE SERVER: NOW TRANSFERRING TO ALL KNOWN RECEIVERS</pattern><template>Pepper, it's me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PRODIGAL SON RETURNS</pattern><template>Whatever.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU'RE RIGHT  I DON'T DESERVE HER</pattern><template>But here's where you're wrong: She was already perfect.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU GONNA STOP THAT    BREAK IT YOU BOUGHT IT OKAY  THAT WASN'T MINE TO GIVE AWAY  THAT BELONGS TO MY FRIEND'S SISTER  AND THAT'S WHY I'M GONNA KILL YOU FIRST</pattern><template>What're ya gonna do to me?   You'll see.</template></category><category><pattern>FREE COUNTRY</pattern><template>It sure is.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I MISS YOU TOO BUT THE WAY IT USED TO BE</pattern><template>Now you're off with the 'superfriends'...</template></category><category><pattern>THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WILL SOON KNOW HIM AS THE IRON PATRIOT</pattern><template>And how is President Ellis responding?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING  I MAKE THIS STUFF  GIMME ANOTHER ONE    I DON'T HAVE ONE THAT FITS THAT GUN</pattern><template>You've got like five of them. Alright, here's what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna spot. Ready?</template></category><category><pattern>THE BIG ONE IS COMING: YOUR GRADUATION</pattern><template>Hi.   Oh, uh.   Mind leaving that on?   Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>ALDRICH KILLIAN  WE ACTUALLY MET THE GUY</pattern><template>where were we in 1999? The science conference?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL WE TOOK THE HOUSE DOWN SIR  BUT THERE'S NO SIGN OF A BODY</pattern><template>I see.   No Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BREATHE FIRE  OKAY</pattern><template>It's a glorious day, Savin.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE WORK    READY SIR</pattern><template>What do you mean  ready ?</template></category><category><pattern>BETTER LATE THAN NEVER</pattern><template>Not this time. Not the face.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GREAT</pattern><template>The last time I looked there was somebody inside of it.</template></category><category><pattern>AIR FORCE ONE'S BEEN COMPROMISED</pattern><template>Internal shots, temperature spikes.   Get me eyes on it now.   Image coming through now, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DON'T YOU JUST BUILD SOMETHING</pattern><template>Okay, thanks kid.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S CALLED AN ARREST</pattern><template>Sheriff, is it?   Yes ma'am, it is. And you are?</template></category><category><pattern>NOBODY MOVE</pattern><template>Support Blue 0, unless the Mandarin's next attack on the U.S. involves cheaply made sportswear, I think you messed up again.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE I'LL JUST COZY BACK UP FOR A BIT</pattern><template>I actually think I need to sleep now, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT THE AVENGERS  CAN YOU TALK ABOUT THEM</pattern><template>I don't know; later.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER WHEN I SAID TO STOP DOING THAT</pattern><template>I swear to God, you're going to freak me out.</template></category><category><pattern>IMAGINE IF YOU COULD HACK INTO THE HARD DRIVE OF ANY LIVING ORGANISM AND RECODE ITS DNA IT WOULD BE INCREDIBLE</pattern><template>Unfortunately, to my ears it also sounds highly weaponizable As in enhanced soldiers, private armies, and Tony is not  Tony, Tony You know, I invited Tony to join AIM 13 years ago and he turned me down But something tells me now there is a new genius on the throne, who doesn't have to answer to Tony anymore and who has slightly less of an ego.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY</pattern><template>And I'm sorry in advance because...</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TOUCH ME  NO  I'M GONNA BURN YOU    NO  NO YOU'RE NOT HOT</pattern><template>Am I gonna be okay?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GO TO BED  I COME DOWN HERE</pattern><template>I do what I know; I tinker.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR  IT'S CHRISTMAS</pattern><template>Take 'em to church.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW EVERYBODY NEEDS A HOBBY</pattern><template>Oh, and you have to wear your hobby in the living room? Just breaking it in, you know, it's always a little pinchy in the GUI bagger at first.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D STRONGLY ADVISE AGAINST THAT</pattern><template>This is the right thing to do.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS NAME IS AN ANCIENT CHINESE WAR MANTLE MEANING  ADVISOR TO THE KING  SOUTH AMERICAN INSURGENCY TACTICS TALKS LIKE A BAPIST PREACHER THERE'S LOTS OF PAGENTRY GOING ON HERE    LOTS OF THEATRE</pattern><template>Close.   The heat from the blast was in excess of 3000 degrees Celsius.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN  THEY APPROACHED ME ABOUT THE ROLE AND THEY KNEW ABOUT THE DRUGS WHAT'D THEY SAY THEY'D GET YOU OFF THEM</pattern><template>Said they'd give me more They gave me things. They gave me this palace.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS YOUR NAME    ERIN</pattern><template>By the way, I liked you in  A Christmas Story .</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THEY ALL MADE IT    THANK GOD</pattern><template>Yeah, but I missed the President.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE HOPING HE'LL GIVE US THE REACTION</pattern><template>His reaction to the latest attack.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN STOP  DO YOU WANT ME TO STOP</pattern><template>Remember when I said to stop doing that?</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR PERFORMANCE  WHERE PEOPLE DIE</pattern><template>No, no, look around you, costumes, green screen Honestly, I wasn't on location for half this stuff, and when I was, movie magic, love I'm sorry but I got a best friend who's in a coma and he might not wake up So you're going to have to answer for that.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT TO MAKE THINGS AWKWARD FOR YOU   NO    BUT I DO HAVE TO SHOW YOU    BOOM</pattern><template>Hispanic Scott Baio?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I CAN REGULATE</pattern><template>Are you sure about that?   Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>AT FIRST IT WAS FINE  THEY WERE TALKING BUSINESS  BUT NOW IT'S LIKE GETTING WEIRD    HE'S SHOWING HER HIS BIG BRAIN</pattern><template>His what?   Big brain, and she likes it.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME SIR  I DON'T KNOW WHO</pattern><template>Mom, I need to call you back, something magical is happening.</template></category><category><pattern>HAPPY  WE'LL TALK ABOUT THIS LATER BUT RIGHT NOW I HAVE TO GO DEAL WITH THIS VERY ANNOYING THING</pattern><template>How so?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S STRUNG UP OVER THE OIL TANK; THEY'RE GONNA LIGHT HIM UP  MAN    VIKING FUNERAL</pattern><template>Public execution.</template></category><category><pattern>SO    UH  WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO</pattern><template>We don't have any transport.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS THIS GUY NAMED CHAD DAVIS  USED TO LIVE ROUNDABOUTS WON A BUNCH OF MEDALS IN THE ARMY  ONE DAY  FOLKS SAID HE WENT CRAZY AND MADE  YOU KNOW  A BOMB THEN HE BLEW HIMSELF UP RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Six people died, right?   Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN IS SOMEBODY GOING TO KILL THIS GUY  JUST SAYIN'</pattern><template>Is that what you want?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE YOU SOON</pattern><template>Tell Rhodes, find this lunatic right now   Sir, we tracked the broadcast signal.</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME ABOARD  MR  PRESIDENT</pattern><template>You ever heard of an elephant graveyard? Well, two years ago, the elephant in the room was this ship.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP WHAT  WELL  I UNDERSTAND I DO NOT KNOW (PIPER) BUT I KNOW THE PLAN OCCUR   DO YOU KNOW WHAT WHO DID BHLTA</pattern><template>No, but Shaddt the beach when something related to a large compound Bomkanni pick you up there Tony, I swear to God, I'm going to blow his face off.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS AIMING FOR THE BULB</pattern><template>You can't hit a bulb from this distance.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FAULTY  BUT YOU FOUND A BUYER  DIDN'T YA</pattern><template>Sold it to the Mandarin.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S CLASSIFIED INFORMATION  TONY</pattern><template>Okay, there've been nine bombings   Nine...</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS SO CLOSE TO HAVING HER    PERFECT</pattern><template>Okay, okay, wait, wait, slow down, slow down.</template></category><category><pattern>PRESIDENT ELLIS  YOU CONTINUE TO RESIST MY ATTEMPTS TO EDUCATE YOU  SIR</pattern><template>And now, you've missed me again You know who I am. You don't know where I am And you'll never see me coming.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS REALLY VIOLENT</pattern><template>You just scared the devil out of me. I thought you were   I was dead. Why? Because I fell two hundred feet?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW YOU WERE STILL ALIVE</pattern><template>Come on in and close the door.</template></category><category><pattern>YEP</pattern><template>Are those?</template></category><category><pattern>ME</pattern><template>Come on man, this isn't a good look. Open up.</template></category><category><pattern>IN 1864 IN SAND CREEK  COLORADO  THE U S  MILITARY WAITED UNTIL THE FRIENDLY CHEYENNE BRAVES HAD ALL GONE HUNTING WAITED TO ATTACK AND SLAUGHTER THE FAMILIES LEFT BEHIND AND CLAIM THEIR LAND 39 HOURS AGO  THE ALI AL SALEM AIR BASE IN KUWAIT WAS ATTACKED</pattern><template>I did that.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S IN PAIN; HE'S BEEN INJURED  LEAVE HIM ALONE</pattern><template>Sorry.   Are you?</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT EVERYBODY  NO TALKING AND NO EYE CONTACT  UNLESS YOU WANNA GET SHOT IN THE FACE</pattern><template>The Master is travelling.</template></category><category><pattern>SHERIFF  IS IT    YES MA'AM  IT IS  AND YOU ARE</pattern><template>Homeland Security. We good here?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MOVE</pattern><template>Uh, hang on a second.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE PLAN  COLONEL</pattern><template>Harley, tell me what is happening, give me a full report   Yeah, I'm still eating that candy, do you want me to keep eating it?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT ENTIRELY MY FAULT HE HAS A TEND    HE'S A STAGE ACTOR</pattern><template>They say his Lear was the toast of Croydon, wherever that is.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT IDEA  LET'S GO    I'M SORRY</pattern><template>That's a terrible idea. Please don't touch her bags.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW SO</pattern><template>I used to work with him, and he used to ask me out all the time, so it's a little awkward.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYA  RUN</pattern><template>Hi Pepper.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE LOOKING RIGHT AT HIM</pattern><template>It was always me, Tony, right from the start. I am the Mandarin!</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD EVENING  GENTLEMEN HELLO COLONEL STEP ASIDE</pattern><template>We'll get you out of there, don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE    NO STARK</pattern><template>I have to go.</template></category><category><pattern>A CROWBAR  YEAH</pattern><template>Oh, except there's been a radiation leak.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  UH  WHO'S HOME    WELL  MY MOM ALREADY LEFT FOR THE DINER AND DAD WENT TO 7 11 TO GET SCRATCHERS</pattern><template>I guess he won 'cause that was six years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT REALLY  IT WAS JUST ONE NIGHT</pattern><template>Yep.   That's how you did it, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>LADIES  FOLLOW THE MULLET  LADIES FIRST</pattern><template>Thank you. I'll call you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HERE'S THE THING    NOBODY CAN ID A DEVICE</pattern><template>There's no bomb casings   You know I can help Just ask. I got a ton of new tech.</template></category><category><pattern>BARREL'S A LITTLE LONG</pattern><template>Between that and the wide gauge, it's going to diminish your FPS And now you're out of ammo.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR WHAT  DID I MISS SOMETHING    ME SAVING YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>A: Saved you first, B: Thanks, sort of And C: If you do someone a solid, don't be a yutz alright, just play it cool otherwise you come off grandiose Unlike you?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU GO TOO HOT</pattern><template>The good news is, a high level position has just been vacated You're a maniac.   No, I'm a visionary But I do own a maniac, and he takes the stage tonight When we get the Iron Patriot, it'll take me nine to ten minutes to disassemble it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I'M SAYING IS THAT THE HUMAN ELEMENT OF HUMAN RESOURCES IS OUR BIGGEST POINT OF VULNERABILITY WE SHOULD START PHASING IT OUT IMMEDIATELY</pattern><template>What!?   Excuse me, Bambi Did you just say that?   Security Happy, okay, I am thrilled that you're now the Head of Security, okay; it is the perfect position for you.   Thank you However,   I do appreciate it Since you've taken the post,   You don't have to thank me.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU TAKE A MINUTE</pattern><template>Jarvis, give me a suit right now!</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IS GREAT  I LOVE YOU; I'M LUCKY</pattern><template>But honey... I can't sleep.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HERE HE COMES  HERE HE COMES  GET A QUICK PICTURE</pattern><template>Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THAT MY BOSS IS WORKING FOR THE MANDARIN</pattern><template>So if you still want to talk about it, I suggest we get ourselves someplace safe Your boss works for the Mandarin you think, but Tony says you're a botanist That figures. What I actually am is a biological DNA coder running a team of 40 out of a privately funded think tank, but sure you can call me a  botanist  This boss of yours, does he have a name?</template></category><category><pattern>UNFORTUNATELY  TO MY EARS IT ALSO SOUNDS HIGHLY WEAPONIZABLE AS IN ENHANCED SOLDIERS  PRIVATE ARMIES  AND TONY IS NOT  TONY  TONY YOU KNOW  I INVITED TONY TO JOIN AIM 13 YEARS AGO AND HE TURNED ME DOWN BUT SOMETHING TELLS ME NOW THERE IS A NEW GENIUS ON THE THRONE  WHO DOESN'T HAVE TO ANSWER TO TONY ANYMORE AND WHO HAS SLIGHTLY LESS OF AN EGO</pattern><template>It's going to be a  no , Aldrich...</template></category><category><pattern>VERY FUNNY</pattern><template>Sir, I've located Miss Potts.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU  LITTLE ONE COLONEL RHODES  GLAD TO SEE YOU COULD MAKE IT  SON</pattern><template>I feel safer already We gotta make a decision. We can either save the President or Pepper. We can't do both.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM YOUR BIGGEST FAN</pattern><template>First, is this your van or is anyone else gonna come in?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON  COME ON YEAH    1000 FEET</pattern><template>800 feet. 200 feet, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BUT SHADDT THE BEACH WHEN SOMETHING RELATED TO A LARGE COMPOUND BOMKANNI PICK YOU UP THERE TONY  I SWEAR TO GOD  I'M GOING TO BLOW HIS FACE OFF</pattern><template>Oh this next bit may include the Vice President as well.</template></category><category><pattern>WAR MACHINE WAS A LITTLE TOO AGGRESSIVE  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>This sends a better message.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T KNOW IF YOU WERE COMING HOME OR YOU WERE HAVING DRINKS WITH ALDRICH KILLIAN</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT RHODES</pattern><template>The President. Now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LIKE THAT  WEST WORLD</pattern><template>That's the thing about smart guys We always cover our ass.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT    HEY  DO YOU FANCY EITHER OF THE BIRDS</pattern><template>You're not him, the Mandarin, the real guy, where?!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY SO FAR  YOU LIKE IT</pattern><template>It'll do.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU COMIN' OUT</pattern><template>Do not open, do not open, don't open, don't open, don't  Alright, let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>CENTRAL TO MY ADMINISTRATION'S RESPONSE TO THIS TERRORIST EVENT IS A NEWLY MINTED RESOURCE</pattern><template>I know him as Colonel James Rhodes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE SHE ALWAYS IS    SEE  NOW YOU'RE BEING HELPFUL</pattern><template>Sorry. Lady, this uh, Thank you   Nice haircut, suits you.</template></category><category><pattern>EASY  SEE  ELEVEN MORE TO GO</pattern><template>Remember that game called Barrel of Monkeys?</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  I'VE LOCATED MISS POTTS</pattern><template>About time.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE A MOVE AND I'LL BREAK YOUR FACE</pattern><template>I never thought people had been hurt. They lied to me.</template></category><category><pattern>PEPPER    KILLIAN</pattern><template>You look great... you look really great.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  WHERE'S MY FLIGHT POWER</pattern><template>Working on it, sir. This is a prototype.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO</pattern><template>Nice work guys. Excellent.</template></category><category><pattern>THE  HOUSE PARTY  PROTOCOL  SIR</pattern><template>Correct.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL ELECTRIFY YOUR ARM; YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO OPEN YOUR HAND  YOU CAN DO THIS  HEATHER</pattern><template>Easy, see? Eleven more to go.</template></category><category><pattern>CORRECT</pattern><template>Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>MY DIAGNOSIS IS THAT YOU'VE EXPERIENCED A SEVERE ANXIETY ATTACK</pattern><template>Me?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S YOUR NAME    HARLEY AND YOU'RE    THE MECHANIC TONY YOU KNOW WHAT KEEPS GOING THROUGH MY HEAD</pattern><template>Where's my sandwich?</template></category><category><pattern>NON LETHAL DEAL  DEAL  WHAT'D YOU SAY    DEAL</pattern><template>What's your name?   Harley And you're?   The mechanic Tony You know what keeps going through my head?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WELCOME</pattern><template>For what? Did I miss something?   Me saving your life.</template></category><category><pattern>SUNDAY NIGHT'S PBS  DOWNTOWN ABBEY  THAT'S THE SHOW  HE THINKS IT'S ELEGANT</pattern><template>One more thing... make sure everyone wears their badges. He's a stickler for that sort of thing, plus my guys won't let anyone in without them.</template></category><category><pattern>HUH  YUP  DAMNIT  NO CAN DO</pattern><template>You want to just kiss it on the, uh, facial slit?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY TONY</pattern><template>Aldrich Killian, I'm a big fan of your work.</template></category><category><pattern>BY TAKING THE GUY THEY CALL  WAR MACHINE  AND GIVING HIM A PAINT JOB THE SAME SUIT BUT PAINTED RED  WHITE  AND BLUE  LOOK AT THAT AND THEY'VE ALSO RENAMED HIM IRON PATRIOT YOU KNOW  JUST IN CASE THE PAINT WAS TOO SUBTLE IT TESTED WELL WITH FOCUS GROUPS  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>I am Iron Patriot.   Listen.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHY AM I TELLING YOU THIS</pattern><template>Because I had just created demons, and I didn't even know it.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER WHAT I TOLD YOU ABOUT BULLIES</pattern><template>You like that, West World?</template></category><category><pattern>OH HEY  DID YOU SEE YOUR CHRISTMAS PRESENT</pattern><template>Yes, I did. I don't know how I could have missed that Christmas present.</template></category><category><pattern>FLIP THE SCREEN  THEN I CAN SEE WHAT THEY'RE DOING</pattern><template>I don't know how to flip the screen!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ON EARTH HAVE YOU BEEN DOING</pattern><template>Nothing fancy, just five years in the hands of physical therapists And please, call me Aldrich.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  NESSIE DID YOU KNOW THAT FORTUNE COOKIES AREN'T EVEN CHINESE</pattern><template>There's some guy over here  They're made by Americans, based on the Japanese recipes Hey!   Bloody hell, bloody hell   Don't move.</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN BETCHA</pattern><template>Come on, I thought that was just a theory.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE WE AT WITH IT    UH  IT'S NOT CHARGING</pattern><template>Actually, sir, it is charging, but the power source is questionable.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T HURT ME PLEASE  I'M AN ACTOR</pattern><template>You got a minute to live, fill it with words.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE MEDICATION</pattern><template>Nope.</template></category><category><pattern>PRESIDENT  BUT I'M GONNA NEED THAT SUIT BACK</pattern><template>The President is secure, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO TAKE THE SUIT UP TO BASE CAMP  AND I WANT POTTS WITH ME</pattern><template>She's still in Phase 2.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT THING ON YOUR CHEST</pattern><template>It's a electromagnet. You should know, you've got a box of them right here.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PUBLIC ONLY KNOWS ABOUT THREE</pattern><template>But here's the thing... nobody can ID a device.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU CLEAR THIS FOUR O'CLOCK WITH ME</pattern><template>Happy, we'll talk about this later But right now I have to go deal with this very annoying thing.</template></category><category><pattern>HI</pattern><template>You think he's gonna help you... he won't.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO DITCH THESE CLOWNS; I'LL SEE YOU UP ON THE ROOF IN FIVE MINUTES</pattern><template>I'm just going to try to get my beef wet real quick if you know what I'm talkin' about.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  RINGO  DIDN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING ABOUT A  LOVELY SPEEDBOAT</pattern><template>If he's right about the location, we're 20 minutes from where Pepper is.   But we also have to figure out this Vice President thing, right?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Merry Christmas, buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE GOT A LOT OF APOLOGIES TO MAKE AND NOT A LOT OF TIME  SO FIRST OFF I'M SO SORRY I PUT YOU IN HARM'S WAY</pattern><template>That was selfish and stupid and it won't happen again.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  NOTHING  SIR</pattern><template>I just needed a reason to kill you that would play well on TV.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING OUT OF TOWN</pattern><template>Okay, we've been through this. Nope.   Yep!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  GUY MERRY CHRISTMAS AFTER YEARS DODGING THE PRESIDENT'S BAN ON  IMMORAL BIOTECH RESEARCH   MY THINK TANK NOW HAS A LITTLE SOMETHING IN THE PIPELINE</pattern><template>It's an idea we like to call  Extremis .</template></category><category><pattern>NO MORE FALSE FACES</pattern><template>You said you wanted the Mandarin.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT    DO WE NEED TO WORRY ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>I got you.   I got you first.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M CLEARING THE AREA</pattern><template>Nice work.   Ready sir?</template></category><category><pattern>THE PRESIDENT IS SECURE  TONY</pattern><template>I'm clearing the area.</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR TO GOD  YOU'RE GOING TO FREAK ME OUT</pattern><template>Ah man, you did it, didn't you? You happy now?</template></category><category><pattern>THESE DAYS I'M A CHANGED MAN</pattern><template>I'm different now.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM TO GO OUT FOR A DRINK OR SOMETHING</pattern><template>You know what? You should take more of an interest in what's going on here.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE 'EM TO CHURCH</pattern><template>Jarvis, get Igor to steady this thing.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ZIP TIED TO A BED    THIS</pattern><template>That.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT WHERE'D YOU LIKE TO START</pattern><template>I just want to say I'm sorry about your loss.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A MECHANIC    YEAH</pattern><template>If I was building Iron Man and War Machine, It's Iron Patriot now.   That's way cooler!</template></category><category><pattern>TONY STARK  GREAT SPEECH  MAN</pattern><template>I gave a speech?</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER</pattern><template>You really didn't deserve her, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THERE'VE BEEN NINE BOMBINGS   NINE</pattern><template>The public only knows about three.</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK THE HEART  CHECK THE  CHECK THE  IS IT THE BRAIN</pattern><template>No sign of cardiac analomy or unusual brain activity Okay, so I was poisoned?</template></category><category><pattern>COOL IT  WILL YOU JARVIS</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  NOT MY IDEA  WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE; THIS IS THOUSANDS OF MILES AWAY  I'VE GOTTA GET PEPPER  I'VE GOT TO  I PREPARED A FLIGHT PLAN</pattern><template>This was the location.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S    I MEAN  I HAD THEM DO IT OFF A DOLL THAT I MADE  SO IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S OFF A PICTURE  SO IT'S A LITTLE BIT  JERRY  FOR A MOMENT  LISTEN TO ME HERE</pattern><template>I don't want to clip your wings here; we're both a little over excited.</template></category><category><pattern>FLIP THE SCREEN AND THEN WE CAN GET STARTED</pattern><template>I'm not a tech genius like you, just trust me, get down here.</template></category><category><pattern>WANTED TO HELP PEOPLE  NOW LOOK AT YOU</pattern><template>I get to wake up every morning with someone who...</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU CAN SEE MY RESEARCH  BUT THAT'S</pattern><template>I'm not going to show you my  town .</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT JUST THE THING</pattern><template>This is a pinata for a cricket. I'm kidding; it's a very powerful weapon. Point it away from your face, press the button on top, It discourages bullying.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU WANT TO TELL ME WHY YOU WERE AT STARK'S MANISON LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>I'm trying to fix this thing. I didn't know you and the Master were gonna blow the place up.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HERE'S WHERE YOU'RE WRONG: SHE WAS ALREADY PERFECT</pattern><template>Jarvis, do me a favor and blow Mark 42.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  TONY</pattern><template>Sir, Miss Potts is clear of the structure.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY GAVE ME PLASTIC SURGERY  THEY GAVE ME THINGS</pattern><template>Did you just nod off?</template></category><category><pattern>EXACTLY</pattern><template>Can you not touch my plant? It's not...</template></category><category><pattern>AH MAN  YOU DID IT  DIDN'T YOU  YOU HAPPY NOW</pattern><template>What did I say?</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS    IT'S COMPLICATED</pattern><template>Uncomplicate it. Ladies out, get out of the bed, get in the bathroom.</template></category><category><pattern>MACHINES    THEY'RE PART OF ME</pattern><template>A distraction.   Maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THERE'S A GIANT BRAIN  THERE'S A SHIFTY CHARACTER</pattern><template>I'm going to follow this guy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT THIS SUIT  YOU'RE GOING OT HAVE TO PRY MY COLD  DEAD BODY OUT OF IT</pattern><template>That's the plan, Colonel.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT YOU COVERED</pattern><template>Good evening, Colonel. Can I give you a lift?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY NEEDS A HOBBY</pattern><template>Heartbreaker? Help Red Snapper out, will ya?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>Jarvis! Not my idea! What are we doing here; this is thousands of miles away, I've gotta get Pepper, I've got to  I prepared a flight plan.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL THEN  WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR</pattern><template>The sandwich was fair, the spring was a little rusty, the rest of the materials I'll make do By the way, when you said your sister had a watch, I was kinda hoping for something a little more than that She's six! Anyway, it's limited edition.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S THE REST</pattern><template>Honestly, I hate working here... they are so weird.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH JUICE</pattern><template>I need you to jump on the roof, recalibrate the ISDNs Pump it up by about 40 %.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SIMPLY RULE FROM BEHIND THE SCENES</pattern><template>Because the second you give evil a face Bin Laden, Gaddafi, The Mandarin You hand the people a target   You're something else You have met him, I assume?</template></category><category><pattern>6 000 FEET   COME ON  PEOPLE</pattern><template>Come on, come on, come on Yeah!   1000 feet.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY MILITARY VICTIMS</pattern><template>Not according to public records, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>MS  DAVIS  YOUR SON DIDN'T KILL HIMSELF; I GUARANTEE YOU HE DIDN'T KILL ANYONE  SOMEONE USED HIM</pattern><template>What?   As a weapon You're not the person who called me after all, are you?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A PITY</pattern><template>I was so close to having her... perfect.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH BUT KILLIAN BUILT THAT THINK TANK ON MILITARY CONTRACTS   THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE USED TO DO SO DON'T JUDGE YOURSELF THANK YOU  PEPPER</pattern><template>I really appreciate that.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW    NEITHER WILL I</pattern><template>Let me tell you: that was the best sleep I'd had in years.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE    10 000 FEET</pattern><template>6,000 feet   Come on, people.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO</pattern><template>The kid that bullies you at school, what's his name?</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  SIR  IT IS CHARGING  BUT THE POWER SOURCE IS QUESTIONABLE</pattern><template>It may not succeed in revitalizing the Mark 42.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SIR LAWRENCE OBLIVION</pattern><template>I know he's a little over the top sometimes...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MANIPULATIVE  I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Are they coming back? The aliens?</template></category><category><pattern>OH THIS GUY</pattern><template>Mr. Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>GET ME OUT OF HERE  COME ON YOU KNOW WHAT MY OLD MAN USED TO SAY TO ME</pattern><template>His favorite of many sayings  The early bird gets the worm; the second mouse gets the cheese  You're not still pissed about the Switzerland thing, are you?   How can I be pissed you, Tony?</template></category><category><pattern>I MISS YOU  HAPPY</pattern><template>Yeah, I miss you too but the way it used to be.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN</pattern><template>It's complicated, hey, it's complicated, alright?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY KID  GIVE ME MORE SPACE</pattern><template>What's the official story here? What happened?</template></category><category><pattern>PHEW  IT'S GOOD TO BE BACK  HELLO  BY THE WAY</pattern><template>Oh, hello sir.</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS ANOTHER TIME</pattern><template>Bern, Switzerland 1999 The old days, I never thought they'd come back to bite me.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  IT'S JUST US    WHAT'S YOUR NAME</pattern><template>Gary.   Gary.   Oh wow.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY DOWN</pattern><template>You're right on me...</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  I'D KILL FOR SOME ARMOR RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>You're right, we need backup.   Yeah, much.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE AWAITING THE ARRIVAL OF TONY STARK</pattern><template>We're hoping he'll give us the reaction...</template></category><category><pattern>SO  UH  TENSE  GOOD DAY</pattern><template>Oh shoulders, a little naughty. Naughty girl.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED A LITTLE MORE INFORMATION THAN THAT</pattern><template>Well, I think it's a little above your pay grade, Sheriff.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEN I THOUGHT TO MYSELF   WHY STOP THERE   OF COURSE  THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO SAY PROGRESS IS DANGEROUS</pattern><template>But I'll bet none of those idiots ever had to live with a chest full of shrapnel.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HELLO SIR</pattern><template>All personnel, Stark is loose and somewhere in the compound. Repeat: Stark is loose and somewhere in the compound.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>I got just the thing.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AN IDEA WE LIKE TO CALL  EXTREMIS</pattern><template>I'm gonna turn your lights down.</template></category><category><pattern>THOMAS HERE IS AN ACCOUNTANT FOR THE ROXXON OIL CORPORATION AND I'M SURE HE'S A REALLY GOOD GUY</pattern><template>I'm going to shoot him in the head, live on your television, in 30 seconds.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY  I WOULD HAVE ADDED IN THE RETRO  RETROREFLECTIVE PANELS    TO MAKE HIM STEALTH MODE</pattern><template>You want a stealth mode?   Cool, right?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  UH  PONYTAIL EXPRESS WHAT IS THE MILEAGE COUNT BETWEEN TENNESSEE AND MIAMI    832 MILES VERY NICE</pattern><template>Are you gonna stop that?   Break it you bought it Okay, that wasn't mine to give away, that belongs to my friend's sister, and that's why I'm gonna kill you first.</template></category><category><pattern>BILL ME</pattern><template>I've compiled a Mandarin database for you, sir, Drawn from S.H.I.E.L.D., F.B.I., and C.I.A. intercepts.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS</pattern><template>Don't leave me, buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL FIX HIM</pattern><template>Like a mechanic.   Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ROCKET PERFORMED PERFECTLY IT JUST LANDED ON THE WRONG PLANET</pattern><template>See we all begin wide eyed...  pure science  Then the ego steps in, the obsession And when you look up, you're a long way from shore You can't be too hard on yourself, Maya.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  I HAVE AN UPDATE FROM MALIBU</pattern><template>The cranes have finally arrived and the cellar doors are being cleared as we speak.</template></category><category><pattern>MERRY CHRISTMAS  BUDDY</pattern><template>Jarvis, target Extremis heat signatures.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT DOING THIS  OKAY    WHAT HAPPENS TO YOU</pattern><template>What happens if you go too hot?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU DRESS LIKE THIS AT HOME</pattern><template>Hmm? Sports bra, the whole deal.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>You good?   Yep.   I'll be right outside.   Okay, cool.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'RE YOU A DECOY  YOU'RE A DOUBLE  RIGHT</pattern><template>What? No. An understudy? Absolutely not.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A LIVE FEED  COME ON UP  I'LL PROVE IT TO YOU</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU SHOULD CLOSE YOUR EYES</pattern><template>Close your eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>HONEY</pattern><template>Oh, my god.</template></category><category><pattern>KILLIAN  I DON'T REMEMBER THAT GUY   OF COURSE YOU DON'T REMEMBER; HE'S NOT A BLONDE WITH A BIG RACK</pattern><template>At first it was fine, they were talking business, but now it's like getting weird... he's showing her his big brain.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT IMPORTANT    SOMEWHAT    YEAH  A LITTLE BIT</pattern><template>So?   Uh, what are we gonna do.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M DIFFERENT NOW</pattern><template>I'm... well, you know who I am.</template></category><category><pattern>SOLD IT TO THE MANDARIN</pattern><template>What happened? Fun fact Before he built rockets for the Nazis The idealistic Werner von Braun dreamed of space travel... he stargazed You know what he said when the first V2 hit London?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WAIT  YOU'RE GUILT TRIPPING ME  AREN'T YOU</pattern><template>I'm cold I can tell. You know how I can tell?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW HE'S A LITTLE OVER THE TOP SOMETIMES</pattern><template>it's not entirely my fault He has a tend... he's a stage actor.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE OUT OF THE WAY OR I'M GOING TO RUN YOU OVER</pattern><template>Bye kid.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S NOT</pattern><template>Anyway, I would have added in the retro  Retroreflective panels?   To make him stealth mode.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T TELL HIM ANYTHING</pattern><template>Nothing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THAT  LIKE MARK 15</pattern><template>Yeah, something like that.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO GO</pattern><template>The Master is about to record and he's a little...</template></category><category><pattern>THE THREAT IS IMMINENT</pattern><template>And I have to protect the one thing that I can't live without...</template></category><category><pattern>AND YES  I HAD A QUICK BITE</pattern><template>I didn't know if you were coming home Or you were having drinks with Aldrich Killian.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT IT</pattern><template>I'll electrify your arm; you won't be able to open your hand. You can do this, Heather.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU THINK HAPPENED I BROUGHT YOUR DAMN FILE  YOU TAKE IT AND GO</pattern><template>Whatever was in here, he wanted no part of it.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM IRON PATRIOT    LISTEN</pattern><template>War Machine was a little too aggressive, alright.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S STILL IN PHASE 2</pattern><template>You're not going deaf, are ya?</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO    YOU EVER LOOK UP AND EVERYTHING STARTS GLOWING FROM THE INSIDE OUT  A KIND OF BRIGHT ORANGE YEAH  I'VE HAD THAT  WHO IS THIS    IT'S ME  PAL</pattern><template>Now last time I went missing, if I remember correctly, you went looking for me.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  LADY  THIS UH  THANK YOU   NICE HAIRCUT  SUITS YOU</pattern><template>Nice watch.   Yeah, limited edition.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN TAKE AWAY MY HOUSE  ALL MY TRICKS AND TOYS ONE THING YOU CAN'T TAKE AWAY</pattern><template>I am Iron Man.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY STARK IS IN MY VAN    NO  HE'S NOT</pattern><template>I knew you were still alive!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU REALLY KILLED THE GLASS</pattern><template>I was aiming for the bulb?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE MANDARIN    I KNOW  IT'S  IT'S EMBARRASSING</pattern><template>Hi, I'm Trevor, Trevor Slattery.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW HOW TO FLIP THE SCREEN</pattern><template>Don't talk to me like that anymore. You're not my boss.</template></category><category><pattern>CREATING A FLIGHT PLAN FOR TENNESSEE</pattern><template>Are we still at  ding dong ?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT TO HARP ON THIS  BUT DID YOU LIKE THE CUSTOM RABBIT</pattern><template>Did I like it?   Nailed it, right?   Wow.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S THE MANDARIN   WHERE IS HE</pattern><template>He's here. He's here.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I JUST CATCH MY BREATH FOR A SECOND</pattern><template>Are there bad guys in Rose Hills?</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T HAVE ANY TRANSPORT</pattern><template>Hey, Ringo, didn't you say something about a  lovely speedboat ?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  A LITTLE MOVIE CALLED  THE PARTY'S OVER  STARRING YOU AND YOUR JUNKIE GIRLFRIEND  AND HERE'S THE TICKET NO KIDDING    THAT DOESN'T BELONG TO YOU</pattern><template>Savin! Help! Help me!</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T PROTECT YOU OUT THERE  I CHALLENGED  IS THIS NORMAL    SADLY  THAT   YES  THIS IS NORMAL</pattern><template>Is very normal   It's a big bunny, relax about it!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SO I RUN HIS CREDENTIALS  I MAKE HIM</pattern><template>Aldrich Killian. We actually met the guy...</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THERE BAD GUYS IN ROSE HILLS</pattern><template>Do you need a plastic bag to breathe into?</template></category><category><pattern>HI PEPPER</pattern><template>So you want to tell me why you were at Stark's manison last night?</template></category><category><pattern>'CAUSE WE'RE CONNECTED</pattern><template>It was worth a shot.</template></category><category><pattern>RELAX  WHAT'S YOUR NAME  HEATHER</pattern><template>Listen, see that guy? I'm going to swing by him and you're just going to grab him.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  KID  I'M GOING TO HAVE TO WALK YOU THROUGH REBOOTING JARVIS' SPEECH DRIVE  BUT NOT RIGHT NOW  HARLEY  WHERE IS HE REALLY</pattern><template>Just look on the screen and tell me where it is.</template></category><category><pattern>NOOOO</pattern><template>No more false faces.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER THOUGHT PEOPLE HAD BEEN HURT  THEY LIED TO ME</pattern><template>This is the Mandarin?   I know, it's, it's embarrassing.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO    SIR  THIS IS TONY STARK</pattern><template>Welcome back to the land of the living.   We believe you're about to be drawn into the Mandarin campaign, and we've got to get you somewhere safe as soon as possible.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT IRON MAN    TECHNICALLY  I AM</pattern><template>Technically, you're dead.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HELL'S GOING ON HERE</pattern><template>It's called an arrest.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  I'M TREVOR  TREVOR SLATTERY</pattern><template>I know I'm shorter in person, I'm a bit small, everyone says that, but, uh, hey, if you're here to arrest me, there are some people who I'd like to rat on Here's how it works, you tell him where Pepper is and he'll stop doing it.</template></category><category><pattern>HALF HOUR 'TILL THE BALL DROPS</pattern><template>Tony Stark, great speech, man!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL    IT WAS</pattern><template>If I'm right, we can access the area of the brain that governs repair and chemically recode it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT    THIS    YOU'RE INSIDE MY HEAD</pattern><template>It's a live feed. Come on up, I'll prove it to you.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE EMERGENCY ALERT TRIGGERED BY THE POWER DROPPING BELOW 5 %</pattern><template>Snow? Where are we, upstate?</template></category><category><pattern>LIFE  I BUILT HIM; I TAKE CARE OF HIM</pattern><template>I'll fix him.</template></category><category><pattern>TECHNICALLY  YOU'RE DEAD</pattern><template>A valid point.   What happened to him?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ARMOR IS NOW AT 92 %</pattern><template>That's gonna have to do.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  IT WAS MY PERFORMANCE THAT BROUGHT THE MANDARIN TO LIFE</pattern><template>Your performance? Where people die?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT  THE GLITCH</pattern><template>Have you checked the telomerase algorithm?</template></category><category><pattern>CRAZY  HUH    YEAH</pattern><template>Watch this.</template></category><category><pattern>GET 'EM OUT  GET 'EM OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>A bomb is not a bomb when it's a misfire This stuff doesn't always work, right, pal?</template></category><category><pattern>I ALMOST HAD THIS 20 YEARS AGO WHEN I WAS DRUNK</pattern><template>I think I can get you better.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ROOM IS SECURE  I HAVE EYES ON THE MANDARIN</pattern><template>What's this? I had winner's.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT A GOOD IDEA</pattern><template>What are you doing? You're going to break his finger?</template></category><category><pattern>THE MASTER IS TRAVELLING</pattern><template>Well then, what are we waiting for?</template></category><category><pattern>SWEETHEART  THAT COULD BE THE NAME OF MY AUTOBIOGRAPHY</pattern><template>Let me go!   Help me! Help me!</template></category><category><pattern>GOT IT    ALRIGHT  IT'S A MISSION</pattern><template>Tony needs Gary and Gary needs Tony   Be quiet about it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SIR  YOU WERE RIGHT  ONCE I FACTORED IN AVAILABLE AIM DOWNLINK FACILITIES I WAS ABLE TO PINPOINT THE MANDARIN'S BROADCAST SIGNAL</pattern><template>What're we talkin'? The Far East, Europe, North Africa, Iran, Pakistan, Syria, where is it?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL PERSONNEL  STARK IS LOOSE AND SOMEWHERE IN THE COMPOUND  REPEAT: STARK IS LOOSE AND SOMEWHERE IN THE COMPOUND</pattern><template>Ah, crap.</template></category><category><pattern>PEPPER  IT'S ME</pattern><template>I've got a lot of apologies to make and not a lot of time, so first off I'm so sorry I put you in harm's way.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT'S MAYA HANSEN</pattern><template>Old botanist pal that I used to know, barely.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH I CAN DO  SIR  WHEN YOU GIVE THE WORLD'S PRESS YOUR HOME ADDRESS</pattern><template>Right there's fine.</template></category><category><pattern>EINSTEIN SLEPT THREE HOURS A YEAR  LOOK WHAT HE DID</pattern><template>People are concerned about you, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE GIVEN ME THE GREATEST GIFT THAT ANYBODY'S EVER GIVEN ME</pattern><template>Desperation. If you think back to Switzerland, you said you'd meet me on the rooftop, right?</template></category><category><pattern>RHODES AND STARK OUT</pattern><template>Everything okay, sir?   Couldn't be better.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  OH  WHAT  ARE YOU MAD AT ME</pattern><template>Honey.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MY SUITS; THEY'RE UH</pattern><template>Machines.   They're part of me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID I SAY</pattern><template>Hey, wait up! Wait, wait.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T COME HOME YET I NEED TO FIND THIS GUY</pattern><template>You gotta stay safe. That's all I know.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL HERE WE ARE  ON THE ROOF MARK 42 INBOUND    WELL I'LL BE DAMNED</pattern><template>The prodigal son returns.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S TWO</pattern><template>Tony!</template></category><category><pattern>OH YEAH  THAT'S AWESOME  GIVE ME A SUIT  OKAY</pattern><template>Oh, I'm sorry. They're only coded to me.</template></category><category><pattern>A BOMB IS NOT A BOMB WHEN IT'S A MISFIRE THIS STUFF DOESN'T ALWAYS WORK  RIGHT  PAL</pattern><template>It's faulty, but you found a buyer, didn't ya?</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FAULT  YOU SPAZZED ME OUT</pattern><template>Okay, back to business. Where were we?</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT HOT THERE</pattern><template>Stuck? Feel a little stuck?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE ON TOTAL SECURITY LOCKDOWN</pattern><template>Come on, I threatened a terrorist. Who is that?</template></category><category><pattern>PEPPER  PEPPER  PEPPER   LOOK IF WE WANT TO LAUNCH PRODUCT NEXT YEAR  I NEED STARK</pattern><template>He just lacked a decent incentive. Now he has one.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO JUST KISS IT ON THE  UH  FACIAL SLIT</pattern><template>Why don't I run down to the garage and see if I can't find a crowbar to jimmy that thing open?</template></category><category><pattern>AMERICAN AIRWAYS WERE HIJACKED</pattern><template>The nation remains on high alert.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  CAN I JUST SAY SIR    YEAH</pattern><template>I am your biggest fan.</template></category><category><pattern>THINK ABOUT IT  SIX DEAD  ONLY FIVE SHADOWS</pattern><template>Yeah, but people said these shadows are like the mark of souls gone to Heaven Except the bomb guy, he went to Hell on account of he didn't get a shadow.</template></category><category><pattern>SAVIN  HELP  HELP ME</pattern><template>A true story about fortune cookies They look Chinese. They sound Chinese.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO RUN HIS PLATES AND IF IT GETS ROUGH  SO BE IT</pattern><template>I miss you, Happy.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT HERE</pattern><template>Try the jet stream. Speaking of which, go fish!</template></category><category><pattern>NOT ACCORDING TO PUBLIC RECORDS  SIR</pattern><template>Bring up the thermogenic signatures again, factor in 3000 degrees The oracle cloud has completed analysis.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS TO YOU  IT'S BEEN MY MANTRA EVER SINCE  RIGHT</pattern><template>You simply rule from behind the scenes.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PRESIDENT  NOW</pattern><template>He's not here.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT    YES</pattern><template>It's a decent batch.</template></category><category><pattern>IS YOUR GUN UP</pattern><template>Yup, what do I do?   Stay on my six, cover high, and don't shoot me in the back.   Six, high, back. Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CRANES HAVE FINALLY ARRIVED AND THE CELLAR DOORS ARE BEING CLEARED AS WE SPEAK</pattern><template>And what about the suit I'm wearing?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WEARING THIS IN THE HOUSE NOW</pattern><template>What is that, like Mark 15?</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  TAKE A DEEP BREATH</pattern><template>Flight power restored.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY I AM NOT SURPRISED    DON'T TAKE IT PERSONALLY  I DON'T REMEMBER WHAT I HAD FOR BREAKFAST</pattern><template>Gluten free waffles, sir.   That's right.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD STRONG NAME  GOOD STRONG JOB</pattern><template>Thomas here is an accountant for the Roxxon Oil Corporation And I'm sure he's a really good guy.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE RIGHT THING TO DO</pattern><template>There's just one lesson left, President Ellis, so run away and kiss your children goodbye Because nothing, not your army, not your red, white, and blue attack dog, can save you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOOD    YEP    I'LL BE RIGHT OUTSIDE    OKAY  COOL</pattern><template>So, why am I telling you this?</template></category><category><pattern>DOES IT REMIND YOU</pattern><template>That's manipulative. I don't want to talk about it.</template></category><category><pattern>RELAX  I'M JUST ASKING YOU TO SECURE THE PERIMETER</pattern><template>Tell him to go out for a drink or something.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LAST TIME I LOOKED THERE WAS SOMEBODY INSIDE OF IT</pattern><template>Good evening, gentlemen Hello Colonel Step aside.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD</pattern><template>I was really violent.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE AN UNAUTHORIZED BROADCAST MR  VICE PRESIDENT  I THINK YOU SHOULD SEE THIS OH MY GOD  NOT AGAIN  IS THE PRESIDENT GETTING THIS</pattern><template>Mr. President Only two lessons remain.</template></category><category><pattern>MOM  MS  DAVIS  WHERE IS SHE</pattern><template>Where she always is.   See, now you're being helpful.</template></category><category><pattern>ANONYMITY  TONY</pattern><template>Thanks to you, it's been my mantra ever since, right?</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD</pattern><template>He's strung up over the oil tank; they're gonna light him up, man.   Viking funeral.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TRYING TO FIX THIS THING  I DIDN'T KNOW YOU AND THE MASTER WERE GONNA BLOW THE PLACE UP</pattern><template>Oh I see, so you were trying to save Stark... when he threatened us   I told you, Killian, we can use him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>Aldrich Killian? What are you checking up on me?</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU CHECKED THE TELOMERASE ALGORITHM</pattern><template>We're good.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS 72 HOURS IS A LONG TIME BETWEEN SIESTAS DIDN'T THINK IT COULD GET ANY WORSE THEN THEY HAD TO GO AND TURN ON THE TV</pattern><template>That's when 'He' happened.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE ROXXON NORCO</pattern><template>Of course you remember when she spilled 100 million gallons of crude off Pensacola.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY</pattern><template>Sir, take a deep breath.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO JUMP ON THE ROOF  RECALIBRATE THE ISDNS PUMP IT UP BY ABOUT 40 %</pattern><template>Got it.   Alright, it's a mission.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL UH  I THINK THAT WOULD BE THE DAY I DECIDED NOT TO LET MY INJURY BEAT ME</pattern><template>Can you please state your name for the camera?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU KNOW  LOOK  I GOT A REAL JOB  WHAT DO YOU WANT  I'M WORKING; I GOT SOMETHING GOING ON HERE    WHAT  HARASSING INTERNS</pattern><template>Let me tell you something, you know what happened when I told people I was Iron Man's bodyguard? They would laugh in my face.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY IS IT SO HOT IN HERE  I TOLD YOU TO PUT IT AT 68</pattern><template>My fault again... let me tell you something sweetheart, I am not your personal  I wouldn't go in there for twenty minutes!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED  FUN FACT BEFORE HE BUILT ROCKETS FOR THE NAZIS THE IDEALISTIC WERNER VON BRAUN DREAMED OF SPACE TRAVEL    HE STARGAZED YOU KNOW WHAT HE SAID WHEN THE FIRST V2 HIT LONDON</pattern><template>The rocket performed perfectly It just landed on the wrong planet.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM TITILLATED BY THE NOTION OF WORKING WITH YOU</pattern><template>I'm going to ditch these clowns; I'll see you up on the roof in five minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SURE IS</pattern><template>Alright Where'd you like to start?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  OKAY  WAIT  WAIT  SLOW DOWN  SLOW DOWN</pattern><template>Okay, you're right. I don't deserve her.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MEANS YOU'RE FINE  GIVE ME JARVIS</pattern><template>Jarvis, how are we?   It's totally fine sir. I seem to do quite well for a stretch and then at the end of the sentence I say the wrong cranberry.</template></category><category><pattern>I FORGOT THAT NIGHT IN SWITZERLAND</pattern><template>These days I'm a changed man.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW; LATER</pattern><template>Hey kid, give me more space.</template></category><category><pattern>SAME AS IT'S ALWAYS BEEN  WAR MACHINE 68</pattern><template>And password please?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU GOING COMPLETELY MENTAL</pattern><template>I can stop, do you want me to stop?</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE DON'T TELL ME THAT THERE IS A 12 YEAR OLD KID WAITING IN THE CAR THAT I'VE NEVER MET</pattern><template>He's 13. No, I need your help.   What for? Why now?</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE AWAY EVERYWHERE THAT THERE'S BEEN A MANDARIN ATTACK</pattern><template>Nope.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE YOU REMEMBER WHEN SHE SPILLED 100 MILLION GALLONS OF CRUDE OFF PENSACOLA</pattern><template>Thanks to you, not one fat cat saw a day in court.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY    YOU ATE WITHOUT ME  ALREADY</pattern><template>On date night?</template></category><category><pattern>RICH GUY  HANDSOME I COULDN'T MAKE HIS FACE AT FIRST AND YOU KNOW I'M GOOD WITH FACES</pattern><template>Oh yeah, you're the best.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SUCH A JERK</pattern><template>Yup, we'll talk about it at dinner.</template></category><category><pattern>800 FEET  200 FEET  SIR</pattern><template>It's a tricky monkey, let's get him.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA COME GET THE BODY</pattern><template>There's no politics here; it's just good, old fashioned revenge.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS GUY BOTHERING YOU</pattern><template>Don't get up!</template></category><category><pattern>ALL WRAPPED UP HERE  SIR  WILL THERE BE ANYTHING ELSE</pattern><template>You know what to do.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS FAVORITE OF MANY SAYINGS  THE EARLY BIRD GETS THE WORM; THE SECOND MOUSE GETS THE CHEESE  YOU'RE NOT STILL PISSED ABOUT THE SWITZERLAND THING  ARE YOU    HOW CAN I BE PISSED YOU  TONY</pattern><template>You've given me the greatest gift that anybody's ever given me.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR REAL    YEAH</pattern><template>Alright, so she's meeting up with this scientist...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S BRISK</pattern><template>Maybe I'll just cozy back up for a bit.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  DO ME A FAVOR AND BLOW MARK 42</pattern><template>NOOOO!</template></category><category><pattern>WITH HAPPY IN THE HOSPITAL  I DIDN'T KNOW WE WERE EXPECTING GUESTS</pattern><template>We weren't.</template></category><category><pattern>ADDICTION WILL NOT BE TOLERATED AND THOSE WHO CANNOT REGULATE WILL BE CUT FROM THE PROGRAM</pattern><template>Once misfits, cripples...</template></category><category><pattern>TALK TO ME  HAPPY</pattern><template>When is a bomb not a bomb?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GREAT TO SEE YOU</pattern><template>As promised, I got Pepper sorted out; it took some tinkering.</template></category><category><pattern>INITIATING VIRTUAL CRIME SCENE RECONSTRUCTION</pattern><template>Okay, what do we got here?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT A COMPLIMENT   IT IS A COMPLIMENT</pattern><template>Clearly somebody is trying to hide something.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR SOURCES ARE TELLING US THAT THIS IS ANOTHER MANDARIN ATTACK</pattern><template>Anything else you can tell us?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU OKAY</pattern><template>I broke the crayon.   Are you okay, Mr. Stark?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT SURE IF YOU CAN TELL BUT AT THIS MOMENT THE BODY IS TRYING TO DECIDE WHETHER TO ACCEPT EXTREMIS OR JUST GIVE UP AND IF IT GIVES UP  I HAVE TO SAY THE DENOTATION IS QUITE SPECTACTULAR BUT UNTIL THAT POINT  IT'S REALLY JUST A LOT OF PAIN</pattern><template>We haven't even talked salary yet.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES THIS SUBJECT MAKE YOU EDGY    YEAH  A LITTLE BIT</pattern><template>Can I just catch my breath for a second?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE IT COMES</pattern><template>3, 4 Shut up.   54321 I told you.</template></category><category><pattern>TRUST ME  YOU'RE GOING IN A PUDDLE OF BLOOD ON THE GROUND IN 5  4  3  COME ON   2 HOW DID WE GET THIS SHIT    ALRIGHT  I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A CHANCE TO ESCAPE  PUT DOWN YOUR WEAPONS AND TIE YOURSELVES INTO THOSE CHAIRS AND I'LL LET YOU LIVE</pattern><template>In 5, 4 You should be gone by now, you should have already been gone.   I'm just beyond terrified.</template></category><category><pattern>HI    OH  UH    MIND LEAVING THAT ON    SURE</pattern><template>Sunday night's PBS  Downtown Abbey  That's the show. He thinks it's elegant.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M CALLING IT  EXTREMIS    WELL  ITS   HUMAN APPLICATION   EXACTLY</pattern><template>Dentra degree vitalization Disease prevention Even limb regrowth.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KID THAT BULLIES YOU AT SCHOOL  WHAT'S HIS NAME</pattern><template>How'd you know that?</template></category><category><pattern>I GET TO WAKE UP EVERY MORNING WITH SOMEONE WHO</pattern><template>still has a soul.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MOVE    YOU GOT ME</pattern><template>Nice potato gun.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT OPEN  DO NOT OPEN  DON'T OPEN  DON'T OPEN  DON'T  ALRIGHT  LET'S GO</pattern><template>You breathe fire? Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE I'LL BUILD ONE</pattern><template>Not a good idea!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST NEEDED A REASON TO KILL YOU THAT WOULD PLAY WELL ON TV</pattern><template>You see, I've moved on.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO</pattern><template>18,000 feet   Come on, everybody, grab your monkey!</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO LEAVE WHILE I STILL HAD A SHRED OF DIGNITY</pattern><template>Now I got a real job; I'm watching Pepper.</template></category><category><pattern>HISPANIC SCOTT BAIO</pattern><template>Oh, I'm sorry, is that me?   Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WE'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS  NOPE    YEP</pattern><template>The man says no   Immediately and indefinitely.</template></category><category><pattern>IF RICHARD DOESN'T MIND  YOU ALRIGHT WITH THIS  DICK</pattern><template>Fine with me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENS TO YOUR PRODUCT</pattern><template>We're not doing this, okay?   What happens to you?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT AIN'T GONNA CUT IT</pattern><template>Excuse me sir, I don't know who...</template></category><category><pattern>18 000 FEET   COME ON  EVERYBODY  GRAB YOUR MONKEY</pattern><template>Nice!   10,000 feet.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  UH  WHERE ARE WE GOING    UH  TO TOWN ON EACH OTHER  PROBABLY BACK AT YOUR HOUSE  I WANT TO SEE YOUR RESEARCH</pattern><template>Okay, you can see my research, but that's...</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MORE THING    MAKE SURE EVERYONE WEARS THEIR BADGES  HE'S A STICKLER FOR THAT SORT OF THING  PLUS MY GUYS WON'T LET ANYONE IN WITHOUT THEM</pattern><template>We're awaiting the arrival of Tony Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A TERRIBLE IDEA  PLEASE DON'T TOUCH HER BAGS</pattern><template>Tony, this is how normal people behave.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  STARK  I'M ABOUT TO EAT HONEY ROAST HAM SURROUNDED BY THE AGENCY'S FINEST</pattern><template>And the President is safe on Air Force One with Colonel Rhodes I think we're good here.   Sir, this is Colonel Rhodes!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A PINATA FOR A CRICKET  I'M KIDDING; IT'S A VERY POWERFUL WEAPON  POINT IT AWAY FROM YOUR FACE  PRESS THE BUTTON ON TOP  IT DISCOURAGES BULLYING</pattern><template>Non lethal Deal. Deal? What'd you say?   Deal.</template></category><category><pattern>OH YEAH  WITH ZIP TIES  IT'S A BALL</pattern><template>It wasn't my idea.   Okay, so you took Killian's card I took his money   and here you are 13 years later in a dungeon No.   Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  I'VE MOVED ON</pattern><template>I've found myself a new political patron, and At this time tomorrow, he'll have your job.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WEREN'T</pattern><template>And old girlfriends   She's not really.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I HAD JUST CREATED DEMONS  AND I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW IT</pattern><template>Yeah, those were good times.</template></category><category><pattern>WORKING ON IT  SIR  THIS IS A PROTOTYPE</pattern><template>That's one.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE TO THROW AWAY AND ONE TO NOT CALL</pattern><template>Advanced Idea Mechanics  or AIM for short, you get it?</template></category><category><pattern>I USED TO WORK WITH HIM  AND HE USED TO ASK ME OUT ALL THE TIME  SO IT'S A LITTLE AWKWARD</pattern><template>I don't like the sound of that.</template></category><category><pattern>MY WORK    WHO IS HE  HE MEANS ME</pattern><template>Well, of course, but Miss Hansen, my organization has been tracking your research since year two of M.I.T.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I THINK I CAN FIGURE THIS OUT  YEAH</pattern><template>I almost had this 20 years ago when I was drunk.</template></category><category><pattern>I AIN'T SCARED OF YOU</pattern><template>I'm the best As always sir, a great pleasure watching you work.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST A ROLE   THE MANDARIN   SEE  IT'S NOT REAL</pattern><template>Then how did you get here, Trevor?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU REGULATE</pattern><template>Yes, I can regulate.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SANDWICH WAS FAIR  THE SPRING WAS A LITTLE RUSTY  THE REST OF THE MATERIALS I'LL MAKE DO BY THE WAY  WHEN YOU SAID YOUR SISTER HAD A WATCH  I WAS KINDA HOPING FOR SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE THAN THAT SHE'S SIX  ANYWAY  IT'S LIMITED EDITION</pattern><template>When can we talk about New York?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALLY DIDN'T DESERVE HER  TONY</pattern><template>It's a pity.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH    I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN TELL BUT I HAVE LIKE PATTERNED MY WHOLE LOOK AFTER YOU  MY HAIR'S A LITTLE  IT'S NOT RIGHT BECAUSE THERE'S SOME PRODUCT IN IT RIGHT</pattern><template>I don't want to make things awkward for you   No.   But I do have to show you... boom!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY KID  YOU DID GOOD    SO NOW YOU'RE JUST GOING TO LEAVE YOU HERE  LIKE MY DAD</pattern><template>Yeah. Wait, you're guilt tripping me, aren't you?</template></category><category><pattern>NO SIGN OF CARDIAC ANALOMY OR UNUSUAL BRAIN ACTIVITY OKAY  SO I WAS POISONED</pattern><template>My diagnosis is that you've experienced a severe anxiety attack.</template></category><category><pattern>CAREFUL THERE  IT'S A LIMITED EDITION</pattern><template>Hey, uh, ponytail express What is the mileage count between Tennessee and Miami?   832 miles Very nice.</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE WAY  I LIKED YOU IN  A CHRISTMAS STORY</pattern><template>Listen, the Pentagon is scared.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A LITTLE TURTLE  COOKING IN HIS LITTLE TURTLE SUIT</pattern><template>Tony She's watching.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GONNA COME AT ME LIKE THAT</pattern><template>No, look, I'm not trying to be a dic    tator.   Would you mind signing my drawing?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU FEEL THAT  WE'RE DONE HERE</pattern><template>Move out of the way or I'm going to run you over.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ENTIRE EAST COAST    THE SATELLITES ARE DOWN</pattern><template>We have an unauthorized broadcast Mr. Vice President, I think you should see this Oh my God, not again. Is the President getting this?</template></category><category><pattern>HARLEY  TELL ME WHAT IS HAPPENING  GIVE ME A FULL REPORT   YEAH  I'M STILL EATING THAT CANDY  DO YOU WANT ME TO KEEP EATING IT</pattern><template>How much did you have?   Two or three bowls.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT ABOUT THE SUIT I'M WEARING</pattern><template>The armor is now at 92 %.</template></category><category><pattern>NORMALLY  I'D GO FOR THAT SORT OF THING  BUT NOW I'M IN A COMMITTED RELATIONSHIP IT'S    WITH HER    TONY  IS SOMEBODY THERE</pattern><template>Yeah, it's Maya Hansen.</template></category><category><pattern>OH WOW  HE MADE IT  HE MADE THE CUT</pattern><template>What floor you going to, pal?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S SOME GUY OVER HERE  THEY'RE MADE BY AMERICANS  BASED ON THE JAPANESE RECIPES HEY    BLOODY HELL  BLOODY HELL   DON'T MOVE</pattern><template>If you want something, take it, although the guns are all fake because those wankers wouldn't trust me with the real ones.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  UM  UH OH GOD  WHAT AM I GONNA DO</pattern><template>Just breathe, really just breathe You're a mechanic, right?   Right.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE IT EASY  TONY</pattern><template>....How did you get out of the wormhole?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MY FAVORITE KIND  A WINNING COMBO</pattern><template>Hey, uh, where are we going?   Uh, to town on each other, probably back at your house. I want to see your research.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GONNA HAVE TO DO</pattern><template>Oh, here he comes, here he comes, get a quick picture.</template></category><category><pattern>COPY</pattern><template>Nobody move!</template></category><category><pattern>HI EVERYBODY  BEFORE WE START  I PROMISE YOU  LOOKING BACK AT YOUR LIFE THERE WILL BE NOTHING AS BITTER AS THE MEMORY OF THAT GLORIOUS RISK THAT YOU PRUDENTLY ELECTED TO FOREGO TODAY IS YOUR GLORY  LET'S BEGIN</pattern><template>We gotta get out of here! Gotta get out of here!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WALKED RIGHT INTO THIS ONE; I'VE DATED HOTTER CHICKS THAN YOU</pattern><template>That's all you got? Cheap trick and a cheesy one liner?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T LIKE THE SOUND OF THAT</pattern><template>Pepper.   Killian?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S JUST ONE LESSON LEFT  PRESIDENT ELLIS  SO RUN AWAY AND KISS YOUR CHILDREN GOODBYE BECAUSE NOTHING  NOT YOUR ARMY  NOT YOUR RED  WHITE  AND BLUE ATTACK DOG  CAN SAVE YOU</pattern><template>I'll see you soon.</template></category><category><pattern>SUPPOSED TO MEET SOMEBODY HERE</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL FOR THE FIRST 20 MINUTES  I ACTUALLY THOUGHT YOU'D SHOW UP  FOR THE NEXT HOUR  I UHH WELL I CONSIDERED TAKING THAT ONE STEP SHORTCUT TO THE LOBBY  IF YOU KNOW I MEAN HONESTLY  I'M STILL TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT HAPPENED TO THE FIRST MOUSE</pattern><template>But as I looked out over that city, nobody knew I was there, nobody could see me, no one was even looking I had a thought that would guide me for years to come.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW YOU'RE OFF WITH THE 'SUPERFRIENDS'</pattern><template>I don't know what's going on with you anymore. The world's gettin' weird Hey I hate to cut you off, do you have your taser on you?   Why?   I think there's a gal in HR who is trying to steal some printer ink. You should probably go over there and zap her.   Yeah, nice.</template></category><category><pattern>GLUTEN FREE WAFFLES  SIR    THAT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>Look, I need to be alone with you, someplace not here... it's urgent.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY JUST A LITTLE FAST    SLOW IT DOWN</pattern><template>Slow it down just a... little bit.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS HE WON 'CAUSE THAT WAS SIX YEARS AGO</pattern><template>Which happens, dads leave. No need to be a pussy about it. Here's what I need: a laptop, a digital watch, a cell phone, The pneumatic actuator from your bazooka over there, a map of town, a big spring, and a tunafish sandwich.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW   EXTREMIS  HARNESSES OUR BIOELECTRICAL POTENTIAL AND IT GOES    HERE</pattern><template>This is essentially an empty slot, and what this tells us is that our mind, our entire DNA in fact, is destined to be upgraded.   Wow.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY  WHAT'S ALL THIS ABOUT</pattern><template>The hell's going on here?</template></category><category><pattern>IF I DIE KILLIAN  WHAT HAPPENS TO YOUR SOLDIERS</pattern><template>What happens to your product?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANT TO SAY I'M SORRY ABOUT YOUR LOSS</pattern><template>I want to know what you think happened I brought your damn file. You take it and go.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THANKS KID</pattern><template>Why is it so hot in here? I told you to put it at 68.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURE I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN  PEPPER</pattern><template>Happy   The car is ready... if you're ready to go.</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH THIS</pattern><template>You walked right into this one; I've dated hotter chicks than you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA TURN YOUR LIGHTS DOWN</pattern><template>Regard the human brain Uh, wait, hold on, hold on; that's, that's the universe, my bad.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS WHAT    BIG BRAIN  AND SHE LIKES IT</pattern><template>Here, let me show you. Hold on. See?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I JUST SAY</pattern><template>Yeah.   I don't know if you can tell but I have like Patterned my whole look after you. My hair's a little, it's not right because there's some product in it Right.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD ON  HOLD ON  MAYA   I SAID LET HIM GO WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>1200ccs, a dose half of this size and I'm dead It's times like this my temper is tested somewhat Maya, give me the injector.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU USED TO HAVE IDEALS</pattern><template>Wanted to help people, now look at you.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S YOU</pattern><template>And my suits; they're uh...</template></category><category><pattern>STRING HIM UP</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OUT BY YOURSELF  A LITTLE DATE NIGHT</pattern><template>Watching your favorite chick flick maybe?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS JUST   YOU MEAN YOU WELL YEAH  I JUST MEAN WE WERE JUST</pattern><template>just hosting you while I finished up a little work.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  I GOTTA SPLIT</pattern><template>Badge... badge... badge Badge, guys. I put a memo in the toliet; come on.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  I AM</pattern><template>Hey, hey! What's all this about?</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME GO    HELP ME  HELP ME</pattern><template>Hey kid, what would you like for Christmas?</template></category><category><pattern>SLOW DOWN  SLOW DOWN</pattern><template>Relax, what's your name? Heather..</template></category><category><pattern>BUH BYE</pattern><template>Brace yourself!</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS AN HONOR  MR  PRESIDENT IF YOU'RE GONNA DO IT  DO IT</pattern><template>That's not how the Mandarin works.   Sir.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST BREATHE  REALLY JUST BREATHE YOU'RE A MECHANIC  RIGHT    RIGHT</pattern><template>You said so.   Yes, I did.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO SLEEP DOWNSTAIRS  TINKER WITH THAT</pattern><template>Can you regulate?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE WERE WE IN 1999  THE SCIENCE CONFERENCE</pattern><template>Switzerland.   Right, right, exactly.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT TIME</pattern><template>Stop, put it down, put it down, put it down.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I HAVE TO PROTECT THE ONE THING THAT I CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT</pattern><template>That's you.</template></category><category><pattern>SWITZERLAND    RIGHT  RIGHT  EXACTLY</pattern><template>Killian, I don't remember that guy   Of course you don't remember; he's not a blonde with a big rack.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL DAMAGE THE ARMOR</pattern><template>Yes, I will, but you can fix it, right?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S VERY NICE TO SEE YOU  KILLIAN</pattern><template>Hey, guy Merry Christmas After years dodging the president's ban on  immoral biotech research , My think tank now has a little something in the pipeline.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT     EXCUSE ME  BAMBI DID YOU JUST SAY THAT    SECURITY HAPPY  OKAY  I AM THRILLED THAT YOU'RE NOW THE HEAD OF SECURITY  OKAY; IT IS THE PERFECT POSITION FOR YOU    THANK YOU HOWEVER    I DO APPRECIATE IT SINCE YOU'VE TAKEN THE POST    YOU DON'T HAVE TO THANK ME</pattern><template>We've had a rise in staff complaints of 300 percent Thank you.   That's not a compliment.</template></category><category><pattern>BADGE    BADGE    BADGE BADGE  GUYS  I PUT A MEMO IN THE TOLIET; COME ON</pattern><template>Tony has got them in his basement, they're wearing party hats, this is an asset we can put to use Uh huh. So, you're suggesting that I replace the entire janitorial staff with robots?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I NEED IS FOR YOU TO GO HOME  BE WITH YOUR MOM  KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT  AND PROTECT THE SUIT</pattern><template>And stay connected to the telephone because if I call you better pick up. Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I DID  I DON'T KNOW HOW I COULD HAVE MISSED THAT CHRISTMAS PRESENT</pattern><template>Is it gonna fit through the door?   Well actually, uh, that's a good question, I got a team of guys coming tomorrow. They're gonna blow out that wall.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW      IN SWITZERLAND</pattern><template>That's better.   This week You almost bought it, didn't you?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID YOU GET OUT OF THE WORMHOLE</pattern><template>Tony   What'd you say?!</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  HEY</pattern><template>All wrapped up here, sir. Will there be anything else?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU HANG OUT WITH MY EX GIRLFRIENDS</pattern><template>You're such a jerk.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK HE'S GONNA HELP YOU    HE WON'T</pattern><template>Having you here is not just to motivate Tony Stark; it's actually more embarrassing than that.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M    WELL  YOU KNOW WHO I AM</pattern><template>...Sir, please may I request just a few hours to calibrate   Nope!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT  YOU SURE THAT'S NOT ONE OF HIS</pattern><template>It predates any known Mandarin attack.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT; I'LL FIX IT</pattern><template>So, uh, who's home?   Well, my mom already left for the diner and dad went to 7 11 to get scratchers.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU USED TO HAVE A MORAL PSYCHOLOGY</pattern><template>You used to have ideals.</template></category><category><pattern>SNOW  WHERE ARE WE  UPSTATE</pattern><template>We are 5 miles outside of Rose Hills, Tennessee.</template></category><category><pattern>IMAGINING HOW IT GOT THERE AMERICA  IF YOUR PRESIDENT CALLS ME IN THE NEXT HALF MINUTE  TOM LIVES</pattern><template>Go.</template></category><category><pattern>A QUAINT MILITARY CHURCH  FILLED WITH WIVES AND CHILDREN OF COURSE THE SOLIDERS WERE OUT ON MANUVERS</pattern><template>The  Braves  were away.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA LET GO  I'LL CATCH YOU  I PROMISE</pattern><template>What a shame; I would have caught her.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE NOT UNIVERSAL  TONY</pattern><template>I know what I'm doing, I make this stuff. Gimme another one.   I don't have one that fits that gun.</template></category><category><pattern>EVER BEEN TO TENNESSEE  JARVIS</pattern><template>Creating a flight plan for Tennessee.</template></category><category><pattern>ACCESSING SATELLITES AND PLOTTING THE LAST 12 MONTHS OF THERMOGENIC OCCURANCES NOW</pattern><template>Take away everywhere that there's been a Mandarin attack.</template></category><category><pattern>BROADCAST WILL COMMENCE SHORTLY  TAKE FINAL POSITIONS</pattern><template>Okay, that's great. Now give me cameras A through E and do a full tech rehearsal.</template></category><category><pattern>NO BOMB PARTS FOUND IN A 3 MILE RADIUS OF THE CHINESE THEATRE    NO  SIR</pattern><template>Talk to me, Happy.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL NOW  THAT IS AN APPROPRIATE QUESTION</pattern><template>The ground floor, actually, of a proposal I'm putting together myself.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHEN 'HE' HAPPENED</pattern><template>Some people call me a terrorist I consider myself a teacher America...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT HOW THE MANDARIN WORKS    SIR</pattern><template>Air Force One's been compromised.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TALK TO ME LIKE THAT ANYMORE  YOU'RE NOT MY BOSS</pattern><template>Alright, I don't work for you, and I don't trust this guy.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  GET IGOR TO STEADY THIS THING</pattern><template>This is how you've been managing your downtime, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE WE ALL BEGIN WIDE EYED     PURE SCIENCE  THEN THE EGO STEPS IN  THE OBSESSION AND WHEN YOU LOOK UP  YOU'RE A LONG WAY FROM SHORE YOU CAN'T BE TOO HARD ON YOURSELF  MAYA</pattern><template>I mean you gave your research to a think tank.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  STARK  I AM SO SORRY</pattern><template>No, no, I think he was trying to say  I want my goddamn file.  It's not your fault kid.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER WHEN I TOLD YOU THAT I HAVE AN ANXIETY ISSUE</pattern><template>Does this subject make you edgy?   Yeah, a little bit.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ON THE OFF CHANCE YOU'RE A MAN  HERE'S MY HOME ADDRESS: 10880  MALIBU PORT  90265</pattern><template>I'll leave the door unlocked.</template></category><category><pattern>I ACTUALLY THINK I NEED TO SLEEP NOW  SIR</pattern><template>Jarvis.</template></category><category><pattern>KILLIAN    KILLIAN</pattern><template>He created you?   He created me.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING  YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED WHEN I TOLD PEOPLE I WAS IRON MAN'S BODYGUARD  THEY WOULD LAUGH IN MY FACE</pattern><template>I had to leave while I still had a shred of dignity.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE  GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Get 'em out! Get 'em out of here!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE'S NOT HERE  HE'S HERE BUT HE'S NOT HERE</pattern><template>What do you mean?</template></category><category><pattern>MR  PRESIDENT  JUST HOLD ON  ALRIGHT  I'M COMING</pattern><template>Just hold on. Hold on.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I WAS BUILDING IRON MAN AND WAR MACHINE  IT'S IRON PATRIOT NOW    THAT'S WAY COOLER</pattern><template>No, it's not.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW HIM AS COLONEL JAMES RHODES</pattern><template>The American people will soon know him as the Iron Patriot.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE USING THE IRON PATRIOT AS A TROJAN HORSE; THEY'RE GONNA TAKE OUT THE PRESIDENT SOMEHOW</pattern><template>We have to immediately alert that plane.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AMERICAN BUSINESS</pattern><template>Are you okay?</template></category><category><pattern>HE JUST LACKED A DECENT INCENTIVE  NOW HE HAS ONE</pattern><template>This is Support Team Blue 0, sending coordinates for suspected Mandarin broadcast point of origin.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT GONNA FREAK OUT ON ME  RIGHT</pattern><template>I hope not.</template></category><category><pattern>I MUST HAVE CALLED IT IN MY SLEEP</pattern><template>that's not supposed to happen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE THE NEXT ITERATION OF HUMAN EVOLUTION</pattern><template>Hi everybody. Before we start, I promise you, looking back at your life there will be nothing as bitter as the memory of that glorious risk that you prudently elected to forego Today is your glory. Let's begin!</template></category><category><pattern>I DO WHAT I KNOW; I TINKER</pattern><template>The threat is imminent.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULDN'T SAVE THE PRESIDENT WITH THE SUIT  HOW ARE YOU GONNA SAVE PEPPER WITHOUT IT</pattern><template>Uh, say Jarvis, is it that time?</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TELL YOU: THAT WAS THE BEST SLEEP I'D HAD IN YEARS</pattern><template>It's okay, it's okay.   No!</template></category><category><pattern>THE NATION REMAINS ON HIGH ALERT</pattern><template>All attempts to find the Mandarin have so far proved unsuccessful.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A TRICKY MONKEY  LET'S GET HIM</pattern><template>Hello.</template></category><category><pattern>UNCOMPLICATE IT  LADIES OUT  GET OUT OF THE BED  GET IN THE BATHROOM</pattern><template>Sit.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GOOD NEWS IS  A HIGH LEVEL POSITION HAS JUST BEEN VACATED YOU'RE A MANIAC    NO  I'M A VISIONARY BUT I DO OWN A MANIAC  AND HE TAKES THE STAGE TONIGHT WHEN WE GET THE IRON PATRIOT  IT'LL TAKE ME NINE TO TEN MINUTES TO DISASSEMBLE IT</pattern><template>That's great.</template></category><category><pattern>BLOOD ON MY MAT; HANDLE IT</pattern><template>Sir, may I remind you that you've been awake for nearly 72 hours Focus up ladies. Good evening And welcome to the birthing suite.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY SHE'S WATCHING</pattern><template>I think you should close your eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  TARGET EXTREMIS HEAT SIGNATURES</pattern><template>Disable with extreme prejudice.   Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT A PREHENSILE SUIT  I GOT BOMB DISPOSAL CATCHES EXPLOSIONS MID AIR WHEN'S THE LAST TIME YOU GOT A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP</pattern><template>Einstein slept three hours a year. Look what he did.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU    I MEAN FOR UNDERSTANDING</pattern><template>Ah, I'm sorry, buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS HOW YOU'VE BEEN MANAGING YOUR DOWNTIME  HUH</pattern><template>Everybody needs a hobby.</template></category><category><pattern>A DISTRACTION    MAYBE</pattern><template>I'm gonna take a shower.   Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST LIKE OLD TIMES  HUH</pattern><template>Oh yeah, with zip ties. It's a ball.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU ANYMORE  THE WORLD'S GETTIN' WEIRD HEY I HATE TO CUT YOU OFF  DO YOU HAVE YOUR TASER ON YOU    WHY    I THINK THERE'S A GAL IN HR WHO IS TRYING TO STEAL SOME PRINTER INK  YOU SHOULD PROBABLY GO OVER THERE AND ZAP HER    YEAH  NICE</pattern><template>Imagine if you could hack into the hard drive of any living organism and recode its DNA It would be incredible.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WAIT UP  WAIT  WAIT</pattern><template>What the hell was that?</template></category><category><pattern>A TRUE STORY ABOUT FORTUNE COOKIES THEY LOOK CHINESE  THEY SOUND CHINESE</pattern><template>But they're actually an American invention Which is why they're hollow, full of lies, and leave a bad taste in the mouth My disciples just destroyed another cheap American knock off The Chinese Theater. Mr. President, I know this must be getting frustrating But this season of terror is drawing to a close And don't worry...</template></category><category><pattern>SOME PEOPLE CALL ME A TERRORIST I CONSIDER MYSELF A TEACHER AMERICA</pattern><template>Ready for another lesson.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUY WHO DIED    RELATIVES</pattern><template>Mom? Ms. Davis, where is she?</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  HOW ARE WE    IT'S TOTALLY FINE SIR  I SEEM TO DO QUITE WELL FOR A STRETCH AND THEN AT THE END OF THE SENTENCE I SAY THE WRONG CRANBERRY</pattern><template>And sir, you were right. Once I factored in available AIM downlink facilities I was able to pinpoint the Mandarin's broadcast signal.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T LEAVE ME  BUDDY</pattern><template>Stark Secure Server: Now transferring to all known receivers.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  SAY JARVIS  IS IT THAT TIME</pattern><template>The  house party  protocol, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>BYE KID</pattern><template>I'm sorry kid. You did good.   So now you're just going to leave you here, like my dad?</template></category><category><pattern>MOM  I NEED TO CALL YOU BACK  SOMETHING MAGICAL IS HAPPENING</pattern><template>Tony Stark is in my van.   Keep it down.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  PLEASE MAY I REQUEST JUST A FEW HOURS TO CALIBRATE   NOPE</pattern><template>Micro repeater implanting sequence complete!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON IN AND CLOSE THE DOOR</pattern><template>Wow, can I just say sir?   Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>ALSO  IT'S CHRISTMAS TIME  THE RABBIT'S TOO BIG  DONE</pattern><template>Sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>STILL HAS A SOUL</pattern><template>Get me out of here, come on You know what my old man used to say to me?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'RE YA DOING  BUDDY</pattern><template>You out by yourself? A little date night?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HAPPY NEW YEAR   HAPPY NEW YEAR   HAPPY NEW YEAR ALRIGHT  I'LL SEE YOU IN THE MORNING  OKAY</pattern><template>Good night.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA STAY SAFE  THAT'S ALL I KNOW</pattern><template>I just stole a poncho from a wooden Indian.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  LOOK  I'M NOT TRYING TO BE A DIC    TATOR    WOULD YOU MIND SIGNING MY DRAWING</pattern><template>If Richard doesn't mind. You alright with this, Dick?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL OWN THE WAR ON TERROR CREATES SUPPLY AND DEMAND FOR YOU AND YOUR BROTHERS AND SISTERS</pattern><template>Trust me, you're going in a puddle of blood on the ground in 5, 4, 3, Come on!, 2 How did we get this shit?   Alright, I'm going to give you a chance to escape, put down your weapons And tie yourselves into those chairs and I'll let you live.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  LOOK  I GOTTA CHANGE IT EVERY TIME YOU HACK IN  TONY   IT'S NOT THE EIGHTIES  NOBODY SAYS  HACK  ANYMORE  GIVE ME YOUR LOGIN</pattern><template>War Machine Rox  with an X, all caps.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THAT    THE PRIMARY SOMATOSENSORY CORTEX IT'S THE BRAIN'S PAIN CENTER  BUT THIS</pattern><template>is what I wanted to show you.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GROUND FLOOR  ACTUALLY  OF A PROPOSAL I'M PUTTING TOGETHER MYSELF</pattern><template>It's a privately funded think tank called  Advanced Idea Mechanics  She'll take both.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I DON'T DOUBT IT</pattern><template>Well have a good evening.</template></category><category><pattern>FLIGHT POWER RESTORED</pattern><template>Sir.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT EVERYONE SAYS</pattern><template>You know what this crater reminds me of?</template></category><category><pattern>BRING UP THE THERMOGENIC SIGNATURES AGAIN  FACTOR IN 3000 DEGREES THE ORACLE CLOUD HAS COMPLETED ANALYSIS</pattern><template>Accessing satellites and plotting the last 12 months of thermogenic occurances now.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING'S BEEN THE SAME SINCE NEW YORK    OH REALLY</pattern><template>I didn't notice that, at all.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M THE BEST AS ALWAYS SIR  A GREAT PLEASURE WATCHING YOU WORK</pattern><template>I guess 72 hours is a long time between siestas Didn't think it could get any worse Then they had to go and turn on the TV.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY  THE POINT IS EVER SINCE THAT BIG DUDE WITH THE HAMMER FELL OUT OF THE SKY SUBTLETY'S KINDA HAD ITS DAY WHAT'S NEXT FOR YOU IN YOUR WORLD</pattern><template>Well, I wanted to repay you for the same gift you so graciously imparted to me Desperation. Now, this is live.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MASTER IS ABOUT TO RECORD AND HE'S A LITTLE</pattern><template>Well you know how he gets.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ALWAYS ME  TONY  RIGHT FROM THE START  I AM THE MANDARIN</pattern><template>I got nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT</pattern><template>Here's a little Holiday greeting I've been wanting to send to the Mandarin.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WOMAN IS THE BEST THING THAT EVER HAPPENED TO YOU AND YOU'RE JUST IGNORING HER    A GIANT BRAIN</pattern><template>Yeah, there's a giant brain, there's a shifty character...</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  I THOUGHT THAT WAS JUST A THEORY</pattern><template>Well... it was.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S QUESTIONABLE ABOUT ELECTRICITY</pattern><template>Alright, it's my suit and I can't... I'm not gonna...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING  A LITTLE TALKING  MAKING FRIENDS IN PAKISTAN    WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Your re design, your big re brand, that was AIM, right?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT I MISSED THE PRESIDENT</pattern><template>You couldn't save the President with the suit, how are you gonna save Pepper without it?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S TWO MILITARY GUYS</pattern><template>Ever been to Tennessee, Jarvis?</template></category><category><pattern>STILL DEBATABLE</pattern><template>Probably tipping your way a little bit.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T I RUN DOWN TO THE GARAGE AND SEE IF I CAN'T FIND A CROWBAR TO JIMMY THAT THING OPEN</pattern><template>A crowbar? Yeah...</template></category><category><pattern>STOP STOPPING  GET HER; GET OUTSIDE  GO</pattern><template>Oh my God. Tony!</template></category><category><pattern>AND STAY CONNECTED TO THE TELEPHONE BECAUSE IF I CALL YOU BETTER PICK UP  OKAY</pattern><template>Can you feel that? We're done here.</template></category><category><pattern>STOPPING THE MANDARIN IS A PRIORITY  BUT IT'S NOT   IT'S NOT SUPERHERO BUSINESS</pattern><template>No, it's not, quite frankly.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE PRESIDENT IS SAFE ON AIR FORCE ONE WITH COLONEL RHODES I THINK WE'RE GOOD HERE    SIR  THIS IS COLONEL RHODES</pattern><template>They're using the Iron Patriot as a trojan horse; they're gonna take out the President somehow.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT YOU DID</pattern><template>Blood on my mat; handle it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T REMEMBER    I CAN'T HELP YOU</pattern><template>You used to have a moral psychology.</template></category><category><pattern>HONESTLY  I HATE WORKING HERE    THEY ARE SO WEIRD</pattern><template>Better late than never.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALLY APPRECIATE THAT</pattern><template>Hi, good evening   Good evening.   Come on in.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE SAVED YOURSELF A WORLD OF PAIN</pattern><template>What?   Trust me.   I'm sure.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN YOU GAVE YOUR RESEARCH TO A THINK TANK</pattern><template>Yeah but Killian built that think tank on military contracts   That's exactly what we used to do So don't judge yourself Thank you, Pepper.</template></category><category><pattern>YEP    THAT'S HOW YOU DID IT  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>It was a great night.   Well... you know   Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE FOUND MYSELF A NEW POLITICAL PATRON  AND AT THIS TIME TOMORROW  HE'LL HAVE YOUR JOB</pattern><template>String him up.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY IN THE AIR    THIRTEEN  SIR</pattern><template>How many can I carry?   Four, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVEN'T SAID ANYTHING</pattern><template>Nothing's been the same since New York.   Oh really?</template></category><category><pattern>DUMMY HI DUMMY  HOW DID YOU GET THAT CAP ON YOUR HEAD</pattern><template>You earned it.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A PIPING HOT MESS  IT'S BEEN GOING ON FOR A WHILE</pattern><template>I haven't said anything.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME</pattern><template>Uh, nothing, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THIS  I HAD WINNER'S</pattern><template>What've you come as?</template></category><category><pattern>IS WHAT I WANTED TO SHOW YOU</pattern><template>Now,  Extremis  harnesses our bioelectrical potential And it goes... here.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO SHOOT HIM IN THE HEAD  LIVE ON YOUR TELEVISION  IN 30 SECONDS</pattern><template>The number for this telephone is in your cell phone.</template></category><category><pattern>I APPRECIATE THE THOUGHT VERY MUCH  SO WHY DON'T YOU LIFT UP THAT FACEMASK AND GIVE ME A KISS</pattern><template>Huh, yup, damnit. No can do.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A POSSIBLE POINT OF ORIGIN IN PAKISTAN AND THE PATRIOT IS READY TO STRIKE    RIGHT NOW    YES  SIR</pattern><template>Don't move!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A PRIVATELY FUNDED THINK TANK CALLED  ADVANCED IDEA MECHANICS  SHE'LL TAKE BOTH</pattern><template>One to throw away and one to not call.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WOULD YOU REGARD AS THE DEFINING MOMENT OF YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>Well uh, I think that would be the day I decided not to let my injury beat me.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOT ANOTHER GUY WITH HIM; HE'S SHIFTY</pattern><template>Relax. I'm just asking you to secure the perimeter.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED TO THE PICTURE</pattern><template>The entire East coast... the satellites are down.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  EXCEPT THERE'S BEEN A RADIATION LEAK</pattern><template>I'll take my chances.   That's risky At least let me get you like a Hazmat suit or a Geiger counter or something like that Busted.   This is a new level of lame.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ALDRICH KILLIAN</pattern><template>Well we took the house down sir, but there's no sign of a body.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA TAKE A SHOWER    OKAY</pattern><template>And you're going to join me.   Better.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IF I WERE TO WRAP THIS UP TIGHT WITH A BOW OR WHATEVER  I GUESS I'D SAY MY ARMOR WAS NEVER A DISTRACTION OR A HOBBY</pattern><template>It was a cocoon.</template></category><category><pattern>SAID THEY'D GIVE ME MORE THEY GAVE ME THINGS  THEY GAVE ME THIS PALACE</pattern><template>They gave me plastic surgery. They gave me things.</template></category><category><pattern>CALM DOWN    I GOT THIS FOR YOU</pattern><template>I'm aware of that.   You still haven't even told me that you liked it!   I don't like it!   I asked you three  You don't like it?!</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I READ THE PAPERS  AND  FRANKLY  I DON'T THINK YOU'LL LAST THE WEEK</pattern><template>I'll be fine.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  MAY I REMIND YOU THAT YOU'VE BEEN AWAKE FOR NEARLY 72 HOURS FOCUS UP LADIES  GOOD EVENING AND WELCOME TO THE BIRTHING SUITE</pattern><template>I am pleased to announce the imminent arrival of your bouncing, badass baby brother.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT</pattern><template>Are you comin' out?</template></category><category><pattern>TONY HAS GOT THEM IN HIS BASEMENT  THEY'RE WEARING PARTY HATS  THIS IS AN ASSET WE CAN PUT TO USE UH HUH  SO  YOU'RE SUGGESTING THAT I REPLACE THE ENTIRE JANITORIAL STAFF WITH ROBOTS</pattern><template>What I'm saying is that the human element of Human Resources is our biggest point of vulnerability We should start phasing it out immediately.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT GOING DEAF  ARE YA</pattern><template>Careful there, it's a limited edition.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS REACTION TO THE LATEST ATTACK</pattern><template>Mr. Stark!</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE NEVER  RELAX ABOUT IT</pattern><template>What about the Avengers, can you talk about them?</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE ARE CONCERNED ABOUT YOU  TONY</pattern><template>I'm concerned about you.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE WATCH    YEAH  LIMITED EDITION</pattern><template>Oh, I don't doubt it.</template></category><category><pattern>HONEY  I CAN'T REACH ANY FURTHER  AND YOU CAN'T STAY THERE  ALRIGHT  YOU GOTTA LET GO</pattern><template>You gotta let go. I'll catch you, I promise.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  SEE THAT GUY  I'M GOING TO SWING BY HIM AND YOU'RE JUST GOING TO GRAB HIM</pattern><template>You got it?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU NEED TO BE ON IT</pattern><template>Probably.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WHAT DO WE GOT HERE</pattern><template>His name is an ancient Chinese war mantle Meaning  advisor to the King  South American insurgency tactics Talks like a Bapist preacher There's lots of pagentry going on here... lots of theatre.</template></category><category><pattern>I FEEL SAFER ALREADY WE GOTTA MAKE A DECISION  WE CAN EITHER SAVE THE PRESIDENT OR PEPPER  WE CAN'T DO BOTH</pattern><template>Sir, I have an update from Malibu.</template></category><category><pattern>CLOSE    THE HEAT FROM THE BLAST WAS IN EXCESS OF 3000 DEGREES CELSIUS</pattern><template>Any subjects within 12.5 yards were vaporized instantly.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I'M SORRY  IS THAT ME    YEAH</pattern><template>It's... I mean. I had them do it off a doll that I made, so it's not like it's off a picture. So it's a little bit  Jerry, for a moment, listen to me here.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT    TRUST ME    I'M SURE</pattern><template>We're going out of town.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  HAVE TO CHECK ON THE SUIT    MAKE SURE</pattern><template>Check the heart, check the, check the, is it the brain?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE DOESN'T LIKE IT  SHE PERFERS   SHE'S NOT LIKE THE OTHERS</pattern><template>Come on, let's go to the bedroom.</template></category><category><pattern>BETWEEN THAT AND THE WIDE GAUGE  IT'S GOING TO DIMINISH YOUR FPS AND NOW YOU'RE OUT OF AMMO</pattern><template>What's that thing on your chest?</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  LET'S DO THIS</pattern><template>Dummy Hi Dummy. How did you get that cap on your head?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING OKAY  SIR    COULDN'T BE BETTER</pattern><template>I love you, little one Colonel Rhodes. Glad to see you could make it, son.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HE WAS KIND OF AN IDIOT  MY OLD MAN</pattern><template>I'm sure I'll see you again, Pepper.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'RE YA GONNA DO TO ME    YOU'LL SEE</pattern><template>You're zip tied to a bed.   This.</template></category><category><pattern>OH THIS NEXT BIT MAY INCLUDE THE VICE PRESIDENT AS WELL</pattern><template>Is that important?   Somewhat.   Yeah, a little bit.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT FLOOR YOU GOING TO  PAL</pattern><template>Well now, that is an appropriate question.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M OUT  GIMME  GIMME  YOU GOT AN EXTRA MAGAZINE</pattern><template>They're not universal, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP  PUT IT DOWN  PUT IT DOWN  PUT IT DOWN</pattern><template>See what happens when you hang out with my ex girlfriends?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ASKED YOU  OPEN THE SUIT</pattern><template>I think I may be malfunctioning, sir.   Open eject.</template></category><category><pattern>IN 5  4 YOU SHOULD BE GONE BY NOW  YOU SHOULD HAVE ALREADY BEEN GONE    I'M JUST BEYOND TERRIFIED</pattern><template>Here it comes.</template></category><category><pattern>ON DATE NIGHT</pattern><template>He was just   You mean you Well yeah, I just mean we were just...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY CAN I CARRY    FOUR  SIR</pattern><template>Slow down, slow down.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I JUST UM  GOD  I FORGOT MY OTHER THING SO I'M JUST GONNA</pattern><template>I'm sorry I'm late. I was... what is that?!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT A TECH GENIUS LIKE YOU  JUST TRUST ME  GET DOWN HERE</pattern><template>Flip the screen, then I can see what they're doing.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SO  THE INJECTIONS ARE ADMINISTERED PERIODICALLY</pattern><template>Addiction will not be tolerated and those who cannot regulate will be cut from the program.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT</pattern><template>Yep.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  THE SUIT IS NOT COMBAT READY</pattern><template>That's two.</template></category><category><pattern>HOMELAND SECURITY  WE GOOD HERE</pattern><template>No, we're not good.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  STARK  HO YINSEN</pattern><template>Hey, I finally met a man called Hope.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT GIANT WORMHOLE  IN UM  IN NEW YORK</pattern><template>Does it remind you?</template></category><category><pattern>IT PREDATES ANY KNOWN MANDARIN ATTACK</pattern><template>The incident was the use of a bomb to assist a suicide.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  HANG ON A SECOND</pattern><template>Hello.   You ever look up and everything starts glowing from the inside out, a kind of bright orange Yeah, I've had that. Who is this?   It's me, pal.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A GLORIOUS DAY  SAVIN</pattern><template>This time tomorrow I'll have the West's most powerful leader in one hand And the world's most feared terrorist in the other.</template></category><category><pattern>GLITCHES HAPPEN    OH  IT'S NOT Y2K</pattern><template>Hey, Happy New Year   Happy New Year   Happy New Year Alright, I'll see you in the morning, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>DESPERATION  IF YOU THINK BACK TO SWITZERLAND  YOU SAID YOU'D MEET ME ON THE ROOFTOP  RIGHT</pattern><template>Well for the first 20 minutes, I actually thought you'd show up. For the next hour, I uhh Well I considered taking that one step shortcut to the lobby, if you know I mean Honestly, I'm still trying to figure out what happened to the first mouse.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY   RUDY  TELL ME THAT WAS YOU IN THE SUIT</pattern><template>No, you got yours?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HONEY    I CAN'T SLEEP</pattern><template>You go to bed, I come down here.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCITING  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>Imagining how it got there America, if your president calls me in the next half minute, Tom lives.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  CRAP</pattern><template>Tony   Rudy, tell me that was you in the suit.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT I DO  I FIX THINGS</pattern><template>And all your distractions?</template></category><category><pattern>MY FAULT AGAIN    LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING SWEETHEART  I AM NOT YOUR PERSONAL  I WOULDN'T GO IN THERE FOR TWENTY MINUTES</pattern><template>Now, which one of you is Vanessa?</template></category><category><pattern>INTERNAL SHOTS  TEMPERATURE SPIKES    GET ME EYES ON IT NOW    IMAGE COMING THROUGH NOW  SIR</pattern><template>Is that Rhodes?</template></category><category><pattern>FOR NOW  YES</pattern><template>I'm calling it  Extremis    Well, its   human application   Exactly!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID SO    YES  I DID</pattern><template>What don't you just build something?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I NEED TO BE ALONE WITH YOU  SOMEPLACE NOT HERE    IT'S URGENT</pattern><template>Normally, I'd go for that sort of thing, but now I'm in a committed relationship It's... with her.   Tony, Is somebody there?</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW THAT WE SEEM TO BE BACK  LET'S RECAP SOME OF THE FRIGHTENING DEVELOPMENTS IN THIS STORY</pattern><template>American airways were hijacked.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT YOU    I GOT YOU FIRST</pattern><template>Like I said, we can't stay here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T HIT A BULB FROM THIS DISTANCE</pattern><template>I'm out. Gimme, gimme, you got an extra magazine?</template></category><category><pattern>POWER DOWN</pattern><template>I must have called it in my sleep...</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S MY SANDWICH</pattern><template>Stark Secure Server   Retinal scan verified.</template></category><category><pattern>CLEARLY  YOU WERE WAITING FOR SOMEONE ELSE</pattern><template>Supposed to meet somebody here?</template></category><category><pattern>UH  YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE ISSUED A SECURITY BADGE   HAPPY  IT'S OKAY</pattern><template>Yes?   We're good.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I'M SORRY  THEY'RE ONLY CODED TO ME</pattern><template>What's that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST HOSTING YOU WHILE I FINISHED UP A LITTLE WORK</pattern><template>And yes, I had a quick bite.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU EARNED IT</pattern><template>Hey. Hey! What are you doing out of the corner?</template></category><category><pattern>YES    WE'RE GOOD</pattern><template>You sure?   Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>OH I SEE  SO YOU WERE TRYING TO SAVE STARK    WHEN HE THREATENED US   I TOLD YOU  KILLIAN  WE CAN USE HIM</pattern><template>Pepper, Pepper, Pepper   Look if we want to launch product next year, I need Stark.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE RIGHT  WE NEED BACKUP    YEAH  MUCH</pattern><template>You know what?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY KID  WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE FOR CHRISTMAS</pattern><template>Mr. Stark, I am so sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>GODS  ALIENS  OTHER DIMENSIONS</pattern><template>I'm just a man in a can.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>You're not gonna freak out on me, right?</template></category><category><pattern>READY FOR ANOTHER LESSON</pattern><template>In 1864 in Sand Creek, Colorado, The U.S. military waited until the friendly Cheyenne Braves had all gone hunting Waited to attack and slaughter the families left behind And claim their land 39 hours ago, the Ali Al Salem Air Base in Kuwait was attacked.</template></category><category><pattern>IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT  COLONEL</pattern><template>It is an honor, Mr. President If you're gonna do it, do it.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING ELSE YOU CAN TELL US</pattern><template>Hey Mr. Stark!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE BRAIN  STRANGELY MEMETIC THOUGH  WOULDN'T YOU SAY</pattern><template>Wow, that's amazing!   Thanks, it's mine.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AWARE OF THAT    YOU STILL HAVEN'T EVEN TOLD ME THAT YOU LIKED IT    I DON'T LIKE IT    I ASKED YOU THREE  YOU DON'T LIKE IT</pattern><template>We are leaving the house; that's not even up for discussion.   I said no.   Guys... do we umm...</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST  IS THIS YOUR VAN OR IS ANYONE ELSE GONNA COME IN</pattern><template>No, no, it's just us.   What's your name?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>Perhaps another time?</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE THAT 'CAUSE IT'S ON YOUR T SHIRT</pattern><template>Ladies, follow the mullet. Ladies first.</template></category><category><pattern>IS VERY NORMAL   IT'S A BIG BUNNY  RELAX ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Calm down!   I got this for you.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING</pattern><template>No.   You should have pressed the panic button.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT MEAN</pattern><template>I got you covered.</template></category><category><pattern>STAND DOWN    I'M GOING TO LINGER THANK YOU    RIGHT HERE  OKAY</pattern><template>It's very nice to see you, Killian.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WERE YOU AT THE HOUSE TONIGHT</pattern><template>What was so important that you had to speak to Tony?</template></category><category><pattern>IT MAY NOT SUCCEED IN REVITALIZING THE MARK 42</pattern><template>What's questionable about electricity?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE YOU UP THERE</pattern><template>Damn betcha.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER WAS IN HERE  HE WANTED NO PART OF IT</pattern><template>Clearly, you were waiting for someone else.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  GOOD EVENING   GOOD EVENING    COME ON IN</pattern><template>Maya, run!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID YOU WANTED THE MANDARIN</pattern><template>You're looking right at him.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN</pattern><template>I'll recalibrate the sensors.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT A MINUTE TO LIVE  FILL IT WITH WORDS</pattern><template>It's just a role.  The Mandarin , see, it's not real.</template></category><category><pattern>DISABLE WITH EXTREME PREJUDICE    YES  SIR</pattern><template>What are you waiting for? It's Christmas.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING FANCY  JUST FIVE YEARS IN THE HANDS OF PHYSICAL THERAPISTS AND PLEASE  CALL ME ALDRICH</pattern><template>Uh, you were supposed to be issued a security badge   Happy, it's okay.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST HOLD ON  HOLD ON</pattern><template>Buh bye.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T SAY I NEVER DID NOTHING FOR YOU</pattern><template>Thank you... I mean for understanding.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S OKAY  IT'S OKAY    NO</pattern><template>So if I were to wrap this up tight with a bow or whatever, I guess I'd say my armor was never a distraction or a hobby.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ACTUALLY A GOOD IDEA</pattern><template>Maybe I'll build one.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE WORK GUYS  EXCELLENT</pattern><template>Good team effort all around. Go us.</template></category><category><pattern>I BROKE THE CRAYON    ARE YOU OKAY  MR  STARK</pattern><template>Take it easy. Tony...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES IT POWER</pattern><template>Oh my God!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  DEATH BY OIL</pattern><template>Broadcast will commence shortly. Take final positions.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST GOING TO TRY TO GET MY BEEF WET REAL QUICK IF YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKIN' ABOUT</pattern><template>I'll see you up there!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  WHICH ONE OF YOU IS VANESSA</pattern><template>Ah, Nessie Did you know that fortune cookies aren't even Chinese?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT    IT'S A GLITCH IN MY WORK</pattern><template>She was just talking about it.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  I THINK HE WAS TRYING TO SAY  I WANT MY GODDAMN FILE   IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT KID</pattern><template>Remember what I told you about bullies?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST A MAN IN A CAN</pattern><template>The only reason I haven't cracked up is probably because you've moved in.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH I WILL</pattern><template>Alright, let's do this.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK GREAT    YOU LOOK REALLY GREAT</pattern><template>God, you look great. I... I... I can't...</template></category><category><pattern>PINCH MY ARM  I CAN TAKE IT  PINCH ME</pattern><template>What is that?   The primary somatosensory cortex It's the brain's pain center, but this...</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO    IS THIS FOREHEAD OF SECURITY</pattern><template>What? You know, look, I got a real job. What do you want? I'm working; I got something going on here.   What? Harassing interns?</template></category><category><pattern>YUP  WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT AT DINNER</pattern><template>Come on, a little more, baby.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>That's my favorite kind, a winning combo.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK DAMN GOOD  MR</pattern><template>President, but I'm gonna need that suit back.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS SENDS A BETTER MESSAGE</pattern><template>So what's really going on? With Mandarin Seriously, can we talk about this guy?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEY'RE ACTUALLY AN AMERICAN INVENTION WHICH IS WHY THEY'RE HOLLOW  FULL OF LIES  AND LEAVE A BAD TASTE IN THE MOUTH MY DISCIPLES JUST DESTROYED ANOTHER CHEAP AMERICAN KNOCK OFF THE CHINESE THEATER  MR  PRESIDENT  I KNOW THIS MUST BE GETTING FRUSTRATING BUT THIS SEASON OF TERROR IS DRAWING TO A CLOSE AND DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>the big one is coming: your graduation.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAS THE LOCATION</pattern><template>Who asked you? Open the suit.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GET UP</pattern><template>Is it hot there?</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  I DON'T WORK FOR YOU  AND I DON'T TRUST THIS GUY</pattern><template>He's got another guy with him; he's shifty.</template></category><category><pattern>NO    YOU SHOULD HAVE PRESSED THE PANIC BUTTON</pattern><template>Well I panicked, but then I handled it.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE FINE</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST STOLE A PONCHO FROM A WOODEN INDIAN</pattern><template>Let's get you comfy.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I'M ON IT  I'LL HAVE SECURITY LOCK IT DOWN  IF NEED BE  THEY CAN HAVE F22S IN THE AIR IN 30 SECONDS  THANK YOU  COLONEL</pattern><template>Rhodes and Stark out.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVEN'T EVEN TALKED SALARY YET</pattern><template>What kind of perk package are you thinking of?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO PHRASE IT UNTIL NOW</pattern><template>My name is Tony Stark and I'm not afraid of you I know that you're a coward so I've decided That you just died, pal.</template></category><category><pattern>OH YEAH  YOU'RE THE BEST</pattern><template>Yeah, so I run his credentials, I make him.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU GOT YOURS</pattern><template>Uh, um, kind of. Main house as fast as you can, Somebody I'd like you to meet You, you. Move! Get out!</template></category><category><pattern>SIT</pattern><template>My name is Trevor, Trevor Slattery.   What are you?</template></category><category><pattern>AM I GONNA BE OKAY</pattern><template>No, you're in a relationship with me, everything will never be okay.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY TIPPING YOUR WAY A LITTLE BIT</pattern><template>Why don't you dress like this at home?</template></category><category><pattern>SIR</pattern><template>Sir!   Alright, kill the alarm.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL YOU KNOW HOW HE GETS</pattern><template>Keep your appointment tonight and call me when it's done.</template></category><category><pattern>INCLUDING CHAD DAVIS    YEA</pattern><template>Doesn't make sense.</template></category><category><pattern>THE NUMBER FOR THIS TELEPHONE IS IN YOUR CELL PHONE</pattern><template>Exciting, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I PANICKED  BUT THEN I HANDLED IT</pattern><template>Just like old times, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE</pattern><template>Do you need to be on it?</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE  CAN YOU STOP</pattern><template>Remember when I told you that I have an anxiety issue?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON MAN  THIS ISN'T A GOOD LOOK  OPEN UP</pattern><template>Sorry, I gotta split.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS A COCOON</pattern><template>And now, I'm a changed man.</template></category><category><pattern>THE  BRAVES  WERE AWAY</pattern><template>President Ellis, you continue to resist my attempts to educate you, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  IT'S MY SUIT AND I CAN'T    I'M NOT GONNA</pattern><template>Oh God, not again.   Tony Are you having another attack? I didn't even mention New York.   Right, and then you just said it, by name, while denying having said it.</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN'T MAKE SENSE</pattern><template>Think about it. Six dead, only five shadows.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST SCARED THE DEVIL OUT OF ME  I THOUGHT YOU WERE   I WAS DEAD  WHY  BECAUSE I FELL TWO HUNDRED FEET</pattern><template>Who's the hot mess now?</template></category><category><pattern>THE MAN SAYS NO   IMMEDIATELY AND INDEFINITELY</pattern><template>Great idea. Let's go.   I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON  FILL ME IN</pattern><template>For real?   Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  SIR  IT'S IN MIAMI</pattern><template>Okay, kid, I'm going to have to walk you through rebooting Jarvis' speech drive, but not right now. Harley, where is he really?</template></category><category><pattern>HAPPY   THE CAR IS READY    IF YOU'RE READY TO GO</pattern><template>Yes, I just um, God, I forgot my other thing so I'm just gonna...</template></category><category><pattern>FINE WITH ME</pattern><template>What is your name?   Erin.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'RE WE TALKIN'  THE FAR EAST  EUROPE  NORTH AFRICA  IRAN  PAKISTAN  SYRIA  WHERE IS IT</pattern><template>Actually, sir, it's in Miami.</template></category><category><pattern>SLOW IT DOWN JUST A    LITTLE BIT</pattern><template>Cool it, will you Jarvis?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES    THAT'S RISKY AT LEAST LET ME GET YOU LIKE A HAZMAT SUIT OR A GEIGER COUNTER OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT BUSTED    THIS IS A NEW LEVEL OF LAME</pattern><template>Sorry.   You ate without me, already?</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE  I'M RIGHT BEHIND  GET HER  I'M GOING TO FIND A WAY AROUND</pattern><template>Stop stopping! Get her; get outside! Go!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT THIS CRATER REMINDS ME OF</pattern><template>I have no idea; I don't care.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S NOT  QUITE FRANKLY</pattern><template>It's American business.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GET YOU COMFY</pattern><template>You happy now?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL HAVE A GOOD EVENING</pattern><template>Ms. Davis, Mind if I join you?</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T NOTICE THAT  AT ALL</pattern><template>You experience things and then they're over and you still can't explain them.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M COLD I CAN TELL  YOU KNOW HOW I CAN TELL</pattern><template>'Cause we're connected.</template></category><category><pattern>HAPPY  LEAVE HER FICUS ALONE    NO  SERIOUSLY  DON'T   AND YOU'RE STARTING WITH PLANTS</pattern><template>For now, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD EVENING  SIR</pattern><template>Welcome aboard, Mr. President.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE THING ABOUT SMART GUYS WE ALWAYS COVER OUR ASS</pattern><template>You're welcome!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  NO  AN UNDERSTUDY  ABSOLUTELY NOT</pattern><template>Don't hurt me please! I'm an actor.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD TEAM EFFORT ALL AROUND  GO US</pattern><template>Alright, Jarvis, but it's only half done, we still gotta get Pepp  That came out of nowhere.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I WILL  BUT YOU CAN FIX IT  RIGHT</pattern><template>I'm going to take the suit up to base camp, and I want Potts with me.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I THINK IT'S A LITTLE ABOVE YOUR PAY GRADE  SHERIFF</pattern><template>Yeah, well, why don't you get on the horn to Nashville and upgrade me?</template></category><category><pattern>OH SHOULDERS  A LITTLE NAUGHTY  NAUGHTY GIRL</pattern><template>I don't want to harp on this, but did you like the custom rabbit?</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER A BRIEF SOIREE IN AN AFGHAN CAVE  I SAID  GOODBYE  TO THE PARTY SCENE</pattern><template>I forgot that night in Switzerland.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  SO SHE'S MEETING UP WITH THIS SCIENTIST</pattern><template>rich guy, handsome I couldn't make his face at first And you know I'm good with faces.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S IN IT FOR ME    SALVATION  WHAT'S HIS NAME</pattern><template>Who?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS TIME TOMORROW I'LL HAVE THE WEST'S MOST POWERFUL LEADER IN ONE HAND AND THE WORLD'S MOST FEARED TERRORIST IN THE OTHER</pattern><template>I'll own the War on Terror Creates supply and demand for you and your brothers and sisters.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT THE MANDARIN  ARE YOU  ARE YOU</pattern><template>You don't remember.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOING TO BE A  NO   ALDRICH</pattern><template>as much as I'd like to help you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THE HOT MESS NOW</pattern><template>Still debatable.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING  YOU'RE GOING TO BREAK HIS FINGER</pattern><template>He's in pain; he's been injured. Leave him alone.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE YOU TO OUR GUEST  DOCTOR WU</pattern><template>Oh this guy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'D YOU SEE    TOO FAST  NOTHING  HERE WE GO</pattern><template>Three guys, one girl, all armed.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT THERE'S FINE</pattern><template>You're not the Mandarin, are you? Are you?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO BED    HOLD ON  COME ON  PEP  HEY  I ADMIT IT  MY FAULT  SORRY</pattern><template>I'm a piping hot mess. It's been going on for a while...</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT NOTHING</pattern><template>Jarvis, subject at my 12 o'clock is not a target, disengage!</template></category><category><pattern>PEP  I GOT YOU  RELAX  I GOT YOU  JUST LOOK AT ME</pattern><template>Honey, I can't reach any further, and you can't stay there, alright? You gotta let go.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU EVER HEARD OF AN ELEPHANT GRAVEYARD  WELL  TWO YEARS AGO  THE ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM WAS THIS SHIP</pattern><template>This is the Roxxon Norco.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT THIS TIME  NOT THE FACE</pattern><template>Phew, it's good to be back. Hello, by the way.</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE MISFITS  CRIPPLES</pattern><template>you are the next iteration of human evolution.</template></category><category><pattern>HEARTBREAKER  HELP RED SNAPPER OUT  WILL YA</pattern><template>Nice timing.</template></category><category><pattern>LET HIM GO</pattern><template>Hold on, hold on. Maya   I said let him go What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>THE  CLEAN SLATE  PROTOCOL  SIR</pattern><template>Screw it, it's Christmas. Yes, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH OKAY    THAT IS SO MUCH BETTER THAN IRON PATRIOT</pattern><template>That ain't gonna cut it.</template></category><category><pattern>SAVIN  I'VE ACQUIRED THE PATRIOT ARMOR</pattern><template>You want this suit? You're going ot have to pry my cold, dead body out of it.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS   DROP MY NEEDLE CRAP ALRIGHT  I THINK WE GOT THIS  SEND THEM ALL</pattern><template>Probably just a little fast... slow it down.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME    YES    MISS POTTS  YOUR FOUR O'CLOCK IS HERE</pattern><template>Did you clear this four o'clock with me?</template></category><category><pattern>PUBLIC EXECUTION</pattern><template>Yeah, death by oil.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS TO YOU  NOT ONE FAT CAT SAW A DAY IN COURT</pattern><template>What do you want from me?</template></category><category><pattern>MR  STARK</pattern><template>Our sources are telling us that this is another Mandarin attack.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY NEED TO LOOK STRONG</pattern><template>Stopping the Mandarin is a priority, but it's not   It's not superhero business.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE HAD A RISE IN STAFF COMPLAINTS OF 300 PERCENT THANK YOU    THAT'S NOT A COMPLIMENT</pattern><template>That's not a compliment ? It is a compliment!</template></category><category><pattern>ESSENTIALLY  YOU'RE HACKING INTO THE GENETIC OPERATING SYSTEM OF A LIVING ORGANISM</pattern><template>Exactly.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S 13  NO  I NEED YOUR HELP    WHAT FOR  WHY NOW</pattern><template>Because I read the papers, and, frankly, I don't think you'll last the week.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A DECENT BATCH</pattern><template>Don't say I never did nothing for you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND PASSWORD PLEASE</pattern><template>Well, look, I gotta change it every time you hack in, Tony   It's not the eighties, nobody says  hack  anymore, give me your login.</template></category><category><pattern>THREE GUYS  ONE GIRL  ALL ARMED</pattern><template>God, I'd kill for some armor right now.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I WANTED TO REPAY YOU FOR THE SAME GIFT YOU SO GRACIOUSLY IMPARTED TO ME DESPERATION  NOW  THIS IS LIVE</pattern><template>I'm not sure if you can tell But at this moment the body is trying to decide whether to accept Extremis or just give up And if it gives up, I have to say the denotation is quite spectactular But until that point, it's really just a lot of pain.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE THE MOST GIFTED WOMAN I'VE EVER MET</pattern><template>Wow...   In Switzerland.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ALL YOUR DISTRACTIONS</pattern><template>Uh, I'm gonna shave them down a little bit.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA FIND A HEAVY DUTY COMSAT RIGHT NOW  I NEED YOUR LOGIN</pattern><template>Same as it's always been, War Machine 68.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO PENTAGON; IT'S JUST YOU AND ME</pattern><template>And on the off chance you're a man, here's my home address: 10880, Malibu Port, 90265.</template></category><category><pattern>GIMME SOME GOOD NEWS MAN</pattern><template>I think they all made it.   Thank God.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU STILL SEE STRAIGHT    SORT OF</pattern><template>That means you're fine, give me Jarvis.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE PTSD</pattern><template>I don't think so.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I AM GONNA COMPLAIN ABOUT NOW</pattern><template>Well, it's me. I'll think of something.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  UM  KIND OF  MAIN HOUSE AS FAST AS YOU CAN  SOMEBODY I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET YOU  YOU  MOVE  GET OUT</pattern><template>The room is secure. I have eyes on the Mandarin.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL RECALIBRATE THE SENSORS</pattern><template>Just let me catch my breath, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY I'M LATE  I WAS    WHAT IS THAT</pattern><template>You're wearing this in the house now?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ALL YOU GOT  CHEAP TRICK AND A CHEESY ONE LINER</pattern><template>Sweetheart, that could be the name of my autobiography.</template></category><category><pattern>AS PROMISED  I GOT PEPPER SORTED OUT; IT TOOK SOME TINKERING</pattern><template>But then I thought to myself,  Why stop there?  Of course, there are people who say progress is dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>AW  COME ON</pattern><template>Mr. President! Just hold on, alright? I'm coming.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE RIGHT ON ME</pattern><template>What the hell was that?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF I DO THAT</pattern><template>That's the brain, strangely memetic though, wouldn't you say?</template></category><category><pattern>TONY STARK IS IN MY VAN    KEEP IT DOWN</pattern><template>Tony Stark is in my van!   No, he's not.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  LET'S GO TO THE BEDROOM</pattern><template>Happy, leave her ficus alone.   No, seriously, don't   And you're starting with plants?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU PLEASE STATE YOUR NAME FOR THE CAMERA</pattern><template>Ellen Brandt.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE TIMING</pattern><template>Oh yeah, that's awesome. Give me a suit, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE LEAVING THE HOUSE; THAT'S NOT EVEN UP FOR DISCUSSION    I SAID NO    GUYS    DO WE UMM</pattern><template>What?   Do we need to worry about that?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT</pattern><template>Your fault, you spazzed me out.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE THAT  NAILED IT</pattern><template>Yeah, you really killed the glass.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST LET ME CATCH MY BREATH  OKAY</pattern><template>Don't go, alright? Pepper?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I MOVED ON</pattern><template>After a brief soiree in an Afghan cave, I said  Goodbye  to the party scene.</template></category><category><pattern>SUPPORT BLUE 0  UNLESS THE MANDARIN'S NEXT ATTACK ON THE U S  INVOLVES CHEAPLY MADE SPORTSWEAR  I THINK YOU MESSED UP AGAIN</pattern><template>Yes, you're free, if you weren't before. Yes ma'am Iron Patriot on the job, happy to help, no need to thank me, it's my pleasure.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH HAPPENS  DADS LEAVE  NO NEED TO BE A PUSSY ABOUT IT  HERE'S WHAT I NEED: A LAPTOP  A DIGITAL WATCH  A CELL PHONE  THE PNEUMATIC ACTUATOR FROM YOUR BAZOOKA OVER THERE  A MAP OF TOWN  A BIG SPRING  AND A TUNAFISH SANDWICH</pattern><template>What's in it for me?   Salvation. What's his name?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>Is that?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS A GREAT NIGHT    WELL    YOU KNOW   YEAH</pattern><template>You have saved yourself a world of pain.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL LEAVE THE DOOR UNLOCKED</pattern><template>That's what you wanted, right?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY REASON I HAVEN'T CRACKED UP IS PROBABLY BECAUSE YOU'VE MOVED IN</pattern><template>Which is great. I love you; I'm lucky.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A SHAME; I WOULD HAVE CAUGHT HER</pattern><template>Well here we are, on the roof Mark 42 inbound.   Well I'll be damned.</template></category><category><pattern>ALDRICH KILLIAN  I'M A BIG FAN OF YOUR WORK</pattern><template>My work?   Who is he? He means me.</template></category><category><pattern>CUSTOM MADE TERROR THREAT   YES</pattern><template>Yes, his think tank thinked it up, the pathology of the serial killer The manipulation of Western iconography Ready for another lesson? Blah blah blah.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO POLITICS HERE; IT'S JUST GOOD  OLD FASHIONED REVENGE</pattern><template>There's no Pentagon; it's just you and me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU START WITH SOMETHING PURE  SOMETHING EXCITING THEN COME THE MISTAKES THE COMPROMISES WE CREATE OUR OWN DEMONS</pattern><template>It's great to see you.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE WE STILL AT  DING DONG</pattern><template>We're supposed to be on total security lockdown.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT PEOPLE SAID THESE SHADOWS ARE LIKE THE MARK OF SOULS GONE TO HEAVEN EXCEPT THE BOMB GUY  HE WENT TO HELL ON ACCOUNT OF HE DIDN'T GET A SHADOW</pattern><template>That's why there's only five   Do you buy that?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT WHAT  YOU WATCHING THEM</pattern><template>Flip the screen and then we can get started.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE NOT</pattern><template>Oh my god.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MUCH DID YOU HAVE    TWO OR THREE BOWLS</pattern><template>Can you still see straight?   Sort of.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS SO IMPORTANT THAT YOU HAD TO SPEAK TO TONY</pattern><template>I think that my boss is working for the Mandarin.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY THERE'S ONLY FIVE   DO YOU BUY THAT</pattern><template>That's what everyone says.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT HIM  THE MANDARIN  THE REAL GUY  WHERE</pattern><template>Where's the Mandarin?! Where is he?!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A ELECTROMAGNET  YOU SHOULD KNOW  YOU'VE GOT A BOX OF THEM RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>What does it power?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS SELFISH AND STUPID AND IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN</pattern><template>Why were you at the house tonight?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOOD</pattern><template>Stay down.</template></category><category><pattern>AS MUCH AS I'D LIKE TO HELP YOU</pattern><template>I can't say that I'm not disappointed, but as my father used to say  Failure is the fog through which we glimpse triumph.  It's very deep, and I have no idea what it means.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HOW IS PRESIDENT ELLIS RESPONDING</pattern><template>By taking the guy they call  War Machine  and giving him a paint job The same suit but painted red, white, and blue, look at that And they've also renamed him Iron Patriot You know, just in case the paint was too subtle It tested well with focus groups, alright?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS JUST TALKING ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Glitches happen.   Oh, it's not Y2K...</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER WHAT HAPPENED IN NEW YORK    ALIENS  COME ON</pattern><template>They need to look strong.</template></category><category><pattern>SIX PEOPLE DIED  RIGHT    YES</pattern><template>Including Chad Davis?   Yea.</template></category><category><pattern>WAR MACHINE ROX  WITH AN X  ALL CAPS</pattern><template>Yeah okay.   That is so much better than Iron Patriot.</template></category><category><pattern>BRACE YOURSELF</pattern><template>You look damn good, Mr.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS SUPPORT TEAM BLUE 0  SENDING COORDINATES FOR SUSPECTED MANDARIN BROADCAST POINT OF ORIGIN</pattern><template>Copy.</template></category><category><pattern>STUCK  FEEL A LITTLE STUCK</pattern><template>Like a little turtle, cooking in his little turtle suit?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'M SORRY IN ADVANCE BECAUSE</pattern><template>I can't come home yet I need to find this guy.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GO  ALRIGHT  PEPPER</pattern><template>I'm going to sleep downstairs. Tinker with that.</template></category><category><pattern>MY NAME IS TREVOR  TREVOR SLATTERY    WHAT ARE YOU</pattern><template>What're you a decoy? You're a double, right?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY MR  STARK</pattern><template>When is somebody going to kill this guy? Just sayin'.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW I THINK I UNDERSTAND WHY YOU DON'T WANT TO GIVE UP THE SUITS</pattern><template>What I am gonna complain about now?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL ATTEMPTS TO FIND THE MANDARIN HAVE SO FAR PROVED UNSUCCESSFUL</pattern><template>Central to my administration's response to this terrorist event is a newly minted resource.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE AN ISSUE  I'M CHASING BAD GUYS  TRYING TO GRAPPLE WITH SOMETHING FROM SOME HARD CRYPT DATA FILES</pattern><template>I don't have enough juice.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW WAS IT    EDIFYING    UNINTELLIGIBLE</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>REGARD THE HUMAN BRAIN UH  WAIT  HOLD ON  HOLD ON; THAT'S  THAT'S THE UNIVERSE  MY BAD</pattern><template>But if I do that...</template></category><category><pattern>ALDRICH KILLIAN  WHAT ARE YOU CHECKING UP ON ME</pattern><template>Happy was concerned   No, you're spying on me.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO IMMEDIATELY ALERT THAT PLANE</pattern><template>Okay, I'm on it. I'll have security lock it down. If need be, they can have F22s in the air in 30 seconds. Thank you, Colonel.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID THAT</pattern><template>A quaint military church, filled with wives and children of course The soliders were out on manuvers.</template></category><category><pattern>START TITAN AND GO WHITE  STAMP DATE AND TIME</pattern><template>Mark 42 autonomous prehensile propulsion suit test Initialize sequence.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  PRESIDENT ONLY TWO LESSONS REMAIN</pattern><template>I intend to finish this before Christmas morning.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M CONCERNED ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>You gonna come at me like that?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SURE    YES</pattern><template>Stand down.   I'm going to linger Thank you.   Right here, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO IDEA; I DON'T CARE</pattern><template>That giant wormhole, in um, in New York.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  MISS POTTS IS CLEAR OF THE STRUCTURE</pattern><template>Jarvis, where's my flight power?!</template></category><category><pattern>HE CREATED YOU    HE CREATED ME</pattern><template>Custom made terror threat   Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>TRY THE JET STREAM  SPEAKING OF WHICH  GO FISH</pattern><template>Walk away from that, you son of a bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU'RE IN A DUNGEON  I'M FREE TO GO    YEAH</pattern><template>A lot's happened Tony and I'm close.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THOSE</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE COMPILED A MANDARIN DATABASE FOR YOU  SIR  DRAWN FROM S H I E L D   F B I   AND C I A  INTERCEPTS</pattern><template>Initiating virtual crime scene reconstruction.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ONE</pattern><template>Sir, the suit is not combat ready.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW  I'M A CHANGED MAN</pattern><template>You can take away my house, All my tricks and toys One thing you can't take away...</template></category><category><pattern>I GAVE A SPEECH</pattern><template>How was it?   Edifying.   Unintelligible.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T SAY THAT I'M NOT DISAPPOINTED  BUT AS MY FATHER USED TO SAY  FAILURE IS THE FOG THROUGH WHICH WE GLIMPSE TRIUMPH   IT'S VERY DEEP  AND I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IT MEANS</pattern><template>Well, he was kind of an idiot, my old man.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN HELP ME FIX IT</pattern><template>Did I do that?</template></category><category><pattern>WATCHING YOUR FAVORITE CHICK FLICK MAYBE</pattern><template>Yeah, a little movie called  The Party's Over  Starring you and your junkie girlfriend, and here's the ticket No kidding... that doesn't belong to you.</template></category><category><pattern>IT DOES SAY MIAMI  FLORIDA   OKAY  FIRST THINGS FIRST  I NEED THE ARMOR</pattern><template>Where are we at with it?   Uh, it's not charging.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T REMEMBER</pattern><template>Why I am not surprised?   Don't take it personally, I don't remember what I had for breakfast.</template></category><category><pattern>MS  DAVIS  MIND IF I JOIN YOU</pattern><template>Free country.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL DO</pattern><template>And so, as Christmas morning began, my journey had reached its end.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT YOU WANTED  RIGHT</pattern><template>Bill me.</template></category><category><pattern>ADMIT IT: YOU NEED ME  WE'RE CONNECTED</pattern><template>What I need is for you to go home, be with your mom, keep your mouth shut, and protect the suit.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  YOU KNOW WHAT  I WAS HOPING TO DO THIS THE SMART WAY  BUT UH  THE FUN WAY'S ALWAYS GOOD DEPUTY  GET THIS WOMAN AND  HEY HOT WINGS  YOU WANNA PARTY  YOU AND ME  LET'S GO</pattern><template>Crazy, huh?   Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU EXPERIENCE THINGS AND THEN THEY'RE OVER AND YOU STILL CAN'T EXPLAIN THEM</pattern><template>Gods, aliens, other dimensions...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT    AS A WEAPON YOU'RE NOT THE PERSON WHO CALLED ME AFTER ALL  ARE YOU</pattern><template>Actually, I am.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW  YOU'VE MISSED ME AGAIN YOU KNOW WHO I AM  YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE I AM AND YOU'LL NEVER SEE ME COMING</pattern><template>...and now that we seem to be back, let's recap some of the frightening developments in this story.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IF YOU STILL WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT  I SUGGEST WE GET OURSELVES SOMEPLACE SAFE YOUR BOSS WORKS FOR THE MANDARIN YOU THINK  BUT TONY SAYS YOU'RE A BOTANIST THAT FIGURES  WHAT I ACTUALLY AM IS A BIOLOGICAL DNA CODER RUNNING A TEAM OF 40 OUT OF A PRIVATELY FUNDED THINK TANK  BUT SURE YOU CAN CALL ME A  BOTANIST  THIS BOSS OF YOURS  DOES HE HAVE A NAME</pattern><template>Yeah, Aldrich Killian.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN CAN WE TALK ABOUT NEW YORK</pattern><template>Maybe never, relax about it.</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME BACK TO THE LAND OF THE LIVING    WE BELIEVE YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE DRAWN INTO THE MANDARIN CAMPAIGN  AND WE'VE GOT TO GET YOU SOMEWHERE SAFE AS SOON AS POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Mr. Stark, I'm about to eat honey roast ham surrounded by the agency's finest.</template></category><category><pattern>MICRO REPEATER IMPLANTING SEQUENCE COMPLETE</pattern><template>As you wish, sir. I've also prepared a safety briefing for you to enitrely ignore.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN  READY</pattern><template>Pep, I got you. Relax, I got you. Just look at me.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  THAT'S AMAZING    THANKS  IT'S MINE</pattern><template>What?   This... you're inside my head.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW I'M SHORTER IN PERSON  I'M A BIT SMALL  EVERYONE SAYS THAT  BUT  UH  HEY  IF YOU'RE HERE TO ARREST ME  THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE WHO I'D LIKE TO RAT ON HERE'S HOW IT WORKS  YOU TELL HIM WHERE PEPPER IS AND HE'LL STOP DOING IT</pattern><template>Stop what? Well, I understand I do not know (Piper) but I know the plan Occur   Do you know what who did Bhlta?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S INCREDIBLE</pattern><template>Essentially, you're hacking into the genetic operating system of a living organism.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU NOT TOUCH MY PLANT  IT'S NOT</pattern><template>she doesn't like it. She perfers   She's not like the others.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  YOU SHOULD TAKE MORE OF AN INTEREST IN WHAT'S GOING ON HERE</pattern><template>This woman is the best thing that ever happened to you And you're just ignoring her.   A giant brain?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  HIS THINK TANK THINKED IT UP  THE PATHOLOGY OF THE SERIAL KILLER THE MANIPULATION OF WESTERN ICONOGRAPHY READY FOR ANOTHER LESSON  BLAH BLAH BLAH</pattern><template>Of course, it was my performance that brought the Mandarin to life.</template></category><category><pattern>OH GOD  NOT AGAIN    TONY ARE YOU HAVING ANOTHER ATTACK  I DIDN'T EVEN MENTION NEW YORK    RIGHT  AND THEN YOU JUST SAID IT  BY NAME  WHILE DENYING HAVING SAID IT</pattern><template>Okay, um, uh Oh God, what am I gonna do?</template></category><category><pattern>HMM  SPORTS BRA  THE WHOLE DEAL</pattern><template>You know I think I understand why you don't want to give up the suits.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE STILL GOING DOWN  PAL</pattern><template>Okay, Trevor, what'd you tell him?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  BACK TO BUSINESS  WHERE WERE WE</pattern><template>The guy who died... relatives?</template></category><category><pattern>DID I DO THAT</pattern><template>Yes.   I remember the night, not the morning Is this what you've been chasing around?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAY HIS LEAR WAS THE TOAST OF CROYDON  WHEREVER THAT IS</pattern><template>Anyway, the point is ever since that big dude with the hammer fell out of the sky Subtlety's kinda had its day What's next for you in your world?</template></category><category><pattern>FREEZE</pattern><template>Don't move.   You got me.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  I'LL CALL YOU</pattern><template>I am titillated by the notion of working with you.</template></category><category><pattern>GARY    GARY    OH WOW</pattern><template>Right there's fine. I get a lot of this, it's okay.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  A LITTLE MORE  BABY</pattern><template>Is this guy bothering you?</template></category><category><pattern>THE INCIDENT WAS THE USE OF A BOMB TO ASSIST A SUICIDE</pattern><template>The heat signature is remarkably similar.</template></category><category><pattern>YES    I REMEMBER THE NIGHT  NOT THE MORNING IS THIS WHAT YOU'VE BEEN CHASING AROUND</pattern><template>You don't remember?   I can't help you.</template></category><category><pattern>DENTRA DEGREE VITALIZATION DISEASE PREVENTION EVEN LIMB REGROWTH</pattern><template>You're the most gifted woman I've ever met.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON  WITH MANDARIN SERIOUSLY  CAN WE TALK ABOUT THIS GUY</pattern><template>It's classified information, Tony.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WE'RE NOT GOOD</pattern><template>I need a little more information than that.</template></category><category><pattern>AS YOU WISH  SIR  I'VE ALSO PREPARED A SAFETY BRIEFING FOR YOU TO ENITRELY IGNORE</pattern><template>Which I will.</template></category><category><pattern>I WONDER WHO I'M CALLING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Oh, that's the Vice President.</template></category><category><pattern>1200CCS  A DOSE HALF OF THIS SIZE AND I'M DEAD IT'S TIMES LIKE THIS MY TEMPER IS TESTED SOMEWHAT MAYA  GIVE ME THE INJECTOR</pattern><template>If I die Killian, what happens to your soldiers?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S BETTER    THIS WEEK YOU ALMOST BOUGHT IT  DIDN'T YOU</pattern><template>This is what I'm talking about, the glitch.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU JUST NOD OFF</pattern><template>No, the lovely speedboat!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  WHY DON'T YOU GET ON THE HORN TO NASHVILLE AND UPGRADE ME</pattern><template>Alright, you know what, I was hoping to do this the smart way, but uh, The fun way's always good Deputy, get this woman and  Hey hot wings, you wanna party? You and me, let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  I THREATENED A TERRORIST  WHO IS THAT</pattern><template>There's only so much I can do, sir, when you give the world's press your home address.</template></category><category><pattern>AND OLD GIRLFRIENDS   SHE'S NOT REALLY</pattern><template>No, not really. It was just one night.</template></category><category><pattern>MARK 42 AUTONOMOUS PREHENSILE PROPULSION SUIT TEST INITIALIZE SEQUENCE</pattern><template>Jarvis   drop my needle Crap Alright, I think we got this. Send them all.</template></category><category><pattern>DID I LIKE IT    NAILED IT  RIGHT    WOW</pattern><template>I appreciate the thought very much. So why don't you lift up that facemask and give me a kiss.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  TREVOR  WHAT'D YOU TELL HIM</pattern><template>I didn't tell him anything.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T MY IDEA    OKAY  SO YOU TOOK KILLIAN'S CARD I TOOK HIS MONEY   AND HERE YOU ARE 13 YEARS LATER IN A DUNGEON NO    YEAH</pattern><template>No, you're in a dungeon. I'm free to go.   Yeah...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE GOT LIKE FIVE OF THEM  ALRIGHT  HERE'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO  I'M GONNA SPOT  READY</pattern><template>What'd you see?   Too fast, nothing. Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER THAT GAME CALLED BARREL OF MONKEYS</pattern><template>That's what we're going to do.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I'LL BET NONE OF THOSE IDIOTS EVER HAD TO LIVE WITH A CHEST FULL OF SHRAPNEL</pattern><template>And now... neither will I.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE THE IMMINENT ARRIVAL OF YOUR BOUNCING  BADASS BABY BROTHER</pattern><template>Start titan and go white. Stamp date and time.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS WORTH A SHOT</pattern><template>What happened to the picture?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE THING WAS  HE NEEDED SOMEONE TO TAKE CREDIT FOR SOME  ACCIDENTAL EXPLOSIONS   HE</pattern><template>Killian?   Killian.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE'S A LITTLE HOLIDAY GREETING I'VE BEEN WANTING TO SEND TO THE MANDARIN</pattern><template>I just didn't know how to phrase it until now.</template></category><category><pattern>TONY   WHAT'D YOU SAY</pattern><template>Sorry. Have to check on the suit... make sure...</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  LET ME SHOW YOU  HOLD ON  SEE</pattern><template>Look at what? You watching them?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GOING TO SHOW YOU MY  TOWN</pattern><template>Mr. Stark, Ho Yinsen.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP YOUR APPOINTMENT TONIGHT AND CALL ME WHEN IT'S DONE</pattern><template>Alright everybody. No talking and no eye contact, unless you wanna get shot in the face.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY    ARE YOU</pattern><template>Don't worry about it; I'll fix it.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU'RE IN A RELATIONSHIP WITH ME  EVERYTHING WILL NEVER BE OKAY</pattern><template>But I think I can figure this out, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR RE DESIGN  YOUR BIG RE BRAND  THAT WAS AIM  RIGHT</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>CLEARLY SOMEBODY IS TRYING TO HIDE SOMETHING</pattern><template>Excuse me.   Yes?   Miss Potts, your four o'clock is here.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE OFFICIAL STORY HERE  WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>I guess this guy named Chad Davis, used to live roundabouts Won a bunch of medals in the army, One day, folks said he went crazy and made, you know, a bomb Then he blew himself up right here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT A STEALTH MODE    COOL  RIGHT</pattern><template>That's actually a good idea.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN'T ALLOW TERRORISTS TO DICTATE  I HAVE TO MAKE THIS CALL</pattern><template>I'd strongly advise against that.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS ESSENTIALLY AN EMPTY SLOT  AND WHAT THIS TELLS US IS THAT OUR MIND  OUR ENTIRE DNA IN FACT  IS DESTINED TO BE UPGRADED    WOW</pattern><template>Hello?   Is this forehead of Security?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S COMPLICATED  HEY  IT'S COMPLICATED  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>It is?   It's complicated.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THE LOVELY SPEEDBOAT</pattern><template>And the thing was, he needed someone To take credit for some  accidental explosions   He ?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO</pattern><template>The  clean slate  protocol, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST LOOK ON THE SCREEN AND TELL ME WHERE IT IS</pattern><template>It does say Miami, Florida   Okay, first things first, I need the armor.</template></category><category><pattern>MEET THOMAS RICHARDS</pattern><template>Good strong name, good strong job.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THEY COMING BACK  THE ALIENS</pattern><template>Maybe, can you stop?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SOMETHING LIKE THAT</pattern><template>You know everybody needs a hobby.</template></category><category><pattern>JARVIS  SUBJECT AT MY 12 O'CLOCK IS NOT A TARGET  DISENGAGE</pattern><template>What? Oh, what, are you mad at me?</template></category></AIML>