<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>WELL  UNFORTUNATELY  00:14:26:24 00:14:31:22  I WANTED TO SEE WHO IS THE DRAGON WARRIOR THIS IS AN INTERESTING MILESTONE ARE YOU REFERRING TO ME</pattern><template>is    from?    you    I?    universe send us Dragon Warrior Why?    Why?    Why?</template></category><category><pattern>SHIVA) LOVED (TAI LOONG) ALSO DID NOT LIKE)  ONE OF THE PRE   OR TIMELY AND NOW HAS THE OPPORTUNITY TO CORRECT THINGS  TRAINS COMBATANTS FOR THE REAL DRAGON AND HAS BEEN SUSPENDED WITH YOU BANDA LARGE FLESHY  DEAL WITH THE MATTER PACKET ENDED UP WAIT  ZANBY HAS FINALLY ADDRESSED THE LEAGUE AND PERHAPS HIS HEART STOPPED INTERNAL PEACE INTERNAL PEACE      HOME  INTERNAL PEACE WHOEVER DOES THIS SOUND  OF SILENT ZHANG)  EXCELLENT) COULD BENEFIT FROM GOOD NEWS NOW ANY TEACHER TO     THAT BAD NEWS LARRY 00:40:47:14 00:40:49:19 THEY MERELY NEWS  NO NEWS GOOD AND BAD TEACHER SEEING YOU WERE CORRECT TAI LONG) ESCAPED FROM PRISON)  THAT WAY THIS BAD NEWS IF THAT WERE NOT BELIEVED DRAGON WARRIOR  CAN STOP IT BANDA</pattern><template>any teacher that Banda was not Dragon Warrior was not supposed to be here  was a coincidence no coincidence Yes, I know  I said this before twice these were not also a coincidence three times my friend old panda  will not achieve their own destiny and you do not if they did not abandon its control they?</template></category><category><pattern>ANY TEACHER THAT BANDA WAS NOT DRAGON WARRIOR WAS NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE  WAS A COINCIDENCE NO COINCIDENCE YES  I KNOW  I SAID THIS BEFORE TWICE THESE WERE NOT ALSO A COINCIDENCE THREE TIMES MY FRIEND OLD PANDA  WILL NOT ACHIEVE THEIR OWN DESTINY AND YOU DO NOT IF THEY DID NOT ABANDON ITS CONTROL THEY</pattern><template>I can not Set bud  when it is off to Shizam and I can not aimed Set EXAMINED  before that time comes but there are things we can control I can control the time the fall fruit ... And I can control where farm seed This is not, you are a teacher Yes, but do whatever  those of cottonseed to become the largest tree Lepage might want Apple or orange but you get Lepage possibly can if you are prepared to guide  and development and the faith but how  How I need you to help teachers No, you need to believe Eden will ensure that you will will try good perhaps the time has come must continue journey without ... What any teacher can not be left must be secured any teacher might be more panda bears scaring    in the region  , but you riding Balakechbc  really? How I came out of there alive?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY THERE IS A PROBLEM  SO I WANT TO SEE MY OLD FRIEND IF NO PROBLEM</pattern><template>did not say this you say We are haunted by a vision Tai Long) will return) this impossible  is in prison nothing is impossible Zeng 00:06:43:10 00:06:48:07) wing of the prison)  and ask them to redouble guard redouble weapons  redouble everything Tai Long) would not leave the prison) lectured milestone one meets its destiny on the road  chosen by the must do something  can not leave, walking in the Valley and revenge reason of such water, my friend  when disturbed becomes difficult vision but if left stabilizes  answer becomes clear Lviv Dragon time but it? Who is qualified to be  reliable secret of boundless power to become combatants Dragon do not know extremes Warning    sorry    Unfortunately 00:07:43:22 00:07:45:06 Why?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DO NOT HAVE ANYTHING  BECAUSE I HAVE EVERYTHING HERE IS HARASSMENT FRIENDS   ATTENDING TO FEEL THE THUNDER BLOW FEET CRAZY  WONDERING COME 00:23:39:02 00:23:40:20 SAW NO WAY BEAR HLA HIT WHY NOT TRY AGAIN  STRONGER HOW THIS</pattern><template>this painful This will be easier than I thought sensitive regions how IMO?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I SAW ENOUGH  WILL SAY L (CHEVY) THAT THERE IS NOTHING TO WORRY HIM BOTH NO I WILL TELL HIM THIS WAIT I THINK THERE IS A SMALL ERROR     EVERYONE THOUGHT I HALL HOLY FIGHTERS IMPOSSIBLE LOOK FOR THIS PLACE SHIELD (FOR WHAT TO WHERE) THE TEACHER I THOUGHT THAT DAMAGED SAIF CHAMPIONS SAID TO BE VERY SHARP  SO  WOUNDED SEEN SHAFT MUCH UNSEEN I SAW THE PAINTINGS OF THIS PAINTING JUST NOT JAR LEGENDARY EX HAM SAID TO CONTAIN THE LIVES OF THE ARMY OF  ECSTASY  WHOLE HELLO    IS TERMINATED VISION     UNFORTUNATELY HE SHOULD COME TO SEE YOU I</pattern><template>Sabri running out if you were not going to somewhere turn    certainly    someone break this , but I fittest parents .. Glue if you are legendary warrior?</template></category><category><pattern>ORIGINAL SUBS: TARAFA@ALKADAH COM TRANLATED SUBS: KAIZER TALES OF A LEGENDARY WARRIOR WHO'S KUNGFU SKILLS WITH THE STUFF OF LEGEND HE TRAVELED THE LAND IN SEARCH OF WORTHY FOES I SEE YOU LIKE TO CHEW MAYBE YOU WOULD LIKE TO CHEW ON MY FACE</pattern><template>The warrior said nothing for his mouth was full then he swallowed then he spoke enough talk! Lets fight!</template></category><category><pattern>IS COMING TO DRAGON SCROLL  AND YOU CAN ONLY STOP AND I SAY THAT YOU DO NOT HAVE  SENSE OF HUMOR ARE YOU SERIOUS</pattern><template>teacher (Togo) stopping  done this before already again Togo) can not)  no longer Our only hope is the Dragon Warrior Banda?    Yes Banda    where he went?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE YOU DISTURBED</pattern><template>may have been on the worst day  in the history of the Congo Fu in the history of China in the history of bad mostly and five .. We must see them  idea that they full I do not like the five  I do not have talons no wings  not cm may be surrendered and come back for cooking barley surrender .. No surrender Noodle  not Noodle you worried by what was often  and what will There is a saying  Yesterday is history tomorrow is a mystery but today is a gift   this is called the present   the gift not    What happens?    fired fired will not go any place Let me 00:30:42:00 00:30:43:15 that come here to will not depart throwers shares We Dead  very Dead Not yet 00:32:16:22 00:32:19:12 can not escape now?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS VERY IMPRESSIVE ONE WAY TO ENTER  AND ONE WAY OUT A GUARD AND ONE PRISONER TOOK ME DOWN WAIT HERE NONE CONCERNED ABOUT  COMPLETELY SECURE PLACE DEAR FORCES YOU HEARD   TOGO) TO FINALLY GIVE DRAGON SCROLL OF A PERSON) AND YOU WILL NOT BE WHAT ARE YOU DOING   DOES NOT MAKE IT ANGRY AND WHAT HE WILL DO   HAS MADE HIM TOTALLY IMMOBILE IS PLANTED ON THE TAIL  SMALL ZAREEF</pattern><template>Well, I saw enough  will say l (Chevy) that there is nothing to worry him both no I will tell him this wait I think there is a small error ... Everyone thought I Hall holy fighters impossible Look for this place shield (for what to where) the teacher I thought that damaged Saif Champions said to be very sharp, so  wounded seen Shaft much unseen I saw the paintings of this painting just not jar legendary ex Ham said to contain the lives of the army of  ecstasy  whole Hello    Is Terminated vision?    unfortunately he should come to see you I.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SUPPOSED TO BE TALKING ABOUT IF IT WILL REMAIN HERE SHOULD KNOW THE PUPILS  FROM THE FIRST PERFECTED  THOUSANDTH OF SKILL KONG FU AND THEN TURNED TO EVIL AND WENT TO PRISON WAS NOT JUST PUPILS SHIVA) AND A SMALL JEDDAH) OH  KABINEH WHILE THE BOY SHOWED SKILL IN THE CONGO FU SHIVA) AND FINALLY) BELIEVED IN HIM  TOLD HIM THAT THE ABILITY OF GREAT WANTED TO DRAGON SCROLL BUT (TOGO)  THE OVERWHELMING OPINION IN HIS HEART  AND REJECTION TAI LONG) HAVE WREAKED HAVOC VALLEY)  ANGRY TRIED TO FORCIBLY TAKE SCROLL AND (SHIVA) WAS FORCED TO DESTROY WHAT CREATED BUT HOW CAN</pattern><template>Shiva) loved (Tai Loong) also did not like)  one of the pre   or timely and now has the opportunity to correct things  trains combatants for the real dragon and has been suspended with you Banda large fleshy  deal with the matter Packet ended up Wait  Zanby has finally addressed the League and perhaps his heart stopped internal peace internal peace .... Home  internal peace whoever does this sound  of silent Zhang), excellent) could benefit from good news now any teacher to ... That bad news Larry 00:40:47:14 00:40:49:19 they merely News  No news good and bad teacher seeing you were correct Tai Long) escaped from prison)  that way this bad news if that were not believed Dragon Warrior  can stop it Banda?</template></category><category><pattern>DOES NOT SPUR  NOW I WILL USE THIS WANTS COME AND TAKE FINALLY 01:11:22:08 01:11:23:17 THIS I SCROLL SCROLL GIVE STRENGTH FINALLY 01:13:57:01 01:13:57:25 YES 01:13:57:25 01:14:00:06 FORCE SCROLL DRAGON IS ME NONE DID NOT QUITE UNDERSTAND IT  ALSO THE FIRST TIME WHY</pattern><template>There is a secret that you're only stop do not can not be defeated You ... Just Banda large fleshy am not a large fleshy Banda Anna Banda big chaff famous know this Alamsake deceive you?</template></category><category><pattern>IS   THIS BANDA YOU BANDA  WHY DO YOU MUCH  SITTING ON</pattern><template>does not spur  Now I will use this wants Come and Take Finally 01:11:22:08 01:11:23:17 this I Scroll Scroll give strength Finally 01:13:57:01 01:13:57:25 Yes 01:13:57:25 01:14:00:06 force Scroll dragon is me NONE did not quite understand it  also the first time Why?</template></category><category><pattern>UNNECESSARY  IN ORDER TO CREATE SOMETHING DISTINCTIVE  BELIEVES THAT IT MUST BE DISTINGUISHED THERE IS A SECRET HAS PROMISED TO HOUSE ANY TEACHER THIS IS NO LONGER YOUR HOUSE  AND I AM NOT PREPARED TEACHER YES  YOU HAVE A FAVORITE NEW PUPIL WHERE (BO) THIS</pattern><template>Is abated?</template></category><category><pattern>OF TAUGHT ME THAT EVEN WITH SUPER BREAKUP</pattern><template>of deprivation of fateful?</template></category><category><pattern>TOO FAR YOU     WHAT A DAY KUNG FU SAAB  RIGHT</pattern><template>has been a long day  and disappointing somewhat So ... Yes, we must sleep now Yes Yes  course But I admire a large  you dramatically in the battle of the river outnumber, each one thousand , but you did not stop sorry about this listen, you do not belong to this place I know I know 00:27:01:01 00:27:04:00 You are right 00:27:04:01 00:27:05:14 ... During my whole life you dream No, I mean you do not belong to here  in this room these rooms  (Property (Whale Yes true 00:27:16:07 00:27:19:08 want to sleep  I stay awake and you have something important tomorrow You are wonderful  last thing I am going to say what was this?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT MY FATHER I WAS THINKING    YES    I WAS THINKING 00:08:21:20 00:08:23:25 WE CAN SELL BEANS  BEFORE THEY SPOIL THIS IS MY SON I TOLD YOU THAT THE DREAM OF A REFERENCE YES  I'M GLAD I SAW ALMOST OUT WHY</pattern><template>not sorry you shouted  I will bring you commemoration No, I go to you in commemoration that wonderful day well as teacher Alice (Togo)?</template></category><category><pattern>HAS BEEN A LONG DAY  AND DISAPPOINTING SOMEWHAT SO     YES  WE MUST SLEEP NOW YES YES  COURSE BUT I ADMIRE A LARGE  YOU DRAMATICALLY IN THE BATTLE OF THE RIVER OUTNUMBER  EACH ONE THOUSAND   BUT YOU DID NOT STOP SORRY ABOUT THIS LISTEN  YOU DO NOT BELONG TO THIS PLACE I KNOW I KNOW 00:27:01:01 00:27:04:00 YOU ARE RIGHT 00:27:04:01 00:27:05:14     DURING MY WHOLE LIFE YOU DREAM NO  I MEAN YOU DO NOT BELONG TO HERE  IN THIS ROOM THESE ROOMS  (PROPERTY (WHALE YES TRUE 00:27:16:07 00:27:19:08 WANT TO SLEEP  I STAY AWAKE AND YOU HAVE SOMETHING IMPORTANT TOMORROW YOU ARE WONDERFUL  LAST THING I AM GOING TO SAY WHAT WAS THIS</pattern><template>did not say anything Well, Good night  from well seems strange situation mandate tagged (Tigress) did not mean that awakens You do not belong to here Yes of course this room I mean do not belong to the Palace of good Shame on you Alkong Fu, and if  you have any respect for us and what we do You have to go by morning large fan I see you found the sacred tree of peaches  of divine wisdom Is this what?  unfortunately I thought it extraordinary tree Lepage understand, you're erosion  when uncomfortable am not uncomfortable  Why think I'm disturbed?</template></category><category><pattern>NONE WAS NOT DESTINED TO BE A COMBATANT YOU DRAGON  THIS IS NOT ZANBY NOT THEIR FAULT   OF LETTING DOWN</pattern><template>of taught me that even with super breakup?</template></category><category><pattern>THINK I AM FOOLISH  I KNOW THAT YOU ARE NOT FIGHTING THE DRAGON NOT ONE OF YOU HEARD HOW FELL FROM THE SKY  BALL FIRE THAT COMBATANTS DO NOT LIKE ANYTHING  WORLD SAW BO) ) IF THIS NAME FINALLY  THE DEDUCTION WORTH FIGHTING BATTLE WILL BE EPIC WE WERE STILL IN THIS  HELPED JUMP NOW SHIVA) WELL COACHED) BUT HE DID NOT KNOW EVERYTHING IMO HAS DONE WELL ANY BANDA IMO DONE WELL</pattern><template>I have been a wonderful hero is the real sign of humility But yes  you are wonderful five has died  No, they breathed asleep?  Not open their eyes we were not equals to attack the nerves become stronger Tai Long)?)  stronger is very fast I thought that we can stop him could have been killers Why did he do?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU READY TO BE RELIABLE  COMPONENT SECRET SOUP FOR THE SECRET AND THEN WILL OR YOUR SORROW  AND MANAGE THE RESTAURANT WHO RECEIVED FROM HIS FATHER  WHO RECEIVED FROM HIS FATHER HIRED BY FRIEND AND HAS DONE PAPA WAS JUST A DREAM NO  IT WAS IMPORTANT TO DREAM BARLEY IN THE VEINS BUT PAPA PAIN     IS TO DO SOMETHING ELSE</pattern><template>addition to the Noodle in fact, when I was young and crazy  I started to run away  and learn how to prepare  Toe Foo Why not done?</template></category><category><pattern>TEACHER (TOGO) STOPPING  DONE THIS BEFORE ALREADY AGAIN TOGO) CAN NOT)  NO LONGER OUR ONLY HOPE IS THE DRAGON WARRIOR BANDA     YES BANDA    WHERE HE WENT</pattern><template>You can not leave  true warrior does not surrender is watching defeated because you Dragon combatant You do not believe this  not believe this never from the first moment they arrived here  I tried to get rid of me Yes, I also but now I ask you to trust teachers as teachers Sathag You are not teachers  and I'm not Dragon Warrior Why, then, did not surrender?  you know I try to get rid of you but you stayed Yes, stayed because every time I offered folds on the head  or I said that I was hurt bad smell but not therefore more than ever  in my life because I am what I am stayed because I thought .. If they can be  anyone can change that makes me what I am  You will greatest milestone Kong Fu in the whole of China but you can change may turn to Dragon Warrior  and I will do Come on, (Tai Loong) in the way now even if it takes a hundred years  Getting to here how this will transform you to Dragon Warrior?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YOU SEE  FLESHY AND THIS SILLY POTBELLY ADDITION TO THE COMPLETE NEGLECT OF PERSONAL HYGIENE WAITED FOR THIS LITTLE HARDWOOD DOES NOT STOP AT THIS PROXIMITY  I CAN SMELL YOURSELF TOGO) SAID THAT I) ALAMSAKE KNOW THIS</pattern><template>You must know what is happening  while Eloy finger not You know what the hardest part?  door is clean holes Submit  I hear you very well  Banda may be (Togo) chose  But when you finished I promise you that you wish did not do of our Will?</template></category><category><pattern>STOPPED WAITED      WHO TOLD YOU TEACHER (TOGO) WAIT THIS  BANDA  CAN NOT BE THE SOLUTION TO OUR PROBLEM WAS JUST A COINCIDENCE NO COINCIDENCE PLIGHT OF ANY TEACHER  HAVE DESERTED  NO  IF NO SURRENDER  BANDA  MORNING WITH SOLUTIONS I'M THE ONE WHO I WOULD BE LETTING DOWN WAIT WHY  DOUBLED GUARD  BACKUP SAFETY PROCEDURES PRISON MAY NOT BE SAFE</pattern><template>questioning the security of prisons?</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  GOOD MORNING MILESTONE I THOUGHT THAT LITTLE MASTICATION HAS BEEN SUSPENDED SUSPENDED</pattern><template>not Yes, we have suspended assisted My God 00:34:33:14 00:34:34:18 when preparing the third Thank you    do not remember it    not really    never    I thought that you can dismiss the entire  during one night require years to develop this flexibility years and the longest battle for application toss this, the only trophy we collect here  joints are bloody and broken bones Yes 00:35:11:20 00:35:13:03 excellent to begin Are you Msttad .... I was born ready sorry I thought you said you're ready this wonderful  to restore it I have been with you any leniency Banda , but not longer your opponent will be the next Anna Well  to start progress order to win you have to find  weak point your opponent and make them suffer take power and use that against him until fall or surrender true warrior, but do not surrender  Do not worry any teacher will not surrendered whether intelligent  will climb grades but he will do will not surrender  is not it?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT WILL STOP (TAI LONG)</pattern><template>would destroy everything  and every one not evacuated valley  (must protect villagers from the wrath (Tai Long What about you?</template></category><category><pattern>DID NOT SAY THIS YOU SAY WE ARE HAUNTED BY A VISION TAI LONG) WILL RETURN) THIS IMPOSSIBLE  IS IN PRISON NOTHING IS IMPOSSIBLE ZENG 00:06:43:10 00:06:48:07) WING OF THE PRISON)  AND ASK THEM TO REDOUBLE GUARD REDOUBLE WEAPONS  REDOUBLE EVERYTHING TAI LONG) WOULD NOT LEAVE THE PRISON) LECTURED MILESTONE ONE MEETS ITS DESTINY ON THE ROAD  CHOSEN BY THE MUST DO SOMETHING  CAN NOT LEAVE  WALKING IN THE VALLEY AND REVENGE REASON OF SUCH WATER  MY FRIEND  WHEN DISTURBED BECOMES DIFFICULT VISION BUT IF LEFT STABILIZES  ANSWER BECOMES CLEAR LVIV DRAGON TIME BUT IT  WHO IS QUALIFIED TO BE  RELIABLE SECRET OF BOUNDLESS POWER TO BECOME COMBATANTS DRAGON DO NOT KNOW EXTREMES WARNING    SORRY    UNFORTUNATELY 00:07:43:22 00:07:45:06 WHY</pattern><template>teacher (Togo) chooses  Dragon Warrior today everyone go  Palace good one of the five will happen  Scroll to the Dragon I waited for a thousand years for this Go the greatest day in the history of the Congo Fu  Go Bo) Where To Go?)  to the  good but you forgot cart barley entire valley there will be  and you will sell them all barley sell barley?</template></category><category><pattern>WILL DEPEND ON COLLISION I THOUGHT YOU SAID THAT IT MAKES US FEEL IMPROVES TRUST ME  BUT MAKES NO  EASY TO FIND A CLIQUE UNDER ALL THIS    FUR FAT    I WAS GOING TO SAY FUR COURSE WHO AM I TO JUDGE THE COMBATANT  BASED ON SIZE SEE ME HERE PERHAPS YOU SHOULD TAKE A LOOK AT THIS AGAIN WELL 00:37:14:15 00:37:17:07 KNOW THAT THE TEACHER (CHEVY) TRIES TO INSPIRE BUT I DID NOT KNOW THAT WELL  I SAID TO BE TRYING TO GET RID OF ME I KNOW IT SEEMS HARSH   BUT IT WAS NOT ALWAYS SO ACCORDING TO LEGEND THERE WAS A TIME  WHERE HE WAS A TEACHER (CHEVY) SMILES NOT WEAR BUT THIS WAS BEFORE BEFORE WHY</pattern><template>not supposed to be talking about if it will remain here should know The pupils, from the first perfected  thousandth of skill Kong Fu and then turned to evil and went to prison was not just pupils Shiva) and a small Jeddah) Oh, Kabineh while the boy showed skill in the Congo Fu Shiva) and finally) believed in him, told him that the ability of great wanted to Dragon Scroll but (Togo), the overwhelming opinion in his heart  and rejection Tai Long) have wreaked havoc valley)  angry tried to forcibly take Scroll and (Shiva) was forced to destroy what created but how can?</template></category><category><pattern>YES 00:09:50:07 00:09:51:17 AND WILL NOT LIVE TO SEE DO YOUR STUDENTS READY</pattern><template>Warning, my friend, who chose  will not bring peace, according to Valley but also you to start the competition No, wait  my way open the door Turkish Enter you, the citizens and led peace honour to extend to you  (Tigress), (snake) five Angry of preparing warriors thousand tons of fire to see this You Get believe me, you citizens  did not see anything yet Learn 00:12:06:03 00:12:07:21 tagged (Tigress) facing unarmed  swords death felt that our Dragon Warrior you, the citizens and led peace teacher (Togo) will choose now  Dragon Warrior not wait What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE TO INDICATE WHY</pattern><template>Well, unfortunately, 00:14:26:24 00:14:31:22  I wanted to see who is the Dragon Warrior This is an interesting milestone Are you referring to me?</template></category><category><pattern>TEACHER (SHIVA)</pattern><template>any teacher Bo)?)  You are alive or we both Dead not teachers  not complete really?</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT KNOW DID NOT KNOW I WAS BROUGHT SWEETS BUT YOU AT A HEIGHT OF 10 FEET ON THE GROUND  AND I FULLY REVOKE NO  THIS</pattern><template>... These  coincidence no coincidence  Come with me know you're trying to be vague  and nature Kong Feuilles but you can not tell me that at least  Where are we going?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I DREAM OF WHAT OTHER</pattern><template>Warning my son finally had a dream Noodle do not know how much I was waiting for this moment this reference reference Why?</template></category><category><pattern>BANDA YOU DO NOT WASH THE BODY  IN THE HOLY LAKE OF TEARS     LAKE REVEALED HERE (TOGO) PUZZLE  HARMONY AND FOCUS BORN HERE  WHERE KUNG FU WANT TO LEARN KUNG FU</pattern><template>Yes 00:52:11:01 00:52:12:01 if I am teacher Well 00:52:15:01 00:52:17:06 not your books Well 00:52:19:10 00:52:21:05 while focusing on the Congo Fu  while focusing you bad but perhaps this Zanby  I can not be coached and trained five I see now that the road to enter you  This is wonderful because I am hungry well, while practicing erosion to begin from you after you Banda So?  Not booby not walked for ten miles has vowed to train  and has trained you can eat Enjoy 00:54:14:10 00:54:15:23 I said you can eat you can eat Can I?    Are You?    m not hungry any teacher segments Where Dragon Warrior?</template></category><category><pattern>ANY TEACHER BO) )  YOU ARE ALIVE OR WE BOTH DEAD NOT TEACHERS  NOT COMPLETE REALLY</pattern><template>You combatant dragon has brought peace to the Valley and I  Thank Thank  (Bo) Thank No, teachers do not not been (Chevy) Please did not complete my Duffer O Dragon Warrior I simply live with peace  Finally if we must stop talking if you can Will I get something to eat?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT YES  WE HAVE SUSPENDED ASSISTED MY GOD 00:34:33:14 00:34:34:18 WHEN PREPARING THE THIRD THANK YOU    DO NOT REMEMBER IT    NOT REALLY    NEVER    I THOUGHT THAT YOU CAN DISMISS THE ENTIRE  DURING ONE NIGHT REQUIRE YEARS TO DEVELOP THIS FLEXIBILITY YEARS AND THE LONGEST BATTLE FOR APPLICATION TOSS THIS  THE ONLY TROPHY WE COLLECT HERE  JOINTS ARE BLOODY AND BROKEN BONES YES 00:35:11:20 00:35:13:03 EXCELLENT TO BEGIN ARE YOU MSTTAD      I WAS BORN READY SORRY I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU'RE READY THIS WONDERFUL  TO RESTORE IT I HAVE BEEN WITH YOU ANY LENIENCY BANDA   BUT NOT LONGER YOUR OPPONENT WILL BE THE NEXT ANNA WELL  TO START PROGRESS ORDER TO WIN YOU HAVE TO FIND  WEAK POINT YOUR OPPONENT AND MAKE THEM SUFFER TAKE POWER AND USE THAT AGAINST HIM UNTIL FALL OR SURRENDER TRUE WARRIOR  BUT DO NOT SURRENDER  DO NOT WORRY ANY TEACHER WILL NOT SURRENDERED WHETHER INTELLIGENT  WILL CLIMB GRADES BUT HE WILL DO WILL NOT SURRENDER  IS NOT IT</pattern><template>will depend on collision I thought you said that it makes us feel IMPROVES Trust me, but makes no  easy to find a clique under all this    fur fat    I was going to say fur course Who am I to judge the combatant  Based on size see me here perhaps you should take a look at this again Well 00:37:14:15 00:37:17:07 know that the teacher (Chevy) tries to inspire but I did not know that well  I said to be trying to get rid of me I know it seems harsh , but it was not always so according to legend there was a time  where he was a teacher (Chevy) smiles not wear but this was before before Why?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS BATTLE BETWEEN ME AND YOU SO THINGS WILL</pattern><template>thus must be has Rot in jail for 20 years  due to weak obey the teacher is not vulnerable knew I Dragon Warrior What did I do?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS PAINFUL THIS WILL BE EASIER THAN I THOUGHT SENSITIVE REGIONS HOW IMO</pattern><template>Now there is zero level not words do not understand the thinking of Bam  (teacher (Togo poor will cause the death of is very strong Dragon Warrior fell from the sky  ball fire while walking the earth shakes yes or at least can  fingers touched the feet fingers, or even finds his feet Well 00:25:56:14 00:25:57:11 Hello  You awake?</template></category><category><pattern>NONE BO) TO GO)  LATE TO WORK COMING UNFORTUNATELY  POPE WORD  UNFORTUNATELY  ARE NOT NOODLE SOUP WHAT WERE YOU DOING THERE  WHAT ALL THIS UPROAR</pattern><template>dreamed crazy dream what?  How would you dream of?</template></category><category><pattern>SHIVA) DID NOT TEACH YOU THIS) NO  I DISCOVERED MYSELF LOOK 01:16:41:23 01:16:42:22 DRAGON WARRIOR IN THIS  WARRIOR KUNG FU IS A GREAT BELOVED SON THANK ABE HI GUYS ANY TEACHER MILESTONE TEACHER</pattern><template>teacher (Shiva)?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT YOU DO NOT CONSIDER IT</pattern><template>think I am foolish  I know that you are not fighting the dragon not one of you heard how fell from the sky  ball fire that combatants do not like anything  world saw Bo)?) if this name Finally, the deduction worth fighting battle will be epic we were still in this  helped Jump now Shiva) well coached) but he did not know everything IMO has done well any Banda IMO done well?</template></category><category><pattern>THESE  COINCIDENCE NO COINCIDENCE  COME WITH ME KNOW YOU'RE TRYING TO BE VAGUE  AND NATURE KONG FEUILLES BUT YOU CAN NOT TELL ME THAT AT LEAST  WHERE ARE WE GOING</pattern><template>I have come to me here for the bathroom?</template></category><category><pattern>THINK SO    ERROR    AM NOT A BELLIGERENT DRAGON AND WILL NEVER BE  EVEN LEARN THE SECRET OF THE DRAGON SCROLL HOW SUCCESSFUL THIS   DEEK PEACE  OR TRUMBLIN</pattern><template>believes that the matter so easily?  I recognize the secret of force untold not First you have to master the highest  level of Kong Fu And this of course is impossible for a person like you person like me?</template></category><category><pattern>QUESTIONING THE SECURITY OF PRISONS</pattern><template>both certainly  Chevy) of the question, I'm just a messenger escape from prison,  Chordam  impossible impressive is not it?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE COME TO ME HERE FOR THE BATHROOM</pattern><template>Banda you do not wash the body  in the holy lake of tears ... Lake revealed here (Togo) puzzle  harmony and focus born here, where Kung Fu Want to learn Kung Fu?</template></category><category><pattern>WAS NEVER RESOLUTIONS IT IS NOW GIVE ME SCROLL 01:08:33:12 01:08:36:17 PREFER TO DIE TELL ME 01:09:32:23 01:09:34:14 TELL ME 01:09:34:15 01:09:37:14 FOR AS LONG AS YOU ARE PROUD OF YOUR FROM THE FIRST MOMENT I WAS PROUD OF YOUR AND WAS PROUD THAT OMAN I LOVED IT VERY MUCH TO SEE WHAT YOU TURN HIM WHAT I DO FOR YOU I     I  I'M SORRY DO NOT WANT AN APOLOGY I WANT TO GIRLS WHY</pattern><template>where is it?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS NO CHARGE TO AWESOMNESS OR ATTRACTIVENESS IT MATTERED NOT TO HOW MANY FOES HE FACED THEY MEASURED NOT TO HIS BODACITY  THERE IS NO NEED BY  BANDA  MOHAB AND BELOVED EVEN THE MOST POWERFUL HEROES  IN CHINA FIVE ANGRY  WE RESPECTED TEACHER AND A GREAT MUST SPEND TIME TOGETHER AGREE BUT SPEND TIME AWAIT IT WHILE FACING THOUSANDS OF 10000  DEMONS OF THE MOUNTAIN     THERE IS ONE THING OF INTEREST P      IS CONDUCT THAN THE WORK BO) CONDUCT) WHY DO YOU HAVE</pattern><template>NONE Bo) to go)  late to work coming Unfortunately, Pope word, unfortunately, are not Noodle Soup What were you doing there  what all this uproar?</template></category><category><pattern>SABRI RUNNING OUT IF YOU WERE NOT GOING TO SOMEWHERE TURN    CERTAINLY    SOMEONE BREAK THIS   BUT I FITTEST PARENTS    GLUE IF YOU ARE LEGENDARY WARRIOR</pattern><template>think so    error    am not a belligerent dragon and will never be  even learn the secret of the Dragon Scroll how successful this?  Deek peace? Or Trumblin?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN NOT LEAVE  TRUE WARRIOR DOES NOT SURRENDER IS WATCHING DEFEATED BECAUSE YOU DRAGON COMBATANT YOU DO NOT BELIEVE THIS  NOT BELIEVE THIS NEVER FROM THE FIRST MOMENT THEY ARRIVED HERE  I TRIED TO GET RID OF ME YES  I ALSO BUT NOW I ASK YOU TO TRUST TEACHERS AS TEACHERS SATHAG YOU ARE NOT TEACHERS  AND I'M NOT DRAGON WARRIOR WHY  THEN  DID NOT SURRENDER   YOU KNOW I TRY TO GET RID OF YOU BUT YOU STAYED YES  STAYED BECAUSE EVERY TIME I OFFERED FOLDS ON THE HEAD  OR I SAID THAT I WAS HURT BAD SMELL BUT NOT THEREFORE MORE THAN EVER  IN MY LIFE BECAUSE I AM WHAT I AM STAYED BECAUSE I THOUGHT    IF THEY CAN BE  ANYONE CAN CHANGE THAT MAKES ME WHAT I AM  YOU WILL GREATEST MILESTONE KONG FU IN THE WHOLE OF CHINA BUT YOU CAN CHANGE MAY TURN TO DRAGON WARRIOR  AND I WILL DO COME ON  (TAI LOONG) IN THE WAY NOW EVEN IF IT TAKES A HUNDRED YEARS  GETTING TO HERE HOW THIS WILL TRANSFORM YOU TO DRAGON WARRIOR</pattern><template>How?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS A SECRET THAT YOU'RE ONLY STOP DO NOT CAN NOT BE DEFEATED YOU     JUST BANDA LARGE FLESHY AM NOT A LARGE FLESHY BANDA ANNA BANDA BIG CHAFF FAMOUS KNOW THIS ALAMSAKE DECEIVE YOU</pattern><template>Shiva) did not teach you this) No, I discovered myself Look 01:16:41:23 01:16:42:22 Dragon Warrior In this  Warrior Kung Fu is a great beloved son Thank Abe Hi guys any teacher milestone teacher?</template></category><category><pattern>WARNING  MY FRIEND  WHO CHOSE  WILL NOT BRING PEACE  ACCORDING TO VALLEY BUT ALSO YOU TO START THE COMPETITION NO  WAIT  MY WAY OPEN THE DOOR TURKISH ENTER YOU  THE CITIZENS AND LED PEACE HONOUR TO EXTEND TO YOU  (TIGRESS)  (SNAKE) FIVE ANGRY OF PREPARING WARRIORS THOUSAND TONS OF FIRE TO SEE THIS YOU GET BELIEVE ME  YOU CITIZENS  DID NOT SEE ANYTHING YET LEARN 00:12:06:03 00:12:07:21 TAGGED (TIGRESS) FACING UNARMED  SWORDS DEATH FELT THAT OUR DRAGON WARRIOR YOU  THE CITIZENS AND LED PEACE TEACHER (TOGO) WILL CHOOSE NOW  DRAGON WARRIOR NOT WAIT WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>What seems I do?</template></category><category><pattern>IS ABATED</pattern><template>this battle between me and you So things will?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOUTED     I DRAGON WARRIOR YOU</pattern><template>is?  This Banda You Banda  Why do you much? Sitting on?</template></category><category><pattern>IS    FROM     YOU    I     UNIVERSE SEND US DRAGON WARRIOR WHY     WHY     WHY</pattern><template>stopped waited  ... Who told you teacher (Togo) Wait this  Banda  can not be the solution to our problem was just a coincidence no coincidence plight of any teacher  have deserted  No, if no surrender  Banda  morning with solutions I'm the one who I would be letting down wait Why? Doubled guard  backup safety procedures prison may not be safe?</template></category><category><pattern>ADDITION TO THE NOODLE IN FACT  WHEN I WAS YOUNG AND CRAZY  I STARTED TO RUN AWAY  AND LEARN HOW TO PREPARE  TOE FOO WHY NOT DONE</pattern><template>because it was just a silly dream you can not imagine that I am prepared  Toe Fu ?</template></category><category><pattern>TO RETURN AND SCARES  HERE IN OUR HEARTS  BUT WILL NOT SUCCEED MAY SUCCEED  SLIGHTLY I'M AFRAID 01:00:11:22 01:00:14:05 YOU CAN DEFEAT ANY BANDA ARE YOU KIDDING   THEY CAN NOT ARE FIVE TEACHERS I'M ONLY ONE BUT YOU HAVE SOMETHING THAT  NOT OWNED BY ONE ANOTHER ACTUALLY THINK I'M READY GRABBED THE DRAGON SCROLL IT FOR YOU WAITED    WHAT HAPPENS WHEN READ</pattern><template>No one knows, but legend says  he will be able to hear butterfly flap really? Hmaraa Yes, sees light at the depth of the cave  hair is around you and movement Could I broke through the walls  Could I do that my heart focused focused Yes 01:01:47:20 01:01:49:04 read it and achieved or your sorrow read it and became belligerent Dragon impossible reopened Thank 01:02:09:01 01:02:10:21 maybe you just analysed Well Here is the it empty    Why?    you    No, I'm not allowed to consider it    empty do not understand Well 01:02:43:24 01:02:46:02 Togo) turtle was crazy in the end) No, (Togo) was the wisest of us all Come 01:02:53:08 01:02:54:15 faced matter, has chosen passerby course, I'm not Dragon Warrior of deceptive?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW</pattern><template>How?    I do not know    do not know This is what I thought This is what she trains for it not try suspensive not trying to stop    Why?    coming with you Why?</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT KNOW MILESTONE  BUT LET'S START FROM ZERO  ZERO THERE IS NO LEVEL OF ZERO PERHAPS I COULD BEGIN THIS THIS  WE USE THIS TO TRAIN CHILDREN  AND KEEP THE DOOR OPEN WHEN IT IS HOT BUT IF YOU INSIST FIVE ANGRY  YOU MORE PHOTO  COME ON   BANDA  US WHAT YOU CAN DO WILL SEE YOU   OR TO WAIT EVEN LONGER TO WORK STRIKE I JUST ATE SO I STILL DIGESTIBLE KUNG FU MOVEMENTS THEREFORE MAY NOT BE  WOULD ALSO BE GOOD LATER STRIKES ONLY WHY YOU</pattern><template>You do not have anything  because I have everything here Is harassment friends?  attending to feel the thunder blow feet crazy  Wondering Come 00:23:39:02 00:23:40:20 saw no way BEAR Hla hit why not try again  stronger How this?</template></category><category><pattern>TOE FOO  ALL OF US OUR PLACE IN THIS WORLD AND MY PLACE HERE  AND PLACE KNOW HERE NO  GO TO THE TABLE 5  7 AND 12 SERVICE WITH A SMILE HEY  STUDENTS IF YOU WERE TRYING VIEJO I THINK TIGRESS)  MORE SPEED) MONKEY) TOP SPEED) STORK) HIGH)  SNAKE) RUSH) WHY</pattern><template>teacher (Togo) wants to see you teacher (Togo) demand?  Is there a problem?</template></category><category><pattern>STOPPED  GO TO SEE THE DRAGON WARRIOR BUT I DO NOT UNDERSTAND  I HAVE DREAMED A DREAM FINALLY BARLEY HAS LIED  NOT DREAM OF BARLEY POPE LOVE KUNG FU COME ON  BENI  TO PREPARE FOR ACTION WELL 00:13:43:14 00:13:46:03 WHAT IS BEING</pattern><template>... Where to indicate why?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN NOT SET BUD  WHEN IT IS OFF TO SHIZAM AND I CAN NOT AIMED SET EXAMINED  BEFORE THAT TIME COMES BUT THERE ARE THINGS WE CAN CONTROL I CAN CONTROL THE TIME THE FALL FRUIT     AND I CAN CONTROL WHERE FARM SEED THIS IS NOT  YOU ARE A TEACHER YES  BUT DO WHATEVER  THOSE OF COTTONSEED TO BECOME THE LARGEST TREE LEPAGE MIGHT WANT APPLE OR ORANGE BUT YOU GET LEPAGE POSSIBLY CAN IF YOU ARE PREPARED TO GUIDE  AND DEVELOPMENT AND THE FAITH BUT HOW  HOW I NEED YOU TO HELP TEACHERS NO  YOU NEED TO BELIEVE EDEN WILL ENSURE THAT YOU WILL WILL TRY GOOD PERHAPS THE TIME HAS COME MUST CONTINUE JOURNEY WITHOUT     WHAT ANY TEACHER CAN NOT BE LEFT MUST BE SECURED ANY TEACHER MIGHT BE MORE PANDA BEARS SCARING    IN THE REGION    BUT YOU RIDING BALAKECHBC  REALLY  HOW I CAME OUT OF THERE ALIVE</pattern><template>did not say this actually , but I thought in my head if he could read my thoughts  of what was said hope that you love this good must try soup Abe secret is, in fact, knows the secret component Why talk about? This wonderful you cook a good reality was wishing that my mouth more mandate (Tigress) must try this Dragon Warrior said to be able to live  full month on nothing but a small paper and energy the universe I think that my body does not know  I Dragon Warrior after would need more than this to  juice and the universe Why?</template></category><category><pattern>THUS MUST BE HAS ROT IN JAIL FOR 20 YEARS  DUE TO WEAK OBEY THE TEACHER IS NOT VULNERABLE KNEW I DRAGON WARRIOR WHAT DID I DO</pattern><template>None was not destined to be a combatant you Dragon  This is not Zanby not their fault?  Of letting down?</template></category><category><pattern>BOTH CERTAINLY  CHEVY) OF THE QUESTION  I'M JUST A MESSENGER ESCAPE FROM PRISON   CHORDAM  IMPOSSIBLE IMPRESSIVE IS NOT IT</pattern><template>this very impressive one way to enter  and one way out A guard and one prisoner took me down wait here none Concerned about  completely secure place Dear forces you heard?  Togo) to finally give Dragon Scroll of a person) and you will not be What are you doing?  does not make it angry and what he will do?  has made him totally immobile Is planted on the tail, small Zareef?</template></category><category><pattern>MAY HAVE BEEN ON THE WORST DAY  IN THE HISTORY OF THE CONGO FU IN THE HISTORY OF CHINA IN THE HISTORY OF BAD MOSTLY AND FIVE    WE MUST SEE THEM  IDEA THAT THEY FULL I DO NOT LIKE THE FIVE  I DO NOT HAVE TALONS NO WINGS  NOT CM MAY BE SURRENDERED AND COME BACK FOR COOKING BARLEY SURRENDER    NO SURRENDER NOODLE  NOT NOODLE YOU WORRIED BY WHAT WAS OFTEN  AND WHAT WILL THERE IS A SAYING  YESTERDAY IS HISTORY TOMORROW IS A MYSTERY BUT TODAY IS A GIFT   THIS IS CALLED THE PRESENT   THE GIFT NOT    WHAT HAPPENS     FIRED FIRED WILL NOT GO ANY PLACE LET ME 00:30:42:00 00:30:43:15 THAT COME HERE TO WILL NOT DEPART THROWERS SHARES WE DEAD  VERY DEAD NOT YET 00:32:16:22 00:32:19:12 CAN NOT ESCAPE NOW</pattern><template>Yes 00:33:06:19 00:33:08:12 I am delighted that the (Chevy) e mail I think they started Sasson wing of there and tell them that the Dragon Warrior  real return Good Morning milestone Banda Banda you wake up has surrendered what we are doing now any teacher  and went Banda who will be the Dragon Warrior?</template></category><category><pattern>I EAT WHILE I WOULD BE UNCOMFORTABLE NO NEED TO EXPLAIN  (I THOUGHT YOU (THE MONKEY IS IN STORE FOR CANDY IN THE TOP SHELF SEE YOU KNOW  I'M CINNAMON NO  I MEAN HOW ARRIVED THERE</pattern><template>do not know did not know I was brought sweets but you at a height of 10 feet on the ground  and I fully REVOKE No, this?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THERE IS ZERO LEVEL NOT WORDS DO NOT UNDERSTAND THE THINKING OF BAM  (TEACHER (TOGO POOR WILL CAUSE THE DEATH OF IS VERY STRONG DRAGON WARRIOR FELL FROM THE SKY  BALL FIRE WHILE WALKING THE EARTH SHAKES YES OR AT LEAST CAN  FINGERS TOUCHED THE FEET FINGERS  OR EVEN FINDS HIS FEET WELL 00:25:56:14 00:25:57:11 HELLO  YOU AWAKE</pattern><template>too far You ... What a day Kung Fu Saab, right?</template></category><category><pattern>WARNING MY SON FINALLY HAD A DREAM NOODLE DO NOT KNOW HOW MUCH I WAS WAITING FOR THIS MOMENT THIS REFERENCE REFERENCE WHY</pattern><template>you ready to be reliable  component secret Soup for the secret and then will or your sorrow  and manage the restaurant who received from his father  who received from his father hired by friend and has done Papa was just a dream No, it was important to dream barley in the veins But Papa pain ... Is to do something else?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS SO DEADLY IN FACT THAT HIS ENEMIES WOULD GO BLIND EXPOSURE TO PURE AWESOMNESS HOW CAN WE REPAY YOU</pattern><template>There is no charge to awesomness or attractiveness It mattered not to how many foes he faced they measured not to his bodacity  there is no need by  Banda  Mohab and beloved even the most powerful heroes  in China five Angry  We respected teacher and a great must spend time together Agree but spend time await it while facing thousands of 10000  demons of the mountain ... There is one thing of interest P .... is conduct than the work Bo) conduct) Why do you have?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS IT</pattern><template>Dragon Warrior taking Scroll  other Party of China now never from you?</template></category><category><pattern>YES 00:52:11:01 00:52:12:01 IF I AM TEACHER WELL 00:52:15:01 00:52:17:06 NOT YOUR BOOKS WELL 00:52:19:10 00:52:21:05 WHILE FOCUSING ON THE CONGO FU  WHILE FOCUSING YOU BAD BUT PERHAPS THIS ZANBY  I CAN NOT BE COACHED AND TRAINED FIVE I SEE NOW THAT THE ROAD TO ENTER YOU  THIS IS WONDERFUL BECAUSE I AM HUNGRY WELL  WHILE PRACTICING EROSION TO BEGIN FROM YOU AFTER YOU BANDA SO   NOT BOOBY NOT WALKED FOR TEN MILES HAS VOWED TO TRAIN  AND HAS TRAINED YOU CAN EAT ENJOY 00:54:14:10 00:54:15:23 I SAID YOU CAN EAT YOU CAN EAT CAN I     ARE YOU     M NOT HUNGRY ANY TEACHER SEGMENTS WHERE DRAGON WARRIOR</pattern><template>How do you know that you do not consider it?</template></category><category><pattern>THE WARRIOR SAID NOTHING FOR HIS MOUTH WAS FULL THEN HE SWALLOWED THEN HE SPOKE ENOUGH TALK  LETS FIGHT</pattern><template>He was so deadly in fact that his enemies would go blind exposure to pure awesomness How can we repay you?</template></category><category><pattern>BO)     I'M SORRY THAT THINGS DID NOT SUCCEED) WAS ESTIMATED TO BE BO) LANCE ANYTHING ELSE)  STILL AWAITING DETERMINATION DOES NOT WE MAKERS NOODLE PLACE IN THE VEINS DO NOT KNOW MY FATHER HONESTLY</pattern><template>sometimes can not believe I am your son Bo) .. I think it is time)  to tell you something he should tell the long time ago Well 01:05:51:10 01:05:53:08 component of the secret ballot Soup Come ... Component is the secret NONE heard me  NONE There is a secret waited  only normal Noodle Soup adds a special sauce  or something like that?</template></category><category><pattern>TEACHER (TOGO) CHOOSES  DRAGON WARRIOR TODAY EVERYONE GO  PALACE GOOD ONE OF THE FIVE WILL HAPPEN  SCROLL TO THE DRAGON I WAITED FOR A THOUSAND YEARS FOR THIS GO THE GREATEST DAY IN THE HISTORY OF THE CONGO FU  GO BO) WHERE TO GO )  TO THE  GOOD BUT YOU FORGOT CART BARLEY ENTIRE VALLEY THERE WILL BE  AND YOU WILL SELL THEM ALL BARLEY SELL BARLEY</pattern><template>but my father I was thinking    yes    I was thinking 00:08:21:20 00:08:23:25 we can sell beans  before they spoil This is my son I told you that the dream of a reference Yes  I'm glad I saw almost out Why?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM THE KILLER    WHY     COULD DELAY SUFFICIENT  SO THAT EVERYONE ESCAPES BUT YOU (CHEVY)  KILLINGS TIME I HAD FINALLY PAID  EIGHTH MISTAKES ASAMAONI ALL OF YOU IS TIME TO SUPPLEMENT  TRIP WITHOUT I'M PROUD OF THAT I TAGGED MUST BE KNOCKED OUT SAFELY DEAR LITTLE COME TO FIND AS MANDATE (SNAKE) FRIDAY VILLAGERS SOUTHERNERS YOU (MANTIS) NORTHERNERS O (STORK) FROM HERE SEE THAT DRAGON WARRIOR HELLO ABE HELLO 01:04:34:08 01:04:36:03 QUALITY OF YOUR RETURN BANI IT'S GOOD TO COME BACK US IN THE FOLLOWING MUST FACE IT FUTURE OF BARLEY  PIECES WITH VEGETABLES WELL AS I WAS THINKING MAYBE THIS TIME  WILL HAVE A KITCHEN THAT CAN STAND IT AYAJBK THIS</pattern><template>Bo) ... I'm sorry that things did not succeed) was estimated to be Bo) Lance anything else)  still awaiting determination does not We makers Noodle place in the veins do not know my father honestly?</template></category><category><pattern>DID NOT SAY ANYTHING WELL  GOOD NIGHT  FROM WELL SEEMS STRANGE SITUATION MANDATE TAGGED (TIGRESS) DID NOT MEAN THAT AWAKENS YOU DO NOT BELONG TO HERE YES OF COURSE THIS ROOM I MEAN DO NOT BELONG TO THE PALACE OF GOOD SHAME ON YOU ALKONG FU  AND IF  YOU HAVE ANY RESPECT FOR US AND WHAT WE DO YOU HAVE TO GO BY MORNING LARGE FAN I SEE YOU FOUND THE SACRED TREE OF PEACHES  OF DIVINE WISDOM IS THIS WHAT   UNFORTUNATELY I THOUGHT IT EXTRAORDINARY TREE LEPAGE UNDERSTAND  YOU'RE EROSION  WHEN UNCOMFORTABLE AM NOT UNCOMFORTABLE  WHY THINK I'M DISTURBED</pattern><template>Why are you disturbed?</template></category><category><pattern>DRAGON WARRIOR TAKING SCROLL  OTHER PARTY OF CHINA NOW NEVER FROM YOU</pattern><template>you shouted ... I Dragon Warrior you?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES CAN NOT BELIEVE I AM YOUR SON BO)    I THINK IT IS TIME)  TO TELL YOU SOMETHING HE SHOULD TELL THE LONG TIME AGO WELL 01:05:51:10 01:05:53:08 COMPONENT OF THE SECRET BALLOT SOUP COME     COMPONENT IS THE SECRET NONE HEARD ME  NONE THERE IS A SECRET WAITED  ONLY NORMAL NOODLE SOUP ADDS A SPECIAL SAUCE  OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT</pattern><template>unnecessary, in order to create something distinctive  believes that it must be distinguished There is a secret has promised to house any teacher This is no longer your house  and I am not prepared teacher Yes, you have a favorite new pupil where (Bo) this?</template></category><category><pattern>OF DEPRIVATION OF FATEFUL</pattern><template>was never resolutions it is now Give me Scroll 01:08:33:12 01:08:36:17 prefer to die Tell me 01:09:32:23 01:09:34:14 Tell me 01:09:34:15 01:09:37:14 for as long as you are proud of your from the first moment I was proud of your and was proud that Oman I loved it very much to see what you turn him what I do for you I ... I  I'm sorry do not want an apology I want to girls Why?</template></category><category><pattern>BELIEVES THAT THE MATTER SO EASILY   I RECOGNIZE THE SECRET OF FORCE UNTOLD NOT FIRST YOU HAVE TO MASTER THE HIGHEST  LEVEL OF KONG FU AND THIS OF COURSE IS IMPOSSIBLE FOR A PERSON LIKE YOU PERSON LIKE ME</pattern><template>Yes, you see  fleshy and this silly Potbelly addition to the complete neglect of personal hygiene waited for this little Hardwood does not stop at this proximity  I can smell yourself Togo) said that I) Alamsake know this?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SORRY YOU SHOUTED  I WILL BRING YOU COMMEMORATION NO  I GO TO YOU IN COMMEMORATION THAT WONDERFUL DAY WELL AS TEACHER ALICE (TOGO)</pattern><template>Yes 00:09:50:07 00:09:51:17 and will not live to see Do your students ready?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>... I dream of b barley barley?  you dream of barley?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT SEEMS I DO</pattern><template>stopped  go to see the Dragon Warrior but I do not understand  I have dreamed a dream finally barley has lied  not dream of barley Pope love Kung Fu Come on, Beni  to prepare for action Well 00:13:43:14 00:13:46:03 What is being?</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD DESTROY EVERYTHING  AND EVERY ONE NOT EVACUATED VALLEY  (MUST PROTECT VILLAGERS FROM THE WRATH (TAI LONG WHAT ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>I am the killer    Why?    could delay sufficient  so that everyone escapes but you (Chevy), killings time I had finally paid  eighth mistakes Asamaoni all of you is time to supplement  trip without I'm proud of that I tagged must be knocked out safely Dear Little Come to find as mandate (snake) Friday Villagers southerners you (Mantis) northerners O (stork) from here see that Dragon Warrior Hello Abe Hello 01:04:34:08 01:04:36:03 quality of your return Bani It's good to come back us in the following must face it future of barley  pieces with vegetables well as I was thinking maybe this time  will have a kitchen that can stand it Ayajbk this?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  OF OUR VERY WELL  I'M EAGER TO BEGIN TO BEGIN WAIT NOW</pattern><template>Yes now 00:22:22:09 00:22:24:07 do not know if I can do everything  these movements unless we try not know yes, but perhaps we can find something  suited to getting more and what is your?</template></category><category><pattern>TEACHER (TOGO) WANTS TO SEE YOU TEACHER (TOGO) DEMAND   IS THERE A PROBLEM</pattern><template>why there is a problem  so I want to see my old friend If no problem?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WE CAN DO IS CONTINUE TRAINING WITH THE PASSAGE OF TIME WILL SHOW  COMBATANT REAL DRAGON WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE</pattern><template>Hello  Good Morning milestone I thought that little mastication has been suspended suspended?</template></category><category><pattern>I DREAM OF B BARLEY BARLEY   YOU DREAM OF BARLEY</pattern><template>Yes, I dream of what other?</template></category><category><pattern>WILL NOT BECOME A COMBATANT DRAGON  UNLESS LOST 500 THOUSAND KILOMETERS AND CLEANED TEETH WHAT THIS COMMOTION IS ISSUED   LAUGHED  I HAVE NOT HEARD OF BEFORE I WORK HARD MAYBE ONE DAY  YOUR EARS WOULD AUTHORIZE THIS IS GOOD 00:45:03:08 00:45:05:06 EARS   WORKED WITH YOU I THOUGHT IT A GOOD COURSE (CHEVY) WHAT DO YOU THINK  I DO YOU BELIEVE THAT THIS FUNNY  TAI LONG) ESCAPED FROM PRISON AND YOU ARE ADOPTING CHILDREN) WHY</pattern><template>is coming to Dragon Scroll  and you can only stop and I say that you do not have  sense of Humor Are you serious?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST KNOW WHAT IS HAPPENING  WHILE ELOY FINGER NOT YOU KNOW WHAT THE HARDEST PART   DOOR IS CLEAN HOLES SUBMIT  I HEAR YOU VERY WELL  BANDA MAY BE (TOGO) CHOSE  BUT WHEN YOU FINISHED I PROMISE YOU THAT YOU WISH DID NOT DO OF OUR WILL</pattern><template>Yes  of our very well, I'm eager to begin to begin Wait now?</template></category><category><pattern>DREAMED CRAZY DREAM WHAT   HOW WOULD YOU DREAM OF</pattern><template>why ...</template></category><category><pattern>YES 00:33:06:19 00:33:08:12 I AM DELIGHTED THAT THE (CHEVY) E MAIL I THINK THEY STARTED SASSON WING OF THERE AND TELL THEM THAT THE DRAGON WARRIOR  REAL RETURN GOOD MORNING MILESTONE BANDA BANDA YOU WAKE UP HAS SURRENDERED WHAT WE ARE DOING NOW ANY TEACHER  AND WENT BANDA WHO WILL BE THE DRAGON WARRIOR</pattern><template>what we can do is continue training with the passage of time will show  combatant real dragon What are you doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE BEEN A WONDERFUL HERO IS THE REAL SIGN OF HUMILITY BUT YES  YOU ARE WONDERFUL FIVE HAS DIED  NO  THEY BREATHED ASLEEP   NOT OPEN THEIR EYES WE WERE NOT EQUALS TO ATTACK THE NERVES BECOME STRONGER TAI LONG) )  STRONGER IS VERY FAST I THOUGHT THAT WE CAN STOP HIM COULD HAVE BEEN KILLERS WHY DID HE DO</pattern><template>to return and scares  here in our hearts, but will not succeed may succeed  slightly I'm afraid 01:00:11:22 01:00:14:05 you can defeat any Banda Are you kidding?  They can not are five teachers I'm only one but you have something that  not owned by one another actually think I'm ready grabbed the Dragon Scroll it for you waited .. What happens when read?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE IT WAS JUST A SILLY DREAM YOU CAN NOT IMAGINE THAT I AM PREPARED  TOE FU</pattern><template>Toe Foo  all of us our place in this world and my place here  and Place know here No, go to the table 5, 7 and 12 service with a smile Hey, students If you were trying Viejo I think Tigress), more speed) monkey) top speed) stork) high)  snake) rush) Why?</template></category><category><pattern>YES NOW 00:22:22:09 00:22:24:07 DO NOT KNOW IF I CAN DO EVERYTHING  THESE MOVEMENTS UNLESS WE TRY NOT KNOW YES  BUT PERHAPS WE CAN FIND SOMETHING  SUITED TO GETTING MORE AND WHAT IS YOUR</pattern><template>I do not know milestone  But let's start from zero, zero there is no level of zero perhaps I could begin this this? We use this to train children  and keep the door open when it is hot But if you insist five Angry  you more photo  Come on,  Banda  us what you can do will see you?  Or to wait even longer to work strike I just ate so I still digestible Kung Fu movements therefore may not be  would also be good later strikes only Why you?</template></category><category><pattern>DID NOT SAY THIS ACTUALLY   BUT I THOUGHT IN MY HEAD IF HE COULD READ MY THOUGHTS  OF WHAT WAS SAID HOPE THAT YOU LOVE THIS GOOD MUST TRY SOUP ABE SECRET IS  IN FACT  KNOWS THE SECRET COMPONENT WHY TALK ABOUT  THIS WONDERFUL YOU COOK A GOOD REALITY WAS WISHING THAT MY MOUTH MORE MANDATE (TIGRESS) MUST TRY THIS DRAGON WARRIOR SAID TO BE ABLE TO LIVE  FULL MONTH ON NOTHING BUT A SMALL PAPER AND ENERGY THE UNIVERSE I THINK THAT MY BODY DOES NOT KNOW  I DRAGON WARRIOR AFTER WOULD NEED MORE THAN THIS TO  JUICE AND THE UNIVERSE WHY</pattern><template>will not become a combatant Dragon  unless lost 500 thousand kilometers and cleaned teeth what this commotion is issued?  laughed? I have not heard of before I work hard maybe one day  your ears would authorize This is good 00:45:03:08 00:45:05:06 ears?  Worked with you I thought it a good course (Chevy) What do you think  I do you believe that this funny  Tai Long) escaped from prison and you are adopting children) Why?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW     I DO NOT KNOW    DO NOT KNOW THIS IS WHAT I THOUGHT THIS IS WHAT SHE TRAINS FOR IT NOT TRY SUSPENSIVE NOT TRYING TO STOP    WHY     COMING WITH YOU WHY</pattern><template>I eat while I would be uncomfortable no need to explain  (I thought you (the monkey is in store for candy in the top shelf see you know, I'm cinnamon No, I mean how arrived there?</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE KNOWS  BUT LEGEND SAYS  HE WILL BE ABLE TO HEAR BUTTERFLY FLAP REALLY  HMARAA YES  SEES LIGHT AT THE DEPTH OF THE CAVE  HAIR IS AROUND YOU AND MOVEMENT COULD I BROKE THROUGH THE WALLS  COULD I DO THAT MY HEART FOCUSED FOCUSED YES 01:01:47:20 01:01:49:04 READ IT AND ACHIEVED OR YOUR SORROW READ IT AND BECAME BELLIGERENT DRAGON IMPOSSIBLE REOPENED THANK 01:02:09:01 01:02:10:21 MAYBE YOU JUST ANALYSED WELL HERE IS THE IT EMPTY    WHY     YOU    NO  I'M NOT ALLOWED TO CONSIDER IT    EMPTY DO NOT UNDERSTAND WELL 01:02:43:24 01:02:46:02 TOGO) TURTLE WAS CRAZY IN THE END) NO  (TOGO) WAS THE WISEST OF US ALL COME 01:02:53:08 01:02:54:15 FACED MATTER  HAS CHOSEN PASSERBY COURSE  I'M NOT DRAGON WARRIOR OF DECEPTIVE</pattern><template>but it will stop (Tai Long)?</template></category></AIML>