<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>BUT NO ROOM FOR DOUBT</pattern><template>Oh, plenty. On every floor.</template></category><category><pattern>THE JAPANESE SHIPPING COMPANY SENT TWO MEN TO TALK TO ME  IN THE MEXICAN HOSPITAL WHERE I WAS RECOVERING</pattern><template>I still have a copy of the report.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ATE A RAT</pattern><template>We had food enough for weeks, but he found the rat in the first few days and he killed it, he dried it in the sun and ate it.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHICH STORY DO YOU PREFER</pattern><template>The one with the tiger.</template></category><category><pattern>AND REMEMBER TO BREATHE NOW  DON'T HOLD YOUR BREATH</pattern><template>Good boy.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  WHAT DO YOU THINK</pattern><template>It's a thunderstorm, let's go and watch.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALIZED LEAVING INDIA MUST HAVE BEEN HARDER FOR HIM THAN IT WAS FOR ME</pattern><template>So?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY BED</pattern><template>It was a human tooth.</template></category><category><pattern>TRY THIS METHOD</pattern><template>Step 1: Choose a day when waves are moderate, but regular.</template></category><category><pattern>IF GOD IS SO PERFECT  AND WE ARE NOT  WHY WOULD HE WANT TO CREATE ALL THIS</pattern><template>Why does he need us at all?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>Step 4: Disregard steps 1 through 3.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TO FIND A WAY TO FEED HIM</pattern><template>I can eat the biscuits, but God made tigers carnivores, So I must learn to catch fish.</template></category><category><pattern>AND FROM THEN ON  YOU WERE PI</pattern><template>Well no, not quite.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOVE ALL  DON'T LOSE HOPE</pattern><template>Few things can sap the spirit faster than sea sickness.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  INSTEAD OF LEAPING FROM ONE RELIGION TO THE NEXT  WHY NOT START WITH REASON</pattern><template>In a few hundred years, science has taken us farther in understanding the universe, than religion has in ten thousand.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING ELSE</pattern><template>You stupid.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM YOUR VESSEL</pattern><template>Whatever comes, I want to know.</template></category><category><pattern>AT THE EDGE OF THE JUNGLE  HE STOPPED</pattern><template>I was certain he was going to look back to me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR FATHER SAID ABOUT COMING BACK HERE</pattern><template>I am sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>RICHARD PARKER WAS A TIGER</pattern><template>Yeah, he got this name through a clerical error.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU LOOK INTO HIS EYES  YOU ARE SEEING YOUR OWN EMOTIONS REFLECTED BACK AT YOU</pattern><template>Nothing else.</template></category><category><pattern>VEGETARIAN  PLEASE</pattern><template>Oh, my sons and I are vegetarians.</template></category><category><pattern>A SEA ANCHOR IS USED AS A DRAG TO KEEP THE BOATS HEAD TO THE WIND</pattern><template>Proper use of them can increase control, and reduce sea sickness during rough seas.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THEN… WHAT MIGHT OCCUR IF YOU RELEASE GAS TOO QUICKLY</pattern><template>Pissing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IS ALSO USED IN MATHEMATICS TO REPRESENT THE RATIO OF ANY CIRCLE'S CIRCUMFERENCE TO ITS DIAMETER</pattern><template>An irrational number of infinite length, usually rounded to three digits, as 3 .14, PI.</template></category><category><pattern>RELIGION IS DARKNESS</pattern><template>My dear Appa believed himself part of the new India.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SLIPPED OUT OF MY HANDS AND SWAM AWAY  AND THE COOK CAME UP  AND HE PUNCHED ME ON THE SIDE OF MY HEAD  AND MY TEETH CLACKED AND I SAW STARS  I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO HIT ME AGAIN  BUT MOTHER STARTED POUNDING ON HIM  WITH HER FISTS  SCREAMING “MONSTER  MONSTER ” SHE YELLED AT ME TO GO TO THE RAFT</pattern><template>“Ni po da!” I thought she was coming with me, or I'd never have!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS BETWEEN A FATHER AND HIS SONS</pattern><template>Selvan, cut away!</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER THAT  THEY HAD NO MORE QUESTIONS</pattern><template>The investigators didn't seem to like the story, exactly.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO IT GOES WITH GOD</pattern><template>Mamaji was right.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT SOME WATER FOR YOU</pattern><template>In the zoo, we fed our tigers an average of five kilos of meat a day.</template></category><category><pattern>IN A FEW HUNDRED YEARS  SCIENCE HAS TAKEN US FARTHER IN UNDERSTANDING THE UNIVERSE  THAN RELIGION HAS IN TEN THOUSAND</pattern><template>That is true.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THIS NEW ONE IS SET IN INDIA</pattern><template>No, Portugal actually.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D ASSUMED YOUR FATHER WAS A MATHEMATICIAN  BECAUSE OF YOUR NAME</pattern><template>No, far from it: I was named after a swimming pool.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID NOT KNOW HINDUS SAID AMEN</pattern><template>Catholic Hindus do.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW RICHARD PARKER'S A TIGER  BUT… I WISH I HAD SAID: “IT'S OVER  WE SURVIVED…” THANK YOU FOR SAVING MY LIFE</pattern><template>I love you, Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>AS FOR GOD  I CAN ONLY TELL YOU MY STORY</pattern><template>You'll decide for yourself what you believe.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU'RE A HINDU FIRST</pattern><template>None of us knows God until someone introduces us.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN THE SHIP SANK</pattern><template>What else do you want from me?</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND VEGETARIAN</pattern><template>No, no. Not at all.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOW ME</pattern><template>There are no lines.</template></category><category><pattern>MY LAST CLASS OF THE DAY WAS MATHEMATICS</pattern><template>4… 3… 7… 5… 8… 5… 8… 5… 8… It's right!</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD LIKE TO BE BAPTIZED</pattern><template>So, you're a Christian, and a Muslim.</template></category><category><pattern>FEW THINGS CAN SAP THE SPIRIT FASTER THAN SEA SICKNESS</pattern><template>Waves are more strongly felt when the boat turns sideways to the current.</template></category><category><pattern>NO PISSING IN THE SCHOOLYARD</pattern><template>Even the teacher started doing it.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  I BROUGHT ALL THE BISCUITS AND WATER ON THE RAFT WITH ME  TO KEEP THEM SAFE… IDIOT</pattern><template>Hunger can change everything you ever thought you knew about yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>I FILLED MY STORES WITH FRESH WATER  ATE SEA WEED UNTIL MY STOMACH COULD TAKE NO MORE  AND BROUGHT AS MANY MEERKATS AS I COULD FIT INTO THE STORAGE LOCKER FOR RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>I couldn't leave without him, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>WITHOUT RICHARD PARKER  I WOULD HAVE DIED BY NOW</pattern><template>My fear of him keeps me alert.</template></category><category><pattern>SCAR THEM</pattern><template>That boy almost lost his arm.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>Amma… Appa, Ravi.</template></category><category><pattern>LET THAT SPIRITUAL ENERGY PULSE THROUGH YOU  AND OUT INTO THE WORLD</pattern><template>Through “Abhinaya”.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO HELP THEM</pattern><template>My family is back there!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WISHED ME WELL… AND THEY LEFT</pattern><template>So the story is… Both the zebra and the sailor… broke their leg.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  MOST TRAVELERS COLLECT POSTCARDS OR TEA CUPS ON THEIR JOURNEYS  BUT NOT MAMAJI</pattern><template>Mamaji collects swimming pools.</template></category><category><pattern>TELLING STORIES IS HIGHLY RECOMMENDED</pattern><template>Above all, don't lose hope.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THIS PLACE  CLOSEST TO THE OCEAN  YOU MIGHT THINK YOU ARE IN THE SOUTH OF FRANCE</pattern><template>A few blocks inland, there's a canal.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S QUITE A STORY</pattern><template>I'd assumed your father was a mathematician, because of your name.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WANTED TO FIND OUT WHY THE SHIP SANK</pattern><template>They didn't believe me, either.</template></category><category><pattern>IT BROKE MY HEART</pattern><template>You know, my father was right.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>So I was sitting in this coffee house in Pondicherry one afternoon mourning my loss, when this old man at the table next to me, struck up a conversation.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FOR YOU</pattern><template>No!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL… THAT'S UP TO YOU</pattern><template>The story is yours now.</template></category><category><pattern>SO… WHAT DID YOU DO</pattern><template>I told them another story.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SAILOR WAS THE SAME MAN WHO BROUGHT RICE AND GRAVY  THE BUDDHIST</pattern><template>We didn't understand much what he said, only that he was suffering.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN  I MET ANANDI</pattern><template>Mother made me study music.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHERE WOULD WE GO</pattern><template>Our life is here, Appa!</template></category><category><pattern>NOT DELIBERATELY  OF COURSE</pattern><template>So then… What might occur if you release gas too quickly?</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN WE RETURNED THE NEXT FOR OUR FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL  I WAS PREPARED</pattern><template>Present, sir!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURE  GRAVY IS NOT MEAT</pattern><template>Is taste. You try?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WOULD SAY THAT ABOUT A NICE MEAL</pattern><template>As for God, I can only tell you my story.</template></category><category><pattern>GO  RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>Go!</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID YOU HAD A STORY THAT WOULD MAKE ME BELIEVE IN GOD</pattern><template>He would say that about a nice meal.</template></category><category><pattern>MAMAJI TELLS ME YOU'RE A LEGEND AMONG SAILORS  TOO… OUT THERE  ALL ALONE</pattern><template>Oh, I don't even know how to sail.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF THE TOWN COUNCIL STOPS SUPPORTING US  I DON'T KNOW WHERE WE WILL BE</pattern><template>So, it is what we have to do.</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE TIME WE REACHED THE MEXICAN SHORE  I WAS AFRAID TO LET GO OF THE BOAT</pattern><template>My strength was gone, I was so weak.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS… WHAT ARE YOU THINKING</pattern><template>This is between a father and his sons.</template></category><category><pattern>HURRAY</pattern><template>God's storm!</template></category><category><pattern>AND NONE IN THE COMPANY… OF AN ADULT BENGAL TIGER</pattern><template>– Hi, Dad.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK THAT TIGER IS YOUR FRIEND</pattern><template>He's an animal, not a playmate!</template></category><category><pattern>“WE NEED MORE FOOD OR WE'LL DIE  THAS WAS THE WHOLE POINT ” “WHAT WAS THE WHOLE POINT”  MOTHER ASKED</pattern><template>You let that poor boy die in order to get bait, you monster!</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN'T UNDERSTAND GOD NOR HIS PERFECTION</pattern><template>But we can understand God's son, and his suffering, as we would of brothers.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>GO</pattern><template>Go on home, I'll leave you alone.</template></category><category><pattern>MINE  YOU UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>Yours! Mine!</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN IF I CAN'T PROVE IT</pattern><template>You know, I've left so much behind… my family, the zoo, India, Anandi… I suppose in the end the whole of life becomes an act of letting go.</template></category><category><pattern>APPA  RAVI  I'M HAPPY I'M GOING TO SEE YOU SOON</pattern><template>Can you feel the rain?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  I WAS THE ONLY ONE WHO SURVIVED THE SHIPWRECK</pattern><template>The Japanese shipping company sent two men to talk to me, in the Mexican hospital where I was recovering.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HAVE I FORGOTTEN ANYTHING</pattern><template>I think you set the stage, So far, we have an Indian boy named after a French swimming pool, on a Japanese ship full of animals, heading to Canada.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE SHIPPING MOST OF THE ANIMALS FOR SALE IN NORTH AMERICA  WE CAN GET FREIGHTER PASSAGE FOR THE WHOLE FAMILY</pattern><template>So… It's settled.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS LAMB IS EXQUISITE</pattern><template>It's the best dish on the table.</template></category><category><pattern>CATHOLIC HINDUS</pattern><template>We get to feel guilty before hundreds of gods, instead of just one.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES THIS MEAN</pattern><template>In the dance, you went from 'batanka', which means the forest, And then you did… and you did… 'Sanputa', which means something that is hidden.</template></category><category><pattern>– BORN AND RAISED… IN PONDICHERRY  IN WHAT WAS THE FRENCH PART OF INDIA</pattern><template>My father owned the zoo.</template></category><category><pattern>4… 3… 7… 5… 8… 5… 8… 5… 8… IT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>He's really doing this!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD HE SEND HIS OWN SON TO SUFFER FOR THE SINS OF ORDINARY PEOPLE</pattern><template>Because he loves us.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL GET THERE</pattern><template>It was four days out of Manila, above the Mariana trench, the deepest part on earth.</template></category><category><pattern>DOUBT IS USEFUL</pattern><template>It keeps Faith a living thing.</template></category><category><pattern>CHRIST NEEDS YOU  GOD</pattern><template>Longing for his words!</template></category><category><pattern>THE LONGER I LISTENED TO THE PRIEST  THE MORE I CAME TO LIKE THE SON OF GOD</pattern><template>Thank you Vishnu, for introducing me to Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT A PILE OF TOOLS  A BUCKET  A KNIFE  A PENCIL  MIGHT BECOME MY GREATEST TREASURES  WITHOUT KNOWING RICHARD PARKER WAS HERE MIGHT EVER BRING ME PEACE</pattern><template>In times like these, I remember that he has as little experience of the real world as I do.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL DECIDE FOR YOURSELF WHAT YOU BELIEVE</pattern><template>Fair enough.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST LIKE YOU LIKE CRICKET  PI HAS HIS OWN INTERESTS</pattern><template>No, Gita. Ravi has a point, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T MEAN TO PUSH YOU</pattern><template>And you have our deepest sympathies.</template></category><category><pattern>I MET KRISHNA FIRST</pattern><template>The gods were my superheroes, growing up.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU HAVE OUR DEEPEST SYMPATHIES</pattern><template>But we have come a long way, and we are no closer to understanding why the ship sank.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING  NO NO NO NO NO</pattern><template>Not for gravy.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE NO LINES</pattern><template>Set your house in order, and dig in for the battle to survive.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER WAS A BUSINESSMAN</pattern><template>He had never tended the animals himself.</template></category><category><pattern>IS TASTE  YOU TRY</pattern><template>Don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE SEEN IT IN THEIR EYES</pattern><template>Find Selvan.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHERE'D THE TOOTH COME FROM</pattern><template>Years ago, some poor fellow just like me must have found himself stranded on that island.</template></category><category><pattern>CATHOLIC HINDUS DO</pattern><template>Catholic Hindus?</template></category><category><pattern>ADIKA</pattern><template>Ravi.</template></category><category><pattern>MY NAME IS PI PATEL</pattern><template>I have been in a shipwreck.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS FOUR DAYS OUT OF MANILA  ABOVE THE MARIANA TRENCH  THE DEEPEST PART ON EARTH</pattern><template>Our ship, the Simsum, pushed on, bullishly indifferent to its surroundings.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ONLY NEED TO CONVERT TO THREE MORE RELIGIONS  PISCINE  AND YOU'LL SPEND YOUR LIFE ON HOLIDAY</pattern><template>Are you going to Mecca this year, Swami Jesus?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AN AMAZING STORY</pattern><template>Will you really let me write it?</template></category><category><pattern>FLATTEN HIS EARS TO HIS HEAD  GROWL  THAT HE WOULD BRING OUR RELATIONSHIP TO AN END IN SOME WAY</pattern><template>But he just stared ahead into the jungle.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE GOING TO TELL ME HOW YOU GOT YOUR NAME  I THINK</pattern><template>Oh yes! I got it from something Mamaji once told my father.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I WAS SITTING IN THIS COFFEE HOUSE IN PONDICHERRY ONE AFTERNOON MOURNING MY LOSS  WHEN THIS OLD MAN AT THE TABLE NEXT TO ME  STRUCK UP A CONVERSATION</pattern><template>Yeah, Mamaji he does that.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER ALL WE HAD BEEN THROUGH  HE DIDN'T EVEN LOOK BACK</pattern><template>But I have to believe there was more in these eyes than my own reflection staring back at me.</template></category><category><pattern>MY STRENGTH WAS GONE  I WAS SO WEAK</pattern><template>I was afraid that in two feet of water, so close to deliverance, I would drown.</template></category><category><pattern>THE COOK WAS A RESOURCEFUL MAN</pattern><template>It was a week later that he… because of me.</template></category><category><pattern>MY ARABIC WAS NEVER VERY GOOD</pattern><template>But the sound and feel of the words brought me closer to God.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THIRSTY GOT TOO BIG  THE HUNTER SOLD HIM TO OUR ZOO  BUT THE NAMES GOT SWITCHED ON THE PAPERWORK</pattern><template>The hunter was listed as Thirsty, and the tiger was called Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'LL ALL BE HERE SOON</pattern><template>Hello!</template></category><category><pattern>PROPER USE OF THEM CAN INCREASE CONTROL  AND REDUCE SEA SICKNESS DURING ROUGH SEAS</pattern><template>For castaways who must share their lifeboats with large dangerous carnivores, it's advisable to establish your territory as your own.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE HE LOVES US</pattern><template>God made himself approachable to us, human, so we could understand him.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM PISCINE MOLITOR PATEL</pattern><template>Know to all as: “PI” The sixteenth letter of the Greek alphabet.</template></category><category><pattern>LIFTING AN ENTIRE MOUNTAIN TO SAVE HIS FRIEND  LAKSHMANA</pattern><template>Ganesh, the elephant headed, risking his life to defend the honor of his mother, Parvati.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GODS WERE MY SUPERHEROES  GROWING UP</pattern><template>Hanuman, the monkey god.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  PORTUGAL ACTUALLY</pattern><template>But it's cheaper living in India.</template></category><category><pattern>THE STRESS OF TRAVELING IS NOT GOOD FOR THE ANIMALS  AND IT HELPS WITH THE SEA SICKNESS</pattern><template>We don't want to be cleaning up, after a seasick orangutan.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU CRAZY</pattern><template>We will get hit by lightning.</template></category><category><pattern>COME OUT</pattern><template>Richard Parker! Come out, you have to see this!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M READY NOW</pattern><template>Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S SELVAM</pattern><template>We shouldn't be in here without him.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAW HOW MY LIFE WOULD END  IF I STAYED ON THAT ISLAND</pattern><template>Alone, forgotten.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A VENUS FLY TRAP</pattern><template>Yes. The whole island.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  PLENTY  ON EVERY FLOOR</pattern><template>Doubt is useful.</template></category><category><pattern>AS IT ALSO HAPPENED  MY MOTHER WAS A BOTANIST IN THE GARDENS</pattern><template>They met, married, and a year later my brother Ravi was born.</template></category><category><pattern>WORDS ARE ALL I HAVE LEFT TO HANG ON TO</pattern><template>Everything mixed up; fragmented.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ENOUGH  ORDER  ORDER</pattern><template>When we returned the next for our first day of school, I was prepared.</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS LISTENING  YOU SEE</pattern><template>We have talked about it for some time.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF WE SELL THEM  WE WILL HAVE ENOUGH TO START A NEW LIFE</pattern><template>But where would we go?</template></category><category><pattern>THE HUNTER WAS LISTED AS THIRSTY  AND THE TIGER WAS CALLED RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>We laughed about it.</template></category><category><pattern>ESTABLISH A STRICT SCHEDULE FOR EATING  KEEPING WATCH  AND GETTING REST</pattern><template>Do not drink urine or seawater.</template></category><category><pattern>TIGER</pattern><template>Richard Parker was a tiger?</template></category><category><pattern>WE DIDN'T UNDERSTAND MUCH WHAT HE SAID  ONLY THAT HE WAS SUFFERING</pattern><template>He'd broken his leg horribly in the fall.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULDN'T LEAVE WITHOUT HIM  OF COURSE</pattern><template>It would be killing him.</template></category><category><pattern>I MET CHRIST IN THE MOUNTAINS WHEN I WAS 12</pattern><template>We were visiting relatives, tea growers in Munnar.</template></category><category><pattern>NONE OF US KNOWS GOD UNTIL SOMEONE INTRODUCES US</pattern><template>I was first introduced to God as a Hindu.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO GAVE YOU THE PERMISSION TO COME BACK HERE</pattern><template>You have just ignored everything I've ever taught you?</template></category><category><pattern>VISHNU  THE SUPREME SOUL  THE SOURCE OF ALL THINGS</pattern><template>Vishnu sleeps, floating on the shoreless cosmic ocean, and we are the stuff of his dreaming.</template></category><category><pattern>DO WE</pattern><template>My father was a businessman.</template></category><category><pattern>THE COMPASSIONATE</pattern><template>The merciful!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HE GOT THIS NAME THROUGH A CLERICAL ERROR</pattern><template>A hunter caught him drinking from a stream when he was a cub, and named him “Thirsty”.</template></category><category><pattern>MY WIFE IS HERE</pattern><template>Do you want to stay for dinner?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT GAVE ME A SIGN TO CONTINUE MY JOURNEY</pattern><template>By the time we reached the Mexican shore, I was afraid to let go of the boat.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE 33 MILLION GODS IN THE HINDU RELIGION</pattern><template>How can I not come to know a few of them?</template></category><category><pattern>WITHOUT SURPRISES  WITHOUT… ANIMALS OR ISLANDS</pattern><template>Yes. The truth.</template></category><category><pattern>RICHARD PARKER NEVER SAW ME AS HIS FRIEND</pattern><template>After all we had been through, he didn't even look back.</template></category><category><pattern>FAITH IS A HOUSE WITH MANY ROOMS</pattern><template>But no room for doubt?</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE ZOO  WE FED OUR TIGERS AN AVERAGE OF FIVE KILOS OF MEAT A DAY</pattern><template>Richard Parker will be getting hungry soon.</template></category><category><pattern>“STOP WHINING AND BE HAPPY”  HE SAID</pattern><template>“We need more food or we'll die, thas was the whole point!” “What was the whole point”, mother asked?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKS AS THOUGH YOUR DRUGS HAVEN'T WORN OFF YET</pattern><template>Orange Juice!</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN THE TEACHER STARTED DOING IT</pattern><template>Not deliberately, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE HAS SEEN THAT FLOATING ISLAND SINCE</pattern><template>And you won't read about those trees in any nature book.</template></category><category><pattern>WE LAUGHED ABOUT IT</pattern><template>And the name stuck!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S AN INCREDIBLE COOK</pattern><template>I didn't know you had a wife.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID YOU MEAN  THE GOD OF LOVE IS HIDING IN THE FOREST</pattern><template>No, that also means 'the Lotus flower'.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>I never thought a small piece of shade could bring me so much happiness.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHY I DIDN'T MAKE HER GO FIRST</pattern><template>I think about that every day.</template></category><category><pattern>SPECTACLE</pattern><template>Don't let the stories and pretty lies fool you, boys.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT BOY ALMOST LOST HIS ARM</pattern><template>But he's just a boy.</template></category><category><pattern>– AND YOUR NAME</pattern><template>– Uh?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING MIXED UP; FRAGMENTED</pattern><template>Can't tell day dreams, night dreams from reality anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>A STORY WE CAN ALL BELIEVE</pattern><template>So a story without things you've never seen before.</template></category><category><pattern>RICHARD PARKER WILL BE GETTING HUNGRY SOON</pattern><template>Tigers are powerful swimmers, and if he gets hungry enough, I'm afraid the little bit of water between us won't be any protection.</template></category><category><pattern>CHALLENGE  I'LL GIVE YOU TWO RUPEES</pattern><template>Run into that church, and drink the holy water.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE DYING  RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>HE STRETCHED HIS LEGS  AND WALKED ALONG THE SHORE</pattern><template>At the edge of the jungle, he stopped.</template></category><category><pattern>MA</pattern><template>Apa!</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WAS DELIVERED ON SHORT NOTICE BY A HERPETOLOGIST  WHO WAS THERE TO CHECK ON THE BENGAL MONITOR LIZARD</pattern><template>Mother and I were both healthy, but the poor lizard escaped, and was trampled by a frightened cassowary.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY FOR THE CHOPPY RIDE</pattern><template>Mine! You understand?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL I KNOW IS THAT EVENTUALLY HE DIED  AND THE ISLAND DIGESTED HIM  LEAVING BEHIND ONLY HIS TEETH</pattern><template>I saw how my life would end, if I stayed on that island.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  THIS IS GOD  RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>Why are you scaring him?</template></category><category><pattern>OYÉ</pattern><template>Hurray!</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WAS NAMED “PISCINE MOLITOR PATEL”</pattern><template>Imagine me trying to explain that name.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT I'M SAYING</pattern><template>Pi!</template></category><category><pattern>TIGERS ARE POWERFUL SWIMMERS  AND IF HE GETS HUNGRY ENOUGH  I'M AFRAID THE LITTLE BIT OF WATER BETWEEN US WON'T BE ANY PROTECTION</pattern><template>I need to find a way to feed him.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP BUSY  BUT AVOID UNNECESSARY EXERTION</pattern><template>The mind can be kept get occupied by playing card games, “Twenty Questions” or “Eye Spy”.</template></category><category><pattern>DURING THE DAY  THOSE POOLS HELD FRESH WATER</pattern><template>But at night, some chemical process turned the water in those pools into acid.</template></category><category><pattern>SCHOOL WAS A BORE  NOTHING BUT FACTS  FRACTIONS AND FRENCH</pattern><template>Words and patterns that went on and on without end, just like my irrational nickname.</template></category><category><pattern>JE M'APPELLE PISCINE MOLITOR PATEL</pattern><template>Dit: Pi.</template></category><category><pattern>A STORM  RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>Christ needs you, God!</template></category><category><pattern>THE COOK THREW ME A LIFE BUOY AND PULL ME ABOARD  AND MOTHER HELD ON SOME BANANAS AND MADE IT TO THE LIFE BOAT</pattern><template>The cook… was a disgusting man.</template></category><category><pattern>LEAVE NOW</pattern><template>We have to go!</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS A LOT TO TAKE IN… TO FIGURE OUT WHAT THAT ALL MEANS</pattern><template>No, if it happened, it happened.</template></category><category><pattern>YEARS AGO  SOME POOR FELLOW JUST LIKE ME MUST HAVE FOUND HIMSELF STRANDED ON THAT ISLAND</pattern><template>And like me, he thought he might stay there forever.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T WANT TO BE CLEANING UP  AFTER A SEASICK ORANGUTAN</pattern><template>Do we?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I DO TEACH THE COURSE ON THE KABBALA AT THE UNIVERSITY</pattern><template>And why not?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM HAPPY BUDDHIST</pattern><template>So I eat rice next to gravy.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE RICHARD PARKER CAN'T BE TAMED</pattern><template>But with God's will, he can be trained.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE'S JUST A BOY</pattern><template>He will be a man sooner than you think.</template></category><category><pattern>– PRESENT  SIR</pattern><template>And from then on, you were Pi?</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE I WAS BORN  HE SAID: “IF YOU WANT YOUR SON TO HAVE A CLEAN SOUL  YOU MUST TAKE HIM ONE DAY TO SWIM IN THE PISCINE MOLITOR”</pattern><template>I never understood why my father took this so much to heart.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I HAVE TO BELIEVE THERE WAS MORE IN THESE EYES THAN MY OWN REFLECTION STARING BACK AT ME</pattern><template>I know it, I felt it.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>We're dying, Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHOULDN'T BE IN HERE WITHOUT HIM</pattern><template>Stop worrying.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>I was asleep, something woke me up, it could have been an explosion, I can't be sure.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR LIFE IS HERE  APPA</pattern><template>Canada.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP IT  STOP IT</pattern><template>No!</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OUR COMPANY CAN UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>A story we can all believe.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL YOU HAVE TO KNOW IS THAT HE LOVES US</pattern><template>God so loved his world that he gave his only son.</template></category><category><pattern>HE CAME UP WITH ONE</pattern><template>He ran a hotel, and he got the idea to open a zoo in the local botanical gardens instead.</template></category><category><pattern>FRENCH CLASS WAS NEXT</pattern><template>Je m'appelle Piscine Molitor Patel.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  FAR FROM IT: I WAS NAMED AFTER A SWIMMING POOL</pattern><template>There was a swimming pool named “Pi”?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE IT IS  FOR YOUR ENJOYMENT  AND INSTRUCTION</pattern><template>The show you've been waiting for all your life, will soon begin!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T WANT GRAVY</pattern><template>Pas de probleme.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NOT AT ALL</pattern><template>– And your name?</template></category><category><pattern>IMAGINE ME TRYING TO EXPLAIN THAT NAME</pattern><template>I barely made it to the age of eleven.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE TRY  PISSING</pattern><template>But I still had the whole day ahead of me.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR ANIMALS ARE WORTH FAR MORE ABROAD THAN HERE IN INDIA</pattern><template>And if the town council stops supporting us, I don't know where we will be.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT COLUMBUS WAS LOOKING FOR INDIA</pattern><template>It takes a lot of work to sell a zoo.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO</pattern><template>Anybody!</template></category><category><pattern>GOD'S STORM</pattern><template>Ma!</template></category><category><pattern>GOD… THANK YOU FOR GIVING ME MY LIFE</pattern><template>I'm ready now.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE WE LEFT  ANANDI AND I HAD TIME ENOUGH TO BREAK EACH OTHER'S HEART</pattern><template>Of course, I'd promised I would come back one day.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAME TWO YEARS AFTER THAT</pattern><template>Sounds magical.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I LOOK FORWARD TO READING IT</pattern><template>You can't.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WORLD HAD LOST SOME OF ITS ENCHANTMENT</pattern><template>School was a bore, nothing but facts, fractions and French.</template></category><category><pattern>– UH</pattern><template>You were going to tell me how you got your name, I think.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  I'D PROMISED I WOULD COME BACK ONE DAY</pattern><template>It's funny… I remember everything else about our last day.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE… ¨ BEFORE… – HEY  “PISSING”</pattern><template>Are you pissing right now?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHAT ALWAYS HURTS THE MOST  IS NOT TAKING A MOMENT TO SAY GOODBYE</pattern><template>I was never able to thank my father, for all I'd learnt from him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN GEOGRAPHY</pattern><template>These are the first twenty decimal places of Pi.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LET THAT POOR BOY DIE IN ORDER TO GET BAIT  YOU MONSTER</pattern><template>He got furious, he started towards her with his fists raised, And Mother slapped him hard right across the face!</template></category><category><pattern>BANANAS DON'T FLOAT</pattern><template>You said the orangutan floated to you on a bundle of bananas, but bananas don't float.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS ALONE IN THE LIFEBOAT… DRIFTING ACROSS THE PACIFIC OCEAN… AND I SURVIVED</pattern><template>After that, they had no more questions.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>It is a lot to take in… to figure out what that all means.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS A HUMAN TOOTH</pattern><template>Don't you see the island was carnivorous?</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE WAY  I ENJOYED YOUR FIRST BOOK</pattern><template>So this new one is set in India?</template></category><category><pattern>THE STORY IS YOURS NOW</pattern><template>“Mr. Patel's is an astounding story.” Of courage and endurance, unparalleled in the history of shipwrecks.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE BOTH RAISED IN A ZOO BY THE SAME MASTER</pattern><template>Now we've been orphaned, left to face our ultimate master together.</template></category><category><pattern>HANUMAN  THE MONKEY GOD</pattern><template>Lifting an entire mountain to save his friend, Lakshmana.</template></category><category><pattern>PI</pattern><template>They're serving dinner below.</template></category><category><pattern>HE JUST KEPT LOOKING AT ME  HIS EYES WERE SO… I'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND THE POINT OF THAT MAN'S SUFFERING</pattern><template>I can still hear him, A happy Buddhist who only ate rice and gravy We didn't save him, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>No one has seen that floating island since.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU THINKING</pattern><template>Are you out of your mind?</template></category><category><pattern>IN ANY CASE  WE ARE NOT HERE TO TALK ABOUT BANANAS OR MEERKATS</pattern><template>Look, I just told a long story, and I'm very tired.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR SHIP  THE SIMSUM  PUSHED ON  BULLISHLY INDIFFERENT TO ITS SURROUNDINGS</pattern><template>It moved with the slow massive confidence of a continent.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A VISION</pattern><template>Come on, this is God, Richard Parker!</template></category><category><pattern>I GREW RESTLESS  SEARCHING FOR SOMETHING THAT MIGHT BRING MEANING BACK INTO MY LIFE</pattern><template>And then, I met Anandi.</template></category><category><pattern>I SPENT THE NEXT DAY PREPARING THE BOAT</pattern><template>I filled my stores with fresh water, ate sea weed until my stomach could take no more, and brought as many meerkats as I could fit into the storage locker for Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>I WEPT LIKE A CHILD  NOT BECAUSE I WAS OVERWHELMED AT HAVING SURVIVED  ALTHOUGH I WAS</pattern><template>I was weeping because Richard Parker left me… so unceremoniously.</template></category><category><pattern>HI</pattern><template>Very nice to meet you.</template></category><category><pattern>IN PERFORMING “SALAH”  THE GROUND I TOUCHED BECAME HOLY GROUND  AND I FOUND A FEELING OF SERENITY AND BROTHERHOOD</pattern><template>This lamb is exquisite.</template></category><category><pattern>I TRAINED WITH HIM THREE TIMES A WEEK AT THE ASHRAM</pattern><template>His lessons would save my life in the end.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING</pattern><template>Of course.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>We'll get there.</template></category><category><pattern>PRESENT  SIR</pattern><template>Piscine Patel.</template></category><category><pattern>TO TELL HIM WITHOUT HIS LESSONS… I WOULD NEVER HAVE SURVIVED</pattern><template>I know Richard Parker's a tiger, but… I wish I had said: “It's over, we survived…” thank you for saving my life.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD A WIFE</pattern><template>And a cat and two children.</template></category><category><pattern>AND… YOU'RE… THE TIGER</pattern><template>Can I ask you something?</template></category><category><pattern>WAVES ARE MORE STRONGLY FELT WHEN THE BOAT TURNS SIDEWAYS TO THE CURRENT</pattern><template>A sea anchor is used as a drag to keep the boats head to the wind.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT</pattern><template>I'm sorry, Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE DAY  MAMAJI SAID TO MY FATHER  THAT OF ALL THE POOLS IN THE WORLD  THE MOST BEAUTIFUL WAS A PUBLIC POOL IN PARIS</pattern><template>That the water there was so clear, you could make your morning coffee with it.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I EAT RICE NEXT TO GRAVY</pattern><template>I'm sure, gravy is not meat.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S STILL FINDING HIS WAY</pattern><template>And how can he find his way, if he does not choose a path?</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN YOUR GAZE OUT ON TO THE HORIZON</pattern><template>Let that spiritual energy pulse through you, and out into the world.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE BEEN IN A SHIPWRECK</pattern><template>I am on a lifeboat, alone… with a tiger.</template></category><category><pattern>IT TAKES A LOT OF WORK TO SELL A ZOO</pattern><template>Before we left, Anandi and I had time enough to break each other's heart.</template></category><category><pattern>CARNIVOROUS</pattern><template>Like a Venus fly trap?</template></category><category><pattern>AS A CHILD  HE'D HAD POLIO</pattern><template>He used to lie in bed wracked with pain, wondering where God was.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD BOY</pattern><template>I hope you don't mind vegetarian.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS SUCH AN EVIL MAN  BUT WORSE STILL HE… HE BROUGHT THE EVIL OUT IN ME</pattern><template>And I have to live with that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE YOU SCARING HIM</pattern><template>I've lost my family, I've lost everything!</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOUR STORY DOES HAVE AN HAPPY ENDING</pattern><template>Well… that's up to you.</template></category><category><pattern>SCIENCE CAN TEACH US MORE ABOUT WHAT IS OUT THERE  BUT NOT WHAT IS IN HERE</pattern><template>Yeah. Some eat meat, some eat vegetable, I do not expect us to all to agree about everything, but I'd much rather have you believe in something I don't agree with, than to accept everything blindly.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GET TO FEEL GUILTY BEFORE HUNDREDS OF GODS  INSTEAD OF JUST ONE</pattern><template>But you're a Hindu first.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S REALLY DOING THIS</pattern><template>By the end of that day, I was “PI Patel”, school legend.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU DO NOT CONCENTRATE  YOU CANNOT EXPRESS YOUR LOVE OF GOD THROUGH DANCE</pattern><template>Feel the ground beneath your feet.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>Touch it Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH SUFFICIENT REPETITION  THE ANIMAL WILL ASSOCIATE THE SOUND OF THE WHISTLE WITH THE DISCOMFORT OF SEA SICKNESS</pattern><template>Similar methods have long been used by circus trainers, though they generally lack access to rough seas.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S SEE THEN  WHERE TO BEGIN</pattern><template>Pondicherry… is the French Riviera of India.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIED</pattern><template>The morning after the cook got his first dorado and I didn't understand what he'd done at first, but Mother did, and I had never seen Mother so angry.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY SHOULD IT HAVE TO MEAN ANYTHING</pattern><template>But some of it is pretty incredible.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S THE MOST MAGNIFICENT CREATURE WE'VE EVER HAD HERE</pattern><template>Look at the way he's turning his head.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>Words are all I have left to hang on to.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  GET AWAY</pattern><template>It's my bed.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HOW CAN HE FIND HIS WAY  IF HE DOES NOT CHOOSE A PATH</pattern><template>Listen, instead of leaping from one religion to the next, why not start with reason?</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE'RE GOING TO LIVE TOGETHER  WE HAVE TO LEARN TO COMMUNICATE</pattern><template>Maybe Richard Parker can't be tamed.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAME TO FAITH THROUGH HINDUISM  AND I FOUND GOD'S LOVE THROUGH CHRIST</pattern><template>But God wasn't finished with me yet.</template></category><category><pattern>DIT: PI</pattern><template>Then geography.</template></category><category><pattern>SO… I KEPT SAYING “I'M SORRY  I'M SORRY”</pattern><template>He just kept looking at me, his eyes were so… I'll never understand the point of that man's suffering.</template></category><category><pattern>MAMAJI  HE DIDN'T TELL ME EVERYTHING  HE JUST SAID I SHOULD LOOK YOU UP WHEN I GOT BACK TO MONTREAL</pattern><template>So what were you doing in Pondicherry?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT GONNA CAUSE ANY TROUBLE</pattern><template>The stress of traveling is not good for the animals, and it helps with the sea sickness.</template></category><category><pattern>I BARELY MADE IT TO THE AGE OF ELEVEN</pattern><template>Before… ¨ Before… – Hey, “Pissing”!</template></category><category><pattern>THE MERCIFUL</pattern><template>Come out!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO HELP MY FAMILY</pattern><template>We have to help them!</template></category><category><pattern>A FEW BLOCKS INLAND  THERE'S A CANAL</pattern><template>Just beyond that is Indian Pondicherry.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY MET  MARRIED  AND A YEAR LATER MY BROTHER RAVI WAS BORN</pattern><template>I came two years after that.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS WEEPING BECAUSE RICHARD PARKER LEFT ME… SO UNCEREMONIOUSLY</pattern><template>It broke my heart.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT AT NIGHT  SOME CHEMICAL PROCESS TURNED THE WATER IN THOSE POOLS INTO ACID</pattern><template>Acid that dissolved those fish.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL DONE  I GIVE TO YOU  THE ASTOUNDING BENGAL TIGER</pattern><template>Hello, Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>SELVAN</pattern><template>.. And so has placed the country in a state of emergency   Under the directive, the states of Gujarat and Tamil Nadu will be placed under the direct authority of the central government…  Things changed after the day of Appa's lesson.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I DON'T  I'M AFRAID HIS LAST MEAL WILL BE A SKINNY VEGETARIAN BOY</pattern><template>Patience!</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE</pattern><template>Isn't that why Mamaji sent you here, after all?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM ON A LIFEBOAT  ALONE… WITH A TIGER</pattern><template>Please send help.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER ALL  YOU CANNOT KNOW THE STRENGTH OF YOUR FAITH UNTIL IT HAS BEEN TESTED</pattern><template>Where's Selvam?</template></category><category><pattern>COME INSIDE AND HAVE SOME DINNER</pattern><template>Vegetarian, please.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YOU REALLY LET ME WRITE IT</pattern><template>Of course.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ELSE DO YOU WANT FROM ME</pattern><template>A story that won't make us look like fools.</template></category><category><pattern>– WE HAVE TO GO NOW</pattern><template>– No please, my father!</template></category><category><pattern>“NI PO DA ” I THOUGHT SHE WAS COMING WITH ME  OR I'D NEVER HAVE</pattern><template>I don't know why I didn't make her go first.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY SONS AND I ARE VEGETARIANS</pattern><template>Do you have anything  No no no no no!</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T SCARE  OKAY</pattern><template>Stay here!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS YOUR BOY  ORANGE JUICE</pattern><template>Don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT SOME OF IT IS PRETTY INCREDIBLE</pattern><template>See, I was the only one who survived the shipwreck.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO… BEFORE WE GET INTO TROUBLE</pattern><template>I want to see him closer.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TALKED ABOUT IT FOR SOME TIME</pattern><template>Do you understand what I'm saying?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'D BROKEN HIS LEG HORRIBLY IN THE FALL</pattern><template>We tried to set it as best we could, but the leg became infected.</template></category><category><pattern>AND LIKE ME  HE THOUGHT HE MIGHT STAY THERE FOREVER</pattern><template>But all that the island gave him by day, it took away again by night.</template></category><category><pattern>VERY NICE TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>Adika.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WANT TO STAY FOR DINNER</pattern><template>She's an incredible cook!</template></category><category><pattern>GOD SO LOVED HIS WORLD THAT HE GAVE HIS ONLY SON</pattern><template>The longer I listened to the priest, the more I came to like the son of God.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AN HINDU  OF COURSE</pattern><template>And a Jew, I suppose.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT DRINK URINE OR SEAWATER</pattern><template>Keep busy, but avoid unnecessary exertion.</template></category><category><pattern>IT KEEPS FAITH A LIVING THING</pattern><template>After all, you cannot know the strength of your faith until it has been tested.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT BEGINS WITH THINKING RATIONALLY</pattern><template>You understand?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THE WAY HE'S TURNING HIS HEAD</pattern><template>Showing off… like a dancer.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUMPED OVER AND TURNED BACK JUST AS THE KNIFE CAME OUT</pattern><template>There wasn't anything I could do.</template></category><category><pattern>SO A STORY WITHOUT THINGS YOU'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE</pattern><template>That's right.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO I WAITED FOR HIS RETURN</pattern><template>I knew he wouldn't be late.</template></category><category><pattern>TO THINK HOW MANY HOURS HE SPENT  WITH ONLY MEERKATS FOR COMPANY</pattern><template>How much loneliness taken on him.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS A WEEK LATER THAT HE… BECAUSE OF ME</pattern><template>Because I couldn't hold on this stupid turtle.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THE TRUTH</pattern><template>So… what did you do?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DOES HE NEED US AT ALL</pattern><template>All you have to know is that he loves us.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PLANTS  THE WATER AND THOSE POOLS  THE VERY GROUND ITSELF</pattern><template>During the day, those pools held fresh water.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MOVED WITH THE SLOW MASSIVE CONFIDENCE OF A CONTINENT</pattern><template>Did you hear that, Ravi?</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO KILL HER RIGHT THEN</pattern><template>But he didn't… The cook didn't stop with bait either, no… The sailor… he went the same way the rat went.</template></category><category><pattern>I STILL HAVE A COPY OF THE REPORT</pattern><template>They had insurance claims to settle.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP IT  NO</pattern><template>Stop it! Stop it!</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE DOING THIS FOR YOU AND RAVI</pattern><template>Come inside and have some dinner.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING I'LL NEVER FORGET</pattern><template>I lost my whole family.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR RELIGION WAS THE ONLY LINK SHE HAD TO HER PAST</pattern><template>I met Christ in the mountains when I was 12.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND</pattern><template>Who gave you the permission to come back here?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT ALL THAT THE ISLAND GAVE HIM BY DAY  IT TOOK AWAY AGAIN BY NIGHT</pattern><template>To think how many hours he spent, with only meerkats for company.</template></category><category><pattern>STEP 2: WITH THE LIFEBOAT FACING INTO THE WAVES  MAKING THE RIDE AS COMFORTABLE AS POSSIBLE  BLOW YOUR WHISTLE SOOTHINGLY</pattern><template>Step 3: Turn the lifeboat sideways to the waves, accompanied by harsh, aggressive use of the whistle.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER A FEW HOURS  A MEMBER OF MY OWN SPECIES FOUND ME</pattern><template>He left and returned with a group who carried me away.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  GO AWAY  GO AWAY</pattern><template>Ama!</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT TO SEE HIM CLOSER</pattern><template>You're not the zookeeper!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL JUST SCAR THEM FOR LIFE</pattern><template>Scar them?</template></category><category><pattern>HE LEFT AND RETURNED WITH A GROUP WHO CARRIED ME AWAY</pattern><template>I wept like a child, not because I was overwhelmed at having survived, although I was.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE JUST STARED AHEAD INTO THE JUNGLE</pattern><template>And then, Richard Parker, my fierce companion, the terrible one who kept me alive… disappeared forever from my life.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S YOUNG  SANTOSH</pattern><template>He's still finding his way.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS LESSONS WOULD SAVE MY LIFE IN THE END</pattern><template>A mouthful of water will not harm you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND A HYENA KILLED THE ZEBRA AND THE ORANGUTAN</pattern><template>So… The hyena is the cook… the sailor is the zebra… your mother is the orangutan.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER OWNED THE ZOO</pattern><template>And I was delivered on short notice by a herpetologist, who was there to check on the Bengal monitor lizard.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT GOD WASN'T FINISHED WITH ME YET</pattern><template>God works in mysterious ways.</template></category><category><pattern>I BET MOTHER AND FATHER FOUND HIM</pattern><template>They'll all be here soon.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I STILL HAD THE WHOLE DAY AHEAD OF ME</pattern><template>French class was next.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T</pattern><template>I threw it out.</template></category><category><pattern>OR TO ROME FOR YOUR CORONATION AS POPE PIUS</pattern><template>You stay out of this, Ravi.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>I'm sorry, what are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>TENDING TO HIS NEEDS GIVES MY LIFE FOCUS</pattern><template>Dolphins.</template></category><category><pattern>WE TRIED TO SET IT AS BEST WE COULD  BUT THE LEG BECAME INFECTED</pattern><template>And the cook said that we had to do something, but he… died.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I COULDN'T HOLD ON THIS STUPID TURTLE</pattern><template>It slipped out of my hands and swam away, and the cook came up, and he punched me on the side of my head, and my teeth clacked and I saw stars, I thought he was going to hit me again, but Mother started pounding on him, with her fists, screaming “monster, monster!” She yelled at me to go to the raft.</template></category><category><pattern>KNOW TO ALL AS: “PI” THE SIXTEENTH LETTER OF THE GREEK ALPHABET</pattern><template>Which is also used in mathematics to represent the ratio of any circle's circumference to its diameter.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MORNING AFTER THE COOK GOT HIS FIRST DORADO AND I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND WHAT HE'D DONE AT FIRST  BUT MOTHER DID  AND I HAD NEVER SEEN MOTHER SO ANGRY</pattern><template>“Stop whining and be happy”, he said.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FAMILY IS BACK THERE</pattern><template>Leave now!</template></category><category><pattern>OH YES  I GOT IT FROM SOMETHING MAMAJI ONCE TOLD MY FATHER</pattern><template>You see, most travelers collect postcards or tea cups on their journeys, but not Mamaji.</template></category><category><pattern>FIND SELVAN</pattern><template>Animals do not think like we do.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE DID</pattern><template>And I was named “Piscine Molitor Patel”.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO RICHARD PARKER WENT AHEAD OF ME</pattern><template>He stretched his legs, and walked along the shore.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DIDN'T BELIEVE ME  EITHER</pattern><template>Thousands of meerkats, on an floating carnivorous island, and no one has ever seen it.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MIND CAN BE KEPT GET OCCUPIED BY PLAYING CARD GAMES  “TWENTY QUESTIONS” OR “EYE SPY”</pattern><template>Community singing is another surefire way to lift the spirits.</template></category><category><pattern>THROUGH “ABHINAYA”</pattern><template>Anandi, come to the front, lead them.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE</pattern><template>I brought you this.</template></category><category><pattern>MY DEAR APPA BELIEVED HIMSELF PART OF THE NEW INDIA</pattern><template>As a child, he'd had polio.</template></category><category><pattern>COMMUNITY SINGING IS ANOTHER SUREFIRE WAY TO LIFT THE SPIRITS</pattern><template>Telling stories is highly recommended.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU WON'T READ ABOUT THOSE TREES IN ANY NATURE BOOK</pattern><template>And yet, if I hadn't found those shores, I would have died.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE MUSLIM QUARTER IS JUST TO THE WEST</pattern><template>When the French handed Pondicherry back to us in 1954, the town decided that some sort of commemoration was in order.</template></category><category><pattern>SOUNDS MAGICAL</pattern><template>Growing up… Amen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOURS  MINE</pattern><template>You understand?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  GITA  RAVI HAS A POINT  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>You cannot follow three different religions at the same time, Piscine.</template></category><category><pattern>﻿1 LIFE OF PI TRANSCRIPT AND SYNC: JCDR – SO  YOU WERE RAISED IN A ZOO</pattern><template>– Born and raised… In Pondicherry, in what was the French part of India.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW IT  I FELT IT</pattern><template>Even if I can't prove it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE SOUND AND FEEL OF THE WORDS BROUGHT ME CLOSER TO GOD</pattern><template>In performing “Salah”, the ground I touched became holy ground, and I found a feeling of serenity and brotherhood.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE A WHOLE LIFE AHEAD OF YOU</pattern><template>We are doing this for you and Ravi.</template></category><category><pattern>PREPARE TO BE AMAZED</pattern><template>Here it is, for your enjoyment, and instruction.</template></category><category><pattern>HUNGER CAN CHANGE EVERYTHING YOU EVER THOUGHT YOU KNEW ABOUT YOURSELF</pattern><template>Here, it's yours!</template></category><category><pattern>TWO CARTONS OF BISCUITS… 93 CANS OF WATER… I'M SORRY</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SHOW YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR ALL YOUR LIFE  WILL SOON BEGIN</pattern><template>Are you ready for the miracle event?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THIS IS A LESSON I DO NOT WANT THEM EVER TO FORGET</pattern><template>Selvan!</template></category><category><pattern>ACID THAT DISSOLVED THOSE FISH</pattern><template>That sent the meerkats scurrying into the trees, and Richard Parker running to the boat.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T YOU SEE THE ISLAND WAS CARNIVOROUS</pattern><template>Carnivorous?</template></category><category><pattern>SO THE STORY IS… BOTH THE ZEBRA AND THE SAILOR… BROKE THEIR LEG</pattern><template>And a hyena killed the zebra and the orangutan.</template></category><category><pattern>– HI  DAD</pattern><template>– Get in.</template></category><category><pattern>IN TIMES LIKE THESE  I REMEMBER THAT HE HAS AS LITTLE EXPERIENCE OF THE REAL WORLD AS I DO</pattern><template>We were both raised in a zoo by the same master.</template></category><category><pattern>ANIMALS DO NOT THINK LIKE WE DO</pattern><template>People who forget that, get themselves killed. That tiger… is not your friend.</template></category><category><pattern>CANADA</pattern><template>I have some opportunities for work in Winnipeg.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS CERTAIN HE WAS GOING TO LOOK BACK TO ME</pattern><template>Flatten his ears to his head, growl, that he would bring our relationship to an end in some way.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW WE'VE BEEN ORPHANED  LEFT TO FACE OUR ULTIMATE MASTER TOGETHER</pattern><template>Without Richard Parker, I would have died by now.</template></category><category><pattern>“MR  PATEL'S IS AN ASTOUNDING STORY ” OF COURAGE AND ENDURANCE  UNPARALLELED IN THE HISTORY OF SHIPWRECKS</pattern><template>Very few castaways can claim to have survived so long at sea.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE BETTER STORY</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FEAR OF HIM KEEPS ME ALERT</pattern><template>Tending to his needs gives my life focus.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT</pattern><template>Thinking.</template></category><category><pattern>HE GOT FURIOUS  HE STARTED TOWARDS HER WITH HIS FISTS RAISED  AND MOTHER SLAPPED HIM HARD RIGHT ACROSS THE FACE</pattern><template>I was stunned!</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER'S BEST FRIEND  MY SWIMMING GURU</pattern><template>I trained with him three times a week at the Ashram.</template></category><category><pattern>OVER HERE</pattern><template>Richard Parker?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE LEAVING INDIA</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>I SURRENDER</pattern><template>What more do you want?</template></category><category><pattern>– R VELUSAMI</pattern><template>– Present, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>MAMAJI WAS RIGHT</pattern><template>It's an amazing story.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  ORANGE JUICE  I DON'T HAVE ANY SEA SICKNESS MEDICINE FOR YOU</pattern><template>Is it right?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD A LOTUS FLOWER HIDE IN THE FOREST</pattern><template>This is Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN  RICHARD PARKER  MY FIERCE COMPANION  THE TERRIBLE ONE WHO KEPT ME ALIVE… DISAPPEARED FOREVER FROM MY LIFE</pattern><template>After a few hours, a member of my own species found me.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOT TO GO</pattern><template>There! Look there!</template></category><category><pattern>STEP 1: CHOOSE A DAY WHEN WAVES ARE MODERATE  BUT REGULAR</pattern><template>Step 2: With the lifeboat facing into the waves, making the ride as comfortable as possible, blow your whistle soothingly.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HE'S MY “HONORARY” UNCLE</pattern><template>I call him “Mamaji”.</template></category><category><pattern>MOTHER MADE ME STUDY MUSIC</pattern><template>And one day, my teacher came down with the flu.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO GO</pattern><template>Who let all the animals out, uh?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE WAS RESOURCEFUL</pattern><template>It was his idea to build the raft to catch fish, we would have died in those first few days without him.</template></category><category><pattern>WRITING A NOVEL</pattern><template>By the way, I enjoyed your first book.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIDN'T EVEN FIGHT BACK  HE KNEW HE'D GONE TOO FAR</pattern><template>Even by his own standards.</template></category><category><pattern>ZEBRA  ZEBRA</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>VERY IMPRESSIVE… PI</pattern><template>Now sit down.</template></category><category><pattern>I I JUST WANTED TO SAY HELLO TO HIM</pattern><template>You think that tiger is your friend.</template></category><category><pattern>FEEL THE GROUND BENEATH YOUR FEET</pattern><template>Open your gaze out on to the horizon.</template></category><category><pattern>COULDN'T LOOK AWAY… HE THREW HER BODY OVERBOARD  AND THEN THE SHARKS CAME</pattern><template>And I saw her, they… saw… Next day, I killed him.</template></category><category><pattern>AMMA… APPA  RAVI</pattern><template>Appa, Ravi, I'm happy I'm going to see you soon.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WITH GOD'S WILL  HE CAN BE TRAINED</pattern><template>No!</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT'S WHAT GAVE HIM HIS HUGE CHEST AND SKINNY LEGS  THAT MADE HIM SUCH A GREAT SWIMMER</pattern><template>Is Francis actually your uncle, he said he was friends with your father?</template></category><category><pattern>SO… THE HYENA IS THE COOK… THE SAILOR IS THE ZEBRA… YOUR MOTHER IS THE ORANGUTAN</pattern><template>And… you're… the tiger.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYBODY</pattern><template>No!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE JUST IGNORED EVERYTHING I'VE EVER TAUGHT YOU</pattern><template>I I just wanted to say Hello to him.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT AT THE VERY END  YOU DID… THIS</pattern><template>None of the others dancers did that.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY</pattern><template>It's hard to believe, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE HEARD SOMETHING</pattern><template>He is listening, you see?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS NEVER ABLE TO THANK MY FATHER  FOR ALL I'D LEARNT FROM HIM</pattern><template>To tell him without his lessons… I would never have survived!</template></category><category><pattern>THINKING</pattern><template>Two cartons of biscuits… 93 cans of water… I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>LOTUS FLOWER IS HIDING IN THE FOREST</pattern><template>Why would a Lotus flower hide in the forest?</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT WERE YOU DOING IN PONDICHERRY</pattern><template>Writing a novel.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE COOK SAID THAT WE HAD TO DO SOMETHING  BUT HE… DIED</pattern><template>The cook said he'd do it, but mother and I had to hold the man down.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE HERE BECAUSE A JAPANESE CARGO SHIP SANK IN THE PACIFIC</pattern><template>Something I'll never forget.</template></category><category><pattern>ANANDI  COME TO THE FRONT  LEAD THEM</pattern><template>Why are you following me?</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF I HADN'T DISCOVERED THAT TOOTH  I WOULD HAVE BEEN LOST  ALONE FOREVER</pattern><template>Even when God seemed to have abandoned me, he was watching.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THE WHOLE ISLAND</pattern><template>The plants, the water and those pools, the very ground itself.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE HAVE COME A LONG WAY  AND WE ARE NO CLOSER TO UNDERSTANDING WHY THE SHIP SANK</pattern><template>Because I don't know!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WE WON'T  IT'LL HIT THE BRIDGE FIRST</pattern><template>Don't tempt the storm, Pi.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD WORKS IN MYSTERIOUS WAYS</pattern><template>And so it was he introduced himself to me again, this time by the name of Allah.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU HEAR THAT  RAVI</pattern><template>Yes, what do you think?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS FIRST INTRODUCED TO GOD AS A HINDU</pattern><template>There are 33 million gods in the Hindu religion.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU SET THE STAGE  SO FAR  WE HAVE AN INDIAN BOY NAMED AFTER A FRENCH SWIMMING POOL  ON A JAPANESE SHIP FULL OF ANIMALS  HEADING TO CANADA</pattern><template>Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>COM'ON</pattern><template>My name is Pi Patel.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN WHEN GOD SEEMED TO HAVE ABANDONED ME  HE WAS WATCHING</pattern><template>Even when he seemed indifferent to my suffering, he was watching.</template></category><category><pattern>I THREW IT OUT</pattern><template>Two years trying to bring this thing to life, and then one day… sputtered, coughed and died.</template></category><category><pattern>STEP 3: TURN THE LIFEBOAT SIDEWAYS TO THE WAVES  ACCOMPANIED BY HARSH  AGGRESSIVE USE OF THE WHISTLE</pattern><template>With sufficient repetition, the animal will associate the sound of the whistle with the discomfort of sea sickness.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FUNNY… I REMEMBER EVERYTHING ELSE ABOUT OUR LAST DAY</pattern><template>But I don't remember saying goodbye.</template></category><category><pattern>THE COOK SAID HE'D DO IT  BUT MOTHER AND I HAD TO HOLD THE MAN DOWN</pattern><template>And I believed him, we needed to do it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD A GOD DO THAT</pattern><template>Why would he send his own son to suffer for the sins of ordinary people?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>He's the most magnificent creature we've ever had here.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S AN ANIMAL  NOT A PLAYMATE</pattern><template>Animals have souls.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU PISSING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Look at him, he is pissing.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THE FRENCH HANDED PONDICHERRY BACK TO US IN 1954  THE TOWN DECIDED THAT SOME SORT OF COMMEMORATION WAS IN ORDER</pattern><template>My father was a clever businessman.</template></category><category><pattern>THE COOK… WAS A DISGUSTING MAN</pattern><template>He ate a rat!</template></category><category><pattern>WHO LET ALL THE ANIMALS OUT  UH</pattern><template>– We have to go now!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CANNOT FOLLOW THREE DIFFERENT RELIGIONS AT THE SAME TIME  PISCINE</pattern><template>Why not?</template></category><category><pattern>IS FRANCIS ACTUALLY YOUR UNCLE  HE SAID HE WAS FRIENDS WITH YOUR FATHER</pattern><template>Well, he's my “honorary” uncle.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO IT WAS HE INTRODUCED HIMSELF TO ME AGAIN  THIS TIME BY THE NAME OF ALLAH</pattern><template>My Arabic was never very good.</template></category><category><pattern>A MOUTHFUL OF WATER WILL NOT HARM YOU</pattern><template>But panic will.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO SAIL</pattern><template>And I wasn't alone out there, Richard Parker was with me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I BELIEVED HIM  WE NEEDED TO DO IT</pattern><template>So… I kept saying “I'm sorry, I'm sorry”.</template></category><category><pattern>PISSING</pattern><template>That's enough! Order! Order!</template></category><category><pattern>GO  COME ON</pattern><template>Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>FOR CASTAWAYS WHO MUST SHARE THEIR LIFEBOATS WITH LARGE DANGEROUS CARNIVORES  IT'S ADVISABLE TO ESTABLISH YOUR TERRITORY AS YOUR OWN</pattern><template>Try this method.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU FOR COMING IN THE FORM OF A FISH AND SAVING OUR LIFE</pattern><template>Thank you!</template></category><category><pattern>I BROUGHT YOU THIS</pattern><template>Why would a God do that?</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE END OF THAT DAY  I WAS “PI PATEL”  SCHOOL LEGEND</pattern><template>Mamaji tells me you're a legend among sailors, too… Out there, all alone.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT ALSO MEANS 'THE LOTUS FLOWER'</pattern><template>Lotus flower is hiding in the forest?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW SIT DOWN</pattern><template>– R Velusami?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN YOU DID 'CHATURA'</pattern><template>But at the very end, you did… this.</template></category><category><pattern>RICHARD PARKER  COME OUT  YOU HAVE TO SEE THIS</pattern><template>It's beautiful!</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO HAS PLACED THE COUNTRY IN A STATE OF EMERGENCY   UNDER THE DIRECTIVE  THE STATES OF GUJARAT AND TAMIL NADU WILL BE PLACED UNDER THE DIRECT AUTHORITY OF THE CENTRAL GOVERNMENT…  THINGS CHANGED AFTER THE DAY OF APPA'S LESSON</pattern><template>The world had lost some of its enchantment.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST BE THIRSTY</pattern><template>Here.</template></category><category><pattern>SAY “I'M SORRY ” WHAT HAVE YOU DONE  PISCINE</pattern><template>You know what your father said about coming back here?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID THE ORANGUTAN FLOATED TO YOU ON A BUNDLE OF BANANAS  BUT BANANAS DON'T FLOAT</pattern><template>Of course they do, you try it for yourself!</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I TOLD HIM MY ABANDONED BOOK  HE SAID:  SO  A CANADIAN WHO'S COME TO FRENCH INDIA    IN SEARCH FOR A STORY  WELL  MY FRIEND    I KNOW AN INDIAN IN FRENCH CANADA  WITH THE MOST INCREDIBLE STORY TO TELL    IT MUST BE FATE THAT THE TWO OF YOU SHOULD MEET   WELL  I HAVEN'T SPOKEN ABOUT RICHARD PARKER IN SO MANY YEARS</pattern><template>So what has Mamaji already told you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  MY FATHER WAS RIGHT</pattern><template>Richard Parker never saw me as his friend.</template></category><category><pattern>A STORY THAT WON'T MAKE US LOOK LIKE FOOLS</pattern><template>We need a simpler story for our report.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU READY FOR THE MIRACLE EVENT</pattern><template>Well done! I give to you, the astounding Bengal tiger!</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE WHO FORGET THAT  GET THEMSELVES KILLED  THAT TIGER… IS NOT YOUR FRIEND</pattern><template>When you look into his eyes, you are seeing your own emotions reflected back at you.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SWIMS IN EVERY POOL HE COMES UPON</pattern><template>One day, Mamaji said to my father, that of all the pools in the world, the most beautiful was a public pool in Paris.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOU'RE A CHRISTIAN  AND A MUSLIM</pattern><template>And an Hindu, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU  RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>You'll always be with me… But I can't be with you.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS TRUE</pattern><template>Your father is right.</template></category><category><pattern>SO</pattern><template>Yeah, have I forgotten anything?</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE END  GOD DIDN'T SAVE HIM  WESTERN MEDICINE DID</pattern><template>My Amma went to college and thought our family was part of the new India as well, But then her parents cut her off, because they thought she was marrying beneath her.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  LORD VISHNU</pattern><template>Thank you for coming in the form of a fish and saving our life!</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAD NEVER TENDED THE ANIMALS HIMSELF</pattern><template>I realized leaving India must have been harder for him than it was for me.</template></category><category><pattern>AN IRRATIONAL NUMBER OF INFINITE LENGTH  USUALLY ROUNDED TO THREE DIGITS  AS 3  14  PI</pattern><template>Very impressive… PI.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FATHER IS RIGHT</pattern><template>Science can teach us more about what is out there, but not what is in here.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SORRY</pattern><template>I was… What are you thinking?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I JUST TOLD A LONG STORY  AND I'M VERY TIRED</pattern><template>We are here because a Japanese cargo ship sank in the Pacific!</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER THOUGHT A SMALL PIECE OF SHADE COULD BRING ME SO MUCH HAPPINESS</pattern><template>That a pile of tools, a bucket, a knife, a pencil, might become my greatest treasures, without knowing Richard Parker was here might ever bring me peace.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SOME EAT MEAT  SOME EAT VEGETABLE  I DO NOT EXPECT US TO ALL TO AGREE ABOUT EVERYTHING  BUT I'D MUCH RATHER HAVE YOU BELIEVE IN SOMETHING I DON'T AGREE WITH  THAN TO ACCEPT EVERYTHING BLINDLY</pattern><template>And that begins with thinking rationally.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU GOING TO MECCA THIS YEAR  SWAMI JESUS</pattern><template>Or to Rome for your coronation as Pope Pius?</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE SEND HELP</pattern><template>God… I give myself to You.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE SAVE MY FAMILY</pattern><template>Don't scare, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>WITH ONE WORD  MY NAME WENT FROM AN ELEGANT FRENCH SWIMMING POOL TO A STINKING INDIAN LATRINE</pattern><template>I was “pissing” everywhere.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN WHEN HE SEEMED INDIFFERENT TO MY SUFFERING  HE WAS WATCHING</pattern><template>And when I was beyond all hope of saving, he gave me rest.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  LET'S EAT</pattern><template>I did not know Hindus said Amen.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE BEST DISH ON THE TABLE</pattern><template>You're all missing out.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T LET THE STORIES AND PRETTY LIES FOOL YOU  BOYS</pattern><template>Religion is darkness.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAD INSURANCE CLAIMS TO SETTLE</pattern><template>They wanted to find out why the ship sank.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE FOLLOWING ME</pattern><template>What does this mean?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S COME TO US</pattern><template>It's a vision!</template></category><category><pattern>I STRUGGLED TO SHORE  AND FELL UPON THE SAND</pattern><template>It was warm and soft, like pressing my face against the cheek of God.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>We are selling the zoo.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ASKED IF I COULD TAKE HIS PLACE  PLAYING RHYTHMS FOR A DANCE CLASS</pattern><template>No!</template></category><category><pattern>I LOST MY WHOLE FAMILY</pattern><template>We don't mean to push you.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL NO  NOT QUITE</pattern><template>Nice try, Pissing.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SENT THE MEERKATS SCURRYING INTO THE TREES  AND RICHARD PARKER RUNNING TO THE BOAT</pattern><template>But where'd the tooth come from?</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN BY HIS OWN STANDARDS</pattern><template>He left the knife out on the bench, and I did to him what he did to the sailor.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STAY OUT OF THIS  RAVI</pattern><template>Just like you like cricket, Pi has his own interests.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHEN I WAS BEYOND ALL HOPE OF SAVING  HE GAVE ME REST</pattern><template>That gave me a sign to continue my journey.</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME TO PI'S ARK</pattern><template>Where is your boy, Orange Juice?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE LOST MY FAMILY  I'VE LOST EVERYTHING</pattern><template>I surrender!</template></category><category><pattern>DOLPHINS</pattern><template>Hey, Richard Parker!</template></category><category><pattern>HE LEFT THE KNIFE OUT ON THE BENCH  AND I DID TO HIM WHAT HE DID TO THE SAILOR</pattern><template>He was such an evil man, but worse still he… He brought the evil out in me!</template></category><category><pattern>GOD MADE HIMSELF APPROACHABLE TO US  HUMAN  SO WE COULD UNDERSTAND HIM</pattern><template>We can't understand God nor his perfection.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE ANIMALS ARE OURS</pattern><template>And if we sell them, we will have enough to start a new life.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS SO SPENT  I COULD HARDLY MOVE</pattern><template>And so Richard Parker went ahead of me.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THE WATER THERE WAS SO CLEAR  YOU COULD MAKE YOUR MORNING COFFEE WITH IT</pattern><template>That a single swim there changed his life.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STUPID</pattern><template>Say “I'm sorry.” What have you done, Piscine?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS STUNNED</pattern><template>I thought he was going to kill her right then.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE  BELIEVING IN EVERYTHING AT THE SAME TIME  IS THE SAME AS NOT BELIEVING IN ANYTHING AT ALL</pattern><template>He's young, Santosh.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YET  IF I HADN'T FOUND THOSE SHORES  I WOULD HAVE DIED</pattern><template>And if I hadn't discovered that tooth, I would have been lost, alone forever.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WASN'T ALONE OUT THERE  RICHARD PARKER WAS WITH ME</pattern><template>Richard Parker?</template></category><category><pattern>AND NO ONE CAN PROVE WHICH STORY IS TRUE AND WHICH IS NOT</pattern><template>In both stories, the ship sinks, my family dies, and I suffer.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  IT'S YOURS</pattern><template>It's time to settle this.</template></category><category><pattern>HE USED TO LIE IN BED WRACKED WITH PAIN  WONDERING WHERE GOD WAS</pattern><template>In the end, God didn't save him, Western medicine did.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE SERVING DINNER BELOW</pattern><template>Piscine.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER WAS A CLEVER BUSINESSMAN</pattern><template>He came up with one.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW WE HAVE TO SEND OUR BOY INTO THE MIDDLE OF THE PACIFIC  AND… AND MAKE ME BELIEVE IN GOD</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IF IT HAPPENED  IT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Why should it have to mean anything?</template></category><category><pattern>SUCH A BRUTE  THAT MAN</pattern><template>But he was resourceful.</template></category><category><pattern>FAIR ENOUGH</pattern><template>Let's see then. Where to begin?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE  LOOK THERE</pattern><template>Zebra! Zebra!</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU VISHNU  FOR INTRODUCING ME TO CHRIST</pattern><template>I came to faith through Hinduism, and I found God's love through Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT THE ZOOKEEPER</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW HE WOULDN'T BE LATE</pattern><template>Richard Parker!</template></category><category><pattern>FOUR OF US SURVIVED  THE COOK AND THE SAILOR WERE ALREADY ABOARD</pattern><template>The cook threw me a life buoy and pull me aboard, and Mother held on some bananas and made it to the life boat.</template></category><category><pattern>RUN INTO THAT CHURCH  AND DRINK THE HOLY WATER</pattern><template>You must be thirsty.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY NOT</pattern><template>Because, believing in everything at the same time, is the same as not believing in anything at all.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT HAS MAMAJI ALREADY TOLD YOU</pattern><template>He said you had a story that would make me believe in God.</template></category><category><pattern>A HUNTER CAUGHT HIM DRINKING FROM A STREAM WHEN HE WAS A CUB  AND NAMED HIM “THIRSTY”</pattern><template>When Thirsty got too big, the hunter sold him to our zoo, but the names got switched on the paperwork.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL GET HIT BY LIGHTNING</pattern><template>No, we won't, it'll hit the bridge first.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU TWO STORIES ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED OUT IN THE OCEAN… NEITHER EXPLAINS WHAT CAUSED THE SINKING OF THE SHIP</pattern><template>And no one can prove which story is true and which is not.</template></category><category><pattern>GANESH  THE ELEPHANT HEADED  RISKING HIS LIFE TO DEFEND THE HONOR OF HIS MOTHER  PARVATI</pattern><template>Vishnu, the supreme soul, the source of all things.</template></category><category><pattern>SO… IT'S SETTLED</pattern><template>We will sail like Columbus.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>I bet mother and father found him.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE DIDN'T… THE COOK DIDN'T STOP WITH BAIT EITHER  NO… THE SAILOR… HE WENT THE SAME WAY THE RAT WENT</pattern><template>The cook was a resourceful man.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS OUR THIRD THERE  RAVI AND I WERE TERRIBLY BORED</pattern><template>Challenge. I'll give you two rupees.</template></category><category><pattern>PATIENCE</pattern><template>Wait!</template></category><category><pattern>AND SOMEWHERE  TWO EYES WERE SMILING AT HAVING ME THERE</pattern><template>I was so spent, I could hardly move.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WAY OF GOD</pattern><template>That's quite a story.</template></category><category><pattern>ANIMALS HAVE SOULS</pattern><template>I have seen it in their eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>MOTHER AND I WERE BOTH HEALTHY  BUT THE POOR LIZARD ESCAPED  AND WAS TRAMPLED BY A FRIGHTENED CASSOWARY</pattern><template>The way of karma, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID PISSING  GUYS</pattern><template>Pissing!</template></category><category><pattern>PAS DE PROBLEME</pattern><template>Hello.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TIME TO SETTLE THIS</pattern><template>If we're going to live together, we have to learn to communicate.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS HIS IDEA TO BUILD THE RAFT TO CATCH FISH  WE WOULD HAVE DIED IN THOSE FIRST FEW DAYS WITHOUT HIM</pattern><template>The sailor was the same man who brought rice and gravy, the Buddhist.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I DON'T REMEMBER SAYING GOODBYE</pattern><template>Pi?</template></category><category><pattern>PARDON</pattern><template>Pas de probleme.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T HIDE YOURSELF</pattern><template>He's come to us!</template></category><category><pattern>AND A CAT AND TWO CHILDREN</pattern><template>So your story does have an happy ending.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN'T TELL DAY DREAMS  NIGHT DREAMS FROM REALITY ANYMORE</pattern><template>A storm, Richard Parker!</template></category><category><pattern>ORANGE JUICE</pattern><template>Welcome to Pi's ark.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THIS SON  I COULDN'T GET HIM OUT OF MY HEAD</pattern><template>If God is so perfect, and we are not, why would he want to create all this?</template></category><category><pattern>STOP WORRYING</pattern><template>I have seen him do this a thousand times.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS A SWIMMING POOL NAMED “PI”</pattern><template>You see, my uncle Francis was born with too much water in his lungs.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONE WITH THE TIGER</pattern><template>That's the better story.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAD FOOD ENOUGH FOR WEEKS  BUT HE FOUND THE RAT IN THE FIRST FEW DAYS AND HE KILLED IT  HE DRIED IT IN THE SUN AND ATE IT</pattern><template>Such a brute, that man.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I HAVE TO LIVE WITH THAT</pattern><template>I was alone in the lifeboat… drifting across the Pacific ocean… and I survived.</template></category><category><pattern>GROWING UP… AMEN</pattern><template>Yeah, let's eat.</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON HOME  I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE</pattern><template>I'll respect that, promise.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE CAN UNDERSTAND GOD'S SON  AND HIS SUFFERING  AS WE WOULD OF BROTHERS</pattern><template>That made no sense!</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE SOME OPPORTUNITIES FOR WORK IN WINNIPEG</pattern><template>I'll be shipping most of the animals for sale in North America, we can get freighter passage for the whole family.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS ASLEEP  SOMETHING WOKE ME UP  IT COULD HAVE BEEN AN EXPLOSION  I CAN'T BE SURE</pattern><template>And then the ship sank.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT A SINGLE SWIM THERE CHANGED HIS LIFE</pattern><template>Before I was born, he said: “If you want your son to have a clean soul, you must take him one day to swim in the piscine Molitor”.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE ARE THE FIRST TWENTY DECIMAL PLACES OF PI</pattern><template>My last class of the day was mathematics.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  IT IS WHAT WE HAVE TO DO</pattern><template>Do you understand?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE SELLING THE ZOO</pattern><template>The zoo was never ours to sell, the land belongs to the town.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER UNDERSTOOD WHY MY FATHER TOOK THIS SO MUCH TO HEART</pattern><template>But he did.</template></category><category><pattern>UH SORRY  YOU'VE BEEN… WORRIED</pattern><template>For my family.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL SAIL LIKE COLUMBUS</pattern><template>But Columbus was looking for India!</template></category><category><pattern>TOUCH IT RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>It's for you.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WASN'T ANYTHING I COULD DO</pattern><template>Couldn't look away… He threw her body overboard, and then the sharks came.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU FEEL THE RAIN</pattern><template>God… Thank you for giving me my life.</template></category><category><pattern>SELVAN  CUT AWAY</pattern><template>He said he's sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ONE DAY  MY TEACHER CAME DOWN WITH THE FLU</pattern><template>He asked if I could take his place, playing rhythms for a dance class.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ZOO WAS NEVER OURS TO SELL  THE LAND BELONGS TO THE TOWN</pattern><template>But the animals are ours.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  JUST LIKE I TOLD YOU</pattern><template>Bananas don't float.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT PANIC WILL</pattern><template>And remember to breathe now, don't hold your breath.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY GIVE ORANGE JUICE TRANQUILIZERS</pattern><template>He's not gonna cause any trouble.</template></category><category><pattern>PISCINE PATEL</pattern><template>Good Morning.</template></category><category><pattern>MAMAJI COLLECTS SWIMMING POOLS</pattern><template>He swims in every pool he comes upon.</template></category><category><pattern>LET THE DRUM ROLLS BEGIN</pattern><template>Prepare to be amazed!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAY THE DOCTOR SWUNG FRANCIS AROUND BY THE ANKLES  TO CLEAR THE WATER OUT</pattern><template>And that's what gave him his huge chest and skinny legs, that made him such a great swimmer.</template></category><category><pattern>MY AMMA WENT TO COLLEGE AND THOUGHT OUR FAMILY WAS PART OF THE NEW INDIA AS WELL  BUT THEN HER PARENTS CUT HER OFF  BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT SHE WAS MARRYING BENEATH HER</pattern><template>Our religion was the only link she had to her past.</template></category><category><pattern>VERY FEW CASTAWAYS CAN CLAIM TO HAVE SURVIVED SO LONG AT SEA</pattern><template>And none in the company… of an adult Bengal tiger.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS “PISSING” EVERYWHERE</pattern><template>No pissing in the schoolyard!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT'S CHEAPER LIVING IN INDIA</pattern><template>Well, I look forward to reading it.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL RESPECT THAT  PROMISE</pattern><template>Go! Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>THE INVESTIGATORS DIDN'T SEEM TO LIKE THE STORY  EXACTLY</pattern><template>They thanked me.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO GET BACK TO THE WORLD  OR DIE TRYING</pattern><template>I spent the next day preparing the boat.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO YEARS TRYING TO BRING THIS THING TO LIFE  AND THEN ONE DAY… SPUTTERED  COUGHED AND DIED</pattern><template>Oh, I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY HERE</pattern><template>You have to help my family!</template></category><category><pattern>– GET IN</pattern><template>We have a guest, let me introduce you.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MADE NO SENSE</pattern><template>Sacrificing the innocent, to atone for the sins of the guilty, what kind of love is that?</template></category><category><pattern>AND A JEW  I SUPPOSE</pattern><template>Well I do teach the course on the Kabbala at the University.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WAY OF KARMA  HUH</pattern><template>The way of God.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED A SIMPLER STORY FOR OUR REPORT</pattern><template>One our company can understand.</template></category><category><pattern>SET YOUR HOUSE IN ORDER  AND DIG IN FOR THE BATTLE TO SURVIVE</pattern><template>Establish a strict schedule for eating, keeping watch, and getting rest.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE SEEN HIM DO THIS A THOUSAND TIMES</pattern><template>I want to meet our new tiger.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>Without surprises, without… animals or islands.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A THUNDERSTORM  LET'S GO AND WATCH</pattern><template>Are you crazy?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS WARM AND SOFT  LIKE PRESSING MY FACE AGAINST THE CHEEK OF GOD</pattern><template>And somewhere, two eyes were smiling at having me there.</template></category><category><pattern>PISCINE</pattern><template>You have a whole life ahead of you.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MUCH LONELINESS TAKEN ON HIM</pattern><template>All I know is that eventually he died, and the island digested him, leaving behind only his teeth.</template></category><category><pattern>STEP 4: DISREGARD STEPS 1 THROUGH 3</pattern><template>Here, Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>PONDICHERRY… IS THE FRENCH RIVIERA OF INDIA</pattern><template>In this place, closest to the ocean, you might think you are in the south of France.</template></category><category><pattern>WORDS AND PATTERNS THAT WENT ON AND ON WITHOUT END  JUST LIKE MY IRRATIONAL NICKNAME</pattern><template>I grew restless, searching for something that might bring meaning back into my life.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT RIGHT</pattern><template>No!</template></category><category><pattern>HE RAN A HOTEL  AND HE GOT THE IDEA TO OPEN A ZOO IN THE LOCAL BOTANICAL GARDENS INSTEAD</pattern><template>As it also happened, my mother was a botanist in the gardens.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE DANCE  YOU WENT FROM 'BATANKA'  WHICH MEANS THE FOREST  AND THEN YOU DID… AND YOU DID… 'SANPUTA'  WHICH MEANS SOMETHING THAT IS HIDDEN</pattern><template>Now for that you did this.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>Don't hide yourself!</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>Sorry for the choppy ride.</template></category><category><pattern>AMA</pattern><template>Apa!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I'VE LEFT SO MUCH BEHIND… MY FAMILY  THE ZOO  INDIA  ANANDI… I SUPPOSE IN THE END THE WHOLE OF LIFE BECOMES AN ACT OF LETTING GO</pattern><template>But what always hurts the most, is not taking a moment to say goodbye.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN EAT THE BISCUITS  BUT GOD MADE TIGERS CARNIVORES  SO I MUST LEARN TO CATCH FISH</pattern><template>If I don't, I'm afraid his last meal will be a skinny vegetarian boy.</template></category><category><pattern>RAVI</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>SACRIFICING THE INNOCENT  TO ATONE FOR THE SINS OF THE GUILTY  WHAT KIND OF LOVE IS THAT</pattern><template>But this son, I couldn't get him out of my head.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>We are leaving India.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD BE KILLING HIM</pattern><template>And so I waited for his return.</template></category><category><pattern>THOUSANDS OF MEERKATS  ON AN FLOATING CARNIVOROUS ISLAND  AND NO ONE HAS EVER SEEN IT</pattern><template>Yes. Just like I told you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL HAVE PLENTY OF FRESH SUPPLIES AFTER WE STOP IN MANILA</pattern><template>Why give Orange Juice tranquilizers?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHY NOT</pattern><template>Faith is a house with many rooms.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  RICHARD PARKER</pattern><template>I got some water for you.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY THANKED ME</pattern><template>They wished me well… and they left.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ALL MISSING OUT</pattern><template>You only need to convert to three more religions, Piscine, and you'll spend your life on holiday.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN STILL HEAR HIM  A HAPPY BUDDHIST WHO ONLY ATE RICE AND GRAVY WE DIDN'T SAVE HIM  OF COURSE</pattern><template>He died.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MAMAJI HE DOES THAT</pattern><template>When I told him my abandoned book, he said:  So, a Canadian who's come to French India,   in search for a story. Well, my friend,   I know an Indian in French Canada, with the most incredible story to tell.   It must be fate that the two of you should meet.  Well, I haven't spoken about Richard Parker in so many years.</template></category><category><pattern>ISN'T THAT WHY MAMAJI SENT YOU HERE  AFTER ALL</pattern><template>My wife is here.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK ABOUT THAT EVERY DAY</pattern><template>I jumped over and turned back just as the knife came out.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  MY UNCLE FRANCIS WAS BORN WITH TOO MUCH WATER IN HIS LUNGS</pattern><template>They say the doctor swung Francis around by the ankles, to clear the water out.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT HIM  HE IS PISSING</pattern><template>With one word, my name went from an elegant French swimming pool to a stinking Indian latrine.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOWING OFF… LIKE A DANCER</pattern><template>No. He heard something.</template></category><category><pattern>LONGING FOR HIS WORDS</pattern><template>The compassionate!</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE NAME STUCK</pattern><template>Let's go… Before we get into trouble!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW FOR THAT YOU DID THIS</pattern><template>And then you did 'Chatura'.</template></category><category><pattern>NONE OF THE OTHERS DANCERS DID THAT</pattern><template>What did you mean, the God of love is hiding in the forest?</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD THEM ANOTHER STORY</pattern><template>Four of us survived, the cook and the sailor were already aboard.</template></category><category><pattern>APA</pattern><template>Ravi!</template></category><category><pattern>TRUE</pattern><template>So which story do you prefer?</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE THEY DO  YOU TRY IT FOR YOURSELF</pattern><template>In any case, we are not here to talk about bananas or meerkats.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I NOT COME TO KNOW A FEW OF THEM</pattern><template>I met Krishna first.</template></category><category><pattern>IN BOTH STORIES  THE SHIP SINKS  MY FAMILY DIES  AND I SUFFER</pattern><template>True.</template></category><category><pattern>ALONE  FORGOTTEN</pattern><template>I had to get back to the world, or die trying.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR MY FAMILY</pattern><template>Our animals are worth far more abroad than here in India.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL ALWAYS BE WITH ME… BUT I CAN'T BE WITH YOU</pattern><template>I don't know what to say.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TEMPT THE STORM  PI</pattern><template>Oyé!</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A GUEST  LET ME INTRODUCE YOU</pattern><template>Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER COMES  I WANT TO KNOW</pattern><template>Show me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I SAW HER  THEY… SAW… NEXT DAY  I KILLED HIM</pattern><template>He didn't even fight back, he knew he'd gone too far.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>And so it goes with God.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MORNING</pattern><template>I am Piscine Molitor Patel.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT FOR GRAVY</pattern><template>You don't want gravy?</template></category><category><pattern>GOD… I GIVE MYSELF TO YOU</pattern><template>I am your vessel.</template></category><category><pattern>I CALL HIM “MAMAJI”</pattern><template>My father's best friend, my swimming guru.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID HE'S SORRY</pattern><template>You'll just scar them for life.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WILL BE A MAN SOONER THAN YOU THINK</pattern><template>And this is a lesson I do not want them ever to forget!</template></category><category><pattern>VISHNU SLEEPS  FLOATING ON THE SHORELESS COSMIC OCEAN  AND WE ARE THE STUFF OF HIS DREAMING</pattern><template>Spectacle.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT TO MEET OUR NEW TIGER</pattern><template>Pi!</template></category><category><pattern>SIMILAR METHODS HAVE LONG BEEN USED BY CIRCUS TRAINERS  THOUGH THEY GENERALLY LACK ACCESS TO ROUGH SEAS</pattern><template>Let the trumpets blow!</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS AFRAID THAT IN TWO FEET OF WATER  SO CLOSE TO DELIVERANCE  I WOULD DROWN</pattern><template>I struggled to shore, and fell upon the sand.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD</pattern><template>Go, Richard Parker.</template></category><category><pattern>– NO PLEASE  MY FATHER</pattern><template>He's got to go!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO</pattern><template>Com'on!</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE VISITING RELATIVES  TEA GROWERS IN MUNNAR</pattern><template>It was our third there, Ravi and I were terribly bored.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST BEYOND THAT IS INDIAN PONDICHERRY</pattern><template>And the Muslim quarter is just to the west.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT</pattern><template>Please save my family!</template></category><category><pattern>LET THE TRUMPETS BLOW</pattern><template>Let the drum rolls begin!</template></category></AIML>