<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>NEXT YEAR  HOW'S YOUR NEW ASSISTANT</pattern><template>She's Good.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID THINGS  I WOULD NEVER DO</pattern><template>Those things saved your life.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT</pattern><template>But I need a favor first.</template></category><category><pattern>OH THAT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>Can I have it back?</template></category><category><pattern>SURE</pattern><template>These companies aren't the question, are they?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SO SORRY ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>I want you to know that you'll never, ever have to go through that again Cause I can take care of us now.</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE DEPT  OPEN THE DOOR PLEASE</pattern><template>Police dept! Open the door!</template></category><category><pattern>OBVIOUSLY  I MISCALCULATED A FEW THINGS</pattern><template>Eddie I know you're in there, Why is it that, the moment your life exceeds your wildest dreams...</template></category><category><pattern>OH GOD</pattern><template>Help!</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW HOW IT WORKS</pattern><template>I get it, I totally get it. You feel invincible.</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE WHEN IS THIS THE DELTA QUARREL</pattern><template>Don... Pull it back!</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK</pattern><template>Since when is this the Delta quarrel?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS GETTING COFFEE</pattern><template>Why? Has there been movement?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK GOOD</pattern><template>Well I uh...</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE THEY'VE WORKED OUT THE BUGS MAYBE</pattern><template>Maybe this is a different batch.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO SEE ME THIS WAY</pattern><template>You look good.</template></category><category><pattern>THE REAL QUESTION IS</pattern><template>Why did you ever put up with me?</template></category><category><pattern>SHOULD BE SUPPLEMENTING PLATINUM DOUBLET REGIMENTS</pattern><template>with lico cimpenti oic acid.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT LAZY  SLOW  SO SLOW</pattern><template>That was two years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WON'T COME OFF    WHY'S THAT</pattern><template>You'd have to back off Libya Really?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Somethin's pumpin' at half mast in there.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I JUST NOTICED THE BOOK</pattern><template>You just saw the corner of it.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN HALF LISTING TO ANY LANGUAGE  I BECAME FLUENT   SO THAT SHAKESPEARE'S TEXT  IT IS POLITE MEDIOCRITY</pattern><template>who'd ever argue with you?</template></category><category><pattern>CONTROL THE WHOLE POWER ENCHILADA</pattern><template>But no, these companies wouldn't get you there in a merging markets You would have...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IN ORDER FOR A CAREER TO EVOLVE  I'M GONNA HAVE TO MOVE ON</pattern><template>That you would even think that, would only show me how unprepared you are, to be on your own.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THREATING ME</pattern><template>Like checks from Dubai, dumping in Chile, disappeared officials When you said the spot...</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT JOB</pattern><template>Edward...</template></category><category><pattern>A DEALER</pattern><template>Yeah uh, Antiques, um...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FLAUNT THEM AND YOU THROW THEM AROUND LIKE A BRAT WITH HIS TRUST FUND</pattern><template>You haven't had to climb up all the greasy little rungs...</template></category><category><pattern>OH I THINK MAYBE YOU DO</pattern><template>Limitless supply.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  EDDIE  GIVE ME A CALL  WHEN YOU GET IN    EDDIE  I AM 40 PAGES FURTHER IN</pattern><template>call me.   It's, a little grandiose but I am still reading.   Okay, how did you do this?   I really... Call me the minute, you get in. Call! Okay?    Who is it?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>No, you're not.</template></category><category><pattern>DON    PULL IT BACK</pattern><template>Excuse me. Mr. Van Loon, Mrs. Atwood is in your office.</template></category><category><pattern>GETTING SMARTER</pattern><template>Obviously, this can not go on   But there is very little on this earth   that 40 million dollars can't solve   and tomorrow at 9:00, Atwood would sign the papers.  Do you wanna call it?</template></category><category><pattern>EDWARD</pattern><template>I think we looking at a second overflow of bent.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THIS IS AN EXCLUSIVE PRODUCT  THAT'S COMING ON THE STREAM NEXT YEAR</pattern><template>They've had clinical tries, and it's F.D.A. approved.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW YOU GONNA PAY ME  IN CIGARETTES</pattern><template>Last year you traded insider information 17 times.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY I HOPE YOU DO LOOKING FOR ME</pattern><template>Think you can run out on me? uh!</template></category><category><pattern>MELISSA</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  YOU SHOULD REALLY BE GLAD ABOUT THIS</pattern><template>Cause me working for you, you'd end up as my bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULDN'T STAY MESSY ON IT   I HADN'T HAD A CIGARETTE IN 6 HOURS; HADN'T EATEN      SO  I'M STEAMIEST AND TIDY</pattern><template>What was this?   A drug for people, who wanted to be more anal retentive?   I wasn't high, wasn't wired...   Just clear. I knew what I needed to do, and how to do it   The next morning, I sent a little probe down into my brain.   No surge of brilliance came up to greet me.   In short, I was back.   But something remained    You're kidding?!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I WANT SOME MORE OF THAT STUFF  OR I SHOOT YOU RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Take your pick.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I SORT A CREATED A UTOPIAN SOCIETY  WHERE  WE ALL SORT OF UH UH UH</pattern><template>It's really... It, it's really, it's re  uh.</template></category><category><pattern>YO BUDDY  LET'S LEAVE HER ALONE</pattern><template>Are you deaf?</template></category><category><pattern>HEADACHES  THROWING UP SO I WENT BACK TO  VERON</pattern><template>he told me about all the people that were dying.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU ALREADY KNEW THAT</pattern><template>You know, you should really be glad about this.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK THAT MY LIFE'S GONNA TAKE SOME SUDDEN UPSWING INTO FAME AND FORTUNE  BY TAKING SOME SHINY BRAIN EXOTIC DRUG</pattern><template>Get. When?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL WHAT THIS DOES  IT LETS YOU ACCESS ALL OF IT</pattern><template>Vernon, look at me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN'S THE LAST TIME YOU ATE SOMETHING</pattern><template>Here he is. Nice Article in the post buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I UH</pattern><template>Yes, I sorta got myself together.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DRIVER'S DISTRACTED; HE'S TEXTING; HE'S GOING 30MPH</pattern><template>He needs 60 feet stop; he doesn't have room to work with.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT IN MY APARTMENT</pattern><template>I moved it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL BE WANTING A FEW TOYS</pattern><template>hotel rooms were no longer an option.   What I needed, was a bunker.  There's a built in safe...</template></category><category><pattern>AND BESIDES  I GET THE STRONG FEELING</pattern><template>that, you're not somebody I want to disappoint.</template></category><category><pattern>PAPERS STACKED LIKE THE HIMALAYAS IN MY OFFICE  AND YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>The stocks went up.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE NEEDS DIRECT ANSWERS</pattern><template>Anything tentative, and you've lost him forever.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  TAKE YOUR TIME</pattern><template>Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  THE SHARE PRICES AREN'T REALLY BASED ON HOW A COMPANY WORKS IT'S ABOUT HOW MASS PSYCHOLOGY WORKS SO  IF I FOUND CERTAIN ALGORITHMS IN THE PERCEPTION OF THE STOCK</pattern><template>Pattern recognition.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T LIKE BEING DOWN TO THIS LAST ONE YOU DO NOT EVEN KNOW HOW TO USE IT</pattern><template>You don't appreciate it.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE AREN'T  CAUSE THERE ARE NO SAFEGUARDS IN HUMAN NATURE</pattern><template>Oh, we're wired to overreach.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  ITS A FIX</pattern><template>Yea, and all you people get caught.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I AM JUST CONNECTING THE DOTS</pattern><template>Is Hank Atwood really gonna go for it?</template></category><category><pattern>I READ BRIAN GREEN'S  THE ELEGANT UNIVERSE   IN 45 MINUTES AND I UNDERSTOOD IT</pattern><template>My, my work rate increased, just as insanely overnight...</template></category><category><pattern>MR  MORRA</pattern><template>what a surprise!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS RIGHT  WHY STICK IT OUT</pattern><template>I had clearly missed the on ramp.   We both knew what was beckoning.   The lower bunk of my childhood bedroom in Jersey.   My Father happy to welcome me into   the challenging field of dental supply inventory.  Eddy Morra!</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT YOU'LL NEVER  EVER HAVE TO GO THROUGH THAT AGAIN CAUSE I CAN TAKE CARE OF US NOW</pattern><template>I'm sure you can.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE DON'T   I CALL YOU AT THE POINT OKAY  WHEN THIS IS OVER OKAY  ALRIGHT OKAY</pattern><template>You know, something doesn't gel here.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WITNESS IDENTIFIED THE MARIA WINBERG SUSPECT</pattern><template>As this person.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ALRIGHT  YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE LIVIN' ON THE STREETS  WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Not much. Uh, I just broke up... What am I, what's up uh, I'm writing... Writing a lot Oh, you still trying to write?</template></category><category><pattern>EDDIE      HERE    IT'S GONNA BE OKAY    YOU'RE GONNA GET OUTTA HERE    EDDIE   ARE YOU OKAY</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>OBVIOUSLY  THIS CAN NOT GO ON   BUT THERE IS VERY LITTLE ON THIS EARTH   THAT 40 MILLION DOLLARS CAN'T SOLVE   AND TOMORROW AT 9:00  ATWOOD WOULD SIGN THE PAPERS   DO YOU WANNA CALL IT</pattern><template>Cold feet?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU GET IT</pattern><template>You are gonna be out on the streets!</template></category><category><pattern>ATWOOD    UM  HE'S AN ICONOCLAST</pattern><template>uhm... He owns about a half of Colorado...</template></category><category><pattern>HE FOLLOWED ME FROM MY BUILDING</pattern><template>I don't know him. Please!</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO NO NO  HONEY</pattern><template>I need yo to get...</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT GONNA DO IT</pattern><template>Oh my God!</template></category><category><pattern>FOR A GUY WITH A 4 DIGIT IQ  I MUST HAVE MISSED SOMETHING</pattern><template>And I hadn't missed much.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY IS HE DEAD</pattern><template>I mean, at what point was the pony express, supposed to ride in with his life saving medication?</template></category><category><pattern>MEANING</pattern><template>clinical trials, guinea pig people.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MY SYNAPSES DIDN'T CHANGE  THAT I KEPT ABSOLUTELY NOTHING</pattern><template>You have no idea, what kind of enemy I can be...</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY    SO WHERE DID YOU MOVE IT</pattern><template>In my house.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS UH  SOMEBODY GAVE ME A WAKEUP CALL</pattern><template>I hope you didn't do it for me.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  MRS  ATWOOD  KARL VAN LOON  MY ASSOCIATE  EDWARD MORRA</pattern><template>Pleasure.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GREAT</pattern><template>how about you? Are you uh...</template></category><category><pattern>NOWHERE</pattern><template>Two years ago, he wasn't even on Forbes radar.</template></category><category><pattern>OR BRAIN DEAD   STUCK FULL OF TUBES</pattern><template>I'll take my chances.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY VERN  I REALLY JUST NEED TO TALK TO YOU</pattern><template>Vern, what happened?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IT'S JUST SOME VITAMINS AND ASPIRIN</pattern><template>You're full of shit Eddie baby...</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IS GONNA COME FIRST</pattern><template>I guess, we gonna find out uh?.</template></category><category><pattern>AGAINST THE AGGRESSIVE OVER EXPANSION</pattern><template>There aren't. Cause there are no safeguards in Human nature.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  COME ON  THE TWO OF YOU TOGETHER</pattern><template>The whole world will have to come begging for energy like Oliver Twist and his bowl of Gruel.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU CRAZY</pattern><template>He is gonna do it.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS MAN  THIS MAN IS CHASING ME</pattern><template>He followed me from my building.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T LIKE ME AND I DON'T BLAME YOU</pattern><template>You see a self defeating, energy sucking, piece of shit who's sponging off your husband...</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD HE WAS AN ANTIQUES DEALER</pattern><template>A dealer?</template></category><category><pattern>WITH ALL LAST NIGHT TO TELL US THAT</pattern><template>Anything?</template></category><category><pattern>GOT ANY IDEAS</pattern><template>What do you think?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT</pattern><template>I'm baffled by this guy...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DON'T  I DON'T WANT THAT</pattern><template>Please don't.  I call you at the point okay, when this is over Okay. Alright Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL GO TO YOUR APARTMENT</pattern><template>It's not in my apartment.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I WANT MORE  SO WHY WOULD YOU UPSET ME</pattern><template>I don't like being down to this last one You do not even know how to use it.</template></category><category><pattern>THINKING NO ONE'S SMARTER THAN YOU</pattern><template>Where the hell have you been?</template></category><category><pattern>WRITTEN BY YOU</pattern><template>All you have to do, is to read 3 pages Just read 3 Pages in the next hour.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  EDDIE MORRA  WHAT'S YOUR SECRET</pattern><template>Medication.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>Everything's sterilized.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS HARDLY A SURPRISE</pattern><template>I, I'm surprised?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BROKE AND I'M DEPRESSED OFF MY ASS</pattern><template>I don't think that my life's gonna take some sudden upswing into fame and fortune, by taking some shiny brain exotic drug.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T EVEN RECOGNIZE YOU ON THE STREET</pattern><template>Well I'm a new man.</template></category><category><pattern>HE TOLD ME ABOUT ALL THE PEOPLE THAT WERE DYING</pattern><template>How much you have been taking Eddie?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD NO CHOICE</pattern><template>I told Lindi everything  So all this energy of yours, all this focus, has been a drug?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T FORGET TO VOTE</pattern><template>Edward, you good?</template></category><category><pattern>I CERTAINLY AM</pattern><template>I mean, if my attorney was really working for Mr. Atwood, trying to save his life...</template></category><category><pattern>TODAY WAS THE DAY  I WAS GONNA KICK ITS ASS   HERE WE GO  HERE WE GO</pattern><template>Here we go. Here we go   Man, It's gonna be great.   Just gotta put in the time and stay in the room.   That's the key concept.   Don't leave the room!   A few weeks passed this way   Maybe a few months.   At least I still had Lindi.  Just like that?</template></category><category><pattern>I FEEL GOOD MAN  WHAT'S IN THIS STUFF</pattern><template>Well, it's just some vitamins and aspirin.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YO TO GET</pattern><template>It's really simple baby. I need my pills.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK   YOU GOT A LONG WAY TO GO  AS A LIAR KIDDO</pattern><template>Heck Karl, I don't know what your..</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE BEEN FOLLOWING ME</pattern><template>No, I just noticed the book.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  I'M SURE YOU HAVE A PORTFOLIO BUT IF DON'T</pattern><template>I'd be very interested working with you.</template></category><category><pattern>LINDI</pattern><template>Oh God!</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU DEAF</pattern><template>I said, leave her alone!</template></category><category><pattern>TAPER OFF I'M OFF IT  KARL</pattern><template>Well on it, or off it, there's no scenario where you are not working for me.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD LINDI EVERYTHING  SO ALL THIS ENERGY OF YOURS  ALL THIS FOCUS  HAS BEEN A DRUG</pattern><template>Well, it was supposed to be legal.</template></category><category><pattern>I SENT OVER MY REVISED PROJECTIONS</pattern><template>I didn't ask for your projections...</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE SHOULD REHEARSE A FEW SCENARIOS</pattern><template>I am eating, Kevin.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL WHAT'S MINE IS YOURS TOO</pattern><template>and you know that I want to share the rest of my life with you.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU TELL EM</pattern><template>No. Now!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M PLUM OUT</pattern><template>You know, these guys are gonna find it...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BELIEVE THAT</pattern><template>Yeah, Of course I believe you.</template></category><category><pattern>KARL VAN LOON WANTS TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>apparently so.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>Written by you?</template></category><category><pattern>NO WHAT  WHEN WE HE TOLD ME ABOUT THIS AMAZING NEW DRUG</pattern><template>I was like,  down the hatch.   and it was. It was amazing.</template></category><category><pattern>ME</pattern><template>No! It's not you You were different before.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BLACKOUTS DIDN'T OCCUR  TOM IS IT POSSIBLE TO CONSTRUCT AN IMPERCEPTIBLE COMPARTMENT</pattern><template>In this jacket?</template></category><category><pattern>UHM    HE OWNS ABOUT A HALF OF COLORADO</pattern><template>So, this is  prepared ? Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D COME THIS CLOSE TO HAVING AN IMPACT IN THE WORLD</pattern><template>And now, the only thing I had an impact on...</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU GO AROUND HIM</pattern><template>Baby, what's happening?</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE A TOAST PLATE</pattern><template>Hey, Karl. Good to see you.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE ONCE YOU KNOW WHAT'S IN IT  YOU CAN TWEAK  RE ENGINEER</pattern><template>get the bugs out.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT NOW I WANNA KNOW WHY THIS DEAL IS DEAD IN THE WATER</pattern><template>Karl.</template></category><category><pattern>MY HUSBAND EXPERIENCED SOME PAIN AND DIZZINESS THIS MORNING</pattern><template>He's currently at Lenox Hill   undergoing test.</template></category><category><pattern>KARL VAN LOON'S AND HANK ATWOOD  HAD NO IDEA   I MIGHT SOON BE CHARGED WITH MURDER   BUT CI CORPS  AN DINE AND OTHERS  ARE JOCKEYING FOR THE SAME INDUSTRIAL CONCESSIONS IN LIBYA THAT BOTH OUR COMPANIES ARE PRETENDING  WE'RE NOT SNIFFING OUT</pattern><template>How do you know this?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT NOW  I JUST WANT TO KEEP YOU BRILLIANT AND HEALTHY</pattern><template>Let's go get some lunch.</template></category><category><pattern>GET  WHEN</pattern><template>Tell him we can't do that.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD BE AN ACT</pattern><template>He's not even 60.</template></category><category><pattern>I GET IT  I TOTALLY GET IT  YOU FEEL INVINCIBLE</pattern><template>Where it will take us Lin, you can't even imagine The things we'll be able to do Where we'll be a year from now The kind of life that we'll finally be able to live Well, you might have to live it without me.</template></category><category><pattern>NO    ABOUT ATWOOD</pattern><template>What? What about Atwood?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  BASED ON YOUR CHARTS AND PROJECTIONS</pattern><template>You know, remind me... Who are you anyway?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THEY GOT NOW ARE SALT COD AND CHEAP CONDOMS</pattern><template>The Brits!</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS FOR STOPPING BY  KARL</pattern><template>Give us a second.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T EVEN TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>I got it!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS</pattern><template>Something wrong in Law school?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE OFF IT RIGHT NOW  AREN'T YOU</pattern><template>Just finish the story.</template></category><category><pattern>JERRY'S IN THE HOSPITAL       HE'S WHAT</pattern><template>Yeah, he's not doing well at all  Yeah, hello. Is Paul Kaplan there?</template></category><category><pattern>SELF IMPROVEMENT MONTH</pattern><template>I guess uh, somebody gave me a wakeup call.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE HAS  I HOPE YOU DON'T THINK YOU'VE GOTTEN ENOUGH FROM ME</pattern><template>on to the next...</template></category><category><pattern>IN FACT  I WAS THINKING</pattern><template>that we should probab...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE A SELF DEFEATING  ENERGY SUCKING  PIECE OF SHIT WHO'S SPONGING OFF YOUR HUSBAND</pattern><template>you're wishing I'd blow my brains out...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHAT DO YOU CARE  MAN</pattern><template>You were married for like five minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN</pattern><template>This is the second time you've turned to vapor.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT TO MAKE CONCESSIONS TO YOU</pattern><template>Karl van Loon's and Hank Atwood, had no idea   I might soon be charged with murder.  But Ci Corps, An Dine and others, are jockeying for the same industrial concessions in Libya that both our companies are pretending, we're not sniffing out.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU ON DRUGS</pattern><template>I had no choice.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>Nothin'.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT EVEN 60</pattern><template>So have you decided Eddie, whatta ya gonna do?</template></category><category><pattern>WE KNOW YOU CAN'T GET ANYMORE</pattern><template>You sure about that?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO  OPEN THE DOOR</pattern><template>Let me see your hands!   I'm the one who called!   I called you guys!</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU STILL THERE</pattern><template>Yeah, I'm here. What happened?    I'm stuck! He'll find me.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL BE COST EFFECTIVE</pattern><template>And you say I am not practical.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD CLEARLY MISSED THE ON RAMP    WE BOTH KNEW WHAT WAS BECKONING    THE LOWER BUNK OF MY CHILDHOOD BEDROOM IN JERSEY    MY FATHER HAPPY TO WELCOME ME INTO   THE CHALLENGING FIELD OF DENTAL SUPPLY INVENTORY   EDDY MORRA</pattern><template>Of all the useless relationships better forgotten and put away in mothballs   Is there any more useless than, the ex brother in law?  Holy Shit, man!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID</pattern><template>I'm an Editor.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BACK  OKAY   WHO'S BACK  EDDIE</pattern><template>Me.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME FOR ONE SEC I THOUGHT WE STRAIGHTENED THIS OUT  DETECTIVE</pattern><template>This isn't about Vernon again, Mr. Morra.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  DOES IT HAVE TO BE THAT KEY</pattern><template>Can it be a new key?</template></category><category><pattern>KEVIN  IT'S EDDIE   EDDIE</pattern><template>Listen, I can't   I can't make the meeting today.  What are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T LOOK LIKE NO ASPIRIN I EVER SEE</pattern><template>I feel good man, what's in this stuff?</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN THE DOOR PLEASE</pattern><template>Police! Open the door!</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Yeah. Take your time.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE STILL DEALING</pattern><template>Brother, I am light years from that now.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK I AM  SOME FINANCIAL INSTITUTION</pattern><template>Alright. You're right.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MAKE ME YOUR COMPETITION</pattern><template>Now I'll open up a line of credit for you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHUT DOWN YOUR LAB</pattern><template>You don't you think some smart ass and NZT might have two or three, or even four labs?</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE WHO AREN'T  USUALLY DON'T CARRY AROUND DRY</pattern><template>academically constipated books about a dead supreme court justice.</template></category><category><pattern>SMARTER THAN ANYONE AROUND HER   CLEARLY  THERE WAS A DIRECT LINK BETWEEN THIS EDDIE      SLIGHTLY DRUNK AT THREE O'CLOCK IN THE AFTERNOON  AND AN EARLIER EDDIE    VOMITING ON HIS BOSS' DESK      OR STEALING HIS DYING AUNTS PERCOCET    SO WHO CAN BLAME LINDIE FOR DUMPING ME    IN THE END  HOW MUCH WORSE COULD IT GET    I DIDN'T WANT TO SEE ANYBODY    ESPECIALLY NOT MY LANDLORD'S NASTY YOUNG WIFE    VALERIE  TUESDAY</pattern><template>Look! Enough! Okay...</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  I DIDN'T KNOW WHO OR WHAT I WAS TALKING TO</pattern><template>105. That's who you were talking to Carl.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WELCOME</pattern><template>All the way home, I thought about Melissa.   How could she be a failure too?.   She'd been so smart.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS THIS    A DRUG FOR PEOPLE  WHO WANTED TO BE MORE ANAL RETENTIVE    I WASN'T HIGH  WASN'T WIRED      JUST CLEAR  I KNEW WHAT I NEEDED TO DO  AND HOW TO DO IT   THE NEXT MORNING  I SENT A LITTLE PROBE DOWN INTO MY BRAIN    NO SURGE OF BRILLIANCE CAME UP TO GREET ME    IN SHORT  I WAS BACK    BUT SOMETHING REMAINED    YOU'RE KIDDING</pattern><template>No   Words have appeared on paper.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COMING OVER LATER</pattern><template>I can't. I don't have a key.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS SICK</pattern><template>You don't get sick You're playing at this level  You get hit by a car, you don't even die.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE SECOND TIME YOU'VE TURNED TO VAPOR</pattern><template>I was in the building.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BRANCHING OUT</pattern><template>I'm starting import export company.</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY MY MONEY  AND MY LIBERTY  I'VE BEEN ALL OVER THEM</pattern><template>We can't allow any disparity in race or physical type between you and the rest of the line up.</template></category><category><pattern>8 5 I'LL TAKE IT</pattern><template>Right away, it was obvious, he was on NZT Next week, I'm gonna need 20 pills.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I REALLY  I REALLY DO WANNA DO THIS AGAIN  SO  CALL ME</pattern><template>And, that's on the house.</template></category><category><pattern>EDDIE  WHAT PILLS    BABY  IT'S COMPLICATED    WHAT ARE YOU TAKING</pattern><template>Are you on drugs?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S YOUR CYCLE HELP</pattern><template>Well, not everybody understands the patterns.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  ABOUT THE LEAK</pattern><template>No... About Atwood.</template></category><category><pattern>ON TO THE NEXT</pattern><template>Well, in order for a career to evolve, I'm gonna have to move on.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW BE WARNED  HE'S MERCURIAL</pattern><template>One minute your best friend, the next, you're a leper.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Finally get to meet the guys that keeps the lights on.</template></category><category><pattern>HM</pattern><template>You're not one of those kind of guys   are you Eddy?</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT KNOW WHO YOU ARE EDDIE  OR WHAT YOUR GAME IS  BUT I'M SURE OF ONE THING  YOU DON'T WORK IN MY WORLD</pattern><template>I'm up to my ass with investment guys...</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES</pattern><template>I told you...Your chances don't exist.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID</pattern><template>This today... The Dow has been YO YO ing   amid speculation, that Van Loon Associates,   and Hank Atwood have negotiated a merger...  Have you been talking to anyone?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE BOTH KNOW WHERE IT'S HEADED  IF YOU CAN  MAINTAIN</pattern><template>Have you asked yourself, what you're gonna do, when you run out?</template></category><category><pattern>VICTOR</pattern><template>The police would later note,    that my apartments previous owner was an arms dealer.   of course these intruders, had been his dissatisfied clients   and the night was still young  Well, I'm sure you're curious to know what happened to your boss.</template></category><category><pattern>I FIRED A FEW PEOPLE  OVER YOUR PROJECTIONS</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>BETTER CALL THE COPS</pattern><template>Can you go around him?</template></category><category><pattern>EIGHT HUNDRED BUCKS    A POP</pattern><template>You're welcome.</template></category><category><pattern>EDDIE WHO</pattern><template>Morra.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW IS MELISSA DOING</pattern><template>Here.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU'RE NOT</pattern><template>You're relieved, that you know things, my team missed.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK YOUR FORTUNE 500 FINANCIAL FRIENDS  WOULD APPRECIATE THE DETAILS  OF YOUR LITTLE DILEMMA WITH THE POLICE</pattern><template>Thursday, I'm gonna need the pills here.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE YOU DIDN'T DO IT FOR ME</pattern><template>No, I just wanted to apologize to you.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT MUCH OF A TRIUMPH  WAS IT    BECAUSE I WOULD DIE HERE TOO    ONLY NZT COULD HELP ME   AND THE LAST OF IT  WAS IN THIS PUG'S BLOODSTREAM   VICTOR</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>THESE COMPANIES AREN'T THE QUESTION  ARE THEY</pattern><template>Explain.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HOW MUCH HAVE YOU WRITTEN ON IT</pattern><template>Not one word.</template></category><category><pattern>IVAN CHEMCORP PHARMACEUTICALS</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>MEET ME TOMORROW AT THE SAINT REGIS AT 10 AND TELL ME HOW THE GUTSY LITTLE SCHMUCK WHO NEEDS A RIDE HOME  WOULD RESTRUCTURE THESE DEALS</pattern><template>And you better be prepared.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S GOOD</pattern><template>You know, I'm really happy you're here with me.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'D GIVE YOU SOMETHING THAT NO ONE ELSE HAS</pattern><template>information from the odd museum show...</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  JUST OUT OF CURIOSITY AND THAT'S ALL</pattern><template>Let me see it.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  THAT'S MUCH BETTER</pattern><template>Great job!</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE PAIN WAS STARTING BEHIND MY EYES</pattern><template>Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHIN'S PUMPIN' AT HALF MAST IN THERE</pattern><template>Walls of your heart are dilated.</template></category><category><pattern>EDDIE  I JUST WANNA HELP YOU  THAT'S ALL</pattern><template>Keep your supply.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING</pattern><template>I will never let them touch me.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT KNOW  HE WAS</pattern><template>I heard he was an antiques dealer.</template></category><category><pattern>MATTER OF FACT  I HAVE A BOOK CONTRACT   REALLY    YEAH</pattern><template>That's great.</template></category><category><pattern>MY NEW FRIEND  KEVIN DOYLE  SHOWED ME HOW YOU CAN LEVERAGE    TWO AND A HALF TIMES YOUR CASH AT DAY TRADING FIRM   I'VE BEEN UPPING THE DOSE FOR OVER A WEEK    IT SEEMED TO CUT MY LEARNING CURVE   HEY  WHY YOU BUYING THAT</pattern><template>The CEO was just indicted But not for the big fat defensive contract he bribed his way into That's still on should be announced next week  I was jacked in, booted up.   At the end of week, My brokerage account.   contained over two million dollars.   word, quickly got out.   You have 19 messages.   four job offers, My bank raising my line of credit   a reporter from the New York Post...  Really call me back Mr. Morra.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A FORMULA WITH A COMPLEX METHOD  BUT OF COURSE  RESEARCH WAS A COMPONENT; MASSIVE RESEARCH I KNEW EVERY HELIX OF EVERY SCRAP OF DNA IN EVERY COMPANY I BOUGHT</pattern><template>Papers stacked like the Himalayas in my office. And you know what?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOTTA SEE THIS FOR MYSELF  I'M DUBIOUS</pattern><template>That's another nice word.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU KNOW THE SMALL AND LARGE INTESTINES IS 20 FOOT LONG</pattern><template>I had no idea, I don't believe it.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE</pattern><template>My husband experienced some pain and dizziness this morning.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  REMIND ME    WHO ARE YOU ANYWAY</pattern><template>I'm sorry Karl, I've had it with this unqualified posturing little prick.</template></category><category><pattern>COUPLE OF KIDS</pattern><template>Couple of kids... Who's the husband?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK</pattern><template>Hm?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS ISN'T ABOUT VERNON AGAIN  MR  MORRA</pattern><template>What is this about?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>Because you'll know what to do.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I GOTTA DO THE FUNERAL AND GOD KNOWS WHAT ELSE      WE CAN'T MEET  OKAY   RIGHT  I GUESS I'LL JUST SEE YOU AT THE FUNERAL THEN  UH</pattern><template>No! I don't, I don't want that.</template></category><category><pattern>BABY  WHAT'S HAPPENING</pattern><template>We're stopped dead.  He's getting out...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS GUY WAS NOT GOING AWAY    A FEW PILLS WOULD BUY ME SOME TIME    HERE IT IS  WE'RE DONE</pattern><template>We will see.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT A FIX</pattern><template>I was able to calculate certain patterns in the algorithms.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  SOMETHING DOESN'T GEL HERE</pattern><template>Write down your number.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HEY  I THINK THEY'RE ACHIEVABLE</pattern><template>And what if I don't like your ideas?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A LEAGUE OF DONATIONS COMING IN  AND I DON'T THINK THEY'RE EVEN GONNA TRY A SECOND DEBATE</pattern><template>Great.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  NOT EVERYBODY UNDERSTANDS THE PATTERNS</pattern><template>and that gave me a little bit more of an uptake, but it's just a parlor trick.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP YOUR SUPPLY</pattern><template>No disruption in service.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST ACTUALLY MET HIM ON THE STREET AND HE ASKED ME TO COME UP</pattern><template>To buy drugs?</template></category><category><pattern>THE  BOYS  AND  THE  KITCHEN</pattern><template>Doesn't sound very, FDA approved Vern.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALLY NEED TO TALK TO YOU  WE'RE TALKING NOW   NO NO  LET'S MEET AT UH  BILLY'S ON GRANT    AT NOON</pattern><template>You can't see me Eddie.  Please please come. Please come.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU TAKE A LOOK AT THE LOWER LEFT HAND COLUMN IN 2008  FIVE COMPANIES WERE JOCKEYING FOR A POSITION BEFORE WE EVEN TOOK NOTICE</pattern><template>Jesus, he looks frail.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE WE SHOULD COOL OFF AND TALK AGAIN I DON'T THINK SO</pattern><template>Don't forget to vote.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HE'S NOT DOING WELL AT ALL  YEAH  HELLO  IS PAUL KAPLAN THERE</pattern><template>Ah, no. No he's not.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M UP TO MY ASS WITH INVESTMENT GUYS</pattern><template>and you don't have the half terrified, half cocky line of crap; which is, not to say, that I like yours any better, but you obviously pick your stocks in a way that I haven't seen before.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT VAN'S GONNA REAR END THAT TAXI</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT A LOT ON MY PLATE  YOU'RE LUCKY I AM HERE</pattern><template>Back in the old times.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THIS IS OVER</pattern><template>I do not know.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW YOU'RE NOT STUPID EDDIE  BUT DON'T MAKE THE CLASSIC SMART PERSON'S MISTAKE</pattern><template>thinking no one's smarter than you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT'S REALLY UH  MY OWN PERSONAL MANIFESTO ABOUT THE PLIGHT OF THE INDIVIDUAL IN THE 21 CENTURY</pattern><template>and I sort a created a Utopian society, where, we all sort of uh uh uh...</template></category><category><pattern>BACK IN THE OLD TIMES</pattern><template>I might peel your skin back, flay you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN</pattern><template>I mean, I took it too.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ARE YA</pattern><template>So, Eddie Morra, What's your secret?</template></category><category><pattern>I SUDDENLY KNEW EVERYTHING; ABOUT EVERYTHING   SURE DUDE  YOU'D GET A SHORT TERM SPIKE</pattern><template>but wouldn't that rapid expansion devalue the stock completely in two years?</template></category><category><pattern>HECK KARL  I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR</pattern><template>Listen, what you about to say is bullshit!</template></category><category><pattern>COUPLE OF KIDS    WHO'S THE HUSBAND</pattern><template>He walked out on her, if you really wanna know.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS CORRECT  AN EDWARD MORRA</pattern><template>He's here.</template></category><category><pattern>DO I LOOK LIKE I AM STILL DEALING</pattern><template>No, you don't. No.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YOU KNOW THE WAY IT WORKS</pattern><template>I know how it works.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT HANK ATWOOD</pattern><template>Atwood...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL IT'S A    I'M BEHIND</pattern><template>I'm behind on my book, and uh, It's pretty booked...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  THE EXACT METHOD OF DELIVERY TO THE BRAIN  UHHH</pattern><template>Dart to the dart board.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WONT BE A PROXY</pattern><template>a crazy prick like him giving away power of attorney?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU ARE NOT IN THE FINANCE GAME</pattern><template>What can you do for Karl van Loon?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM STILL THE SAME PERSON</pattern><template>I wasn't when I was on it.</template></category><category><pattern>PORTUGAL WITH HIS BIG MASSIVE NAVY</pattern><template>All they got now are salt Cod and cheap condoms.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE EVERYTHING  KARL</pattern><template>I'm 50 moves ahead of you and everybody else.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU DON'T HAVE THE HALF TERRIFIED  HALF COCKY LINE OF CRAP; WHICH IS  NOT TO SAY  THAT I LIKE YOURS ANY BETTER  BUT YOU OBVIOUSLY PICK YOUR STOCKS IN A WAY THAT I HAVEN'T SEEN BEFORE</pattern><template>Take a look at these companies and tell me what you think.</template></category><category><pattern>CREATIVE PROBLEMS  UM</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>UNBELIEVABLE</pattern><template>Have you got it?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SURE ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>I shut down your lab this morning.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S NOT INVADE RUSSIA IN THE WINTER</pattern><template>Let's go home. Let's pop a beer.</template></category><category><pattern>NO DISRUPTION IN SERVICE</pattern><template>Give you piece of mind. That's all.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TAKE YOU TO A HOSPITAL</pattern><template>No no no no, honey...</template></category><category><pattern>JUST BETWEEN US    WERE YOU THERE</pattern><template>I don't remember.</template></category><category><pattern>BY A HAIR</pattern><template>Sure, the stocks rose, but who wants to do all that work, for a shitty little uptake?</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE DEPT  OPEN THE DOOR</pattern><template>Open the door please!</template></category><category><pattern>FINALLY GET TO MEET THE GUYS THAT KEEPS THE LIGHTS ON</pattern><template>Karl?</template></category><category><pattern>GET THE BUGS OUT</pattern><template>Taper off I'm off it, Karl.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  CAUSE THERE ARE SAFEGUARDS</pattern><template>Against the aggressive over expansion?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE GOT SOME KIND OF INTERNET  HOME SALES KINDA JOB</pattern><template>Couple of kids.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL NEED IT TO CONTACT YOU LATER</pattern><template>Worth the risk?   What would you do?   Vern's cash, combined with an unprecedented surge in motivation   enabled me to finish the book in 4 days   A tablet a day, and what I could do with my day, was limitless.   In learned to play the piano in 3 days.   Math became useful And fun...  All in.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO GO</pattern><template>Oh Shit! Listen listen listen listen...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I NEED A FAVOR FIRST</pattern><template>Obviously, I'm in no condition to go out right now So I was wondering if you could pop down to the uh, dry cleaners; grab my suit for me?</template></category><category><pattern>I MIGHT PEEL YOUR SKIN BACK  FLAY YOU</pattern><template>Flay. That's a nice word, I didn't know this before.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING  MAN</pattern><template>Are you still there?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT CAN YOU DO FOR KARL VAN LOON</pattern><template>Since when do you speak Italian?</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT WEEK  YOU CAN GO  FUCK YOURSELF</pattern><template>Not that you'll feel anything.</template></category><category><pattern>I SUDDENLY HAD EXTRA REASON TO GET AWAY FROM HER    I HAD THOUGHTLESSLY INGESTED A SUBSTANCE   LIKE THE RENT'S NOT LOW ENOUGH</pattern><template>I had gotten remarkably little information from Vernon about what this drug would do.  you can even be a biker messenger and come up with that. Really!</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE DON'T HESITATE TO TELLS US</pattern><template>Obviously, we want to be as helpful and as practical as possible, Mrs. Atwood.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM EATING  KEVIN</pattern><template>Hey! Are you up for this?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GETTING CLOSER</pattern><template>Lindi, I love you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WOULDN'T THAT RAPID EXPANSION DEVALUE THE STOCK COMPLETELY IN TWO YEARS</pattern><template>No, cause there are safeguards.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  UM SPART'S WEREN'T BIG ON AMENITIES</pattern><template>Yea, and they eventually got their asses kicked.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY OTHER METEORIC RISES MIGHT BE EXPLAINED BY NZT    AT LEAST I HAD SOME    MY LIFE WASN'T IN JEOPARDY  YOU WAIT HERE</pattern><template>only my money. and my liberty  I've been all over them.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BEHIND ON MY BOOK  AND UH  IT'S PRETTY BOOKED</pattern><template>including my days and nights, if you really want to know.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE</pattern><template>When's the last time you ate something?</template></category><category><pattern>I HADN'T HEARD HER VOICE IN TEN YEARS      EDDIE</pattern><template>Melissa?   You were there?  um, just, just before. I had run into him on the street, and uh, yeah  Oh God   I wish I was more surprised, he was involved in some stuff.   I better not to say anymore.  No, no, that's probably a good idea.</template></category><category><pattern>WE COULD HAVE BEEN PARTNERS</pattern><template>So Ivan makes NZT.</template></category><category><pattern>WANNA TELL ME YOUR WHEREABOUTS THE NIGHT OF APRIL 2ND</pattern><template>I couldn't keep this quite on my own   Enter Morris Brant, the most lethal lawyer in New York.  You're lucky, somebody wiped the room.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM NOW ON  I'D HAPPILY BE HIS ERRAND BOY    WASH HIS WINDOWS  SCRUB HIS TOILETS      ANYTHING I CAN DO  TO GET MY HANDS ON THIS LITTLE CLEAR PILL   THAT WOULD BRING BACK  ENHANCED EDDIE   VERN</pattern><template>Vern?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO ASSESS YOUR COMPETITION  BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T COMPETED</pattern><template>Don't make me your competition.</template></category><category><pattern>MY BRAIN WAS JUST POURING THIS STUFF OUT    EVERYTHING I'D EVER READ  HEARD  SEEN WAS NOW ORGANIZED AND AVAILABLE   HERE IT IS  HERE YOU GO  EDDIE  HEY</pattern><template>Listen, I'm sure you have a portfolio but if don't...</template></category><category><pattern>JUST FINISH THE STORY</pattern><template>Well, I didn't take anymore and I didn't die But after a while I realized that I couldn't concentrate on anything for longer than 10 minutes..</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE MY OWN ASSISTANT</pattern><template>You believe that?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS ISN'T THE MATRIX</pattern><template>You have to know Eddie... I wrote you off.</template></category><category><pattern>I WASN'T WHEN I WAS ON IT</pattern><template>I did things, I would never do.</template></category><category><pattern>HELP</pattern><template>This man, this man is chasing me.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT</pattern><template>Hold on. There's guy from Ivan Chemcorp's in your office.</template></category><category><pattern>HE KNEW  HE HAD ME   SURE</pattern><template>From now on, I'd happily be his errand boy.   Wash his windows, scrub his toilets...   Anything I can do, to get my hands on this little clear pill   that would bring back, enhanced Eddie.  Vern?</template></category><category><pattern>VERN  WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Don't worry about it. I'm fine.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY WROTE MOST OF THIS GUY'S MAJOR OPINIONS</pattern><template>you'd ruler the clerks sons... They'd love to talk to you; exonerate their dad.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE YOUR PICK</pattern><template>This guy was not going away.   A few pills would buy me some time    Here it is. We're done.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DID YOU EVER PUT UP WITH ME</pattern><template>I was in love with you.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MAY BE ON YOUR MIND  THAT YOU'RE NOT GONNA CONTINUE TO WORK FOR ME ANYMORE</pattern><template>This has been the learning experience of my life.</template></category><category><pattern>A LITTLE INTIMIDATED</pattern><template>We started up again   her place.   my place.   basically everyplace.   In a sizzling 3 days of trading, the unknown Mr. Morra   trumped the market, prompting one top hedge fund manger to comment:   He's Houdini. He's a prophet of our times.   Okay, give me that.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURE YOU CAN</pattern><template>I can make us safe.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL IT'S NOT AS I IF HAVE A BLACK BOOK WITH YOUR NAME IN IT</pattern><template>If that's what you're talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT GAVE ME A LITTLE BIT MORE OF AN UPTAKE  BUT IT'S JUST A PARLOR TRICK</pattern><template>so then I went to door number 3 You're really implying that you've, some sort of ultimate formula?</template></category><category><pattern>SO  EDDIE  YOU ARE INTERESTED AFTER ALL</pattern><template>That stuff's amazing.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS ABOUT</pattern><template>The witness identified the Maria Winberg suspect...</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  AND I TOLD THEM THAT   FORGET IT</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>AND HOW AM I GONNA LOOK IF YOU DON'T</pattern><template>I know. Listen...   Sh! Listen to me. Pull yourself together   get down to the meeting Okay. Okay. I, I, I, I'll be there. I'll be there.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SO WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE    SOME UNKNOWN  UNTESTED  POSSIBLY DANGEROUS DRUG   SCAMMED OUT OF SOME UNIDENTIFIED LAB SOMEWHERE    GIVEN TO ME BY A HIGHLY UNRELIABLE GUY I HADN'T SEEN IN YEARS    SO YOU WANT SOME MORE</pattern><template>Yes. Definitely.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S IMPORTANT  I REALLY NEED TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>I realized, that there were other people, who I might now about NZT.   Vern's other clients.  Yeah, Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T APPRECIATE IT</pattern><template>You see, I dissolve it in solution.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  UH   LIV TOLD YOU THAT  I'M LOOKING FOR A SHORT TERM LOAN</pattern><template>Yeah, and I told them that   forget it.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE YOU'LL KNOW WHAT TO DO</pattern><template>You'll take it and then you'll know.  He's got a knife. Eddie, I can't think my way out of a knife.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S LIKE HEFNER MOVING OUT OF THE MANSION</pattern><template>I bought Ivan several months ago.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'S IT GOING</pattern><template>Well it's a... I'm behind.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO MONTHS AFTER I'D STARTED NZT      I WAS BROKERING THE BIGGEST MERGER IN CORPORATE HISTORY   IRONICALLY  IT'S GONNA BE CRUDE  CRUDE IS GONNA BE WHERE WE'RE GONNA HIT EM</pattern><template>Which yields a projected profit of 200%.</template></category><category><pattern>EDDIE I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE  WHY IS IT THAT  THE MOMENT YOUR LIFE EXCEEDS YOUR WILDEST DREAMS</pattern><template>The Knife  appears in your back.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVEN'T HAD TO BRIBE OR CHARM OR THREATEN YOUR WAY  TO SIT AT THIS TABLE</pattern><template>You don't know how to assess your competition, because you haven't competed...</template></category><category><pattern>CALL ME    IT'S  A LITTLE GRANDIOSE BUT I AM STILL READING    OKAY  HOW DID YOU DO THIS    I REALLY    CALL ME THE MINUTE  YOU GET IN  CALL  OKAY     WHO IS IT</pattern><template>Hey, Vernon, its Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE'S MY EX WIFE'S BROTHER</pattern><template>I just actually met him on the street and he asked me to come up.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS</pattern><template>Wouldn't know, I don't see you her.</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL I FOUND A MORE</pattern><template>permanent solution.  Unless you see a real threat, I never want it known that I have any security.</template></category><category><pattern>911    WHAT'S YOUR EMERGENCY   HI  I NEED TO REPORT UH    A MURDER</pattern><template>7B, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  I CAN'T PASS THE TEST RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>And how am I gonna look if you don't?</template></category><category><pattern>I SHUT DOWN YOUR LAB THIS MORNING</pattern><template>Eddie, I just wanna help you. That's all.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'D HAVE TO BACK OFF LIBYA REALLY</pattern><template>But, you don't want hear this from some schmuck who needs a ride home.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I HADN'T MISSED MUCH</pattern><template>I'd come this close to having an impact in the world.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  LIKE SOME OFF SHORE LAB MAKING FAKE VIAGRA  COME ON VERN</pattern><template>No. This is an exclusive product, that's coming on the stream next year.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU GUYS TIGHT</pattern><template>Hang out a lot?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WALKED OUT ON HER  IF YOU REALLY WANNA KNOW</pattern><template>But what do you care, man?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  BETTER GET BETTER</pattern><template>But Atwood wouldn't get better because Atwood was out of NZT.  Well, why are we surprised?</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE HANDLES THE RENT  SO YOU CAN FEED YOUR CRAP TO HIM</pattern><template>I suddenly had extra reason to get away from her.   I had thoughtlessly ingested a substance.  Like the rent's not low enough!</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU GOT IT</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS ON HIS WAY</pattern><template>Now be warned, he's mercurial.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE ARE TECTONIC PLATES THAT ARE SHIFTING RIGHT UNDER US</pattern><template>Pardon me one second.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES IT MATTER  I KNOW NOW</pattern><template>I wish you'd come to me at first, Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT THAT YOU'LL FEEL ANYTHING</pattern><template>I don't think your fortune 500 financial friends, would appreciate the details, of your little dilemma with the police.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  YOU DO KNOW  YOU'RE A FREAK</pattern><template>Your deductive powers are a gift from God, or chance, or straight shot of sperm...</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE STOPPING AND THINKING</pattern><template>Hey! We're doing pretty well.</template></category><category><pattern>I FOUND THAT IF I MAINTAINED AN EVEN DOSE  REMEMBERED TO EAT   DRANK NO ALCOHOL</pattern><template>The blackouts didn't occur  Tom is it possible to construct an imperceptible compartment?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOOD</pattern><template>Okay, its a fix.</template></category><category><pattern>105  THAT'S WHO YOU WERE TALKING TO CARL</pattern><template>Delirium.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL CALL IT AGAIN  SIR   OKAY  THE DECISION COULD'VE CHANGED</pattern><template>That makes sense   but discourtesy doesn't.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULD HAVE BOUGHT IVAN AT 33 A SHARE</pattern><template>We could have been partners.</template></category><category><pattern>APPARENTLY SO</pattern><template>But you are not in the finance game?</template></category><category><pattern>SO</pattern><template>How is Melissa doing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  BECAUSE I AM NOT STUPID</pattern><template>Nobody can operate at that level of mental activity and not crash.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK   THE BIGGEST CONTRIBUTOR  GIVE HIM HIS TWO CRAPPY LITTLE MINUTES</pattern><template>Ivan Chemcorp pharmaceuticals?</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON</pattern><template>If you take a look at the lower left hand column in 2008, five companies were jockeying for a position before we even took notice.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE MOVED UPSTATE</pattern><template>She got some kind of Internet, home sales kinda job.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  VERNON  ITS EDDIE</pattern><template>Eddie who?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE MARRIED FOR LIKE FIVE MINUTES</pattern><template>Look, I don't wanna talk about her.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GONNA TAKE TOO LONG</pattern><template>It is was it is. Or you'll kill people.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THERE'S SOMETHING YOU'RE HIDING FROM ME  I SMELL IT ON YOU</pattern><template>Right now,I wanna know why this deal is dead in the water!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY   TYLER  I GOTTA GO</pattern><template>I'm sick.</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO NO NO NO  LET ME LOOK</pattern><template>Can you see him?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SORRY</pattern><template>Hey, don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE YOU PIECE OF MIND  THAT'S ALL</pattern><template>And in return... I do what?</template></category><category><pattern>NO   WORDS HAVE APPEARED ON PAPER</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>NOBODY CAN OPERATE AT THAT LEVEL OF MENTAL ACTIVITY AND NOT CRASH</pattern><template>I stopped taking it.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL YOU HAVE TO DO  IS TO READ 3 PAGES JUST READ 3 PAGES IN THE NEXT HOUR</pattern><template>and, if you don't want to keep reading, I'll give you back the advance.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN DOING FOR THE LAST DAY   DON'T YOU GET IT  THIS IS YOUR TEST</pattern><template>Yeah. Well, I can't pass the test right now.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE AT LEAST YOU CAN GO TO THE BANK</pattern><template>What you got there?</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD</pattern><template>And then I began to form, an idea.   Suddenly, I knew exactly what I needed do.   It wasn't writing.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BRITS</pattern><template>Now they're just sitting in their dank little isle and fussing over their suits.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>The driver's distracted; he's texting; he's going 30mph...</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  IT'S TWO O'CLOCK IN THE AFTERNOON</pattern><template>When has that ever stopped you?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS</pattern><template>What? About the leak?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S IN IT</pattern><template>They've identified these, receptors in the brain that activate specific circuits.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOW</pattern><template>Well, I'm afraid I'm gonna have to leave you here Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SEE IT</pattern><template>What's in it?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'S YOUR DAY GOING</pattern><template>I've had better.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT ONE WORD</pattern><template>Creative problems, um?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID THIS GUY DO</pattern><template>I do not know. He was...</template></category><category><pattern>MY NEIGHBOR  MUST HAVE OPENED HIS DOOR TO COMPLAIN</pattern><template>For a guy with a 4 digit IQ, I must have missed something...</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN TAKING A LOT</pattern><template>Well maybe...</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME  MR  VAN LOON  MRS  ATWOOD IS IN YOUR OFFICE</pattern><template>Ah. Mrs. Atwood, Karl van Loon, My associate, Edward Morra.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS IT BRANT  OR SOMEONE ELSE    THE POLICE STATION  THE COAT ROOM   MR  MORRA</pattern><template>Mr. Morra.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU GOT THERE</pattern><template>What is it?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU DON'T  NO</pattern><template>Come on, let's get a drink I wanna hear about this book.</template></category><category><pattern>I  I HAVE A SUPPLY STASHED</pattern><template>you want me to go get it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T REALLY LIVE HERE  DO YOU</pattern><template>Well, um Spart's weren't big on amenities.</template></category><category><pattern>A FIGHT  I DON'T KNOW HOW TO FIGHT    OR DO I    IF YOUR ASSAILANTS DO NOT STOP  YOUR INSISTENCE WILL DISTRACT THE ATTACKER    OFF BALANCING YOUR OPPONENT  CAN MAKE USE OF HIS MOMENTUM   WHAT BAR WAS THIS    WHEN IT FINALLY STOPPED   I COULDN'T ACCOUNT FOR THE LAST 18 HOURS IN MY LIFE   HEY  IT'S ME</pattern><template>I thought you were coming over.   Is everything okay?</template></category><category><pattern>OH WHOA  WHOA  THIS MUST BE SOME  BIG ASS MERGER YOU'RE CONTEMPLATING AND THERE'S REALLY ONLY ONE COMPANY WITH ENOUGH BLING TO JUSTIFY A MERGER WITH VAN LOON AND ASSOCIATIONS</pattern><template>Who've you been talking to?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DIDN'T TAKE ANYMORE AND I DIDN'T DIE BUT AFTER A WHILE I REALIZED THAT I COULDN'T CONCENTRATE ON ANYTHING FOR LONGER THAN 10 MINUTES</pattern><template>I missed deadlines...</template></category><category><pattern>HE WASN'T PLAYING US  HE'S DYING</pattern><template>What do you know about this?</template></category><category><pattern>INTERESTING POINT    GRAMMATICALLY  THIS GUY WAS AN IDIOT WHICH SORT OF GIVES CREDENCE TO THE THEORY THAT ONE OF THE CLERKS  HE HAD FIRED</pattern><template>actually wrote most of this guy's major opinions.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU DOIN  HON</pattern><template>Nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF IT WAS A HALLUCINOGEN    IT'S PATHETIC</pattern><template>Oh my God! Listening to her rag   If I were tripping, I'd jump out a window   Hello!  Are you listening to me?</template></category><category><pattern>I STOPPED TAKING IT</pattern><template>Then?</template></category><category><pattern>ISN'T YOUR VAN LOON MEETING TOMORROW</pattern><template>Eddie?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY NOT</pattern><template>Because it worked out so well for you last time.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU OKAY</pattern><template>What are you doing out here?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM AT YOUR DISPOSAL</pattern><template>You don't really live here, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MINUTE YOUR BEST FRIEND  THE NEXT  YOU'RE A LEPER</pattern><template>And he needs direct answers.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK  I DON'T KNOW WHERE YOU ARE</pattern><template>I was under the impression, our business was settled.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULDN'T KNOW  I DON'T SEE YOU HER</pattern><template>She moved upstate.</template></category><category><pattern>TO OUR PLACE</pattern><template>It'll be cost effective.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW  THE ONLY THING I HAD AN IMPACT ON</pattern><template>was the sidewalk.</template></category><category><pattern>KARL</pattern><template>Mr. Morra.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IN RETURN    I DO WHAT</pattern><template>Give a little advice maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>INCLUDING MY DAYS AND NIGHTS  IF YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW</pattern><template>Well, how much have you written on it?</template></category><category><pattern>BRIEFLY    THIS ISN'T WORKING   WELL  EVEN THOUGH EVERYTHING YOU SAID IS TRUE  I STILL LOVE YOU</pattern><template>I gotta get back to work.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S SAY 45 HUMPH  $45 000</pattern><template>40 million's plenty Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT YOU  ARE YOU UH</pattern><template>You still dealing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ASKED YOU</pattern><template>Hastings has it's own history.</template></category><category><pattern>MY  MY WORK RATE INCREASED  JUST AS INSANELY OVERNIGHT</pattern><template>and my boss started to hate me They offered me his job.</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS GONNA DO IT</pattern><template>He's not gonna do it.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S JUST NOT DO THIS</pattern><template>I am gonna hand in 90 pages tomorrow on Friday You just wait to see what she says.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T REMEMBER</pattern><template>I don't want to make concessions to you...</template></category><category><pattern>HE KILLED TWO GUYS</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>LIMITLESS SUPPLY</pattern><template>We know you can't get anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT  YOU'RE NOT MAKING ANYMORE</pattern><template>That's right. I'm not. I thought better of it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVEN'T GIVEN ME THE ANSWER</pattern><template>You haven't you asked the question.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST THIS ONCE</pattern><template>Oh, No, no, no...</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW I'M RIGHT</pattern><template>I mean, I didn't know who or what I was talking to.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S SOMEONE FOLLOWING ME</pattern><template>Are you sure?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T PAY</pattern><template>You know what we do?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'VE IDENTIFIED THESE  RECEPTORS IN THE BRAIN THAT ACTIVATE SPECIFIC CIRCUITS</pattern><template>And you know how they say that we can access only 20% of our brain?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BAFFLED BY THIS GUY</pattern><template>Comes out of nowhere, so strong... Has me on the run, before I could even get to anybody in his camp.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M HERE NOW</pattern><template>Come on, keep going.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO BE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES</pattern><template>or brain dead   stuck full of tubes?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I'LL HOLD</pattern><template>It took them forever.   And the longer I stood there, the clearer I saw   Vern had known, whoever had done this   And one guess, what they'd been looking for   But had they found it?  Shit. If you ever cooked, I'd be dead too.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA BE ABLE TO LOOK BEHIND ME IF THE OPPORTUNITY PRESENTS ITSELF</pattern><template>And don't wear the same color suit.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS WAS IT IS  OR YOU'LL KILL PEOPLE</pattern><template>Look. You need 12 18 months I'll give you two million dollars If you can do it in 6 I found that we could cart the cost, 30%.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS IN THE BUILDING</pattern><template>I was getting coffee?</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH YOU'D COME TO ME AT FIRST  EDDIE</pattern><template>I could have bought Ivan at 33 a share.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I SORTA GOT MYSELF TOGETHER</pattern><template>NZT will do that to you..</template></category><category><pattern>GO  GO</pattern><template>Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS DITHERING  HE WAS THE THIRD FROM THE RIGHT  NO NOT HIM    HERE YOU GO  A THING OF BEAUTY</pattern><template>You had that made?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  FROM 12 000 TO 2 3 MILLION IN TEN DAYS</pattern><template>I do have a formula, Mr. Pierce.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE A LOOK AT THESE COMPANIES AND TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK</pattern><template>Right now?</template></category><category><pattern>SOON YOU NEED TO GET THAT REPLACED</pattern><template>But you already knew that.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE GONNA BE OUT ON THE STREETS</pattern><template>And then I felt it.   I was blind, but now I see.    What's wrong?</template></category><category><pattern>SIT DOWN</pattern><template>What do you know about Hank Atwood?</template></category><category><pattern>WORKS BETTER  IF YOU'RE ALREADY SMART</pattern><template>Vernon, who did this to you?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M AFRAID I'M GONNA HAVE TO LEAVE YOU HERE EDDIE</pattern><template>But I really, I really do wanna do this again. So, call me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN HAS THAT EVER STOPPED YOU</pattern><template>So.</template></category><category><pattern>AND</pattern><template>a little intimidated.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T BOOKS    IT WAS MUCH BIGGER THAN THAT   BUT IT WILL TAKE MONEY TO GET THERE   IN A DOWN MARKET  NO ONE WAS MAKING MUCH</pattern><template>But, no one had NZT.   Armed Vern's last 800 Dollars, I made $2,000 in a day.   Next day, 7500   It was too slow   I'd need more capital.   Banks weren't lending to guys like me.  That's him in the corner back there.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN MAKE US SAFE</pattern><template>I'm back! Okay   Who's back? Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU KNOW WHAT EDDIE  LET'S NOT EVEN GO THERE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Right now, I just want to keep you brilliant and healthy.</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE THINGS SAVED YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>But they weren't me.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  EDDIE</pattern><template>This is hardly a surprise.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I'M REALLY HAPPY YOU'RE HERE WITH ME</pattern><template>I'm proud of you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WISHING I'D BLOW MY BRAINS OUT</pattern><template>but my existence shouldn't make you this upset   What is it?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S STILL ON</pattern><template>Oh! Based on your charts and projections?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL NOW YOU'RE GOING BACKWARDS  WHAT ELSE YOU GOT</pattern><template>A prediction.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AN EDITOR</pattern><template>I have my own assistant.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE HAD BETTER</pattern><template>I still can't deal with that haircut.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A WASTE OF MY TIME  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>I'm getting out of this side of the business.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>There's a formula with a complex method  but of course, research was a component; massive research I knew every helix of every scrap of DNA in every company I bought.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH LICO CIMPENTI OIC ACID</pattern><template>I suddenly knew everything; about everything.  Sure dude! You'd get a short term spike...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STILL DEALING</pattern><template>Do I look like I am still dealing?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN DOING SOME CONSULTING FOR A PHARMACEUTICAL COMPANY</pattern><template>What, like some off shore lab making fake Viagra? Come on Vern.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST ASPIRIN</pattern><template>Don't look like no aspirin I ever see.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  DO YOU THINK WE CAN MEET SOMEWHERE</pattern><template>I really need to talk to you  we're talking now.  No no, let's meet at uh, Billy's on Grant... At noon?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY BUDDY  ARE YOU TRYING TO PISS ME OFF</pattern><template>What are you doing, man?</template></category><category><pattern>I'D START THERE</pattern><template>Interesting point... Grammatically, this guy was an idiot which sort of gives credence to the theory that one of the clerks, he had fired..</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A BIG SWISS BANK ACCOUNT YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>Let's not invade Russia in the winter.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN</pattern><template>Sit down.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW HOW IT'S GOING</pattern><template>I am, I was, your girlfriend.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT IT IS</pattern><template>You're still dealing.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING</pattern><template>I'll call it again, sir.  Okay, the decision could've changed...</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T GO IN  I WANTED TO WALK  MOVE  DIGEST  INGEST   THERE ARE MOMENTS IN LIFE   MOMENTS  WHEN YOU KNOW  YOU'VE CROSSED A BRIDGE  YOUR OLD LIFE IS OVER    VAN LOON WAS MY BRIDGE</pattern><template>I finally had my shot.   Wall Street would provide my nest egg.   but then how far could I go?   CEO? A global force? Maybe president.   time, somebody shook up the free world and got the things done.   Suddenly, there was another skip.  How have I gone the last 20 blocks?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE STOPPED DEAD   HE'S GETTING OUT</pattern><template>Eddie, he's walking over here.</template></category><category><pattern>OBVIOUSLY  WE WANT TO BE AS HELPFUL AND AS PRACTICAL AS POSSIBLE  MRS  ATWOOD</pattern><template>Thank you, gentlemen.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT MUCH  UH  I JUST BROKE UP    WHAT AM I  WHAT'S UP UH  I'M WRITING    WRITING A LOT OH  YOU STILL TRYING TO WRITE</pattern><template>Matter of fact, I have a book contract   Really?   Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AN UNPARALLELED THREE TIER SECURITY SYSTEM</pattern><template>A fortress, with a hell of a view.</template></category><category><pattern>NO   NO</pattern><template>I mean, does it have to be that key?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>Of all the people I called...   three were dead, and the rest were sick.   Hello  Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THERE'S BEEN MOVEMENT ALRIGHT</pattern><template>Atwood's in a coma.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM  I WAS  YOUR GIRLFRIEND</pattern><template>That word doesn't even begin to describe what you are to me.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM WE CAN'T DO THAT</pattern><template>No. You tell em.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S NOT YOU YOU WERE DIFFERENT BEFORE</pattern><template>I am still the same person.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I DON'T SEE YOU BEFORE  AND I DON'T LIKE YOU ALREADY WHY DO I GIVE YOU $100 000 DOLLARS</pattern><template>Because...</template></category><category><pattern>SO HAVE YOU DECIDED EDDIE  WHATTA YA GONNA DO</pattern><template>When this is over?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT ONE OF THOSE KIND OF GUYS   ARE YOU EDDY</pattern><template>we lose you, if there's a screen in the room?</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT TELL ME I LOOK GOOD LIKE THIS  I KNOW</pattern><template>I didn't want you to see me this way.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GOVERNMENTAL BRIBES SYSTEM IS ITSELF CORRUPT SO OF COURSE  INFORMATION ABOUT ITS INNER WORKINGS  LIKE ANYTHING  CAN BE BOUGHT</pattern><template>Go on.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU GOT A FIX ON THE GAME</pattern><template>No, not a fix.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  WHAT YOU ABOUT TO SAY IS BULLSHIT</pattern><template>I know there's something you're hiding from me. I smell it on you!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  WHAT</pattern><template>What did this guy do?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT EXCUSED</pattern><template>What, a man in your employ, can't take a piss, Karl?</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU ASKED YOURSELF  WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO  WHEN YOU RUN OUT</pattern><template>When did you know?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING'S A TECHNICALITY FROM HERE ON  ISN'T IT  EDDIE</pattern><template>I think we both know where it's headed, if you can, maintain.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU TAKE THIS  YOU'RE MINE    OKAY   YOU UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>you don't pay...</template></category><category><pattern>THE POLICE WOULD LATER NOTE     THAT MY APARTMENTS PREVIOUS OWNER WAS AN ARMS DEALER    OF COURSE THESE INTRUDERS  HAD BEEN HIS DISSATISFIED CLIENTS   AND THE NIGHT WAS STILL YOUNG  WELL  I'M SURE YOU'RE CURIOUS TO KNOW WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR BOSS</pattern><template>I certainly am.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NEVER STAND TOO CLOSE TOGETHER</pattern><template>I wanna be able to look behind me if the opportunity presents itself.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D SEEN IT BEFORE</pattern><template>12 years ago in college.  sitting on the couch with a T.A.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SENATE  WELL WHO KNOWS</pattern><template>Everything's a technicality from here on. Isn't it, Eddie?</template></category><category><pattern>DO I LOOK GOOD TO YOU</pattern><template>I'm broke and I'm depressed off my ass.</template></category><category><pattern>IN MY HOUSE</pattern><template>Unbelievable!</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT AWAY  IT WAS OBVIOUS  HE WAS ON NZT NEXT WEEK  I'M GONNA NEED 20 PILLS</pattern><template>Next week, you can go, fuck yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>VERNON DIDN'T TELL YOU ANY OF THIS  DID HE</pattern><template>No What, when we he told me about this amazing new drug...</template></category><category><pattern>SAFER THOUGH MY STASH NOW WAS    I WAS NOT SITTING AROUND UNTIL I RAN OUT   WELL  CAN I COMBINE THESE INGREDIENTS IN THE SAME EXACT QUANTITY  YES</pattern><template>but, the exact method of delivery to the brain, uhhh...</template></category><category><pattern>OUTSIDE LENNOX HILL HOSPITAL TODAY    MORE TWISTS AND TURNS IN THE VAN LOON   ATWOOD MERGER    THERE IS ABSOLUTELY    NO TRUTH TO THE RUMOR OF THIS MERGER    NONE WHATSOEVER    MY HUSBAND IS HAVING TESTS</pattern><template>it's a difficult time   We would appreciate you direct, your further questions to our attorney.   Ah, Yes...We have no further comments at this time...   we're just awaiting the results   from the latest round of test, and hoping the best.   Thank you!  Eddie...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MAKES BOTH OF US VERY HAPPY CAMPERS</pattern><template>I found that if I maintained an even dose, remembered to eat   drank no alcohol...</template></category><category><pattern>I  I'M SURPRISED</pattern><template>Let's just not do this.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M 50 MOVES AHEAD OF YOU AND EVERYBODY ELSE</pattern><template>What makes you think I don't know the guy with a beat on you right now?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  IF MY ATTORNEY WAS REALLY WORKING FOR MR  ATWOOD  TRYING TO SAVE HIS LIFE</pattern><template>Why is he dead?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HOW ARE YOU  EDDIE</pattern><template>Good to see you again.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING WRONG IN LAW SCHOOL</pattern><template>How do you know I am in law school?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN BE MAKING ACCUSATIONS LIKE THAT AND BE WALKING AROUND ALIVE</pattern><template>That you wouldn't even think that shows me how unprepared your are to fight me.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  ARE YOU UP FOR THIS</pattern><template>You sure?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T PROPOSE</pattern><template>Why not?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  YOU NEED 12 18 MONTHS I'LL GIVE YOU TWO MILLION DOLLARS IF YOU CAN DO IT IN 6 I FOUND THAT WE COULD CART THE COST  30%</pattern><template>and uhm...</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT FRANCE  WE GOT POLAND</pattern><template>We got a big Swiss bank account You know what...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE NO IDEA  WHAT KIND OF ENEMY I CAN BE</pattern><template>That van's gonna rear end that taxi.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT ATWOOD WOULDN'T GET BETTER BECAUSE ATWOOD WAS OUT OF NZT   WELL  WHY ARE WE SURPRISED</pattern><template>How many other meteoric rises might be explained by NZT?   At least I had some.   My life wasn't in jeopardy  You wait here.</template></category><category><pattern>TRY TO TAPER OFF  OTHERWISE  THE HEADACHES ARE JUST BEGINNING</pattern><template>I have to go.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S WEAK CIRCUMSTANTIAL AT BEST</pattern><template>Just between us... Were you there?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE UH</pattern><template>Like, Viennese kinda uh, um chairs and stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN  THEN I GOT  I GOT SCARED</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>40 MILLION'S PLENTY EDDIE</pattern><template>There's a lot more where that'll come from You know, Eddie...</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN DID YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Does it matter? I know now.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WE'RE DOING PRETTY WELL</pattern><template>We got France. We got Poland.</template></category><category><pattern>I FINALLY HAD MY SHOT    WALL STREET WOULD PROVIDE MY NEST EGG    BUT THEN HOW FAR COULD I GO    CEO  A GLOBAL FORCE  MAYBE PRESIDENT    TIME  SOMEBODY SHOOK UP THE FREE WORLD AND GOT THE THINGS DONE    SUDDENLY  THERE WAS ANOTHER SKIP   HOW HAVE I GONE THE LAST 20 BLOCKS</pattern><template>I got another 10 blocks   ...and then...  I was way up town.</template></category><category><pattern>A GIFT  NOT EARNED</pattern><template>You do not know what I know, because you have not earned those powers.</template></category><category><pattern>OR I GONNA MAKE YOU TELL ME QUESTION IS</pattern><template>Which is gonna come first?</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND</pattern><template>What do you think I am, some financial institution?</template></category><category><pattern>SOME OF OUR IDEAS ARE A BIT AMBITIOUS</pattern><template>But hey! I think they're achievable.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  I DISSOLVE IT IN SOLUTION</pattern><template>you shoot it.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GET UP  I SAID DON'T GET UP  SIT DOWN</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEN I DISCOVERED THIS THING    GOOGLE</pattern><template>Did you know the small and large intestines is 20 foot long?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS TWO YEARS AGO</pattern><template>I haven't been the same since.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IVAN MAKES NZT</pattern><template>We it'll never officially exist.</template></category><category><pattern>MORRA</pattern><template>not a good time, Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST SAW THE CORNER OF IT</pattern><template>How did you know that?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL MAYBE</pattern><template>Maybe they've worked out the bugs maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A LOT MORE WHERE THAT'LL COME FROM YOU KNOW  EDDIE</pattern><template>it may be on your mind, that you're not gonna continue to work for me anymore...</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  LISTEN      SH  LISTEN TO ME  PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER   GET DOWN TO THE MEETING OKAY  OKAY  I  I  I  I'LL BE THERE  I'LL BE THERE</pattern><template>Hey. How are you, Eddie?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S HERE</pattern><template>The victim's sister.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  KARL  GOOD TO SEE YOU</pattern><template>How are ya?</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE WHEN DO YOU SPEAK ITALIAN</pattern><template>Self improvement month.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I GOT SICK</pattern><template>Headaches, throwing up So I went back to, Veron...</template></category><category><pattern>EDDIE  HE'S WALKING OVER HERE</pattern><template>Lindi...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT STUPID</pattern><template>I know you're not stupid Eddie, but don't make the classic smart person's mistake...</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING'S STERILIZED</pattern><template>We're gonna keep you alive through the whole shebang.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU LOOK AT COLUMN 4  THIS WAS THE FIRST</pattern><template>You're good.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  UH  WHAT  WHAT'S IT CALLED</pattern><template>Doesn't have a street name yet.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T YOU THINK SOME SMART ASS AND NZT MIGHT HAVE TWO OR THREE  OR EVEN FOUR LABS</pattern><template>So what. You're not making anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>EDWARD  YOU GOOD</pattern><template>Yeah! Told you I have a lunch.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE CHECKS FROM DUBAI  DUMPING IN CHILE  DISAPPEARED OFFICIALS WHEN YOU SAID THE SPOT</pattern><template>You wanna go to war with me?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT WE DO</pattern><template>I cut you at waist.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN I BEGAN TO FORM  AN IDEA    SUDDENLY  I KNEW EXACTLY WHAT I NEEDED DO    IT WASN'T WRITING</pattern><template>It wasn't books.   It was much bigger than that   But it will take money to get there.  In a down market, no one was making much.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE LEGAL</pattern><template>I, I have a supply stashed.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME YOUR KEYS</pattern><template>I'll go to your apartment.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THEY'RE JUST SITTING IN THEIR DANK LITTLE ISLE AND FUSSING OVER THEIR SUITS</pattern><template>No one stopping and thinking...</template></category><category><pattern>LAST YEAR YOU TRADED INSIDER INFORMATION 17 TIMES</pattern><template>You threating me?</template></category><category><pattern>NZT WILL DO THAT TO YOU</pattern><template>What do you mean?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE EDDIE EDDIE  COME OUT</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>It's just aspirin.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'VE YOU BEEN TALKING TO</pattern><template>Oh, I am just connecting the dots.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN'T ALLOW ANY DISPARITY IN RACE OR PHYSICAL TYPE BETWEEN YOU AND THE REST OF THE LINE UP</pattern><template>they're as close to your clones, as I could possibly get.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S CURRENTLY AT LENOX HILL   UNDERGOING TEST</pattern><template>I just want you to know we have every intention of signing the contract.</template></category><category><pattern>WE STARTED UP AGAIN   HER PLACE    MY PLACE    BASICALLY EVERYPLACE    IN A SIZZLING 3 DAYS OF TRADING  THE UNKNOWN MR  MORRA   TRUMPED THE MARKET  PROMPTING ONE TOP HEDGE FUND MANGER TO COMMENT:   HE'S HOUDINI  HE'S A PROPHET OF OUR TIMES    OKAY  GIVE ME THAT</pattern><template>He's god!?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO HOME  LET'S POP A BEER</pattern><template>Let's live off the interest.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASURE</pattern><template>I wanted to make this as confidential as possible.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT STUFF'S AMAZING</pattern><template>Works better, if you're already smart.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS LIKE   DOWN THE HATCH    AND IT WAS  IT WAS AMAZING</pattern><template>I read Brian Green's, The Elegant Universe   in 45 minutes and I understood it.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  I CAN'T   I CAN'T MAKE THE MEETING TODAY   WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>I can't come in today.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T SEE ME EDDIE   PLEASE PLEASE COME  PLEASE COME</pattern><template>It's important. I really need to know what you're talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE ALL THIS DATA TO ANALYZE</pattern><template>What have you been doing for the last day?  Don't you get it? This is your test.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T ASK FOR YOUR PROJECTIONS</pattern><template>I know, but I think If you take a look at them...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS  ATWOOD 101  I MEAN</pattern><template>Doesn't everybody know about Atwood?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SICK</pattern><template>I'm sorry!</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT TO TALK ABOUT YOU  OKAY</pattern><template>Tell me about this book.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL NEVER PROCEED ME YOU'LL ALWAYS FOLLOW ME</pattern><template>never more than 15 steps behind.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WHOLE WORLD WILL HAVE TO COME BEGGING FOR ENERGY LIKE OLIVER TWIST AND HIS BOWL OF GRUEL</pattern><template>Well now you're going backwards. What else you got?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>I rely on your discretion.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE AS CLOSE TO YOUR CLONES  AS I COULD POSSIBLY GET</pattern><template>It's gotta be, just one big handsome blur to this guy.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHO MAKES THEM</pattern><template>I do not know.</template></category><category><pattern>BEATS ME OUT OF TWO PROPERTIES  INVESTMENT COMPANIES UP NORTH</pattern><template>We're here in the front of the hotel where a woman...   identified as Maria Winberg, was found dead in her room last night.   a victim of foul play..   Miss Winberg was a well known socialite...   but was also known for her dedicated charity work around the city.   Police spent hours, questioning hotel staff and patrons.   and an eye witness reported seeing a man leaving the scene.  How can we convince him that I can raise his game?</template></category><category><pattern>AS THIS PERSON</pattern><template>Wanna tell me your whereabouts the night of April 2nd?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE  CURLY CUE LEG THINGS</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL NEVER LET THEM TOUCH ME</pattern><template>My neighbor, must have opened his door to complain.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE WAY HOME  I THOUGHT ABOUT MELISSA    HOW COULD SHE BE A FAILURE TOO     SHE'D BEEN SO SMART</pattern><template>Smarter than anyone around her   Clearly, there was a direct link between this Eddie...   Slightly drunk at three o'clock in the afternoon, and an earlier Eddie.   vomiting on his boss' desk...   or stealing his dying aunts Percocet.   So who can blame Lindie for dumping me?   In the end, how much worse could it get?   I didn't want to see anybody.   Especially not my landlord's nasty young wife    Valerie, Tuesday...</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS IN LOVE WITH YOU</pattern><template>So when does the book come out?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T  I DON'T HAVE A KEY</pattern><template>Oh that's right.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM GONNA HAND IN 90 PAGES TOMORROW ON FRIDAY YOU JUST WAIT TO SEE WHAT SHE SAYS</pattern><template>Eddie!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FORGET ABOUT ME EH</pattern><template>No no no 12:00 and you're not here!</template></category><category><pattern>IT TOOK THEM FOREVER    AND THE LONGER I STOOD THERE  THE CLEARER I SAW   VERN HAD KNOWN  WHOEVER HAD DONE THIS   AND ONE GUESS  WHAT THEY'D BEEN LOOKING FOR   BUT HAD THEY FOUND IT   SHIT  IF YOU EVER COOKED  I'D BE DEAD TOO</pattern><template>Police dept! Open the door please.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT KNOW</pattern><template>You haven't given me the answer.</template></category><category><pattern>AND LATER   WHAT ARE GONNA BE BOTHERING ME WITH</pattern><template>Well, given where you're heading...</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO GET SOME LUNCH</pattern><template>After you, Senator.</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T BE BOTHERING MUCH AT FIRST</pattern><template>And later...What are gonna be bothering me with?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT  YOU'RE NOT SOMEBODY I WANT TO DISAPPOINT</pattern><template>Don't get up. I said don't get up. Sit down!</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SEE YOUR HANDS    I'M THE ONE WHO CALLED    I CALLED YOU GUYS</pattern><template>So you guys tight?</template></category><category><pattern>IN THIS JACKET</pattern><template>In all of them.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER MORE THAN 15 STEPS BEHIND</pattern><template>And never stand too close together.</template></category><category><pattern>VERNON  WHO DID THIS TO YOU</pattern><template>Trust me, you do not want to know.</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN'T EVERYBODY KNOW ABOUT ATWOOD</pattern><template>Where was he two years ago?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  NO ONE HAD NZT    ARMED VERN'S LAST 800 DOLLARS  I MADE $2 000 IN A DAY    NEXT DAY  7500   IT WAS TOO SLOW   I'D NEED MORE CAPITAL    BANKS WEREN'T LENDING TO GUYS LIKE ME   THAT'S HIM IN THE CORNER BACK THERE</pattern><template>So, uh...Liv told you that, I'm looking for a short term loan?</template></category><category><pattern>VERY EXITING STUFF</pattern><template>I got a lot on my plate, you're lucky I am here.</template></category><category><pattern>I BOUGHT IVAN SEVERAL MONTHS AGO</pattern><template>I'm surprised you didn't hear.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  THESE GUYS ARE GONNA FIND IT</pattern><template>Or I gonna make you tell me Question is...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW I AM IN LAW SCHOOL</pattern><template>People who aren't, usually don't carry around dry..</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAS GREAT   SO MOM  I'VE BEEN DOING A LITTLE RESEARCH ON AUNT HELEN'S TUMOR  AND</pattern><template>it's totally clear, that anybody with Familial Adomis Phalacrosis...</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  KEVIN</pattern><template>I made some new friends who invited me to the beach.   The beach, was not nearby.   All my fear, all my shyness, gone!   But mere lounging wasn't enough.   only problem, if I wasn't moving forward   I felt like I was going to explode    Anybody ever jumped?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  TOLD YOU I HAVE A LUNCH</pattern><template>I am sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW HOW MUCH THAT COSTS</pattern><template>Eight hundred bucks... A pop.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DESERVE IT</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD ON  THERE'S GUY FROM IVAN CHEMCORP'S IN YOUR OFFICE</pattern><template>I've a lunch.</template></category><category><pattern>BROTHER  I AM LIGHT YEARS FROM THAT NOW</pattern><template>I've been doing some consulting for a pharmaceutical company.</template></category><category><pattern>AND TRUST ME WHEN I SAY THIS I AM NOT EVEN BEING CREATIVE</pattern><template>There's no way you can be making accusations like that and be walking around alive.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CEO WAS JUST INDICTED BUT NOT FOR THE BIG FAT DEFENSIVE CONTRACT HE BRIBED HIS WAY INTO THAT'S STILL ON SHOULD BE ANNOUNCED NEXT WEEK  I WAS JACKED IN  BOOTED UP    AT THE END OF WEEK  MY BROKERAGE ACCOUNT    CONTAINED OVER TWO MILLION DOLLARS    WORD  QUICKLY GOT OUT    YOU HAVE 19 MESSAGES    FOUR JOB OFFERS  MY BANK RAISING MY LINE OF CREDIT   A REPORTER FROM THE NEW YORK POST     REALLY CALL ME BACK MR  MORRA</pattern><template>No one makes money that fast  This Article's gonna get written   with or without you.   And finally, Kevin Doyle, trying to sound casual.   Eddie, I was talking you up to my boss and well, the impossible happened bud.  But we got you a meeting with Karl van Loon.</template></category><category><pattern>EXPLAIN</pattern><template>Unless you're playing both sides of the fence.</template></category><category><pattern>PERMANENT SOLUTION   UNLESS YOU SEE A REAL THREAT  I NEVER WANT IT KNOWN THAT I HAVE ANY SECURITY</pattern><template>You'll never proceed me You'll always follow me.</template></category><category><pattern>YEA  AND ALL YOU PEOPLE GET CAUGHT</pattern><template>What are you gonna do then?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'S IT BEEN  LIKE NINE YEARS</pattern><template>God!</template></category><category><pattern>THE STOCKS WENT UP</pattern><template>by a hair.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MAKES SENSE   BUT DISCOURTESY DOESN'T</pattern><template>It's still on.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I WALK YOU TO WORK</pattern><template>What you doin, hon?</template></category><category><pattern>TO BUY DRUGS</pattern><template>No, No! What?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT ANOTHER 10 BLOCKS      AND THEN     I WAS WAY UP TOWN</pattern><template>Hey! Watch it!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA KEEP YOU ALIVE THROUGH THE WHOLE SHEBANG</pattern><template>You're gonna get a front row seat, baby!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I HAVEN'T BEEN TALKING TO ANYBODY  KARL</pattern><template>I'm not stupid!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ON A SPECIAL MEDICATION</pattern><template>okay.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  EDDIE</pattern><template>Okay  Eddie, give me a call, when you get in.   Eddie, I am 40 pages further in.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU BETTER BE PREPARED</pattern><template>I am at your disposal.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE THAT GUY    THAT WAS ME  NOT SO LONG AGO    WHAT KIND OF GUY  WITHOUT A DRUG OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM LOOKS THIS WAY    ONLY A WRITER    STRANGELY ENOUGH  NOBODY BELIEVED THAT I ACTUALLY HAD A BOOK CONTRACT   WELL IT'S BEST RATED AS A SCI FI NOVEL</pattern><template>but it's really uh, my own personal manifesto about the plight of the individual in the 21 century.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL SEE</pattern><template>Until I found a more...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'D RULER THE CLERKS SONS    THEY'D LOVE TO TALK TO YOU; EXONERATE THEIR DAD</pattern><template>that'd give you something that no one else has...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE A CREEP AREN'T YOU</pattern><template>You've been following me.</template></category><category><pattern>WALLS OF YOUR HEART ARE DILATED</pattern><template>Aorta's not standing up.</template></category><category><pattern>COLD FEET</pattern><template>With all last night to tell us that.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS TRYING TO MAKE</pattern><template>waiting for her coming back out of the bathroom, hoping she'd have a condom.   Somehow, my unconscious had served that up.   A memory I'd never even recorded...   or was there the whole time and I all I need was the access?  If you're writing a paper, that's not the book I'd use.</template></category><category><pattern>WAITING FOR HER COMING BACK OUT OF THE BATHROOM  HOPING SHE'D HAVE A CONDOM    SOMEHOW  MY UNCONSCIOUS HAD SERVED THAT UP    A MEMORY I'D NEVER EVEN RECORDED      OR WAS THERE THE WHOLE TIME AND I ALL I NEED WAS THE ACCESS   IF YOU'RE WRITING A PAPER  THAT'S NOT THE BOOK I'D USE</pattern><template>Who asked you?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN I FELT IT    I WAS BLIND  BUT NOW I SEE     WHAT'S WRONG</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE  VIENNESE KINDA UH  UM CHAIRS AND STUFF</pattern><template>like, curly cue leg things.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD GOTTEN REMARKABLY LITTLE INFORMATION FROM VERNON ABOUT WHAT THIS DRUG WOULD DO   YOU CAN EVEN BE A BIKER MESSENGER AND COME UP WITH THAT  REALLY</pattern><template>What if it was a hallucinogen?.  It's pathetic!</template></category><category><pattern>OBVIOUSLY  I'M IN NO CONDITION TO GO OUT RIGHT NOW SO I WAS WONDERING IF YOU COULD POP DOWN TO THE UH  DRY CLEANERS; GRAB MY SUIT FOR ME</pattern><template>And maybe grab a little breakfast for us.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALIZE THIS IS A USELESS PLATITUDE  BUT IF THERE'S ANYTHING WE CAN DO</pattern><template>Please don't hesitate to tells us.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE US A SECOND</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A SURPRISE</pattern><template>They told me somebody from Ivan was coming across...</template></category><category><pattern>PATTERN RECOGNITION</pattern><template>That's your cycle help?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I HAVE IT BACK</pattern><template>No   No?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WORD DOESN'T EVEN BEGIN TO DESCRIBE WHAT YOU ARE TO ME</pattern><template>Partner? Squeeze?</template></category><category><pattern>ATWOOD</pattern><template>Atwood... Um, He's an iconoclast...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THE ASKING PRICE</pattern><template>8.5 I'll take it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT MY EXISTENCE SHOULDN'T MAKE YOU THIS UPSET   WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>That's none of your business!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE HERE IN THE FRONT OF THE HOTEL WHERE A WOMAN      IDENTIFIED AS MARIA WINBERG  WAS FOUND DEAD IN HER ROOM LAST NIGHT    A VICTIM OF FOUL PLAY     MISS WINBERG WAS A WELL KNOWN SOCIALITE      BUT WAS ALSO KNOWN FOR HER DEDICATED CHARITY WORK AROUND THE CITY    POLICE SPENT HOURS  QUESTIONING HOTEL STAFF AND PATRONS    AND AN EYE WITNESS REPORTED SEEING A MAN LEAVING THE SCENE   HOW CAN WE CONVINCE HIM THAT I CAN RAISE HIS GAME</pattern><template>Got any ideas?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WATCH IT</pattern><template>a fight? I don't know how to fight.   or do I?   if your assailants do not stop, your insistence will distract the attacker.   off balancing your opponent, can make use of his momentum   What bar was this?   When it finally stopped   I couldn't account for the last 18 hours in my life   Hey, it's me.</template></category><category><pattern>LINDI  I LOVE YOU</pattern><template>Eddie...   Here.   It's gonna be okay.   You're gonna get outta here.   Eddie.  Are you okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M STARTING IMPORT EXPORT COMPANY</pattern><template>very exiting stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  GIVEN WHERE YOU'RE HEADING</pattern><template>Some of our ideas are a bit ambitious.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVEN'T DONE THE TIME IN THAT FIRST MARRIAGE  TO THE GIRL WITH THE RIGHT FATHER</pattern><template>You think you can leap over, all in a single bound.</template></category><category><pattern>MEDICATION</pattern><template>I'm on a special medication.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS A GREAT LEAP FORWARD</pattern><template>Right?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A DIFFICULT TIME   WE WOULD APPRECIATE YOU DIRECT  YOUR FURTHER QUESTIONS TO OUR ATTORNEY    AH  YES   WE HAVE NO FURTHER COMMENTS AT THIS TIME      WE'RE JUST AWAITING THE RESULTS   FROM THE LATEST ROUND OF TEST  AND HOPING THE BEST    THANK YOU   EDDIE</pattern><template>I know you're in there Eddie Eddie, come out.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD I HAVE KILLED SOMEONE    WAS IS IT EVEN ME    EDDIE  THIS IS MELISSA    LISTEN    VERNON HASN'T BEEN GIVING YOU ANYTHING HAS HE  BECAUSE THAT STUFF IS DANGEROUS</pattern><template>Melissa?</template></category><category><pattern>A CRAZY PRICK LIKE HIM GIVING AWAY POWER OF ATTORNEY</pattern><template>Well, better get better.</template></category><category><pattern>THURSDAY  I'M GONNA NEED THE PILLS HERE</pattern><template>Getting smarter...</template></category><category><pattern>INFORMATION FROM THE ODD MUSEUM SHOW</pattern><template>a half read article,  some PBS documentary...   was all bubbling up in my frontal lobes,   mixing itself together   into a sparkling cocktail of useful information.   She didn't have a chance.  What, what, what are your suggestions?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION  OUR BUSINESS WAS SETTLED</pattern><template>Well I want some more of that stuff, or I shoot you right here.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  HAS THERE BEEN MOVEMENT</pattern><template>Yeah! There's been movement alright.</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE  OPEN THE DOOR</pattern><template>Let's go! Open the door!</template></category><category><pattern>HOTEL ROOMS WERE NO LONGER AN OPTION    WHAT I NEEDED  WAS A BUNKER   THERE'S A BUILT IN SAFE</pattern><template>central surveillance, vault grade pneumatic doors.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>...and besides, I get the strong feeling...</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE WAS HE TWO YEARS AGO</pattern><template>Hm?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE CARELESS WITH THOSE POWERS</pattern><template>You flaunt them and you throw them around like a brat with his trust fund.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SURE</pattern><template>Because I got a little bit on the line here.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHIN'</pattern><template>I don't know what to do.</template></category><category><pattern>WRITE DOWN YOUR NUMBER</pattern><template>I'll need it to contact you later.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER YOU  SENATOR</pattern><template>Thanks for stopping by, Karl.</template></category><category><pattern>VERN</pattern><template>Oh God.</template></category><category><pattern>I ALREADY HAVE</pattern><template>As a matter of fact...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE SOME LEFT  GOOD</pattern><template>Well you go home and you take it.</template></category><category><pattern>I STILL CAN'T DEAL WITH THAT HAIRCUT</pattern><template>I don't even recognize you on the street.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT</pattern><template>I know I'm right.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MAYBE GRAB A LITTLE BREAKFAST FOR US</pattern><template>He knew, he had me.  Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>YEA  AND THEY EVENTUALLY GOT THEIR ASSES KICKED</pattern><template>I didn't go in. I wanted to walk, move, digest, ingest   There are moments in life   moments, when you know, you've crossed a bridge. Your old life is over.   Van Loon was my bridge.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>That's like Hefner moving out of the mansion.</template></category><category><pattern>DELUSIONS OF GRANDEUR I DON'T HAVE DELUSIONS OF GRANDEUR I HAVE AN ACTUAL RECIPE FOR GRANDEUR</pattern><template>I do not know who you are Eddie, or what your game is, But I'm sure of one thing, you don't work in my world.</template></category><category><pattern>WE IT'LL NEVER OFFICIALLY EXIST</pattern><template>Obviously, I don't need to point out the advantages for you..</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU SEE HIM</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  THE BOYS IN THE KITCHEN  ARE CALLING IT NZT 48</pattern><template>The  boys  and, the  kitchen ?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>Eddie!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVEN'T YOU ASKED THE QUESTION</pattern><template>Well, Given the scale of my contribution...</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING</pattern><template>You should sleep.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH UH  ANTIQUES  UM</pattern><template>Like uh...</template></category><category><pattern>DELIRIUM</pattern><template>Hm hm.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD SUCH A POOR VOCABULARY</pattern><template>But then I discovered this thing... Google.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST LISTEN TO ME  IT'LL COME ON IN 30 SECONDS  AND YOU'LL THINK YOUR WAY OUT  THAT'S WHAT IT DOES</pattern><template>He's getting closer.</template></category><category><pattern>12 YEARS AGO IN COLLEGE   SITTING ON THE COUCH WITH A T A</pattern><template>I was trying to make...</template></category><category><pattern>I MOVED IT</pattern><template>Okay... So where did you move it?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  KEEP GOING</pattern><template>I can to write you a check.</template></category><category><pattern>CLINICAL TRIALS  GUINEA PIG PEOPLE</pattern><template>that's gonna take too long.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU KNOW HOW THEY SAY THAT WE CAN ACCESS ONLY 20% OF OUR BRAIN</pattern><template>Well what this does, it lets you access all of it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL DIE  IF YOU JUST STOP</pattern><template>Try to taper off. Otherwise, the headaches are just beginning.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW THIS</pattern><template>The governmental bribes system is itself corrupt So of course, information about its inner workings, like anything, can be bought.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY KARL  I'VE HAD IT WITH THIS UNQUALIFIED POSTURING LITTLE PRICK</pattern><template>Look...</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE A LITTLE ADVICE MAYBE</pattern><template>I won't be bothering much at first.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AS SOON AS HE IS ABLE  WE WILL PROCEED</pattern><template>I realize this is a useless platitude, but if there's anything we can do...</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE A LUNCH</pattern><template>Look...The biggest contributor, give him his two crappy little minutes?</template></category><category><pattern>OBVIOUSLY  I DON'T NEED TO POINT OUT THE ADVANTAGES FOR YOU</pattern><template>Oh I think maybe you do.</template></category><category><pattern>I MISSED DEADLINES</pattern><template>Got lazy. Slow. So slow.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOOT IT</pattern><template>It goes straight into the blood and brain.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU SAY I AM NOT PRACTICAL</pattern><template>Can I walk you to work?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I DON'T WANNA TALK ABOUT HER</pattern><template>I want to talk about you. Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO NO  I'M GONNA  I'M GONNA GO GET IT</pattern><template>Give me your keys.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO KNOW EDDIE    I WROTE YOU OFF</pattern><template>I was sick.</template></category><category><pattern>AN OVERBOOKED FUND RAISER; THAT'S A FIRST</pattern><template>Well, here he comes. I'll ask him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'D EVER ARGUE WITH YOU</pattern><template>This was great.  So mom, I've been doing a little research on aunt Helen's tumor. And...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT YOU WOULD EVEN THINK THAT  WOULD ONLY SHOW ME HOW UNPREPARED YOU ARE  TO BE ON YOUR OWN</pattern><template>I mean, you do know, you're a freak?</template></category><category><pattern>OF ALL THE PEOPLE I CALLED      THREE WERE DEAD  AND THE REST WERE SICK    HELLO  HELLO</pattern><template>Go! GO!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURPRISED YOU DIDN'T HEAR</pattern><template>No. No. Well, I know they keep me hoppin' here.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I SUPPOSE  I CAN HELP YOU WITH THAT</pattern><template>Just this once.</template></category><category><pattern>WORTH THE RISK    WHAT WOULD YOU DO    VERN'S CASH  COMBINED WITH AN UNPRECEDENTED SURGE IN MOTIVATION   ENABLED ME TO FINISH THE BOOK IN 4 DAYS   A TABLET A DAY  AND WHAT I COULD DO WITH MY DAY  WAS LIMITLESS    IN LEARNED TO PLAY THE PIANO IN 3 DAYS    MATH BECAME USEFUL AND FUN     ALL IN</pattern><template>Even half listing to any language, I became fluent.  So that Shakespeare's text, it is polite mediocrity.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT NO  THESE COMPANIES WOULDN'T GET YOU THERE IN A MERGING MARKETS YOU WOULD HAVE</pattern><template>Oh whoa! Whoa, this must be some, big ass merger you're contemplating And there's really only one company with enough bling to justify a merger with Van Loon and associations.</template></category><category><pattern>PEEL YOUR SKIN UP OVER YOUR HEAD AND TIE A KNOT IN IT YOU DON'T DIE FROM THIS  YOU SUFFOCATE GOOD LUCK</pattern><template>My new friend, Kevin Doyle, showed me how you can leverage.   two and a half times your cash at day trading firm   I've been upping the dose for over a week.   It seemed to cut my learning curve.  Hey, Why you buying that?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT IF I DON'T LIKE YOUR IDEAS</pattern><template>Well then we'll say... God speed.  and your candle will have shed a brief but lovely light.</template></category><category><pattern>AND UHM</pattern><template>Excuse me for one sec I thought we straightened this out, detective.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOTTA GET BACK TO WORK</pattern><template>You didn't even tell me what happened.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME ABOUT THIS BOOK</pattern><template>How's it going?</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS  HE LOOKS FRAIL</pattern><template>Could be an act.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS LESS THAN USUALLY EQUIPPED TO ANSWER    THE DULLNESS WAS COMING ON   I WAS OVERDUE TO TAKE MY NZT</pattern><template>And the pain was starting behind my eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I'M A NEW MAN</pattern><template>I've already ordered.</template></category><category><pattern>FDA APPROVED  THAT'S A LAUGH</pattern><template>You didn't really believe that shit. Did ya?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GONNA KILL ME TOO</pattern><template>No no no no no. Let me look.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL ON IT  OR OFF IT  THERE'S NO SCENARIO WHERE YOU ARE NOT WORKING FOR ME</pattern><template>How you gonna pay me? In cigarettes?</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU WERE COMING OVER    IS EVERYTHING OKAY</pattern><template>Call me when you get this.   Even off NZT, I decided to give Van Loon's files a shot.   they were hieroglyphs.     Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN THE DOOR</pattern><template>And so, here I am.   I knew that they will kill me slowly and horribly.   But this choice would at least be mine   But we're instinctive creatures...   We wanna live.   so my foggy brain tried to remember   where one tablet of NZT might be   it was possible.   and possible was enough.  Hey, Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS ABLE TO CALCULATE CERTAIN PATTERNS IN THE ALGORITHMS</pattern><template>If you look at column 4, This was the first...</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOTTA BE  JUST ONE BIG HANDSOME BLUR TO THIS GUY</pattern><template>Who was out there?   the woman's husband?   the hotel maid?   Was this how, it was all going to end?  Not the dimmest clue.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT THE VISCERAL KIND OF SPIKE YOU WANT IN SHORT TIME HOLDING  SO</pattern><template>I dispensed with all the hard statics and I went right to the rumor mill So your bought your stocks based on what the tom toms beating in the street?</template></category><category><pattern>I CUT YOU AT WAIST</pattern><template>peel your skin up over your head and tie a knot in it You don't die from this, You suffocate Good luck.</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN'T HAVE A STREET NAME YET</pattern><template>But, the boys in the kitchen, are calling it NZT 48.</template></category><category><pattern>HANG OUT A LOT</pattern><template>No. He's my ex wife's brother.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THATS ME NOW</pattern><template>I am moving out of the energy business.</template></category><category><pattern>FLAY  THAT'S A NICE WORD  I DIDN'T KNOW THIS BEFORE</pattern><template>I had such a poor vocabulary.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD SLEEP</pattern><template>Isn't your Van Loon meeting tomorrow?</template></category><category><pattern>AND  THAT'S ON THE HOUSE</pattern><template>I don't want it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE NEEDS 60 FEET STOP; HE DOESN'T HAVE ROOM TO WORK WITH</pattern><template>I see everything, Karl.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  YOU GET YOUR SHOT</pattern><template>Meet me tomorrow at the Saint Regis at 10 and tell me how the gutsy little schmuck who needs a ride home, would restructure these deals.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT HISTORY    ALL THE COUNTRIES THAT EVER RULED THE WORLD</pattern><template>Portugal with his big massive navy.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU   YOUR CHANCES DON'T EXIST</pattern><template>We shut down your lab.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  DEFINITELY</pattern><template>Alright, we'll talk about it.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE THIS IS A DIFFERENT BATCH</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>HE GOT INTO THE CAB BEHIND ME  AND HE'S MAKING EVERY TURN I'M MAKING</pattern><template>Better call the cops.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU THINK I DIDN'T LEARN ANYTHING</pattern><template>that my synapses didn't change, that I kept absolutely nothing?</template></category><category><pattern>CALL ME WHEN YOU GET THIS    EVEN OFF NZT  I DECIDED TO GIVE VAN LOON'S FILES A SHOT    THEY WERE HIEROGLYPHS      HELLO</pattern><template>Kevin, it's Eddie.  Eddie?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN TO WRITE YOU A CHECK</pattern><template>Check.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS  WE GONNA FIND OUT UH</pattern><template>This is a waste of my time, you know.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW WE HAVE EVERY INTENTION OF SIGNING THE CONTRACT</pattern><template>And as soon as he is able, we will proceed.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE LOOKING AT A SECOND OVERFLOW OF BENT</pattern><template>There's a league of donations coming in, and I don't think they're even gonna try a second debate.</template></category><category><pattern>SO UH  WE SHOULD PROBABLY UM  MEET OR SOMETHING  RIGHT</pattern><template>No, I gotta do the funeral and God knows what else...   We can't meet, okay?  Right. I guess I'll just see you at the funeral then. uh?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT ME TO GO GET IT</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  A MAN IN YOUR EMPLOY  CAN'T TAKE A PISS  KARL</pattern><template>Was it Brant, or someone else?   The police station? The coat room?  Mr. Morra...</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WAS OUT THERE    THE WOMAN'S HUSBAND    THE HOTEL MAID    WAS THIS HOW  IT WAS ALL GOING TO END   NOT THE DIMMEST CLUE</pattern><template>He was dithering  He was the third from the right. No not him.   Here you go. A thing of beauty.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE ALREADY ORDERED</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE GONNA BE ALIVE THIS TIME NEXT YEAR</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>OH SHIT  LISTEN LISTEN LISTEN LISTEN</pattern><template>You forget about me eh?</template></category><category><pattern>AND  IF YOU DON'T WANT TO KEEP READING  I'LL GIVE YOU BACK THE ADVANCE</pattern><template>Okay, Eddie.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  I TOOK IT TOO</pattern><template>Vernon didn't tell you any of this, did he?</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID  LEAVE HER ALONE</pattern><template>Hey buddy, are you trying to piss me off?</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  YOU'RE RIGHT</pattern><template>Maybe at least you can go to the bank.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I AM GONNA STOP TAKING IT</pattern><template>There's just some things I have to do to keep us safe and to, to set us up And then, I'm gonna get off it... I mean, that's the plan.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL TAKE IT AND THEN YOU'LL KNOW   HE'S GOT A KNIFE  EDDIE  I CAN'T THINK MY WAY OUT OF A KNIFE</pattern><template>Just listen to me. It'll come on in 30 seconds, and you'll think your way out. That's what it does.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANNA GO TO WAR WITH ME</pattern><template>And trust me when I say this I am not even being creative.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU SURE</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THINK YOU CAN RUN OUT ON ME  UH</pattern><template>You think, I don't know where you are?</template></category><category><pattern>ATWOOD'S IN A COMA</pattern><template>He wasn't playing us, he's dying.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  LET'S GET A DRINK I WANNA HEAR ABOUT THIS BOOK</pattern><template>I don't know, it's two o'clock in the afternoon.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TRUE  I DID MARRY ONCE  RIGHT OUT OF COLLEGE   TO MELISSA    I DO</pattern><template>briefly.   This isn't working.  Well, even though everything you said is true, I still love you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M PROUD OF YOU</pattern><template>And...</template></category><category><pattern>COMES OUT OF NOWHERE  SO STRONG    HAS ME ON THE RUN  BEFORE I COULD EVEN GET TO ANYBODY IN HIS CAMP</pattern><template>beats me out of two properties, investment companies up north...</template></category><category><pattern>ACADEMICALLY CONSTIPATED BOOKS ABOUT A DEAD SUPREME COURT JUSTICE</pattern><template>You are a creep aren't you?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO THEN</pattern><template>Well it's not as I if have a black book with your name in it...</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  LISTEN  I JUST  AH</pattern><template>I have all this data to analyze.</template></category><category><pattern>HM HM</pattern><template>I sent over my revised projections.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S JUST SOME THINGS I HAVE TO DO TO KEEP US SAFE AND TO  TO SET US UP AND THEN  I'M GONNA GET OFF IT    I MEAN  THAT'S THE PLAN</pattern><template>Look! I have a plan. I swear I'm gonna get off it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND DON'T WEAR THE SAME COLOR SUIT</pattern><template>This isn't the Matrix!</template></category><category><pattern>THEN</pattern><template>Then I got sick.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH YIELDS A PROJECTED PROFIT OF 200%</pattern><template>That makes both of us very happy campers.</template></category><category><pattern>CERTAINLY  SIR</pattern><template>Safer though my stash now was,   I was not sitting around until I ran out.  Well, can I combine these ingredients in the same exact quantity? Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THE VICTIM'S SISTER</pattern><template>I hadn't heard her voice in ten years.     Eddie?</template></category><category><pattern>7B  YES</pattern><template>Okay, I'll hold.</template></category><category><pattern>SO    YOU TELL ME WHERE THE REST IS</pattern><template>I'm plum out..</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GONNA GET A FRONT ROW SEAT  BABY</pattern><template>not much of a triumph, was it?   because I would die here too.   only NZT could help me   and the last of it, was in this pug's bloodstream.  Victor!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IT WILL TAKE US LIN  YOU CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE THE THINGS WE'LL BE ABLE TO DO WHERE WE'LL BE A YEAR FROM NOW THE KIND OF LIFE THAT WE'LL FINALLY BE ABLE TO LIVE WELL  YOU MIGHT HAVE TO LIVE IT WITHOUT ME</pattern><template>Look! I am gonna stop taking it.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM MOVING OUT OF THE ENERGY BUSINESS</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>I COULDN'T KEEP THIS QUITE ON MY OWN   ENTER MORRIS BRANT  THE MOST LETHAL LAWYER IN NEW YORK   YOU'RE LUCKY  SOMEBODY WIPED THE ROOM</pattern><template>It's weak circumstantial at best.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS THE SIDEWALK</pattern><template>You see that guy?   That was me, Not so long ago.   What kind of guy, without a drug or alcohol problem looks this way?   Only a writer.   strangely enough, nobody believed that I actually had a book contract.  Well it's best rated as a sci fi novel...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE FULL OF SHIT EDDIE BABY</pattern><template>I'm sorry   Tyler, I gotta go.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY    I NEED YOU TO GO INTO THE BAG AND TAKE ONE OF THE PILLS</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>You're not excused.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE GO  HERE WE GO   MAN  IT'S GONNA BE GREAT    JUST GOTTA PUT IN THE TIME AND STAY IN THE ROOM    THAT'S THE KEY CONCEPT    DON'T LEAVE THE ROOM    A FEW WEEKS PASSED THIS WAY   MAYBE A FEW MONTHS    AT LEAST I STILL HAD LINDI   JUST LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Come on, Eddie...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS HAS BEEN THE LEARNING EXPERIENCE OF MY LIFE</pattern><template>I hope has. I hope you don't think you've gotten enough from me.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW I'LL OPEN UP A LINE OF CREDIT FOR YOU</pattern><template>You'll be wanting a few toys.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS TODAY    THE DOW HAS BEEN YO YO ING   AMID SPECULATION  THAT VAN LOON ASSOCIATES    AND HANK ATWOOD HAVE NEGOTIATED A MERGER     HAVE YOU BEEN TALKING TO ANYONE</pattern><template>NO. I haven't been talking to anybody, Karl.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'LL NEVER GIVE YOU THIS CHANCE AGAIN</pattern><template>I know. Listen. I just, ah...</template></category><category><pattern>PARTNER  SQUEEZE</pattern><template>Paramour. Inamorata Cleaning Lady. Bank.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT BE UNGRATEFUL</pattern><template>You know how much that costs?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE</pattern><template>I quintupled my money 4 days in a row.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  WHAT ABOUT ATWOOD</pattern><template>Look...You got a long way to go  as a liar kiddo...</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  YOU CAN'T HAVE THE FLU RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>He'll never give you this chance again.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE HE IS  NICE ARTICLE IN THE POST BUDDY</pattern><template>He is on his way.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHEN DOES THE BOOK COME OUT</pattern><template>Next year. How's your new assistant?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HE STARTED GETTING HEADACHES  THEN HE COLLAPSED AT WORK    NOW HE'S IN THE I C U    OKAY  WELL PLEASE GIVE HIM MY BEST</pattern><template>thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I QUINTUPLED MY MONEY 4 DAYS IN A ROW</pattern><template>So you got a fix on the game?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL THEN WE'LL SAY    GOD SPEED   AND YOUR CANDLE WILL HAVE SHED A BRIEF BUT LOVELY LIGHT</pattern><template>But you know what Eddie, let's not even go there right now.</template></category><category><pattern>EDDIE</pattern><template>Outside Lennox Hill Hospital today,   more twists and turns in the Van Loon   Atwood merger.   There is absolutely.   no truth to the rumor of this merger.   None whatsoever!   My husband is having tests...</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW HIM  PLEASE</pattern><template>Yo buddy! Let's leave her alone.</template></category><category><pattern>PARAMOUR  INAMORATA CLEANING LADY  BANK</pattern><template>Well be there that..</template></category><category><pattern>A FORTRESS  WITH A HELL OF A VIEW</pattern><template>What is the asking price?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN IT BE A NEW KEY</pattern><template>to our place?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL YOU'RE AN AMAZING CON ARTIST  OR YOU'RE A VERY SMART YOUNG MAN</pattern><template>I mean, come on! The two of you together...</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I HAVE A PLAN  I SWEAR I'M GONNA GET OFF IT</pattern><template>Okay I hope you do Looking for me?</template></category><category><pattern>PARDON ME ONE SECOND</pattern><template>Was it possible?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT IT</pattern><template>You did?</template></category><category><pattern>I MADE SOME NEW FRIENDS WHO INVITED ME TO THE BEACH    THE BEACH  WAS NOT NEARBY    ALL MY FEAR  ALL MY SHYNESS  GONE    BUT MERE LOUNGING WASN'T ENOUGH    ONLY PROBLEM  IF I WASN'T MOVING FORWARD   I FELT LIKE I WAS GOING TO EXPLODE    ANYBODY EVER JUMPED</pattern><template>Are you crazy?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TAKE THE DOSE DOWN  BUT YOU DON'T JUST STOP</pattern><template>You'll die, if you just stop!</template></category><category><pattern>A HALF READ ARTICLE   SOME PBS DOCUMENTARY      WAS ALL BUBBLING UP IN MY FRONTAL LOBES    MIXING ITSELF TOGETHER   INTO A SPARKLING COCKTAIL OF USEFUL INFORMATION    SHE DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE   WHAT  WHAT  WHAT ARE YOUR SUGGESTIONS</pattern><template>We'd really worked on her paper too.   In 45 minutes, it was a polished gem.   She was pleased.   Home...   but it couldn't be my home, could it!?   and who would live like this?   My first thought... Torch it!.   But, saner heads prevailed.   What was this drug?</template></category><category><pattern>WAS IT POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Could I have killed someone?   Was is it even me?   Eddie? This is Melissa..  Listen... Vernon hasn't been giving you anything has he? Because that stuff is dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE MAKES MONEY THAT FAST  THIS ARTICLE'S GONNA GET WRITTEN   WITH OR WITHOUT YOU    AND FINALLY  KEVIN DOYLE  TRYING TO SOUND CASUAL    EDDIE  I WAS TALKING YOU UP TO MY BOSS AND WELL  THE IMPOSSIBLE HAPPENED BUD   BUT WE GOT YOU A MEETING WITH KARL VAN LOON</pattern><template>Karl van Loon wants to meet you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T REALLY BELIEVE THAT SHIT  DID YA</pattern><template>Okay, so what do we have here?   some unknown, untested, possibly dangerous drug   scammed out of some unidentified lab somewhere.   given to me by a highly unreliable guy I hadn't seen in years    So you want some more?</template></category><category><pattern>WE LOSE YOU  IF THERE'S A SCREEN IN THE ROOM</pattern><template>These are tectonic plates that are shifting right under us.</template></category><category><pattern>AORTA'S NOT STANDING UP</pattern><template>Soon you need to get that replaced.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT MAKES YOU THINK I DON'T KNOW THE GUY WITH A BEAT ON YOU RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>How do you know you're gonna be alive this time next year?</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO  HERE I AM    I KNEW THAT THEY WILL KILL ME SLOWLY AND HORRIBLY    BUT THIS CHOICE WOULD AT LEAST BE MINE   BUT WE'RE INSTINCTIVE CREATURES      WE WANNA LIVE    SO MY FOGGY BRAIN TRIED TO REMEMBER   WHERE ONE TABLET OF NZT MIGHT BE   IT WAS POSSIBLE    AND POSSIBLE WAS ENOUGH   HEY  EDDIE</pattern><template>You know, I want more, so why would you upset me?</template></category><category><pattern>SO THEN I WENT TO DOOR NUMBER 3 YOU'RE REALLY IMPLYING THAT YOU'VE  SOME SORT OF ULTIMATE FORMULA</pattern><template>Well, from 12,000 to 2.3 million in ten days.</template></category><category><pattern>MELISSA    YOU WERE THERE   UM  JUST  JUST BEFORE  I HAD RUN INTO HIM ON THE STREET  AND UH  YEAH  OH GOD   I WISH I WAS MORE SURPRISED  HE WAS INVOLVED IN SOME STUFF    I BETTER NOT TO SAY ANYMORE   NO  NO  THAT'S PROBABLY A GOOD IDEA</pattern><template>So uh, we should probably um, meet or something, right...</template></category><category><pattern>IS HANK ATWOOD REALLY GONNA GO FOR IT</pattern><template>Well you're an amazing con artist, or you're a very smart young man...</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO NO 12:00 AND YOU'RE NOT HERE</pattern><template>I'm here now.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOD</pattern><template>You coming over later?</template></category><category><pattern>GOD</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>DART TO THE DART BOARD</pattern><template>Meaning?</template></category><category><pattern>HIS BOSS WAS DEAD    SO  I DIDN'T MATTER NOW    BUT HE DID NOT APPRECIATE THAT MORRIS BRANT HAD KEPT THE PILLS FOR HIMSELF    AND IT WAS ALL STILL POSSIBLE  AFTER 12 MONTHS ACTUALLY  NOW THERE'S NO MORE TICKETS</pattern><template>Yeah, I got it.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WE'RE WIRED TO OVERREACH</pattern><template>look at history... All the countries that ever ruled the world...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HERE HE COMES  I'LL ASK HIM</pattern><template>Ah! That's much better.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT A GOOD TIME  EDDIE</pattern><template>Hey Vern, I really just need to talk to you.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO</pattern><template>Okay... I need you to go into the bag and take one of the pills.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IT'S GONNA PAY OFF SENATOR MORRA</pattern><template>The Senate, well who knows?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVEN'T HAD TO CLIMB UP ALL THE GREASY LITTLE RUNGS</pattern><template>You haven't been board lined at the fundraisers...</template></category><category><pattern>AS A MATTER OF FACT</pattern><template>I fired a few people, over your projections.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVEN'T BEEN BOARD LINED AT THE FUNDRAISERS</pattern><template>you haven't done the time in that first marriage, to the girl with the right father...</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THIS IS  PREPARED   EDDIE</pattern><template>What is this, Atwood 101? I mean...</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  BUT I THINK IF YOU TAKE A LOOK AT THEM</pattern><template>I already have.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT IT</pattern><template>Do not be ungrateful.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>How's your day going?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  WELL  I KNOW THEY KEEP ME HOPPIN' HERE</pattern><template>Well, it's gonna pay off Senator Morra.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  YOU DON'T WANT HEAR THIS FROM SOME SCHMUCK WHO NEEDS A RIDE HOME</pattern><template>Alright. You get your shot.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEY WEREN'T ME</pattern><template>Yes. You know the way it works...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK YOU CAN LEAP OVER  ALL IN A SINGLE BOUND</pattern><template>You haven't had to bribe or charm or threaten your way, to sit at this table.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I GOT IT</pattern><template>An overbooked fund raiser; that's a first!</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY    I AM SURE YOU'RE CURIOUS TOO</pattern><template>But don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WE SHOULD PROBAB</pattern><template>Don't propose.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  OF COURSE I BELIEVE YOU</pattern><template>You deserve it.</template></category><category><pattern>CAUSE ME WORKING FOR YOU  YOU'D END UP AS MY BITCH</pattern><template>Maybe we should cool off and talk again I don't think so.</template></category><category><pattern>I RELY ON YOUR DISCRETION</pattern><template>There wont be a proxy.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT  I'M NOT  I THOUGHT BETTER OF IT</pattern><template>See once you know what's in it, you can tweak, re engineer...</template></category><category><pattern>TWO YEARS AGO  HE WASN'T EVEN ON FORBES RADAR</pattern><template>That was a great leap forward.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T COME IN TODAY</pattern><template>I'm sick.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU KNOW THAT I WANT TO SHARE THE REST OF MY LIFE WITH YOU</pattern><template>In fact, I was thinking...</template></category><category><pattern>I DISPENSED WITH ALL THE HARD STATICS AND I WENT RIGHT TO THE RUMOR MILL SO YOUR BOUGHT YOUR STOCKS BASED ON WHAT THE TOM TOMS BEATING IN THE STREET</pattern><template>Sure. The share prices aren't really based on how a company works it's about how mass psychology works So, if I found certain algorithms in the perception of the stock...</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  ENOUGH  OKAY</pattern><template>Steve handles the rent, so you can feed your crap to him!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>You don't even know what it is.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I GOT A LITTLE BIT ON THE LINE HERE</pattern><template>Have a toast plate.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'D REALLY WORKED ON HER PAPER TOO    IN 45 MINUTES  IT WAS A POLISHED GEM    SHE WAS PLEASED    HOME      BUT IT COULDN'T BE MY HOME  COULD IT     AND WHO WOULD LIVE LIKE THIS    MY FIRST THOUGHT    TORCH IT     BUT  SANER HEADS PREVAILED    WHAT WAS THIS DRUG</pattern><template>I couldn't stay messy on it   I hadn't had a cigarette in 6 hours; hadn't eaten...   So, I'm steamiest and tidy.</template></category><category><pattern>CENTRAL SURVEILLANCE  VAULT GRADE PNEUMATIC DOORS</pattern><template>It's an unparalleled three tier security system.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  STOP TALKING  DON'T MOVE</pattern><template>He killed two guys.</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN'T SOUND VERY  FDA APPROVED VERN</pattern><template>FDA approved. That's a laugh.</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK</pattern><template>Check Are you out of your mind?</template></category><category><pattern>VERNON  LOOK AT ME</pattern><template>Do I look good to you?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  AT WHAT POINT WAS THE PONY EXPRESS  SUPPOSED TO RIDE IN WITH HIS LIFE SAVING MEDICATION</pattern><template>his boss was dead.   So, I didn't matter now.   But he did not appreciate that Morris Brant had kept the pills for himself.   and it was all still possible  after 12 months Actually, now there's no more tickets.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GETTING OUT OF THIS SIDE OF THE BUSINESS</pattern><template>I'm branching out...</template></category><category><pattern>I WANTED TO MAKE THIS AS CONFIDENTIAL AS POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Of course.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL BE THERE THAT</pattern><template>Well what's mine is yours too.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  NO  NO HE'S NOT</pattern><template>uh, uh, Paul passed away   uh, three days ago  Oh my God! I'm so sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT YOU WOULDN'T EVEN THINK THAT SHOWS ME HOW UNPREPARED YOUR ARE TO FIGHT ME</pattern><template>You're not longer equipped to fight me.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS JUST CAME FOR YOU</pattern><template>Alright, I'm gonna ask you again Eddie...</template></category><category><pattern>I COULDN'T MAKE IT HOME</pattern><template>I'll take you to a hospital.</template></category><category><pattern>LASTS MUCH LONGER</pattern><template>So... You tell me where the rest is?</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR DEDUCTIVE POWERS ARE A GIFT FROM GOD  OR CHANCE  OR STRAIGHT SHOT OF SPERM</pattern><template>or whatever, or whoever the hell, wrote your life script.</template></category><category><pattern>OF ALL THE USELESS RELATIONSHIPS BETTER FORGOTTEN AND PUT AWAY IN MOTHBALLS   IS THERE ANY MORE USELESS THAN  THE EX BROTHER IN LAW   HOLY SHIT  MAN</pattern><template>How's it been, like Nine years?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE IT WORKED OUT SO WELL FOR YOU LAST TIME</pattern><template>it's true, I did marry once, right out of college   to melissa..  I do!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAD THAT MADE</pattern><template>I did.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T GET SICK YOU'RE PLAYING AT THIS LEVEL  YOU GET HIT BY A CAR  YOU DON'T EVEN DIE</pattern><template>You're absolutely right.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  THE STOCKS ROSE  BUT WHO WANTS TO DO ALL THAT WORK  FOR A SHITTY LITTLE UPTAKE</pattern><template>It's not the visceral kind of spike you want in short time holding. So...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE RELIEVED  THAT YOU KNOW THINGS  MY TEAM MISSED</pattern><template>The minute, the instant, that's no longer true...</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING TENTATIVE  AND YOU'VE LOST HIM FOREVER</pattern><template>I think we should rehearse a few scenarios.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I JUST WANTED TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU</pattern><template>And that you know, that apparently, my capacity for self sabotage wasn't boundless after all.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'VE HAD CLINICAL TRIES  AND IT'S F D A  APPROVED</pattern><template>Alright, just out of curiosity and that's all...</template></category><category><pattern>AND MY BOSS STARTED TO HATE ME THEY OFFERED ME HIS JOB</pattern><template>And then, then I got, I got scared.</template></category><category><pattern>OR WHATEVER  OR WHOEVER THE HELL  WROTE YOUR LIFE SCRIPT</pattern><template>A gift. not earned.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S REALLY    IT  IT'S REALLY  IT'S RE  UH</pattern><template>Today was the day, I was gonna kick its ass   Here we go. Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  GIVEN THE SCALE OF MY CONTRIBUTION</pattern><template>let's say 45 Humph! $45,000?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ANOTHER NICE WORD</pattern><template>Anyway... I am sure you're curious too.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD NO IDEA  I DON'T BELIEVE IT</pattern><template>I gotta see this for myself. I'm dubious.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I'M HERE  WHAT HAPPENED     I'M STUCK  HE'LL FIND ME</pattern><template>Okay, stop talking. Don't move...</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S LIVE OFF THE INTEREST</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>A PREDICTION</pattern><template>It won't come off.   Why's that?</template></category><category><pattern>I DO HAVE A FORMULA  MR  PIERCE</pattern><template>delusions of grandeur I don't have delusions of grandeur I have an actual recipe for grandeur.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I PLEASE SPEAK WITH JERRY BRADEN</pattern><template>Jerry's in the hospital..     He's what?</template></category><category><pattern>I'D BE VERY INTERESTED WORKING WITH YOU</pattern><template>Okay, Kevin.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL YOU GO HOME AND YOU TAKE IT</pattern><template>You take the dose down, But you don't just stop.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT YOU KNOW  THAT APPARENTLY  MY CAPACITY FOR SELF SABOTAGE WASN'T BOUNDLESS AFTER ALL</pattern><template>The real question is...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>I'd seen it before.</template></category><category><pattern>TRUST ME  YOU DO NOT WANT TO KNOW</pattern><template>So, uh, what, what's it called?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT  I'M FINE</pattern><template>So, Eddie, you are interested after all.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S REALLY SIMPLE BABY  I NEED MY PILLS</pattern><template>Eddie, what pills?   Baby, it's complicated.   What are you taking?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVEN'T BEEN THE SAME SINCE</pattern><template>You have some left? Good.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MUCH YOU HAVE BEEN TAKING EDDIE</pattern><template>I've been taking a lot.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOLD ME SOMEBODY FROM IVAN WAS COMING ACROSS</pattern><template>Yes, thats me now.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  UH  PAUL PASSED AWAY   UH  THREE DAYS AGO  OH MY GOD  I'M SO SORRY</pattern><template>Yeah, he started getting headaches, then he collapsed at work.   Now he's in the I.C.U..  Okay, well please give him my best.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MINUTE  THE INSTANT  THAT'S NO LONGER TRUE</pattern><template>Two months after I'd started NZT...   I was brokering the biggest merger in corporate history.  Ironically, it's gonna be crude. Crude is gonna be where we're gonna hit em.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALIZED  THAT THERE WERE OTHER PEOPLE  WHO I MIGHT NOW ABOUT NZT    VERN'S OTHER CLIENTS   YEAH  HI</pattern><template>May I please speak with Jerry Braden?</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  LISTENING TO HER RAG   IF I WERE TRIPPING  I'D JUMP OUT A WINDOW   HELLO   ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME</pattern><template>Do you get it?</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  I'M GONNA ASK YOU AGAIN EDDIE</pattern><template>What do you know about this?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TOTALLY CLEAR  THAT ANYBODY WITH FAMILIAL ADOMIS PHALACROSIS</pattern><template>should be supplementing Platinum doublet regiments...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DO NOT KNOW WHAT I KNOW  BECAUSE YOU HAVE NOT EARNED THOSE POWERS</pattern><template>You're careless with those powers.</template></category><category><pattern>IT GOES STRAIGHT INTO THE BLOOD AND BRAIN</pattern><template>lasts much longer.</template></category><category><pattern>HASTINGS HAS IT'S OWN HISTORY</pattern><template>I'd start there.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KNIFE  APPEARS IN YOUR BACK</pattern><template>Well, I'll tell you one thing...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT LONGER EQUIPPED TO FIGHT ME</pattern><template>Do you think I didn't learn anything...</template></category><category><pattern>IN ALL OF THEM</pattern><template>Certainly, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>UNLESS YOU'RE PLAYING BOTH SIDES OF THE FENCE</pattern><template>control the whole power enchilada...</template></category></AIML>