<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>A FEW LAPS AGO  JAMES HUNT WAS LOOKING LIKE CHAMPION ELECT    NOW IT LOOKS AS THOUGH IT'S ALL GONE WRONG FOR HIM     JAMES</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>I BROUGHT YOU ALONG TODAY BECAUSE YOU SEEM LIKE A LONELY KIND OF GUY</pattern><template>I thought if I introduced you to some nice people, that could rub off on you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND 'TOY ' GOD  IT'S SO FLIMSY</pattern><template>For something that costs so much.</template></category><category><pattern>HUNT NURSING HIS CAR BACK TO THE PIT STOP    THAT BACK MARKER'S GOING PAST HUNT   LAP 70 4 LAPS TO GO  LOOK AT THAT LEFT FRONT TYRE  RIGHT FRONT TYRE  SORRY    NO TREAD ON IT AT ALL  AND THE OTHER ONE IS FLAT   LET'S GO  LET'S GO</pattern><template>Okay? When did you break your gear lever?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A GOOD DRIVER  BUT AN IMMORTAL FUCK APPARENTLY</pattern><template>I don't know about you, but that's not an act I'd like to follow.</template></category><category><pattern>TRIED WHAT</pattern><template>Everything We replaced the entire exhaust system.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DIDN'T</pattern><template>And who knows, if it had been just the drinking, or the dope, or the infidelity or the moods, it might even have worked.</template></category><category><pattern>SUPERB NEWS</pattern><template>Well done, James.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE</pattern><template>I had a skin graft operation where they put half my right thigh in my face.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS FORMULA 3</pattern><template>What's that?</template></category><category><pattern>BOUGHT HIS WAY IN RATHER THAN MESS ABOUT IN THE LOWER DIVISIONS</pattern><template>I thought  Bloody hell, he's right.  No sponsorship, Superstar.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY  I WILL BE ONE DAY</pattern><template>Morning, everyone.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  I NEED IT MORE THAN YOU DO</pattern><template>I mean, I have a hot head, an inability to tolerate discipline...</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES  IS THERE ANYTHING YOU'D LIKE TO ADD</pattern><template>If Niki is being tricky and getting a kicky out of playing mind games, then fine, I'm flattered.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THERE I WAS THINKING YOU WERE ABOUT TO WAX LYRICAL   ABOUT THE ROMANCE OF FLIGHT</pattern><template>No, that's all bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A WANKER</pattern><template>Fuck you!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FINE  JUST GOT A LITTLE PROBLEM WITH AN AUSTRIAN RAT AND HIS TEAM OF ITALIAN CHEATS WHO'VE DESTROYED MY CAR</pattern><template>What are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THE WINNER OF THE GUILD OF MOTORING WRITERS AWARD</pattern><template>Driver of the Year...</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS  GET ME IN THERE  PETE</pattern><template>Say anything, just get me in that room.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HE CAN BE A LOOSE CANON</pattern><template>And, yeah, he will drive you all mad, but in terms of raw talent and right stuff, there is no better driver in the world.</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES  YOUR 50 POINTS BEHIND LAUDA IN THE CHAMPIONSHIP</pattern><template>You've had another retirement today.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW IS IT AT THE BACK</pattern><template>Not planning on being there for long.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE HAD TO RESORT TO CHEATING</pattern><template>You're driving an illegal car and call me a cheater? Pathetic.</template></category><category><pattern>TELEVISION RIGHTS HAVE BEEN SOLD ALL AROUND THE WORLD</pattern><template>The showdown between you and Niki is all anyone wants to see.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I DON'T HAVE TO HIJACK IT  EITHER</pattern><template>As long as I pay for it.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S OUTRAGEOUS</pattern><template>Was he quicker in my car?</template></category><category><pattern>THE SPONSORS LIKE HIM</pattern><template>What do you want, a driver or a brush salesman?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>I'm stopping  His mechanics are asking what the problem is.   But wait! Niki Lauda's getting out of the car!   This is sensational!   The reigning World Champion, Niki Lauda,   is out of this race.  It's too dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S INFORMATION I'LL SHARE WITH YOU UNDER CERTAIN CONDITIONS ONLY</pattern><template>Go on.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THE ENGINE BLOCK</pattern><template>Any mounting or fixing plates, strip it out also.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER IT  MY LITTLE JERRY FRIEND</pattern><template>Jawohl! Remember ze name.</template></category><category><pattern>MARLENE</pattern><template>With a car like that, the rest of us never stood a chance, did we?</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT THE RACE IN SPAIN I WON</pattern><template>Yeah, in a car which is not legal.</template></category><category><pattern>COPER FUCKING SUCAR</pattern><template>And we need a replacement.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S PETER  SOMETHING'S UP AT MCLAREN</pattern><template>What have you heard?</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE HE DIDN'T LISTEN TO ME    FOR JAMES  ONE WORLD TITLE WAS ENOUGH    HE HAD PROVED WHAT HE NEEDED TO PROVE    TO HIMSELF AND ANYONE WHO DOUBTED HIM    AND TWO YEARS LATER HE RETIRED    WHEN I SAW HIM NEXT IN LONDON SEVEN YEARS LATER    ME AS CHAMPION AGAIN    HIM AS BROADCASTER    HE WAS BAREFOOT ON A BICYCLE  WITH A FLAT TYRE    STILL LIVING EACH DAY LIKE HIS LAST    WHEN I HEARD HE'D DIED AGED 45  OF A HEART ATTACK    I WASN'T SURPRISED    I WAS JUST SAD    PEOPLE ALWAYS THINK OF US AS RIVALS    BUT HE WAS AMONG THE VERY FEW I LIKED   AND EVEN FEWER THAT I RESPECTED    HE REMAINS THE ONLY PERSON I ENVIED   BORN3O</pattern><template>SUBTITLED BY GUSSI, S.A. DE C.V.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS THE DESCRIPTION</pattern><template>Mostly positive in terms of appearance.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SOUNDS FUCKING AWFUL</pattern><template>But sine they're right about most things, they're probably right about that too.</template></category><category><pattern>AT CRYSTAL PALACE TODAY  JAMES HUNT'S ON POLE  WITH AUSTRIAN NEWCOMER NIKI LAUDA ALONGSIDE HIM AND DAVE WALKER COMPLETING ROW 1</pattern><template>Row 2 is Mike Beuttler and Dave Morgan, with Tony Trimmer and Gerry Birrell.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU CAN  I CAN</pattern><template>You know, are you ever not an asshole?</template></category><category><pattern>THE RACE IS GOING AHEAD</pattern><template>Television rights have been sold all around the world.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>Are you leaving?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU ASK</pattern><template>I'll put on a tie, I'll smile for sponsors, say the right things.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WHEN DID YOU BREAK YOUR GEAR LEVER</pattern><template>Nine or ten laps ago.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  HE WAS</pattern><template>He went back to the house to take a call.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT TEAMMATES ARE FOR</pattern><template>Where the hell are we going?</template></category><category><pattern>IN MY HOMETOWN  VIENNA    MY FAMILY'S FAMOUS FOR ONE THING:   BUSINESS    MY GRANDFATHER WAS A BUSINESSMAN    MY FATHER  TOO    SO WHEN THEY HEARD I WANTED TO RACE CARS FOR A LIVING    THEY ARE A FEW THINGS TO SAY   GOOD</pattern><template>So if my family wasn't going to help me,   I decided to risk everything and take out a Loan myself.   I found a Formula 1 team with an Ok car   and an owner who had run out of money   and was willing to accept my terms.  And so, ladies and gentlemen, I'm delighted to say...</template></category><category><pattern>AND THESE ARE YOUR MECHANICS</pattern><template>They're reporting exclusively to you, as per contract.</template></category><category><pattern>HUNT  JAMES HUNT</pattern><template>You see, you share information and I share information.</template></category><category><pattern>ELECTRIC TENSION HERE AT FUJI    80 000 BEDRAGGLED RACE FANS   AND THE RACING GRUDGE MATCH OF THE DECADE    AND THERE'S MARIO ANDRETTI IN POLE POSITION    JAMES HUNT ALONGSIDE HIM    ON ROW TWO OF THE GRID    THERE IS NIKI LAUDA    AND ON ROW THREE OF THE GRID  JOE SCHECKETER FROM SOUTH AFRICA   IN THE SIX WHEEL TYRRELL    BEHIND HIM  THE REST OF THE 25 CAR FIELD    THERE'S THE FLAG AND FINALLY THE JAPANESE GRAND PRIX   IS UNDERWAY    IN THIS CONDITIONS IT MUST BE ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE   TO DRIVE A 450 HORSEPOWER CAR    AND IT'S ANDRETTI WHO HAS THE LEAD    BUT HUNT IS ATTACKING    HUNT'S GOING ROUND THE OUTSIDE OF ANDRETTI    NIKI LAUDA FOLLOWING HIM THROUGH    HUNT LEADS INTO THE FIRST RIGHT HANDER    HUNT COMES THROUGH TO COMPLETE HIS FIRST LAP LEADING THE FIELD    AT LEAST HE HAS CLEAR VISION IN FRONT OF HIM    NIKI LAUDA BEHIND HIM  EATING HIS SPRAY    LAUDA IS SLOWING    NIKI LAUDA IS BRINGING THE FERRARI NO</pattern><template>1 into the pit!   Some sort of problem, we can't imagine what,   so early in the race.  What's wrong with the car?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I'M ASKING YOU TO</pattern><template>This is an incredible battle between Niki Lauda   in the red Ferrari and James Hunt   in the white Hesketh.   ...the challenge of Niki Lauda...   Lauda attacking Hunt. He gets through on the inside.   Goes wide at the exit.   Hunt is past again.   Once more, Lauda tries to sneak up the inside.   They're absolutely side by side, wheel to wheel.   So evenly matched.   Fantastic battle between these two great drivers.   Hunt is now ahead once more.   But Lauda's coming back again now.   Lauda once more sneaks up the inside.   And again he runs wide.</template></category><category><pattern>30 SECONDS TO GO</pattern><template>Electric tension here at Fuji.   80,000 bedraggled race fans   and the racing grudge match of the decade.   And there's Mario Andretti in pole position,   James Hunt alongside him.   On row two of the grid,   there is Niki Lauda,   and on row three of the grid, Joe Schecketer from South Africa   in the six wheel Tyrrell.   Behind him, the rest of the 25 car field.   There's the flag and finally the Japanese Grand Prix   is underway!   In this conditions it must be almost impossible   to drive a 450 horsepower car!   And it's Andretti who has the lead,   but Hunt is attacking.   Hunt's going round the outside of Andretti!   Niki Lauda following him through!   Hunt leads into the first right hander!   Hunt comes through to complete his first lap leading the field.   At least he has clear vision in front of him.   Niki Lauda behind him, eating his spray.   Lauda is slowing!   Niki Lauda is bringing the Ferrari no.</template></category><category><pattern>ALEXANDER DOESN'T KNOW WHAT HE'S TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>I was. I'm not anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD EMERSON'S OFF</pattern><template>He's dumped them in it.</template></category><category><pattern>DID HE BUY HIS WAY IN THERE TOO</pattern><template>Well, the old man took Regazzoni back and he insisted on it apparently.</template></category><category><pattern>BEING DRIVEN ROUND 170 MPH</pattern><template>To all intents and purposes, this thing's a bomb on wheels.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY SO HEAVY</pattern><template>It's a V12 engine.</template></category><category><pattern>THE NEW ME IS VERY PROFESSIONAL</pattern><template>Early to bed, early to rise.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL SEE IN SPAIN</pattern><template>SPAIN HUNT WINS LAUDA 2ND James Hunt finally takes his first victory of the season here in Spain, after a brilliant drive.</template></category><category><pattern>FANTASTIC</pattern><template>Well done.</template></category><category><pattern>20% RISK</pattern><template>No, Niki, don't bring the percentages into this.</template></category><category><pattern>TO ME  THAT'S LOSING</pattern><template>Yes, I was. I admit it.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT EVEN HIS OWN TEAMMATES</pattern><template>Right. Because I'm a serious guy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY AM I AN ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Well...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW IS THAT WINNING</pattern><template>James!</template></category><category><pattern>HE WENT BACK TO THE HOUSE TO TAKE A CALL</pattern><template>He'll be back shortly.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT DID YOUR WIFE SAY WHEN SHE SAW YOUR FACE</pattern><template>She said,  Sweetie , you don't need a face to drive.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GOING TO NEED A COUPLE OF STITCHES</pattern><template>It's a nasty cut.</template></category><category><pattern>YEP  THAT'S HER</pattern><template>Lotus 59.</template></category><category><pattern>MORNING  EVERYONE</pattern><template>This is Nursie.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A LOWER DIVISION  WHERE IDIOTS LIKE ME MESS ABOUT IN THE HOP OF BEING TALENT SPOTTED TO RACE IN F1</pattern><template>You look disappointed.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE NO LENGTHS TO WHICH I WILL NOT GO</pattern><template>And I mean it.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  PLEASE</pattern><template>Why are we here, Niki? Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>GRANDE PREMIO DO BRAZIL INTERLAGOS JANUARY 1976  WELCOME TO SÄO PAULO  BRAZIL  AND THE INTERLAGOS CIRCUIT   FOR THE FIRST RACE IN THE 1976 FORMULA 1 SEASON    WHERE THE MAIN NEWS IS JAMES HUNT QUALIFIED FASTEST    BEATING NIKI LAUDA'S FERRARI TO POLE POSITION   BY JUST 200TH OF A SECOND   NEW CAR</pattern><template>I noticed.</template></category><category><pattern>APPARENTLY  TOOK OUT A LOAN AND BOUGHT HIS WAY IN WITH TWO MILLION AUSTRIAN SHILLINGS</pattern><template>Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>FINE</pattern><template>Niki, can you confirm to us exactly which procedures you had and the expectations for you recovery?</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES HUNT IS NOW OFFICIALLY CONFIRMED   AS FINISHING THIRD HERE IN JAPAN    AND THAT MEANS HE IS CHAMPION OF THE WORLD    OUR NEW WORLD CHAMPION  JAMES HUNT    BY JUST ONE SINGLE POINT    DID WE REALLY WIN   WORLD BLOODY CHAMPION</pattern><template>What are you going to do now?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT IN A HURRY</pattern><template>I'm not being paid.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE ALWAYS AT HOME  ON YOUR OWN  LOOKING AFTER YOURSELF  BEING A GOOD LITTLE BOY</pattern><template>Take a drink on me, James.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WANNA BE SUCCESSFUL</pattern><template>Yes, so do I.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE SAID   SWEETIE   YOU DON'T NEED A FACE TO DRIVE</pattern><template>You just need the right foot.  I'm being serious.</template></category><category><pattern>NO CHANCE</pattern><template>We've been working on it all night.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS HELL</pattern><template>And while doing it, I was watching television.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  BUBBLES  WHATEVER IT TAKES TO BEAT THAT PRICK NEXT YEAR  JUST SAY IT  YOU'RE WORD IS MY COMMAND</pattern><template>There are no lengths to which I will not go.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NIKI  DON'T BRING THE PERCENTAGES INTO THIS</pattern><template>Don't be a pro.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AMAZING  ALL THESE FACILITIES AND YOU MAKE A PIECE OF CRAP LIKE THIS</pattern><template>Ferrari family,   our good friend Clay Regazzoni.  You are family and friend to the commendatore as long as you win.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHEN DID ALL THIS START</pattern><template>That weekend I went skiing.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  IT DOESN'T LOOK TOO GOOD  BUT ONE UNEXPECTED ADVANTAGE IS IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO PERSPIRE THROUGH A SKIN GRAFT  SO SWEAT WILL NEVER RUN INTO MY EYES AGAIN  WHICH IS GOOD FOR A DRIVER</pattern><template>When they heard about your condition, Ferrari immediately hired a replacement driver, Carlos Reutemann.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL THEM THE TRUTH</pattern><template>Now, what is happening?   They're talking to the team manager.   Lauda explaining something.   With Lauda out, James Hunt knows he has to finish   this race in third place or higher to be World Champion.   But the job's not done yet for James Hunt.   In these dreadful conditions,   he still has to go the distance.   Fifteen laps to go here at Fuji.   James Hunt or Niki Lauda?   This extraordinary season is not over yet.   In this treacherous final round, can James Hunt hang on?   And the scoreboard tells a story.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NIKI LAUDA  FORMULA 1 DRIVER  AND HE JUST SIGNED WITH FERRARI</pattern><template>Him?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN TOLD TO AVOID YOU</pattern><template>By whom?</template></category><category><pattern>I WON  OKAY</pattern><template>On the all important day when it came down to it, we raced on equal terms, equally good cars.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT YET  BUT I WILL</pattern><template>If you can, I can.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT MEANS BEATING NIKI LAUDA  NOT BEING A SHOW PONY FOR SPONSORS</pattern><template>I heard about this thing with Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WE DO  IT'S PASSION  LOVE</pattern><template>Which is why we are prepared to risk our lives for it.</template></category><category><pattern>HUNT'S STILL IN THE LEAD    BUT NIKI LAUDA IS RIGHT ON HIS TAIL    HUNT AND LAUDA ARE PROVING TO BE IN A CLASS OF THEIR OWN    THEY'RE LEAVING THE PACK FAR BEHIND   HERR RED DEVIL'S ON HIS TAIL</pattern><template>Lauda takes a look down the inside...   ...and he's sold him a dummy!   Lauda is through!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE IN THE CLOSING LAPS OF THIS RACE AT WATKINS GLEN    THEY COME DOWN THE HILL    AND HUNT'S GOT A PROBLEM    HUNT PULLS ACROSS TO THE LEFT    LAUDA GOES AHEAD ON HIS OWN    A SAD END TO A WONDERFUL BATTLE    HUNT PUSHING OFF THE MARSHAL    THE CHEQUERED FLAG IS WAITING FOR LAUDA   AND FOR FERRARI    THE TITLE GOING TO NIKI LAUDA    WHO WINS THE RACE    WHO WINS THE WORLD CHAMPIONSHIP   DO I LOOK LIKE A RACING DRIVER NOW</pattern><template>Congratulations.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU CRAZY</pattern><template>Clay's a senior figure in F1.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY THINK THAT'D BE GOOD FOR ME</pattern><template>What do you think?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  I HAVE A HOT HEAD  AN INABILITY TO TOLERATE DISCIPLINE</pattern><template>Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>THE MINUTE YOU DON'T  CIAO  CIAO</pattern><template>I totally understand.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S THE REAL THING  TEDDY</pattern><template>He's what we all came into this for.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY</pattern><template>God gave me an Ok mind, but a really good ass which can feel everything in a car.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT</pattern><template>Except we are, or were.</template></category><category><pattern>I NOTICED THAT TOO</pattern><template>Level playing field now, my rally little friend.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT WEEK</pattern><template>No. What, are you nuts?</template></category><category><pattern>CONGRATULATIONS</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID IT  YOU'RE GOING TO BE WORLD CHAMPION</pattern><template>Not yet.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS HE QUICKER IN MY CAR</pattern><template>He was, wasn't he?</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU</pattern><template>Press conference over.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT SINE THEY'RE RIGHT ABOUT MOST THINGS  THEY'RE PROBABLY RIGHT ABOUT THAT TOO</pattern><template>You don't fancy getting married, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S BEEN HERE SINCE 5 A M</pattern><template>walking the track.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL SON IT OUT</pattern><template>They're killing us out there.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK</pattern><template>What the fuck d'you think we're doing?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  BECAUSE I'M A SERIOUS GUY</pattern><template>I go to bed early, I look after myself, after my car.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE YOU ON RACE DAY  CHAMP</pattern><template>You will...</template></category><category><pattern>THEY FELT YOUR REPUTATION PRECEDED YOU</pattern><template>And what does that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS SEASON'S FIGHT FOR THE F1 WORLD CHAMPIONSHIP   HAS SO FAR BEEN THE STORY OF TWO MEN    THUS FAR IT'S BEEN GOING PRETTY MUCH THE WAY OF NIKI LAUDA    BUT JAMES HUNT HAS QUALIFIED FASTEST HERE    HE IS ON POLE POSITION FOR THE GERMAN GRAND PRIX   WITH NIKI LAUDA ALONGSIDE IN THE BLOOD RED FERRARI    IT'S A LONG RACE    IF THE TRACK STARTS TO DRY OUT    THE WET WEATHER TYRES WILL NO LONGER BE AS QUICK    NIKI LAUDA AND JAMES HUNT    SIDE BY SIDE ON THE FRONT OF THE GRID    GO AWAY ABSOLUTELY AS ONE    LAUDA VERY AGGRESSIVE ON HUNT THERE    FORCING THE MCLAREN ONTO THE GRASS    LAUDA HAS THE LEAD RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>He leads into the first corner!   Hunt is in second place!   Mass storming past Hunt!   He made the right choice to go with the dry weather tyres.   Mass passing Lauda now!   Jochen Mass, in the number 12 McLaren, takes the lead!   Jochen Mass, the clear leader, with everybody else   making the decision to change tyres   after just one lap of this race.  Come on, let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  WHAT IS HAPPENING    THEY'RE TALKING TO THE TEAM MANAGER    LAUDA EXPLAINING SOMETHING    WITH LAUDA OUT  JAMES HUNT KNOWS HE HAS TO FINISH   THIS RACE IN THIRD PLACE OR HIGHER TO BE WORLD CHAMPION    BUT THE JOB'S NOT DONE YET FOR JAMES HUNT    IN THESE DREADFUL CONDITIONS    HE STILL HAS TO GO THE DISTANCE    FIFTEEN LAPS TO GO HERE AT FUJI    JAMES HUNT OR NIKI LAUDA    THIS EXTRAORDINARY SEASON IS NOT OVER YET    IN THIS TREACHEROUS FINAL ROUND  CAN JAMES HUNT HANG ON    AND THE SCOREBOARD TELLS A STORY</pattern><template>Lap 58.   Hunt in the lead.  Oh, God, his tyres, they're blistering.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL DONE  SUPERSTAR</pattern><template>Another season like that, I'll move you up to the big time.</template></category><category><pattern>NINE DAYS OUT OF TEN YOU'LL BE PULLING YOUR HAIR OUT  BUT ON THAT TENTH DAY JAMES WILL BE UNBEATABLE</pattern><template>That is the day you will wish you had him in your car.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE REPORTING EXCLUSIVELY TO YOU  AS PER CONTRACT</pattern><template>Pleasure.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD A SKIN GRAFT OPERATION WHERE THEY PUT HALF MY RIGHT THIGH IN MY FACE</pattern><template>Now, it doesn't look too good, but one unexpected advantage is it's impossible to perspire through a skin graft, so sweat will never run into my eyes again, which is good for a driver.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ONLY WANTED TO SHOW ME HIS PRIDE AND JOY</pattern><template>Rhymes with 'boy' if you ask me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE CHAMPION OF THE WORLD</pattern><template>James Hunt is now officially confirmed   as finishing third here in Japan,   and that means he is champion of the world.   Our new World Champion, James Hunt,   by just one single point.   Did we really win?  World bloody Champion!</template></category><category><pattern>SCREW YOU</pattern><template>I brought you along today because you seem like a lonely kind of guy.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JAMES  GO ON  JAMES</pattern><template>Go, James!</template></category><category><pattern>SONY  WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>You did it!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT LUMP WEIGHS 190K ON ITS OWN</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEVER WANTED TO BE MARRIED IN THE FIRST PLACE</pattern><template>Yes, I did.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A COMBINATION OF FACTORS  NOT ALL OF WHICH I'M PREPARED TO DISCUSS HERE</pattern><template>But justice being done re the disqualification in Spain helps and having my car back at its best again.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS  I'M NOT ANYMORE</pattern><template>The new me is very professional.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOU DON'T THINK I'M READY NOW</pattern><template>You are.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THAT AFFECTION  ALL THOSE SMILES  IS A SIGN OF DISRESPECT</pattern><template>They don't fear you. Whereas compared that to me.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'S THAT WORKING OUT FOR YOU  BY THE WAY</pattern><template>Fine.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH WAS</pattern><template>I'd be happy to show you if you like.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE YOU APPROVE</pattern><template>No vulgar logos for cigarettes or condoms.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT'S NOVEMBER  THE 14TH</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>The risks were totally unacceptable.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S THE WORLD CHAMPION</pattern><template>He's got everything to lose.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS BULLSHIT</pattern><template>If the race is cancelled, none of us get our race fees.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WANT YOU BACK IN ONE PIECE</pattern><template>You're too far back. There's too many drivers in front of you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUBBLES</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY MOUNTING OR FIXING PLATES  STRIP IT OUT ALSO</pattern><template>When you've done that, we have to look at the aerodynamics, front and rear wing.</template></category><category><pattern>SO AS WE APPROACH THE HALFWAY POINT   IN THIS YEAR'S FORMULA 1 SEASON    FERRARI AND NIKI LAUDA SEEM CLEARLY ON TOP   AND JAMES HUNT AND MCLAREN ARE STRUGGLING   SO  FIVE RACES IN  HOW'S IT GOING SO FAR</pattern><template>It's fine. Just got a little problem with an Austrian rat and his team of Italian cheats who've destroyed my car.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW GO HOME TO YOUR WIFE AND ASK HER HOW YOU LOOK</pattern><template>Prick.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN WE GO  YEAH</pattern><template>Okay, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL COME STRAIGHT TO THE POINT</pattern><template>Our esteemed lead driver...</template></category><category><pattern>NIKI  LET'S RACE</pattern><template>Gentlemen, please.</template></category><category><pattern>HUNT  IT RHYMES WITH CUNT</pattern><template>A word that happens to describe you perfectly.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT NOW  WITH ZERO INCENTIVE OR REWARD  WHY WOULD I DRIVE FAST</pattern><template>Because I'm asking you to.</template></category><category><pattern>SUZY</pattern><template>JUST MARRIED Hey, hey, hey!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  TEDDY  I THOUGHT I COULD MAKE UP THE GROUND</pattern><template>Sony? What are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE'S GOING ON WETS</pattern><template>I don't know why it became such a big thing.   We were just drivers busting each other's balls.   To me this is perfectly normal,   but other people saw it differently,   that whatever it was between us went deeper.   The other thing I'm remembered for   is what happened on 1st August 1976,   when I was chasing him like an asshole.  Yeah, that's the one. On the second shelf. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL A BIT OF A BLUR</pattern><template>Have you been at Fiorano?</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IS WHY WE ARE PREPARED TO RISK OUR LIVES FOR IT</pattern><template>Not me.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IN A CAR WHICH IS NOT LEGAL</pattern><template>Five eighths of an inch too wide.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD SOMEONE PLEASE TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Who are you? Should I know you?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT JUSTICE BEING DONE RE THE DISQUALIFICATION IN SPAIN HELPS AND HAVING MY CAR BACK AT ITS BEST AGAIN</pattern><template>Are you worried?</template></category><category><pattern>I FULLY EXPECT THE NEXT PRESS CONFERENCE WE WILL HAVE WILL BE WITH ME AS WORLD CHAMPION</pattern><template>Intermittent heavy rain has been forecast   here at Fuji today, along with strong winds   and occasional fog   rolling in from the mountain.   And so with today's Japanese Grand Prix to come,   Lauda's lead a mere three points.   What a way to finish the season.   Hunt or Lauda?   The final chapter will unfold when we bring you extended coverage...  They've got to cancel the race.</template></category><category><pattern>IT TURNS OUT NOT LIKE THE LOWER DIVISIONS AT ALL</pattern><template>What are you saying?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS NOT BAD</pattern><template>No, it's not bad.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO POINT THREE</pattern><template>So, have a think, work out your priorities and get back to me.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE THE CAR BEING SO GOOD HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH ME</pattern><template>Come on, Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT</pattern><template>That's a lower division, where idiots like me mess about in the hop of being talent spotted to race in F1.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU REALLY THINK YOUR MARRIAGE CAN SURVIVE WITH THE WAY YOU LOOK NOW</pattern><template>And I'm being serious too.</template></category><category><pattern>SUZY JOINS THE BURTON SHOW    HUNT'S WIFE SEES ACTOR AS LIZ FLIES TO MUM  JESUS</pattern><template>Blonde model Suzy Hunt   stepped on to the dizzy Elizabeth Taylor Richard Burton   roundabout of romance yesterday.  Is that from him?</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>I don't think they'd insure me.</template></category><category><pattern>THEIR SHINS ARE OPEN TO HERE</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DRIVERS' MEETING IN GERMANY  BEFORE THE RACE</pattern><template>I swayed the room.</template></category><category><pattern>NEW REAR SUSPENSION</pattern><template>New wishbones.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HIM</pattern><template>Nothing. Nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S JUST GOING PAST    MARIO ANDRETTI'S LOTUS THERE   NIKI</pattern><template>Get me out!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE GAME</pattern><template>See you.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT SHOULDN'T</pattern><template>So in many ways I feel responsible for what happened...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE PREPARED TO DIE</pattern><template>To me, that's losing.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO NEED TO DRIVE FAST</pattern><template>It just increases the percentage of risk.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO</pattern><template>Hi, James.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL PUT ON A TIE  I'LL SMILE FOR SPONSORS  SAY THE RIGHT THINGS</pattern><template>I can beat this guy, trust me.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT RACE SHOULD NEVER HAVE GONE AHEAD</pattern><template>No, it shouldn't.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D BE HAPPY TO SHOW YOU IF YOU LIKE</pattern><template>Sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>ASA FUCKING P</pattern><template>Fortunately a few hands have already gone up, good people.</template></category><category><pattern>AND OUR SPECIAL GUEST  FORMULA 1 CHAMPION  JAMES HUNT   JAMES HUNT WORLD CHAMPION JAMES HUNT AGAINST ALL ODDS WAIT  COME ON</pattern><template>There's no better motor oil than Havoline.</template></category><category><pattern>SKIING</pattern><template>Before I go back to New York.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STILL HAVEN'T</pattern><template>This is Formula 3.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ONLY A MATTER OF TIME</pattern><template>It's too wide.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU BEEN AT FIORANO</pattern><template>Pre season testing.</template></category><category><pattern>MY ASS</pattern><template>Sorry?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S SEE WHERE WE ARE IN FIVE RACES TIME</pattern><template>Hunt has the pit Lane pole position,   which should give him the best chance   of outdragging Lauda's Ferrari.   If ever there was a doubt about   whether Lauda had a serious challenger to this season,   Hunt and his McLaren have certainly given us the answer.  BRAZIL LAUDA WINS HUNT HAS ENGINE FAILURE GRAND PRIX SOUTH AFRICA 76  Here in South Africa, James Hunt is determined   to make amends after that disastrous retirement in Brazil.   But it's Lauda who takes the flag here at Kyalami.   James Hunt comes home second   to confirm his championship challenge at last   and score his first points of the season.  That wind you can feel is me breathing down your neck.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T WANT HIM TO DO WHAT LAUDA JUST DID</pattern><template>Why? What did he do?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST MAKE IT NARROWER</pattern><template>I don't care how.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IS THERE A QUESTION NOW</pattern><template>So is there a question now or are you just trying to piss me off?</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T JUST WIN THE BIGGEST THING OF MY LIFE SO I COULD GET RIGHT BACK TO WORK</pattern><template>Why? You have to.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IN MANY WAYS I FEEL RESPONSIBLE FOR WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>You were.</template></category><category><pattern>GET IN</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>SOME GERMAN</pattern><template>Austrian.</template></category><category><pattern>ARSEHOLE</pattern><template>Heading into the Grand Hotel hairpin, second gear.   Turn in hard, looking for late apex,   gentle with the bar.   Heading into Portier, second gear,   clip the apex,   light brake, stay in second,   looking for a good exit.   Heading through the tunnel, gradual right,   up through third, fourth, fifth...  ls Alexander around?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SHOULD CANCEL THE RACE</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>SPAIN HUNT WINS LAUDA 2ND JAMES HUNT FINALLY TAKES HIS FIRST VICTORY OF THE SEASON HERE IN SPAIN  AFTER A BRILLIANT DRIVE</pattern><template>It was only a matter of time.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE KILLING US OUT THERE</pattern><template>Go an get your dick wet.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A NOBODY</pattern><template>He's never won a bloody thing.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Niki, let's race.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOOD FOR EVERYONE THAT THE QUICKEST CAR HAPPENS TO BE A LEGAL CAR</pattern><template>James, your 50 points behind Lauda in the championship.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO SAY  THAT IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>MOSTLY POSITIVE IN TERMS OF APPEARANCE</pattern><template>Negative only in terms of character.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY HONOR  NIKI</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BUSINESS</pattern><template>I would do the same.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S JUST A LITTLE COFFIN  REALLY</pattern><template>Surrounded by high octane fuel in here.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU'RE NOT TERRIBLE</pattern><template>You're just who you are at this point in your life.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>To let the condensation out.</template></category><category><pattern>NEW WISHBONES</pattern><template>I wanna make sure this thing is legal, no doubts.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I WAS  I ADMIT IT</pattern><template>I was prepared to die to beat you that day.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HORSEPOWER ARE YOU GETTING</pattern><template>No, no, 450.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE YOU SAID  CONDOMS AN CIGARETTES  VULGAR  RIGHT</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR SOMETHING THAT COSTS SO MUCH</pattern><template>There's no comfort, no protection, nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>GO TO WORK  KICK ASS</pattern><template>And then, after the race, I go home instead of going to bars and talk all this bullshit with all these assholes.</template></category><category><pattern>SAME AS REGAZZONI'S</pattern><template>Identical in every detail.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYONE SEEN SUZY</pattern><template>She's supposed to be here today.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>THE SHOWDOWN BETWEEN YOU AND NIKI IS ALL ANYONE WANTS TO SEE</pattern><template>With heavy rain continuing to fall here at Fuji,   a decision has finally been made.   The 1976 Japanese Grand Prix will go ahead.   All drivers to your cars, please.   Five minutes to go.    All right?</template></category><category><pattern>REGAZZONI'S FERRARI AND JACQUES LAFITTE IN THE LIGIER   HAVE GONE AHEAD   COME ON  HURRY</pattern><template>You did it. You're going to be World Champion!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU DO</pattern><template>Fine, thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WANTS YOU TO TAKE IT FOR A SPIN</pattern><template>Gloves, please.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR LAP CHARTS SHOW HUNT IN THIRD PLACE    WELL  IF THE SCOREBOARD'S RIGHT    IT MEANS HE'S JUST MISSED OUT ON THE CHAMPIONSHIP    CRUSHING DEFEAT FOR HUNT AFTER SUCH A HEROIC DRIVE    I CAN SEE THE RACE STEWARDS CONFERRING    EXAMINING THE OFFICIAL LAP CHARTS    WE'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE TO WAIT FOR THEIR VERDICT HERE   LET'S GET YOU OUT OF HERE  BUDDY</pattern><template>I'm sorry, Teddy. I thought I could make up the ground.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST IT'S A LEGAL MONSTER</pattern><template>You've had to resort to cheating.</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD ABOUT THIS THING WITH NIKI</pattern><template>Everyone has.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL NEED THESE</pattern><template>Okay, start her up.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK</pattern><template>It sounds fucking awful.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE JUST A ROOKIE</pattern><template>The only reason we took you on is because you're paying us.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE SAME CAR</pattern><template>...McLaren M23 has proved very controversial here.</template></category><category><pattern>GO AN GET YOUR DICK WET</pattern><template>You're a wanker!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>There won't be no points for me either.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST KEEP THEM CLOSED</pattern><template>Wait for it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS</pattern><template>Okay, but if you want my advice, I'd let this one go.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU USING MAGNESIUM PARTS</pattern><template>Now the engine block.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I'M QUICKER THAN ALL OF YOU</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE IN A FERRARI</pattern><template>I'm in a Hesketh.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT BASTARD  HUNT   I'D SAY</pattern><template>I hate that guy.  And one day, the doctor came and said,  Mr. Lauda, may I offer a piece of advice?   Stop thinking of it as a curse to have been given an enemy in life.   It can be blessing too.   A wise man gets more from his enemies than a fool from his friends.  And you know what? He was right.</template></category><category><pattern>DRIVERS PLEASE BRING THEM TO THE SCRUTINEERING BAY NOW</pattern><template>All right, Superstar?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  AND WILL HE GO FOR THAT GAP WHEN NO ONE ELSE WILL</pattern><template>Will he put his life on the line the day it really matters?</template></category><category><pattern>NIKI  CAN YOU CONFIRM TO US EXACTLY WHICH PROCEDURES YOU HAD AND THE EXPECTATIONS FOR YOU RECOVERY</pattern><template>Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHY IT BECAME SUCH A BIG THING    WE WERE JUST DRIVERS BUSTING EACH OTHER'S BALLS    TO ME THIS IS PERFECTLY NORMAL    BUT OTHER PEOPLE SAW IT DIFFERENTLY    THAT WHATEVER IT WAS BETWEEN US WENT DEEPER    THE OTHER THING I'M REMEMBERED FOR   IS WHAT HAPPENED ON 1ST AUGUST 1976    WHEN I WAS CHASING HIM LIKE AN ASSHOLE   YEAH  THAT'S THE ONE  ON THE SECOND SHELF  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Trauma trolley, please.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER EXPECTED NORMALITY</pattern><template>God knows I walked into this with my eyes open.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO</pattern><template>Lauda.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  YEAH</pattern><template>I think I've got something for you on that last question,   about Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>MY WHAT</pattern><template>And when you brake, your foot goes all the way down, which means there's air in the system.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY  LOOK AT THE WAY HE'S DRIVING  LIKE AN OLD MAN</pattern><template>There's no need to drive fast.</template></category><category><pattern>DO I LOOK LIKE I'M FEELING PRESSURE</pattern><template>I'm World Champion and on the verge to become World Champion again.</template></category><category><pattern>NIKI LAUDA</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D BEAT HIM IN A MCLAREN</pattern><template>It's the only car out there as quick as the Ferrari.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU COMPLAINED AND YOUR TEAM OF LAWYERS LEANED ON THE AUTHORITIES  NOW WE'VE HAD TO REBUILD THE CAR   AND IT'S BECOME A MONSTER</pattern><template>At least it's a legal monster.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  NIKI  I TRIED TO WRITE YOU A LETTER AT THE TIME  TO APOLOGISE</pattern><template>The drivers' meeting in Germany, before the race.</template></category><category><pattern>NEED A HAND HERE</pattern><template>Yeah, hold it, Teddy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Where is everybody?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M STOPPING  HIS MECHANICS ARE ASKING WHAT THE PROBLEM IS    BUT WAIT  NIKI LAUDA'S GETTING OUT OF THE CAR    THIS IS SENSATIONAL    THE REIGNING WORLD CHAMPION  NIKI LAUDA    IS OUT OF THIS RACE   IT'S TOO DANGEROUS</pattern><template>Niki, you want me to say there was a problem with the car, for the media?</template></category><category><pattern>LAUDA'S FACING THE WRONG WAY    THE BACK MARKER'S GONE THROUGH    YOU CAN SEE WHY HUNTER'S FELLOW DRIVERS CALL HIM     HUNT THE SHUNT    ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Go on, James!</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT RIGHT</pattern><template>Suzy. Friend of Alex's.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS PREPARED TO DIE TO BEAT YOU THAT DAY</pattern><template>And that's the effect you have on me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND TODAY  WITH THE RAIN  THE RISK IS MORE</pattern><template>I suppose that all depends on how good you are in the rain.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN TELL  SEEING YOUR REACTION</pattern><template>I'll spend the rest of my life with a face that frightens people.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SAYING LOOK AFTER YOURSELF</pattern><template>We want you back in one piece.</template></category><category><pattern>NEGATIVE ONLY IN TERMS OF CHARACTER</pattern><template>I've been told to avoid you.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT ENOUGH</pattern><template>It needs to be 500.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THE OLD MAN TOOK REGAZZONI BACK AND HE INSISTED ON IT APPARENTLY</pattern><template>He says that Niki's a genius setting up the cars.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  TIME TO START KILLING PHEASANTS</pattern><template>Actually, it's the deadline for securing sponsorship for the forthcoming Formula 1 season.</template></category><category><pattern>NIKI</pattern><template>Good to see you!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  ME TOO  WHERE WE GOING</pattern><template>Anywhere I want to go.</template></category><category><pattern>MIGHT HAVE BEEN A BIRTHDAY OR SOMETHING</pattern><template>It's all a bit of a blur.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DON'T LIKE IT WHEN IT'S NOT GOING THEIR WAY</pattern><template>That's the game.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  SUPERSTAR</pattern><template>Never better, patron.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE A DRINK ON ME  JAMES</pattern><template>Thank you, Niki. I might just have two.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T DEAL WITH IT  SO YOU'RE THE ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Screw you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE MATTER</pattern><template>Do you know what the date it is today?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE'S A CLEVER GUY AND HE'S USED HIS TIME WELL WHILE I WAS LYING HALF DEAD IN HOSPITAL WHILE I WAS LYING HALF DEAD IN HOSPITAL TO WIN SOME POINTS</pattern><template>And what did your wife say when she saw your face?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T UNDERSTAND  WHY AM I SUPPOSED TO DO THIS</pattern><template>I don't know, Clay.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>This car is fine. I just had a service a week ago.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S FORMULA 1</pattern><template>Yes, she is, Superstar.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MR  BURTON HAS FOUND A WAY OF FEELING YOUNG AGAIN  WHICH MAKES HIM HAPPY</pattern><template>Let's hope his pockets are deep.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A DISASTER  COME ON</pattern><template>What's going on, you assholes?</template></category><category><pattern>SO SAYS THE NOBODY  WHO HAD TO PAY FOR HIS OWN DRIVE</pattern><template>How's that working out for you, by the way?</template></category><category><pattern>MEANS HE'S STOKED</pattern><template>All Formula 3 cars to the assembly area.</template></category><category><pattern>VILLAGE OF WATKINS GLEN  WHEN THE SEASON STARTED  PEOPLE WONDERED   WHETHER LORD HESKETH AND HIS TEAM   OF UPPER CLASS ENTHUSIASTS WERE BRINGING GLAMOUR   TO THE RACING COMMUNITY OR JUST COMEDY    CERTAINLY IT WAS THE FIRST TIME ANYONE HAD SEEN   A BUTLER SEWING OYSTERS AND CAVIAR IN THE PITS    BUT THEY HAVE MADE QUITE AN IMPACT    6TH IN FRANCE  4TH IN BRITAIN AND 3RD IN HOLLAND    ALL DRIVERS ON THE TRACK  CAUTION FLAGS ARE OUT    A SEVERE CRASH AT THE ESSES    RED FLAG  THERE'S A CAR OFF THE TRACK    AND REPORTS ARE REACHING ME THAT THERE'S BEEN   A SERIOUS ACCIDENT IN QUALIFYING    THE IDENTITY OF THE DRIVER WE DON'T CURRENTLY HAVE    BUT AS YOU CAN TELL FROM ALL THE ACTIVITY GOING ON   TOWARDS THE TRACK  IT WAS CLEARLY A GRAVE INCIDENT INDEED    WE WILL  OF COURSE  HAVE MORE INFORMATION AS WE GET IT    BUT IT IS THE SIGHT AND SOUND OF F1 NOBODY LIKES TO SEE     GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME</pattern><template>Hey, come on!</template></category><category><pattern>PUT REGAZZONI IN THE CAR</pattern><template>See what happens.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN BEAT THIS GUY  TRUST ME</pattern><template>Just give me the drive.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S SEE WHERE WE ARE AFTER LAP ONE</pattern><template>Let's see where we are in five races time.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S NO BEAUTY  BUT GOES LIKE THE SLAPPERS</pattern><template>Nothing to be worried about.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I INTEND TO ENJOY MYSELF FIRST</pattern><template>Some of life needs to be for pleasure.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE GOT TO GO</pattern><template>Careful in this thing.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU CALL THAT WINNING</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THOSE IN FAVOR OF RACING</pattern><template>Gentlemen, the race is on.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I CAN SEE WHY THIS SUITS YOU JUST FINE</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY GAVE ME THE FIRST CLASS EDUCATION  BUT THAT WENT ALL TERRIBLY WRONG AND I ENDED UP WITH YOU LOT</pattern><template>Thank you. I need it more than you do.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M STARVING  LET'S GET SOME FOOD</pattern><template>BOLOGNA, ITALY   Where are you going?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  SO</pattern><template>We aren't looking for sponsorship.</template></category><category><pattern>SURROUNDED BY HIGH OCTANE FUEL IN HERE</pattern><template>Being driven round 170 mph.</template></category><category><pattern>I NOTICED</pattern><template>Pole position.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT ABOUT YOUR SOUL  YOUR HEART</pattern><template>They've got ideas about that, too.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE RACING</pattern><template>Maybe you should ask Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CAR'S EVIL</pattern><template>It's fucking undriveable!</template></category><category><pattern>AGAIN THE HESKETH       SUZY  WE'RE READY  COME ON</pattern><template>Just one second.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW WE'RE BOTH CHAMPIONS OF THE WORLD</pattern><template>It was not bad.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  I DO</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  LOVER  WHICH MAKES HER HAPPY</pattern><template>And Mr. Burton has found a way of feeling young again, which makes him happy.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING WE REPLACED THE ENTIRE EXHAUST SYSTEM</pattern><template>Barely made the difference.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID IT BECAUSE YOU HOPED IT MIGHT CHANGE YOU  SETTLE YOU DOWN  HELP WITH THE RACING</pattern><template>No, I didn't.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO REALLY BELIEVE IT TO MAKE IT POSSIBLE</pattern><template>James, is there anything you'd like to add?</template></category><category><pattern>HAS DITCHED US FOR ANOTHER TEAM AT THE LAST MINUTE</pattern><template>Coper fucking sucar.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I'VE GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU ON THAT LAST QUESTION    ABOUT NIKI</pattern><template>You heard about that?</template></category><category><pattern>WONDERFUL</pattern><template>No wonder she left him.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT BRINGS YOU HERE</pattern><template>A friend's wedding.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT FOR IT</pattern><template>There.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT BEING PAID</pattern><template>Right now, with zero incentive or reward, why would I drive fast?</template></category><category><pattern>FINE  THEN LET'S RACE</pattern><template>Yeah!</template></category><category><pattern>IS NIKI GONNA CHANGE</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I SHALL BE GETTING DRUNK</pattern><template>It's wonderful, absolute dream.</template></category><category><pattern>COME HERE</pattern><template>Actually, credit where it's due, we got the idea from Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SHE IS  SUPERSTAR</pattern><template>Your brother and I got together with the bean counters.</template></category><category><pattern>AS LONG AS I PAY FOR IT</pattern><template>I'm starving. Let's get some food.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE HERE TODAY</pattern><template>We didn't wanna tell you before the race.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA OF THE SIGNIFICANCE OF THAT DATE</pattern><template>I don't know. Time to start killing pheasants?</template></category><category><pattern>SO NIKI LAUDA  JUST 42 DAYS   AFTER HIS NEAR FATAL ACCIDENT AT NÜBURGRING    WILL RACE HERE TODAY  AT MONZA   AGAINST ALL MEDICAL ADVICE AND NO DOUBT IN INCREDIBLE PAIN    PHOTOGRAPHERS  PLEASE  CLEAR THE GRID   NIKI  IT'S TIME</pattern><template>Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU SAYING</pattern><template>I'm saying look after yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING  NOTHING</pattern><template>Didn't want to ruin your day.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THAT DOESN'T HAVE THE SLIGHTEST EFFECT ON SPEED</pattern><template>But you complained and your team of lawyers leaned on the authorities. Now we've had to rebuild the car   and it's become a monster.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S WRONG WITH THE CAR</pattern><template>Niki! What's wrong with the car?</template></category><category><pattern>MY CAR IS YOUR CAR</pattern><template>On one condition, though.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HOLD IT  TEDDY</pattern><template>Okay, start the bastard.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR POINTS</pattern><template>That bastard, Hunt,  I'd say.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS TO YOUR IMPECCABLE SURVIVAL INSTINCTS</pattern><template>Fuck you! What's your name?</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T BE A MINUTE</pattern><template>Niki!</template></category><category><pattern>GRAND PRIX MONACO 76  AND WITH HUNT DISQUALIFIED FROM HIS SPAIN WIN    HIS CHAMPIONSHIP HERE IS NOT GOING WELL    AND NOW IT'S ALL GONE WRONG HERE AT MONACO    HIS ENGINE IS SMOKING    SMOKE POURING FROM THE ENGINE OF THAT MCLAREN    AND JAMES HUNT IS OUT   CAN YOU TELL US WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Sure. It's magic, we've taken a great car, a great piece of engineering and overnight turned it into a big, huge stinking turd.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A FERRARI</pattern><template>It's a shitbox!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT  I'VE GOT TO FIND YOU A CAR FIRST</pattern><template>Well, go on, then.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TYRE CHANGING FRENZY CAUSED A HUGE RESHUFFLING OF THE PACK      WITH MASS IN THE LEAD NOW</pattern><template>You're clear. Go!  Lauda urging his mechanics to hurry.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT US</pattern><template>We were both a pair of kids when we met.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WHAT  ARE YOU NUTS</pattern><template>I didn't just win the biggest thing of my life so I could get right back to work.</template></category><category><pattern>FITTI FUCKING PALDI</pattern><template>Has ditched us for another team at the last minute.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE MY JOB  I LOVE COMPETING</pattern><template>I love racing.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BANKS HAVE STEPPED IN  STARTED LAYING EVERYONE OFF</pattern><template>Probably have to sell this place.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEY DON'T WANT ME DOING THAT ANYMORE</pattern><template>They want my body like a Temple and my mind like a monk.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIGHT WIN ONE RACE  MAYBE TWO  BECAUSE YOU'RE AGGRESSIVE</pattern><template>But in the long run, over the course of a season, no chance.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THE RACE IS CANCELLED  NONE OF US GET OUR RACE FEES</pattern><template>That's true, you leave without your fee, but you might leave with your life.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE APPEALING</pattern><template>We'll son it out.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS HAIRY</pattern><template>You know how to get noticed.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL</pattern><template>By now I'm both quicker than you and better at setting up a car.</template></category><category><pattern>﻿1     WHAT HAS TURNED INTO A CLASSIC FORMULA 1 SEASON       WITH THE WEATHER CONDITIONS SO UNCERTAIN    THE DRIVERS PREPARE FOR         THE TRACK IS STILL DANGEROUSLY WET    BUT FOLLOWING A DRIVERS MEETING  A DECISION HAS BEEN TAKEN    THREE MINUTES TO GO</pattern><template>Everybody off the grid now.   25 drivers start every season in Formula 1,   and each year, two of us die.   What kind of person does a job like this?   Not normal men, for sure.   Rebels,   lunatics,   dreamers.   People who are desperate to make a Mark   and are prepared to die trying.   My name is Niki Lauda,   and racing people know me for two things.   The first is my rivalry with him.  What about Hunt? Has he changed?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS A NASTY BLOW</pattern><template>Done with a bloody crowbar.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE TOO FAR BACK  THERE'S TOO MANY DRIVERS IN FRONT OF YOU</pattern><template>There's always next year.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  YEAH  HE WILL DRIVE YOU ALL MAD  BUT IN TERMS OF RAW TALENT AND RIGHT STUFF  THERE IS NO BETTER DRIVER IN THE WORLD</pattern><template>He's the real thing, Teddy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HEAR THAT NOISE WHEN YOU ACCELERATE</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU LEAVING</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>LAUDA</pattern><template>Bought his way in rather than mess about in the lower divisions.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU SAY</pattern><template>She's Formula 1.</template></category><category><pattern>CAREFUL IN THIS THING</pattern><template>James.</template></category><category><pattern>AUSTRIAN</pattern><template>He's been here since 5 a.m.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  WE DO  YEAH</pattern><template>It's my honor, Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>SO LET'S SEE WHERE MR  REUTEMANN FINISHES AND WHERE I FINISH TODAY</pattern><template>James Hunt and McLaren have caught up a lot while you were away.</template></category><category><pattern>IF NIKI IS BEING TRICKY AND GETTING A KICKY OUT OF PLAYING MIND GAMES  THEN FINE  I'M FLATTERED</pattern><template>The fact is momentum is with me.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH A CAR LIKE THAT  THE REST OF US NEVER STOOD A CHANCE  DID WE</pattern><template>Maybe the car being so good has something to do with me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WING BRACKETS NEED</pattern><template>Fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON</pattern><template>A guaranteed place in the team.</template></category><category><pattern>ABSOLUTELY FINE</pattern><template>We all thought you'd been in an accident.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SO DO I</pattern><template>But that means beating Niki Lauda, not being a show pony for sponsors.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO COMFORT  NO PROTECTION  NOTHING</pattern><template>No, it's just a little coffin, really.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  YOU SHARE INFORMATION AND I SHARE INFORMATION</pattern><template>That's what teammates are for.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS MY WHOLE LIFE</pattern><template>VILLAGE OF WATKINS GLEN  When the season started, people wondered   whether Lord Hesketh and his team   of upper class enthusiasts were bringing glamour   to the racing community or just comedy.   Certainly it was the first time anyone had seen   a Butler sewing oysters and caviar in the pits.   But they have made quite an impact.   6th in France, 4th in Britain and 3rd in Holland.   All drivers on the track, caution flags are out.   A severe crash at the Esses.   Red flag. There's a car off the track.   And reports are reaching me that there's been   a serious accident in qualifying.   The identity of the driver we don't currently have,   but as you can tell from all the activity going on   towards the track, it was clearly a grave incident indeed.   We will, of course, have more information as we get it,   but it is the sight and sound of F1 nobody likes to see.    Get your hands off me!</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER</pattern><template>You might win one race, maybe two, because you're aggressive.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ECONOMICS  FORMULA 1  REALITIES THEREOF</pattern><template>It turns out not like the lower divisions at all.</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON  JAMES</pattern><template>The Kraut's out of it!</template></category><category><pattern>SO DON'T LET ME DOWN NOW</pattern><template>I need you busting my balls.</template></category><category><pattern>AS LONG AS I'M BACK IN MARANELLO MONDAY MORNING</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>NURSIE  THIS IS BUBBLES HORSELY  TEAM MANAGER</pattern><template>How do you do?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>The tyre changing frenzy caused a huge reshuffling of the pack,     with Mass in the lead now.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M WORLD CHAMPION AND ON THE VERGE TO BECOME WORLD CHAMPION AGAIN</pattern><template>Hunt now has the opportunity to win, but it's not so easy to become a champion.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T WE GO AWAY AT THE WEEKEND</pattern><template>Skiing.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE YOU SHOULD ASK NIKI</pattern><template>He's the World Champion.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T CARE HOW</pattern><template>New rear suspension.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT'S THE EFFECT YOU HAVE ON ME</pattern><template>You'd pushed me that far.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>Just go easy out there.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST I THINK IT WAS A WEDDING</pattern><template>Might have been a birthday or something.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS EVERYBODY</pattern><template>What's the matter?</template></category><category><pattern>TO STARE DEATH IN THE FACE AND TO CHEAT IT</pattern><template>Come on, there's nobility in that.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  CREDIT WHERE IT'S DUE  WE GOT THE IDEA FROM NIKI</pattern><template>Who?</template></category><category><pattern>BY NOW I'M BOTH QUICKER THAN YOU AND BETTER AT SETTING UP A CAR</pattern><template>You can't deal with it, so you're the asshole.</template></category><category><pattern>EQUAL TERMS  THE WAY IT WAS IN FORMULA 3    ID' BEAT YOU AND YOU KNOW IT</pattern><template>Never.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE YOUR OWN FRIENDS</pattern><template>Come on, Clay.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  IT'S MAGIC  WE'VE TAKEN A GREAT CAR  A GREAT PIECE OF ENGINEERING AND OVERNIGHT TURNED IT INTO A BIG  HUGE STINKING TURD</pattern><template>BELGIUM MAY 1976 Shit!</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS  YOU CRAZY BASTARD</pattern><template>You came 3rd! You got the points!</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING ELSE</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>TO ALL INTENTS AND PURPOSES  THIS THING'S A BOMB ON WHEELS</pattern><template>You're James, aren't you?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  FIRE HER UP</pattern><template>This season's fight for the F1 World Championship   has so far been the story of two men.   Thus far it's been going pretty much the way of Niki Lauda.   But James Hunt has qualified fastest here.   He is on pole position for the German Grand Prix   with Niki Lauda alongside in the blood red Ferrari.   It's a long race.   If the track starts to dry out,   the wet weather tyres will no longer be as quick.   Niki Lauda and James Hunt,   side by side on the front of the grid,   go away absolutely as one!   Lauda very aggressive on Hunt there,   forcing the McLaren onto the grass.   Lauda has the lead right now!</template></category><category><pattern>A GROWN UP</pattern><template>Right, and will he go for that gap when no one else will?</template></category><category><pattern>HOT HEADED JERKS IN FORMULA 3</pattern><template>Disowned by our families.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S ALWAYS NEXT YEAR</pattern><template>So that's it? It's over?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BUT THERE'D BE ONE RACE LESS WHERE I  OR ANYONE ELSE HERE    COULD CATCH YOU</pattern><template>James is right.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ARE YOU FEELING  NIKI</pattern><template>Fine.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M IN A HESKETH</pattern><template>Equal terms, the way it was in Formula 3,   Id' beat you and you know it.</template></category><category><pattern>BRAMBILLA VERY CLOSE BEHIND HIM  CLOSING ON HIM ALL THE TIME    AND HE'S TRYING TO DRIVE INSIDE JAMES HUNT    HUNT CUTS ACROSS THE ORANGE MARCH NOSE    HUNT NOT HAVING THAT AT ALL</pattern><template>And he's spinning.   He missed Hunt but almost took James Hunt out of the race   and out of the world championship.   Now we find Mario Andretti closing on James Hunt.   Mario Andretti's going past Hunt!   Hunt is slowing. James Hunt seems to have a problem.   Despite this wet conditions,   these wet weather tyres wear extremely fast.  Hunt's tyres, they're gone.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU AND SUZY GETTING BACK TOGETHER</pattern><template>It's all very amicable.</template></category><category><pattern>CLAY'S A SENIOR FIGURE IN F1</pattern><template>You're just a rookie!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T WANNA KNOW</pattern><template>Actually, I do.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD GAVE ME AN OK MIND  BUT A REALLY GOOD ASS WHICH CAN FEEL EVERYTHING IN A CAR</pattern><template>You don't know what you're talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY NOT</pattern><template>It's a Ferrari!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S HIS FAULT</pattern><template>Is that right?</template></category><category><pattern>IN NEW YORK  WORKING</pattern><template>You know, I've never seen you with her once.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE THE HELL ARE WE GOING</pattern><template>I promise it'll be worth it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WANT ME TO STOP MESSING AROUND  SETTLE DOWN  GET MARRIED WITH THE NEXT NICE GIRL I MEET</pattern><template>They think that'd be good for me.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST THERE'S SOMETHING BEHIND THE FACADE</pattern><template>James.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  450</pattern><template>It's not enough.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Hold still.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YEAH</pattern><template>We're in the closing laps of this race at Watkins Glen.   They come down the hill.   And Hunt's got a problem!   Hunt pulls across to the left!   Lauda goes ahead on his own.   A sad end to a wonderful battle.   Hunt pushing off the marshal.   The chequered flag is waiting for Lauda   and for Ferrari!   The title going to Niki Lauda,   who wins the race,   who wins the World Championship.  Do I look like a racing driver now?</template></category><category><pattern>ALISTAIR  WE NEED TO LIFT IT</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY CREATURES I'VE EVER REALLY LOVED OR TREATED HONORABLY ARE BUDGERIGARS</pattern><template>So in any normal area of life, I'd be, or I am, a total liability.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE</pattern><template>What do you say?</template></category><category><pattern>IF I HAD MORE TALENT AND COULD EARN BETTER MONEY WITH SOMETHING ELSE  I WOULD</pattern><template>How do you know you will make money here?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALL THOUGHT YOU'D BEEN IN AN ACCIDENT</pattern><template>I have.</template></category><category><pattern>600 KILOS</pattern><template>But that's crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>JACKY ICKX</pattern><template>I'm quicker than Jacky.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TOO WIDE</pattern><template>Disqualified.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO NOW</pattern><template>I shall be getting drunk.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  AND RATS ARE RATS</pattern><template>Thank you. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>NO DANGER OF THAT</pattern><template>Let me give you some advice.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S IMPORTANT IS HOW IT FEELS TO ME  AND IT FEELS LIKE HE ADORES ME</pattern><template>James!</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW EXACTLY</pattern><template>What was the description?</template></category><category><pattern>ON ONE CONDITION  THOUGH</pattern><template>It's a piece of shit.</template></category><category><pattern>BLONDE MODEL SUZY HUNT   STEPPED ON TO THE DIZZY ELIZABETH TAYLOR RICHARD BURTON   ROUNDABOUT OF ROMANCE YESTERDAY   IS THAT FROM HIM</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WANNA SEE THE CAR')   SURE</pattern><template>Hello.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A THEORY WHY WOMEN LIKE RACING DRIVERS    IT'S NOT BECAUSE THEY RESPECT WHAT WE DO    DRIVING ROUND AND ROUND IN CIRCLES    MOSTLY THEY THINK THAT'S PATHETIC   AND THEY'RE PROBABLY RIGHT    IT'S OUR CLOSENESS TO DEATH    THE CLOSER YOU ARE TO DEATH  THE MORE ALIVE YOU FEEL    THE MORE ALIVE YOU ARE  AND THEY CAN SEE THAT IN YOU    THEY FEEL THAT IN YOU    MY NAME IS JAMES HUNT    MY FATHER IS A STOCKBROKER    MY SISTER IS A BARRISTER   AND MY BROTHER IS AN ACCOUNTANT    AND I    WELL  I DO THIS    IT'S A WONDERFUL WAY TO LIVE</pattern><template>It's the only way to drive.   As if each day is your last.  I've never been to a Grand Prix before.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  I TOLD YOU TO GO ON SLICKS</pattern><template>You should've taken my advice.</template></category><category><pattern>VERY TRUE</pattern><template>I fall out with people left and right.</template></category><category><pattern>NIKI  WHAT'S WRONG WITH THE CAR</pattern><template>Nothing. Car's perfect.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  JAMES</pattern><template>Now go home to your wife and ask her how you look.</template></category><category><pattern>ALEXANDER</pattern><template>He says you're a bad boy.</template></category><category><pattern>RHYMES WITH 'BOY' IF YOU ASK ME</pattern><template>And 'toy.' God, it's so flimsy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE JUST A CHARGER AND A PARTY GUY</pattern><template>That's why everybody likes you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE WE HERE  NIKI  COME ON</pattern><template>Well, all those in favor of cancelling the race.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY HAVE TO SELL THIS PLACE</pattern><template>On, Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>I GO TO BED EARLY  I LOOK AFTER MYSELF  AFTER MY CAR</pattern><template>Yes, you're very well behaved.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IS THERE A QUESTION NOW OR ARE YOU JUST TRYING TO PISS ME OFF</pattern><template>You still think you can win?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE CAR</pattern><template>Yep, that's her.</template></category><category><pattern>GEMMA</pattern><template>Nursie, this is Bubbles Horsely, team manager.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS COULD BE   THE WORLD CHAMPIONSHIP    HE'S GOT HIM    HUNT CROSSES THE LINE    HE NEEDED TO FINISH THIRD TO SCORE ENOUGH POINTS   TO BE WORLD CHAMPION    AND IN THE CONFUSION HERE WE'RE BEING TOLD   THAT HE MAY HAVE FINISHED 5TH   HE FINISHED FIFTH</pattern><template>Our lap charts show Hunt in third place.   Well, if the scoreboard's right,   it means he's just missed out on the championship.   Crushing defeat for Hunt after such a heroic drive.   I can see the race stewards conferring,   examining the official lap charts.   We're just going to have to wait for their verdict here.  Let's get you out of here, buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  COME ON  JAMES</pattern><template>You did it because you hoped it might change you, settle you down, help with the racing.</template></category><category><pattern>ANOTHER SEASON LIKE THAT  I'LL MOVE YOU UP TO THE BIG TIME</pattern><template>Come on, you don't think I'm ready now?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN  AFTER THE RACE  I GO HOME INSTEAD OF GOING TO BARS AND TALK ALL THIS BULLSHIT WITH ALL THESE ASSHOLES</pattern><template>Arseholes?</template></category><category><pattern>SURELY NO WAY BACK FOR THE BRIT   CONCENTRATE  SUPERSTAR</pattern><template>Just brings it back under control!   Sliding the McLaren on the very edge there.   Hunt's M23 twitching this way and that under braking.   And he almost loses it right there.   Hunt on the tail of Jacques Lafitte   in the blue Ligier.  Don't do it, James.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  PLEASE</pattern><template>...drivers please bring them to the scrutineering bay now.</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD YOU WERE SPENDING MORE AND MORE TIME   IN ONE OF THESE</pattern><template>Do you fly?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  AS OF NOW  IF YOU WANT ME TO STAY  WE RIP UP THE CONTRACT  I DON'T PAY YOU A CENT</pattern><template>That's outrageous!</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S WHAT WE ALL CAME INTO THIS FOR</pattern><template>Nine days out of ten you'll be pulling your hair out, but on that tenth day James will be unbeatable.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S DIRTY POLITICS AND DIRTY TRICKS  THAT'S WHAT'S GOING WRONG</pattern><template>So as we approach the halfway point   in this year's Formula 1 season,   Ferrari and Niki Lauda seem clearly on top   and James Hunt and McLaren are struggling.  So, five races in, how's it going so far?</template></category><category><pattern>BARELY MADE THE DIFFERENCE</pattern><template>Are you using magnesium parts?</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH ASSHOLE SAID THIS</pattern><template>Yes, of course, I'm frightened, and so are you.</template></category><category><pattern>IT JUST INCREASES THE PERCENTAGE OF RISK</pattern><template>We're not in a hurry.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT HIM</pattern><template>He's here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD GO HOME MORE OFTEN TOO</pattern><template>I heard you got married.</template></category><category><pattern>A FEW WEEKS AGO YOU WERE OUT OF THE RUNNING COMPLETELY AND NOW YOU'RE RIGHT BACK IN IT</pattern><template>What's changed?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DON'T FEAR YOU  WHEREAS COMPARED THAT TO ME</pattern><template>Yes, compared to you, whom no one likes.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS WIFE</pattern><template>That's going to need a couple of stitches.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FAT  LITTLE  INBRED BEAUTY</pattern><template>Come here.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>Please, clear the grid.   One minute to go.   The returning Niki Lauda seems overwhelmed.   He's been overtaken by car after car.   Lauda's off line. He runs wide onto the grass.   He wrestles it back onto the track,   but that was a bad moment for Niki.   Niki Lauda's the reigning world champion,   but maybe in his current state he's a danger out there,   to himself and to the rest of the field.   And Stuck has collided with Mario Andretti's Lotus!   Niki's boxed in! He's got nowhere to go!   Niki Lauda's actually making a move.   He's on Brambilla's tail.   He pulls out of the slipstream to overtake.   Lauda's starting to find the form   that early in this race we believed he'd lost.   Lauda's now lapping faster than Reutemann   and closing the gap ahead.   Lauda closing on Carlos Reutemann,   the man called in to be his replacement   in the Ferrari team.   And there's James Hunt's McLaren,   smoking stationary by the side of the road.   This is bad news for Hunt's championship hopes.   It's Ronnie Peterson   who comes home the winner here at Monza.   But all eyes are on the man who finishes a brilliant fourth!   Niki Lauda!   What a race, what a man, what a season.   With a 4th place finish and three priceless points,   Niki Lauda is a major step closer   to retaining the World Championship.   So the long, grueling and incredibly dramatic season   comes down to this final race in Japan,   in the shadow of Mount Fuji.   Niki Lauda goes into this deciding race at Fuji   just three points ahead of James Hunt,   Hunt knowing he must beat the Austrian fair and square   to take the title.  James, do you think you can cope with the pressure?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ONLY SLEPT WITH ME BECAUSE YOU THOUGHT I WAS FAMOUS</pattern><template>That's not true!</template></category><category><pattern>1:53</pattern><template>Okay, now put him in my car and he'll go 2 seconds faster.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE JUST WHO YOU ARE AT THIS POINT IN YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>God help anyone who wants more.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S VERY SIMPLE</pattern><template>Hunt, it rhymes with cunt!</template></category><category><pattern>POLE POSITION</pattern><template>I noticed that too.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WON'T BE NO POINTS FOR ME EITHER</pattern><template>No, but there'd be one race less where I, or anyone else here,   could catch you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF YOU DRIVE IT  YOU MAKE MY LIFE  NIKI  EH</pattern><template>Would someone please tell me what's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  THE RACE IS ON</pattern><template>Ridiculous.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A PIECE OF SHIT</pattern><template>It's dog shit.</template></category><category><pattern>I FALL OUT WITH PEOPLE LEFT AND RIGHT</pattern><template>The only creatures I've ever really loved or treated honorably are budgerigars.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A NASTY CUT</pattern><template>It was a nasty blow.</template></category><category><pattern>GET BACK TO WORK</pattern><template>I will, Niki, I will.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO STAY WITHIN THE RULES  STICK TO REGULATION  SUPPRESS THE EGO</pattern><template>It helps with the racing.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  COMPARED TO YOU  WHOM NO ONE LIKES</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  ALL THOSE IN FAVOR OF CANCELLING THE RACE</pattern><template>All those in favor of racing.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU  BUT THAT'S NOT AN ACT I'D LIKE TO FOLLOW</pattern><template>But if that doesn't bother you...</template></category><category><pattern>A WORD THAT HAPPENS TO DESCRIBE YOU PERFECTLY</pattern><template>Who was that?</template></category><category><pattern>TRUST ME  THIS RACE IS ALL ABOUT THE START</pattern><template>Need a hand here?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK  JAMES</pattern><template>30 seconds to go.</template></category><category><pattern>AND RACING OVERALLS WHICH READ  SEX  BREAKFAST OF CHAMPIONS   SO WHEN DO WE START</pattern><template>Soon as you're ready.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE KRAUT</pattern><template>What about him?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>I'm not sure that was meant as a compliment.</template></category><category><pattern>AND TODAY  WITH THE RAIN  IT'S ANYTHING BUT PERFECT  SO I CALLED THIS MEETING TO TAKE VOTE TO CANCEL THE RACE</pattern><template>Cancel the race?</template></category><category><pattern>BRM</pattern><template>Sign the release form. I'll let them know you're here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE DRIVING AN ILLEGAL CAR AND CALL ME A CHEATER  PATHETIC</pattern><template>Rules are rules.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD BE APPEALING THIS</pattern><template>We are appealing.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE</pattern><template>But, trust me, watching you win those races, while I was fighting for my life...</template></category><category><pattern>A WELL ADJUSTED KNIGHT IN SHINING ARMOUR</pattern><template>No danger of that.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  NIKI  I MIGHT JUST HAVE TWO</pattern><template>Right, Bubbles, whatever it takes to beat that prick next year, just say it, you're word is my command.</template></category><category><pattern>DISQUALIFIED</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>SEVERAL CARS ARE INVOLVED    LOOKS LIKE IT MIGHT BE ONE OF THE FERRARIS     COME THIS WAY</pattern><template>Come on, come on!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAID WITH TIME IT WOULD BE FINE</pattern><template>But it won't.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE FUCKING WANKER</pattern><template>But this was a good race for you, no, Niki?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YOU'RE VERY WELL BEHAVED</pattern><template>Go to work, kick ass.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOT GO AHEAD</pattern><template>I won't be a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S IN THE LEAD    HUNT WILL BE DETERMINED TO MAKE UP FOR THAT MISTAKE    HUNT'S IN LAUDA'S SLIPSTREAM    LAUDA'S NOT LEAVING ANY GAP    THE LOTUS GOES FOR THE INSIDE    IT'S AN AGGRESSIVE MOVE FROM HUNT    THERE'S CONTACT    THE LEADERS HAVE SPUN OUT</pattern><template>Lauda's facing the wrong way!   The back marker's gone through!   You can see why Hunter's fellow drivers call him.    Hunt the Shunt.   Asshole!</template></category><category><pattern>I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>It's business.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL VERY AMICABLE</pattern><template>My wife has found herself a new backer...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE POINT OF HAVING A MILLION CUPS  MEDALS AND PLANES IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANY FUN</pattern><template>How is that winning?</template></category><category><pattern>HE LEADS INTO THE FIRST CORNER    HUNT IS IN SECOND PLACE    MASS STORMING PAST HUNT    HE MADE THE RIGHT CHOICE TO GO WITH THE DRY WEATHER TYRES    MASS PASSING LAUDA NOW    JOCHEN MASS  IN THE NUMBER 12 MCLAREN  TAKES THE LEAD    JOCHEN MASS  THE CLEAR LEADER  WITH EVERYBODY ELSE   MAKING THE DECISION TO CHANGE TYRES   AFTER JUST ONE LAP OF THIS RACE   COME ON  LET'S GO</pattern><template>See? I told you to go on slicks.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  LAUDA  ARE YOU FEELING PRESSURE</pattern><template>Do I look like I'm feeling pressure?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALREADY TRIED</pattern><template>Tried what?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  CLAY</pattern><template>He wants you to take it for a spin.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THERE'S A PROBLEM WITH THE CAR  WE'LL FIX IT</pattern><template>The car is a piece of shit.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES IT BEFORE EVERY RACE</pattern><template>Good sign, actually.</template></category><category><pattern>NURSIE  MEN LOVE WOMEN  BUT EVEN MORE THAN THAT  MEN LOVE CARS</pattern><template>Come on, James!</template></category><category><pattern>MR  STANLEY</pattern><template>Good morning.</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE EIGHTHS OF AN INCH TOO WIDE</pattern><template>You know that doesn't have the slightest effect on speed.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO BETTER MOTOR OIL THAN HAVOLINE</pattern><template>Yes, me too. Where we going?</template></category><category><pattern>THE KRAUT'S OUT OF IT</pattern><template>Lauda is clearly furious.   There's every reason to expect sharp words in the pit.   It's going to be victory for Hunt.   It's going to be an ignominious defeat for Niki Lauda.   So James Hunt scores his third major Formula 3 win   of the season here, at Crystal Palace,   after a desperate battle with Niki Lauda.   Lauda was unable so restart   after Hunt's aggressive move caused them both to spin out   in the last lap of the race.  Hard luck. Better luck next time.</template></category><category><pattern>CLEAR</pattern><template>Fuck it!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE'S CONSISTENT  DEPENDABLE</pattern><template>A grown up.</template></category><category><pattern>HIM</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT YET</pattern><template>A few laps ago, James Hunt was looking like champion elect.   Now it looks as though it's all gone wrong for him.    James.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE TO BE A CHAMPION  IT TAKES MORE THAN JUST BEING QUICK</pattern><template>It's the whole picture.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL DONE  JAMES</pattern><template>Superstar!</template></category><category><pattern>HELP ME</pattern><template>Several cars are involved.   Looks like it might be one of the Ferraris.    Come this way!</template></category><category><pattern>WALKING THE TRACK</pattern><template>You might actually have to concentrate today, James.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE ONLY CAR OUT THERE AS QUICK AS THE FERRARI</pattern><template>Which is why I'm here, begging.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT DOES THAT MEAN</pattern><template>It's my other line. Look, I'll get back to you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVEN'T YET</pattern><template>Not yet, but I will.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD KNOWS I WALKED INTO THIS WITH MY EYES OPEN</pattern><template>I just hoped I'd married someone who is half as impressive on the inside as he is on the outside!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  THERE'S NOBILITY IN THAT</pattern><template>It's like being knights.</template></category><category><pattern>A GUARANTEED PLACE IN THE TEAM</pattern><template>And a paid contract on equal terms with Regazzoni for two years.</template></category><category><pattern>ON THE ALL IMPORTANT DAY WHEN IT CAME DOWN TO IT  WE RACED ON EQUAL TERMS  EQUALLY GOOD CARS</pattern><template>And I put my life on the line and I saw it through.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS RACE HAS GONE WRONG FOR HIM SO FAR    HIS CHAMPIONSHIP RIVAL  JAMES HUNT    IS A LONG WAY UP THE ROAD    LAUDA PASSING CAR AFTER CAR</pattern><template>He's just going past.   Mario Andretti's Lotus there.  Niki!</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  CLEAR THE GRID    ONE MINUTE TO GO    THE RETURNING NIKI LAUDA SEEMS OVERWHELMED    HE'S BEEN OVERTAKEN BY CAR AFTER CAR    LAUDA'S OFF LINE  HE RUNS WIDE ONTO THE GRASS    HE WRESTLES IT BACK ONTO THE TRACK    BUT THAT WAS A BAD MOMENT FOR NIKI    NIKI LAUDA'S THE REIGNING WORLD CHAMPION    BUT MAYBE IN HIS CURRENT STATE HE'S A DANGER OUT THERE    TO HIMSELF AND TO THE REST OF THE FIELD    AND STUCK HAS COLLIDED WITH MARIO ANDRETTI'S LOTUS    NIKI'S BOXED IN  HE'S GOT NOWHERE TO GO    NIKI LAUDA'S ACTUALLY MAKING A MOVE    HE'S ON BRAMBILLA'S TAIL    HE PULLS OUT OF THE SLIPSTREAM TO OVERTAKE    LAUDA'S STARTING TO FIND THE FORM   THAT EARLY IN THIS RACE WE BELIEVED HE'D LOST    LAUDA'S NOW LAPPING FASTER THAN REUTEMANN   AND CLOSING THE GAP AHEAD    LAUDA CLOSING ON CARLOS REUTEMANN    THE MAN CALLED IN TO BE HIS REPLACEMENT   IN THE FERRARI TEAM    AND THERE'S JAMES HUNT'S MCLAREN    SMOKING STATIONARY BY THE SIDE OF THE ROAD    THIS IS BAD NEWS FOR HUNT'S CHAMPIONSHIP HOPES    IT'S RONNIE PETERSON   WHO COMES HOME THE WINNER HERE AT MONZA    BUT ALL EYES ARE ON THE MAN WHO FINISHES A BRILLIANT FOURTH    NIKI LAUDA    WHAT A RACE  WHAT A MAN  WHAT A SEASON    WITH A 4TH PLACE FINISH AND THREE PRICELESS POINTS    NIKI LAUDA IS A MAJOR STEP CLOSER   TO RETAINING THE WORLD CHAMPIONSHIP    SO THE LONG  GRUELING AND INCREDIBLY DRAMATIC SEASON   COMES DOWN TO THIS FINAL RACE IN JAPAN    IN THE SHADOW OF MOUNT FUJI    NIKI LAUDA GOES INTO THIS DECIDING RACE AT FUJI   JUST THREE POINTS AHEAD OF JAMES HUNT    HUNT KNOWING HE MUST BEAT THE AUSTRIAN FAIR AND SQUARE   TO TAKE THE TITLE   JAMES  DO YOU THINK YOU CAN COPE WITH THE PRESSURE</pattern><template>Well, I've never really understood what that means.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME OF LIFE NEEDS TO BE FOR PLEASURE</pattern><template>What's the point of having a million cups, medals and planes if you don't have any fun?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'VE NEVER REALLY UNDERSTOOD WHAT THAT MEANS</pattern><template>I love my job. I love competing.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE A GARGLE WITH THIS</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE'S SPINNING    HE MISSED HUNT BUT ALMOST TOOK JAMES HUNT OUT OF THE RACE   AND OUT OF THE WORLD CHAMPIONSHIP    NOW WE FIND MARIO ANDRETTI CLOSING ON JAMES HUNT    MARIO ANDRETTI'S GOING PAST HUNT    HUNT IS SLOWING  JAMES HUNT SEEMS TO HAVE A PROBLEM    DESPITE THIS WET CONDITIONS    THESE WET WEATHER TYRES WEAR EXTREMELY FAST   HUNT'S TYRES  THEY'RE GONE</pattern><template>Hunt nursing his car back to the pit stop.   That back marker's going past Hunt.  LAP 70 4 LAPS TO GO  Look at that left front tyre, right front tyre, sorry.   No tread on it at all. And the other one is flat.  Let's go! Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>I SWAYED THE ROOM</pattern><template>Yes, you did.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU WORRIED</pattern><template>Welcome to the legendary Nüburgring.   This is a 14.2 mile track,   complete with 185 corners and bends.   Welcome to the Nüburgring,   the most dangerous circuit on the season calendar.   In Formula 1 it is known   as  The Graveyard.    The weather conditions are far from ideal   and latest reports indicate there is no relief in sight.  Gentlemen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR BROTHER AND I GOT TOGETHER WITH THE BEAN COUNTERS</pattern><template>And since the economics of F1 are not so significantly different to the economics of F2, well, we thought if we were going to be losing money, we might as well be doing it on the big roulette table in F1.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'VE GOT IDEAS ABOUT THAT  TOO</pattern><template>They want me to stop messing around, settle down, get married with the next nice girl I meet.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHEN YOU BRAKE  YOUR FOOT GOES ALL THE WAY DOWN  WHICH MEANS THERE'S AIR IN THE SYSTEM</pattern><template>Anything else?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHEN IT'S ALL OF THEM</pattern><template>Yes, I know, I'm terrible.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW HOW TO GET NOTICED</pattern><template>I thought it went well, to be honest.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS NURSIE</pattern><template>Gemma.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S LIKE BEING KNIGHTS</pattern><template>You English, you're such assholes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FAN BELT IS LOOSE</pattern><template>My What?</template></category><category><pattern>THE FLOOD  WHICH SWEPT DOWN BIG THOMPSON CANYON IN COLORADO    WAS THE WORST SINCE RECORDS BEGAN    IN FORMULA 1 TODAY  VICTORY CELEBRATIONS WERE MUTED   AFTER A HORRIFIC ACCIDENT INVOLVING WORLD CHAMPION    NIKI LAUDA    DUE TO SAFETY CONCERNS BEFORE THE RACE    THE AUSTRIAN HAD SAID HE WOULD NOT TAKE PAN    BUT IN THE END HE DID    HE WAS MAKING UP FOR LOST TIME WHEN HE WENT OFF THE TRACK    PUNCTURING THE FERRARI'S FUEL TANK    BRETT LUNGER WAS UNABLE TO AVOID THE FLAMING WRECK   BUT WAS UNHURT AND JOINED OTHER DRIVERS TO RESCUE LAUDA    WHO WAS TAKEN TO MANHEIM HOSPITAL WITH SEVERE BURNS    THE INCIDENT REMINDING US AGAIN OF THE DANGERS OF FORMULA 1    NIKI LAUDA WAS TRAPPED FOR ALMOST A MINUTE   IN A SEARING INFERNO OF 800 PLUS DEGREES    JAMES HUNT GAINS ON THE ABSENT NIKI LAUDA   28TH DAY IN HOSPITAL 29TH AUGUST 1976</pattern><template>Morning, chaps.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S TRUE  YOU LEAVE WITHOUT YOUR FEE  BUT YOU MIGHT LEAVE WITH YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>It also means that you would effectively win the championship.</template></category><category><pattern>DRIVERS OF TOP STATURE WE'VE LOST JUST IN THE PAST 4 SEASONS   HAVE INCLUDED PIERS COURAGE    JOCHEN RINDT    JO SIFFERT    ROGER WILLIAMSON   AND TODAY  AT WATKINS GLEN    FORMULA 1 HAS CLAIMED ANOTHER DRIVER    THE TYRRELL TEAM HAVE WITHDRAWN FROM THE RACE    THEIR PLACES ON THE GRID WILL BE LEFT EMPTY     TERRIBLE</pattern><template>They should cancel the race.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  SUZY  ONLY A STRANGER WOULD INVITE ME SKIING WHEN THEY KNOW I HAVEN'T GOT A FUCKING DRIVEL I CAN'T WATCH THIS</pattern><template>What were you hoping for anyway?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S HERE</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK IT</pattern><template>James Hunt rejoins the race in sixth position.   There are four laps to go.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A SHITBOX</pattern><template>It understeers like crazy and the weight distribution is a disaster.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S JUST BEEN SIGNED BY FERRARI</pattern><template>You're kidding me?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE ALL SEEN THE RAIN THAT HAS BEEN FALLING TODAY</pattern><template>Those of you with experience know the ring needs perfect conditions to be even remotely acceptable in terms of risk.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW YOU WILL MAKE MONEY HERE</pattern><template>You haven't yet.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE STILL QUICK   BRITISH GRAND PRIX BRANDS HATCH SUNDAY 18TH JULY 1976  HUNT HAS REALLY CLOSED THE GAP ON LAUDA   AS THEY HEAD INTO DRUIDS    NIKI LAUDA IS UNDER REAL PRESSURE FROM JAMES HUNT   AS THEY GO UP THE HILL INTO DRUIDS CORNER    AND HUNT IS IN FRONT OF LAUDA    SO JAMES HUNT GETS THE PLAUDITS OF THE CROWD    THE FIRST BRITON TO WIN A BRITISH GRAND PRIX   AT BRANDS HATCH SINCE JIM CLARK IN 1964   JAMES  AT THE MOMENT YOU'VE GOT A TERRIFIC EDGE OVER THE REST   HOW HAVE YOU ACHIEVED THIS ADVANTAGE   BIG BALLS</pattern><template>Following an inquiry into the disqualification   of driver James Hunt from the Spanish Grand Prix,   it has been decided to overturn this disqualification   and to restore his victory and reinstate his points.  James!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL HAVE YOU DONE</pattern><template>The car's evil!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  ASSHOLE</pattern><template>That was my line. I had that corner.</template></category><category><pattern>DIDN'T WANT TO RUIN YOUR DAY</pattern><template>It's...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE DISQUALIFIED</pattern><template>How can we be disqualified?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHILE DOING IT  I WAS WATCHING TELEVISION</pattern><template>You winning all my points.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ALL EARS</pattern><template>Don't go to men who are willing to kill themselves driving in circles looking for normality.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  A VERY GOOD ONE  VERY EXPENSIVE</pattern><template>This car's as good as new.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW MY POSITION</pattern><template>20% risk.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO</pattern><template>Regazzoni's Ferrari and Jacques Lafitte in the Ligier   have gone ahead.  Come on, hurry!</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASURE</pattern><template>Do you wanna see the car')   Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WERE YOU HOPING FOR ANYWAY</pattern><template>A well adjusted knight in shining armour?</template></category><category><pattern>WITH HEAVY RAIN CONTINUING TO FALL HERE AT FUJI    A DECISION HAS FINALLY BEEN MADE    THE 1976 JAPANESE GRAND PRIX WILL GO AHEAD    ALL DRIVERS TO YOUR CARS  PLEASE    FIVE MINUTES TO GO     ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD</pattern><template>Nothing. Why?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T BE A PRO</pattern><template>The minute you do that, you kill what's good about this.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY OFF THE GRID NOW    25 DRIVERS START EVERY SEASON IN FORMULA 1    AND EACH YEAR  TWO OF US DIE    WHAT KIND OF PERSON DOES A JOB LIKE THIS    NOT NORMAL MEN  FOR SURE    REBELS    LUNATICS    DREAMERS    PEOPLE WHO ARE DESPERATE TO MAKE A MARK   AND ARE PREPARED TO DIE TRYING    MY NAME IS NIKI LAUDA    AND RACING PEOPLE KNOW ME FOR TWO THINGS    THE FIRST IS MY RIVALRY WITH HIM   WHAT ABOUT HUNT  HAS HE CHANGED</pattern><template>No, he's going on wets.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS</pattern><template>Niki Lauda.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID IT</pattern><template>Did what?</template></category><category><pattern>GO  JAMES</pattern><template>Hunt's still in the lead,   but Niki Lauda is right on his tail!   Hunt and Lauda are proving to be in a class of their own.   They're leaving the pack far behind.  Herr Red Devil's on his tail.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IS WHY I'M HERE  BEGGING</pattern><template>I'll do whatever you ask.</template></category><category><pattern>DONE WITH A BLOODY CROWBAR</pattern><template>Why? What did you do?</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD YOU GOT MARRIED</pattern><template>Yes, I did.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS MY LINE  I HAD THAT CORNER</pattern><template>You mean the one that you spun out of and finished facing the other way?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON</pattern><template>Keep trying   Come this way.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT ISN'T JUST BUSINESS  IS IT</pattern><template>What we do. It's passion, love.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Absolutely fine.</template></category><category><pattern>SIGN THE RELEASE FORM  I'LL LET THEM KNOW YOU'RE HERE</pattern><template>Mr. Stanley.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FACT IS MOMENTUM IS WITH ME</pattern><template>I've never felt better.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE CLEAR  GO   LAUDA URGING HIS MECHANICS TO HURRY</pattern><template>It's a disaster! Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL ALSO LET THE WATER IN</pattern><template>Not if you're leading.</template></category><category><pattern>I ACCEPT EVERY TIME I GET IN MY CAR THERE'S 20% CHANCE I COULD DIE  AND I CAN LIVE WITH IT  BUT NOT ONE PERCENT MORE</pattern><template>And today, with the rain, the risk is more.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT A GOOD ONE</pattern><template>Yes, a very good one, very expensive.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  COME ON</pattern><template>Drivers of top stature we've lost just in the past 4 seasons   have included Piers Courage,   Jochen Rindt,   Jo Siffert,   Roger Williamson   and today, at Watkins Glen,   Formula 1 has claimed another driver.   The Tyrrell team have withdrawn from the race.   Their places on the grid will be left empty.    Terrible.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WE'D BETTER MOVE THE OIL COOLERS TO THE OLD POSITION</pattern><template>The wing brackets need...</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE THE TRACK RECORD HERE</pattern><template>I'm the only person in history to do the ring in under 7 Min., so, actually, it's to my advantage to race here today.</template></category><category><pattern>PERSONALLY I'VE ALWAYS BEEN A GREAT BELIEVER IN GETTING THERE ON THE DAY  PUTTING MY FOOT DOWN AND PLAYING CHICKEN WITH EVERYONE ELSE</pattern><template>But they don't want me doing that anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID YOU DO TO THE CAR</pattern><template>That's information I'll share with you under certain conditions only.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK OFF TO NEW YORK  DEAR</pattern><template>There must be a moisturiser or an eye shadow somewhere that needs your vapid mush to flog it.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  JAMES</pattern><template>It's James! Go on, James!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS CAR IS FINE  I JUST HAD A SERVICE A WEEK AGO</pattern><template>Not a good one.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME WHAT</pattern><template>SUZY JOINS THE BURTON SHOW.   HUNT'S WIFE SEES ACTOR AS LIZ FLIES TO MUM  Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT IN A HURRY  ARE YOU</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL HE PUT HIS LIFE ON THE LINE THE DAY IT REALLY MATTERS</pattern><template>The sponsors like him.</template></category><category><pattern>AND A PAID CONTRACT ON EQUAL TERMS WITH REGAZZONI FOR TWO YEARS</pattern><template>Are you crazy?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED A DRIVE  PETE  I NEED YOU TO FIND ME A DRIVE</pattern><template>I mean, what about Lotus?</template></category><category><pattern>NIKI  YOU WANT ME TO SAY THERE WAS A PROBLEM WITH THE CAR  FOR THE MEDIA</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WINNING ALL MY POINTS</pattern><template>Your points?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK D'YOU THINK WE'RE DOING</pattern><template>GRAND PRIX MONACO 76  And with Hunt disqualified from his Spain win,   his championship here is not going well.   And now it's all gone wrong here at Monaco!   His engine is smoking!   Smoke pouring from the engine of that McLaren!   And James Hunt is out!  Can you tell us what happened?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  ARE YOU EVER NOT AN ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Why am I an asshole?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY COULD NEVER HAVE IMAGINED IT  THOSE PIONEERS WHO INVENTED THE AUTOMOBILE  THAT IT WOULD POSSESS US LIKE THIS  IN OUR IMAGINATIONS  OUR DREAMS</pattern><template>Nursie, men love women, but even more than that, men love cars!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST HOPED I'D MARRIED SOMEONE WHO IS HALF AS IMPRESSIVE ON THE INSIDE AS HE IS ON THE OUTSIDE</pattern><template>At least there's something behind the facade.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T WANT ME BACK</pattern><template>You never wanted to be married in the first place.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I PUT MY LIFE ON THE LINE AND I SAW IT THROUGH</pattern><template>And you call that winning?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THE RACETRACK TELEPHONED AHEAD THAT I WAS COMING</pattern><template>Hunt. James Hunt.</template></category><category><pattern>RATS ARE UGLY  SURE  AND NOBODY LIKE THEM  BUT THEY'RE VERY INTELLIGENT AND THEY HAVE A STRONG SURVIVAL INSTINCT</pattern><template>Wonderful.</template></category><category><pattern>IS REUTEMANN DRIVING TODAY TOO</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS CAR'S AS GOOD AS NEW</pattern><template>Relax.</template></category><category><pattern>RELAX</pattern><template>You're not in a hurry, are you?</template></category><category><pattern>ARSEHOLES</pattern><template>You should go home more often too.</template></category><category><pattern>FERRARI FAMILY    OUR GOOD FRIEND CLAY REGAZZONI   YOU ARE FAMILY AND FRIEND TO THE COMMENDATORE AS LONG AS YOU WIN</pattern><template>The minute you don't, ciao, ciao.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOOD FOR DISCIPLINE</pattern><template>You have to stay within the rules, stick to regulation, suppress the ego.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCEPT WE ARE  OR WERE</pattern><template>I've made something of a miscalculation.</template></category><category><pattern>BELGIUM MAY 1976 SHIT</pattern><template>What the hell have you done?</template></category><category><pattern>CLAY REGAZZONI</pattern><template>How are you?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GO TO MEN WHO ARE WILLING TO KILL THEMSELVES DRIVING IN CIRCLES LOOKING FOR NORMALITY</pattern><template>I never expected normality.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU WANT  A DRIVER OR A BRUSH SALESMAN</pattern><template>We wanna be successful.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHO KNOWS  IF IT HAD BEEN JUST THE DRINKING  OR THE DOPE  OR THE INFIDELITY OR THE MOODS  IT MIGHT EVEN HAVE WORKED</pattern><template>But when it's all of them...</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL  NIKI  I WILL</pattern><template>But I intend to enjoy myself first.</template></category><category><pattern>DRIVER OF THE YEAR</pattern><template>is James Hunt.</template></category><category><pattern>TRAUMA TROLLEY  PLEASE</pattern><template>I think the racetrack telephoned ahead that I was coming.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU KNOW  FORMULA 1 DRIVERS  THEY HAVE LONG HAIR  ARE SEXY</pattern><template>their shins are open to here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAME 3RD  YOU GOT THE POINTS</pattern><template>You're champion of the world!</template></category><category><pattern>CLAY</pattern><template>Let me introduce you to our number one driver.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF THAT DOESN'T BOTHER YOU</pattern><template>What's his name, the driver?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IN THE LONG RUN  OVER THE COURSE OF A SEASON  NO CHANCE</pattern><template>Right. Why is that?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL NEVER WIN THE CHAMPIONSHIP WITH JACKY ICKX   YOU JUST MIGHT WITH JAMES</pattern><template>GRANDE PREMIO DO BRAZIL INTERLAGOS JANUARY 1976  Welcome to Säo Paulo, Brazil, and the Interlagos circuit   for the first race in the 1976 Formula 1 season,   where the main news is James Hunt qualified fastest,   beating Niki Lauda's Ferrari to pole position   by just 200th of a second.  New car.</template></category><category><pattern>NIKI  OKAY</pattern><template>I'm good.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT HIMSELF A DRIVE  WITH BRM</pattern><template>How the hell did he do that?</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT IT WENT WELL  TO BE HONEST</pattern><template>They don't like it when it's not going their way.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THANK YOU FOR THIS AND FOR ACKNOWLEDGING THAT</pattern><template>I'm going to give it to my father and tell him to put it on the mantelpiece and imagine it's a first class degree in medicine.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK THEY'D INSURE ME</pattern><template>You should try.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'D HAVE CRASHED</pattern><template>But we didn't, did we?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE SHE IS  P160</pattern><template>Same as Regazzoni's?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'D PUSHED ME THAT FAR</pattern><template>And it felt great!</template></category><category><pattern>IT UNDERSTEERS LIKE CRAZY AND THE WEIGHT DISTRIBUTION IS A DISASTER</pattern><template>It's amazing, all these facilities and you make a piece of crap like this.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  NIKI</pattern><template>You're in a Ferrari.</template></category><category><pattern>IF IT'S THE TRACK MANAGER YOU'RE TAKING ON YOUR DATE TONIGHT</pattern><template>It's none of your business.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T SAY THAT</pattern><template>Why not?</template></category><category><pattern>SAY ANYTHING  JUST GET ME IN THAT ROOM</pattern><template>I'll come straight to the point.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  NIKI  EVERY NOW AND THEN IT HELPS IF PEOPLE LIKE YOU</pattern><template>In places the track is still dangerously wet,   but following a drivers meeting, a decision has been taken.   One minute to go.  Jochen's going on slicks.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE I GO BACK TO NEW YORK</pattern><template>Talk to me, James. Don't make a stranger of me.</template></category><category><pattern>NIKI  IS THAT OTHER PEOPLE OR IS THAT YOU</pattern><template>I won, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>SUZY  FRIEND OF ALEX'S</pattern><template>Yeah, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>PRICK</pattern><template>So Niki Lauda, just 42 days   after his near fatal accident at Nüburgring,   will race here today, at Monza   against all medical advice and no doubt in incredible pain.   Photographers, please, clear the grid.  Niki, it's time.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S DOG SHIT</pattern><template>But if you drive it, you make my life, Niki, eh?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE THE BETTER CAR</pattern><template>And possibly I'm the better driver.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  WHAT ABOUT LOTUS</pattern><template>You don't wanna know.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YOU DID</pattern><template>That race should never have gone ahead.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S RACING</pattern><template>Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING TO BE WORRIED ABOUT</pattern><template>Does it before every race.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NEVER WON A BLOODY THING</pattern><template>Apparently, took out a Loan and bought his way in with two million Austrian shillings.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN THE ONE THAT YOU SPUN OUT OF AND FINISHED FACING THE OTHER WAY</pattern><template>I think that corner had you.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  GENTLEMEN  PLEASE BE QUIET</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>MCLAREN M23 HAS PROVED VERY CONTROVERSIAL HERE</pattern><template>Just make it narrower.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWHERE I WANT TO GO</pattern><template>And I don't have to hijack it, either.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Jesus. It's Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  YOU HAVE TO</pattern><template>To prove to all the people who will always say you just won it because...</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME TO THE LEGENDARY NÜBURGRING    THIS IS A 14 2 MILE TRACK    COMPLETE WITH 185 CORNERS AND BENDS    WELCOME TO THE NÜBURGRING    THE MOST DANGEROUS CIRCUIT ON THE SEASON CALENDAR    IN FORMULA 1 IT IS KNOWN   AS  THE GRAVEYARD     THE WEATHER CONDITIONS ARE FAR FROM IDEAL   AND LATEST REPORTS INDICATE THERE IS NO RELIEF IN SIGHT   GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>Well, gentlemen, please be quiet.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A WASTE OF TIME</pattern><template>You know, Niki, every now and then it helps if people like you.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE YOU</pattern><template>See you later.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BEFORE EVER REACHING THE HOSPITAL</pattern><template>Is Reutemann driving today too?</template></category><category><pattern>MY WIFE HAS FOUND HERSELF A NEW BACKER</pattern><template>I mean, lover, which makes her happy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STILL THINK YOU CAN WIN</pattern><template>Yes, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THAT'S IT  IT'S OVER</pattern><template>Clear!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL DONE</pattern><template>Thank you so much.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE NEED A REPLACEMENT</pattern><template>Asa fucking P.</template></category><category><pattern>JAWOHL  REMEMBER ZE NAME</pattern><template>It's very simple.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU WITH HER ONCE</pattern><template>No?</template></category><category><pattern>HUNT NOW HAS THE OPPORTUNITY TO WIN  BUT IT'S NOT SO EASY TO BECOME A CHAMPION</pattern><template>You have to really believe it to make it possible.</template></category><category><pattern>TO PROVE TO ALL THE PEOPLE WHO WILL ALWAYS SAY YOU JUST WON IT BECAUSE</pattern><template>Because of what? Because of your accident?</template></category><category><pattern>1 5 CM</pattern><template>It's the same car.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANNA CHANGE</pattern><template>Is Niki gonna change?</template></category><category><pattern>1000CC  COSWORTH MAE ENGINE</pattern><template>She's no beauty, but goes like the slappers.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S HOPE HIS POCKETS ARE DEEP</pattern><template>They'll need to be.</template></category><category><pattern>SOON AS YOU'RE READY</pattern><template>Ready?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE NO IDEA  HE LOOKS LIKE A RAT  DOESN'T HE</pattern><template>In my hometown, Vienna,   my family's famous for one thing:   Business.   My grandfather was a businessman,   my father, too.   So when they heard I wanted to race cars for a living,   They are a few things to say.  Good.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  WHAT DID YOU DO</pattern><template>Nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>THE RACE WOULD SIMPLY BE CANCELLED</pattern><template>This is bullshit!</template></category><category><pattern>FERRARI TEST TRACK FIORANO  ITALY IT'S TERRIBLE</pattern><template>Drives like a pig.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'LL NEED TO BE</pattern><template>And I found a way to be single and have an ex wife without it costing me a Penny, which has to go down as the biggest win of my career.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS  IT'S NIKI</pattern><template>What about him?</template></category><category><pattern>NO VULGAR LOGOS FOR CIGARETTES OR CONDOMS</pattern><template>Just plain white with the flags.</template></category><category><pattern>NINE OR TEN LAPS AGO</pattern><template>Alistair, we need to lift it!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  GO ON  THEN</pattern><template>Chop chop. Don't wait too long.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE OF WHAT  BECAUSE OF YOUR ACCIDENT</pattern><template>Niki, is that other people or is that you?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE</pattern><template>If you call a friendly disagreement with another driver an accident.</template></category><category><pattern>THINK ABOUT IT</pattern><template>All that affection, all those smiles, is a sign of disrespect.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>Listen.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING</pattern><template>Only what she asked me to do.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D SAY WE PUSH IT</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MOVE WAS TOTAL SUICIDE</pattern><template>What if I hadn't braked?</template></category><category><pattern>HE MADE A MISTAKE  WENT INTO THE CORNER TOO FAST</pattern><template>It's his fault.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA LEAVE WITHOUT YOU</pattern><template>James!</template></category><category><pattern>IDENTICAL IN EVERY DETAIL</pattern><template>How much does she weigh?</template></category><category><pattern>THE CAR IS A PIECE OF SHIT</pattern><template>You should be appealing this.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD SIGN  ACTUALLY</pattern><template>Means he's stoked.</template></category><category><pattern>A FRIEND'S WEDDING</pattern><template>At least I think it was a wedding.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GO EASY OUT THERE</pattern><template>What are you saying?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SPEND THE REST OF MY LIFE WITH A FACE THAT FRIGHTENS PEOPLE</pattern><template>You know, Niki, I tried to write you a letter at the time, to apologise.</template></category><category><pattern>PETER HUNT</pattern><template>Fuck!</template></category><category><pattern>PRESS CONFERENCE OVER</pattern><template>That was hairy.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WEEKEND I WENT SKIING</pattern><template>Why have you come here, James?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S DUMPED THEM IN IT</pattern><template>Jesus. Get me in there, Pete.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF I HADN'T BRAKED</pattern><template>We'd have crashed.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT WON'T</pattern><template>I can tell, seeing your reaction.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NEW</pattern><template>Some German.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WANT MY BODY LIKE A TEMPLE AND MY MIND LIKE A MONK</pattern><template>And what about your soul, your heart?</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES</pattern><template>I'll see you on race day, champ.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHERE IS SHE  THIS MYSTERIOUS WIFE</pattern><template>In New York, working.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  HELL  ISN'T THAT WHAT WE'RE IN THIS FOR</pattern><template>To stare death in the face and to cheat it?</template></category><category><pattern>TALK TO ME  JAMES  DON'T MAKE A STRANGER OF ME</pattern><template>You know, Suzy, only a stranger would invite me skiing when they know I haven't got a fucking drivel I can't watch this.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I MEAN IT</pattern><template>What the hell's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT IF I INTRODUCED YOU TO SOME NICE PEOPLE  THAT COULD RUB OFF ON YOU</pattern><template>Forget it.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU REALLY THINK IT UPSETS ME  JAMES  CALLING ME A RAT BECAUSE I LOOK LIKE ONE</pattern><template>I don't mind it.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU FLY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>IT HELPS WITH THE RACING</pattern><template>And there I was thinking you were about to wax lyrical   about the romance of flight.</template></category><category><pattern>DOUBT THAT WILL HELP IN THE MEANTIME</pattern><template>Why don't we go away at the weekend?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST BRINGS IT BACK UNDER CONTROL    SLIDING THE MCLAREN ON THE VERY EDGE THERE    HUNT'S M23 TWITCHING THIS WAY AND THAT UNDER BRAKING    AND HE ALMOST LOSES IT RIGHT THERE    HUNT ON THE TAIL OF JACQUES LAFITTE   IN THE BLUE LIGIER   DON'T DO IT  JAMES</pattern><template>He's inches away from the pit wall!   He's inches away from the Ligier!   James Hunt has made up another place,   but it's not enough and this race is running out.   And Watson has spun!</template></category><category><pattern>PUMPING THE SHIT OUT OF MY LUNGS</pattern><template>It was hell.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP TRYING   COME THIS WAY</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE FOR PRE SEASON TESTING</pattern><template>BRM?</template></category><category><pattern>IT NEEDS TO BE 500</pattern><template>And the engine needs to be.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU BUSTING MY BALLS</pattern><template>Get back to work.</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY WHAT SHE ASKED ME TO DO</pattern><template>Which was...?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  WHY IS THAT</pattern><template>Because to be a champion, it takes more than just being quick.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHAT THE DATE IT IS TODAY</pattern><template>Yes. It's November, the 14th.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FUCKING UNDRIVEABLE</pattern><template>If there's a problem with the car, we'll fix it.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD DO THE SAME</pattern><template>But it isn't just business, is it?</template></category><category><pattern>BEHIND YOU  HE MADE THE SAME MISTAKE</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID YOU DISAGREE ABOUT</pattern><template>It's none of your business.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE WHOLE PICTURE</pattern><template>You're just a charger and a party guy.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN WE BE DISQUALIFIED</pattern><template>1.5 cm.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THIS WAS A GOOD RACE FOR YOU  NO  NIKI</pattern><template>It's good for everyone that the quickest car happens to be a legal car.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOOD</pattern><template>All right, fire her up.</template></category><category><pattern>DISOWNED BY OUR FAMILIES</pattern><template>Headed nowhere.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE JAMES  AREN'T YOU</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>IN PLACES THE TRACK IS STILL DANGEROUSLY WET    BUT FOLLOWING A DRIVERS MEETING  A DECISION HAS BEEN TAKEN    ONE MINUTE TO GO   JOCHEN'S GOING ON SLICKS</pattern><template>You wanna change?</template></category><category><pattern>READY</pattern><template>I've been waiting for this my whole life.</template></category><category><pattern>DRIVES LIKE A PIG</pattern><template>You can't say that.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME INTRODUCE YOU TO OUR NUMBER ONE DRIVER</pattern><template>Clay Regazzoni.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK GOOD  NIKI</pattern><template>The only guy to have burnt his face and it be an improvement.</template></category><category><pattern>MY PARENTS ALWAYS WANTED ME TO BE A DOCTOR OR A STOCKBROKER OR SOMETHING</pattern><template>They gave me the first class education, but that went all terribly wrong and I ended up with you lot.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I FOUND A WAY TO BE SINGLE AND HAVE AN EX WIFE WITHOUT IT COSTING ME A PENNY  WHICH HAS TO GO DOWN AS THE BIGGEST WIN OF MY CAREER</pattern><template>I have a flight to catch.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>He's Niki Lauda, Formula 1 driver, and he just signed with Ferrari.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HERE'S THE MAN</pattern><template>Looking good.</template></category><category><pattern>MORNING  CHAPS</pattern><template>Hey, here's the man.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK DISAPPOINTED</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYONE HAS</pattern><template>You really thing you can beat him?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I KNOW  I'M TERRIBLE</pattern><template>No, you're not terrible.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WILL</pattern><template>champ.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE YOU LATER</pattern><template>James, are you all right?</template></category><category><pattern>NO WONDER SHE LEFT HIM</pattern><template>Anyone seen Suzy?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU SO MUCH</pattern><template>Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE MATTER  NO ONE EVER SEEN A SPOT OF BLOOD BEFORE</pattern><template>Are you all right?</template></category><category><pattern>HI  JAMES</pattern><template>It's Peter. Something's up at McLaren.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A FLIGHT TO CATCH</pattern><template>SUZY HUNT RACES TO RICHARD BURTON CIRCUIT PAUL RICARD CHAMPIONNAT DU MONDE  We haven't seen this sort of intensity   from James Hunt all season long.   Reports have been coming out of the McLaren camp all week   that their car is now fully legal and faster than ever.  FRANCE HUNT WINS LAUDA RETIRES  Never mind the bloody wets.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE GOT TO GET YOU BACK</pattern><template>You don't want me back.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HEARD ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>James?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY THING I'VE GOT GOING FOR ME IS I'M QUICK IN A CAR</pattern><template>So thank you for this and for acknowledging that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THAT</pattern><template>He's new.</template></category><category><pattern>AND RICHARD BURTON  WILL HE BE ABLE TO GIVE YOU MORE</pattern><template>You know, he has quite the bad boy reputation himself.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD I BE JEALOUS</pattern><template>Think about it.</template></category><category><pattern>WATSON HAS SPUN    HUNT MANAGES TO WEAVE HIS WAY BETWEEN THE BACK MARKER   AND THE STATIONARY PENSKE    HE'S CATCHING REGAZZONI  BUT IN THESE CONDITIONS    IT'S ONE THING TO CATCH UP  QUITE ANOTHER TO OVERTAKE    HE'S ALONGSIDE CLAY REGAZZONI</pattern><template>This could be   the world championship!   He's got him!   Hunt crosses the line.   He needed to finish third to score enough points   to be World Champion,   and in the confusion here we're being told   that he may have finished 5th.  He finished fifth?</template></category><category><pattern>TEN MINUTES TO THE WARM UP LAP</pattern><template>Ten minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THE TYRE MARKS</pattern><template>So says the nobody, who had to pay for his own drive.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  HE HAS QUITE THE BAD BOY REPUTATION HIMSELF</pattern><template>What's important is how it feels to me, and it feels like he adores me.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  OF COURSE  I'M FRIGHTENED  AND SO ARE YOU</pattern><template>I accept every time I get in my car there's 20% chance I could die, and I can live with it, but not one percent more.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FIT THE DESCRIPTION</pattern><template>Is that right?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE</pattern><template>No chance.</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES IS RIGHT</pattern><template>This is just tactics!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S WONDERFUL  ABSOLUTE DREAM</pattern><template>And our special guest, Formula 1 champion, James Hunt.  JAMES HUNT WORLD CHAMPION JAMES HUNT AGAINST ALL ODDS Wait. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T MIND IT</pattern><template>Rats are ugly, sure, and nobody like them, but they're very intelligent and they have a strong survival instinct.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE MUST BE A MOISTURISER OR AN EYE SHADOW SOMEWHERE THAT NEEDS YOUR VAPID MUSH TO FLOG IT</pattern><template>Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>DID HE GO TWO SECONDS FASTER</pattern><template>Two point three.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALLY THING YOU CAN BEAT HIM</pattern><template>I'd beat him in a McLaren.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY  SOMETHING WILL TURN UP</pattern><template>Doubt that will help in the meantime.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIGHT ACTUALLY HAVE TO CONCENTRATE TODAY  JAMES</pattern><template>You'll need these.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE ENGINE NEEDS TO BE</pattern><template>We already tried.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS THAT NIKI'S A GENIUS SETTING UP THE CARS</pattern><template>FERRARI TEST TRACK FIORANO, ITALY It's terrible.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE HE'S JUST FRIGHTENED</pattern><template>Which asshole said this?</template></category><category><pattern>CANCEL THE RACE</pattern><template>There would be no change to the situation as far as points is concerned.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HIS NAME  THE DRIVER</pattern><template>Hunt. James Hunt.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THEY HEARD ABOUT YOUR CONDITION  FERRARI IMMEDIATELY HIRED A REPLACEMENT DRIVER  CARLOS REUTEMANN</pattern><template>Yeah, before ever reaching the hospital.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ENGLISH  YOU'RE SUCH ASSHOLES</pattern><template>You know my position.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO DRIVE    AS IF EACH DAY IS YOUR LAST   I'VE NEVER BEEN TO A GRAND PRIX BEFORE</pattern><template>You still haven't.</template></category><category><pattern>WE AREN'T LOOKING FOR SPONSORSHIP</pattern><template>Like you said, condoms an cigarettes, vulgar, right?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'LL BE BACK SHORTLY</pattern><template>He only wanted to show me his pride and Joy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU'VE DONE THAT  WE HAVE TO LOOK AT THE AERODYNAMICS  FRONT AND REAR WING</pattern><template>Okay, thank you. Good night.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH ELAPSED AT MIDNIGHT LAST NIGHT   AND WE DIDN'T ATTRACT ANY</pattern><template>Well, so?</template></category><category><pattern>I HATE THAT GUY   AND ONE DAY  THE DOCTOR CAME AND SAID   MR  LAUDA  MAY I OFFER A PIECE OF ADVICE    STOP THINKING OF IT AS A CURSE TO HAVE BEEN GIVEN AN ENEMY IN LIFE    IT CAN BE BLESSING TOO    A WISE MAN GETS MORE FROM HIS ENEMIES THAN A FOOL FROM HIS FRIENDS   AND YOU KNOW WHAT  HE WAS RIGHT</pattern><template>Look at us.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S NOT BAD</pattern><template>So don't let me down now.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS THE DAY YOU WILL WISH YOU HAD HIM IN YOUR CAR</pattern><template>You'll never win the championship with Jacky Ickx.  You just might with James.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ARE YOU</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SAYING IT'S OVER  SUPERSTAR</pattern><template>The banks have stepped in, started laying everyone off.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  BUT IF YOU WANT MY ADVICE  I'D LET THIS ONE GO</pattern><template>I'm not questioning your taste.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE MADE SOMETHING OF A MISCALCULATION</pattern><template>The economics, Formula 1, realities thereof.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD TRY</pattern><template>It's good for discipline.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Do you really think it upsets me, James, calling me a rat because I look like one?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT PLANNING ON BEING THERE FOR LONG</pattern><template>Ten minutes to the warm up lap.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE NEVER FELT BETTER</pattern><template>I fully expect the next press conference we will have will be with me as World Champion.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S INCHES AWAY FROM THE PIT WALL    HE'S INCHES AWAY FROM THE LIGIER    JAMES HUNT HAS MADE UP ANOTHER PLACE    BUT IT'S NOT ENOUGH AND THIS RACE IS RUNNING OUT    AND WATSON HAS SPUN</pattern><template>Watson has spun!   Hunt manages to weave his way between the back marker   and the stationary Penske.   He's catching Regazzoni, but in these conditions,   it's one thing to catch up, quite another to overtake.   He's alongside Clay Regazzoni!</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT NIKI</pattern><template>You heard about that?</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT FELT GREAT</pattern><template>I mean, hell, isn't that what we're in this for?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE</pattern><template>I'm not. I've got to find you a car first.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  CLAY</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>IT ALSO MEANS THAT YOU WOULD EFFECTIVELY WIN THE CHAMPIONSHIP</pattern><template>So I can see why this suits you just fine.</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES  ARE YOU ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Good, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE EQUALLY RESPONSIBLE FOR GETTING ME BACK IN THE CAR</pattern><template>How are you feeling, Niki?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  NIKI</pattern><template>I know what you're going to say, that it's none of my business.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IF MY FAMILY WASN'T GOING TO HELP ME    I DECIDED TO RISK EVERYTHING AND TAKE OUT A LOAN MYSELF    I FOUND A FORMULA 1 TEAM WITH AN OK CAR   AND AN OWNER WHO HAD RUN OUT OF MONEY   AND WAS WILLING TO ACCEPT MY TERMS   AND SO  LADIES AND GENTLEMEN  I'M DELIGHTED TO SAY</pattern><template>that the winner of the Guild of Motoring Writers Award.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST NEED THE RIGHT FOOT   I'M BEING SERIOUS</pattern><template>Do you really think your marriage can survive with the way you look now?</template></category><category><pattern>HEADED NOWHERE</pattern><template>And now we're both champions of the world.</template></category><category><pattern>RIDICULOUS</pattern><template>What a waste of time.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T FANCY GETTING MARRIED  DO YOU</pattern><template>Suzy.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE DIDN'T  DID WE</pattern><template>Thanks to your impeccable survival instincts.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD TO SEE YOU</pattern><template>I heard you were spending more and more time   in one of these.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL VERY DULL  BUT ACCORDING TO THE TEAM  THE BEST WAY TO KEEP BEATING THE GOOSE STEPPER ' IS THAT WHAT YOU WERE DOING WHEN I CAME IN</pattern><template>Yes, visualization techniques, memorising the circuit, in this case Monaco, which is up next.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL FORMULA 3 CARS TO THE ASSEMBLY AREA</pattern><template>Now, please.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING  WHY</pattern><template>I heard Emerson's off.</template></category><category><pattern>SUPERSTAR</pattern><template>Fantastic!</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'M BEING SERIOUS TOO</pattern><template>Fuck you.</template></category><category><pattern>TRY SAYING THAT AND TELL ME YOU'RE NOT JEALOUS</pattern><template>Why would I be jealous?</template></category><category><pattern>I SUPPOSE THAT ALL DEPENDS ON HOW GOOD YOU ARE IN THE RAIN</pattern><template>I have the track record here.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING  CAR'S PERFECT</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS REGAZZONI'S TIME</pattern><template>1:53.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS JUST TACTICS</pattern><template>Maybe he's just frightened.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU GIVE ME A LIFT TO THE NEAREST TOWN  ANYWHERE WITH A TRAIN STATION</pattern><template>Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IN ANY NORMAL AREA OF LIFE  I'D BE  OR I AM  A TOTAL LIABILITY</pattern><template>The only thing I've got going for me is I'm quick in a car.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WAS THAT</pattern><template>I've no idea. He looks like a rat, doesn't he?</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD STILL</pattern><template>What the hell are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE OF YOU WITH EXPERIENCE KNOW THE RING NEEDS PERFECT CONDITIONS TO BE EVEN REMOTELY ACCEPTABLE IN TERMS OF RISK</pattern><template>And today, with the rain, it's anything but perfect, so I called this meeting to take vote to cancel the race.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WOULD BE NO CHANGE TO THE SITUATION AS FAR AS POINTS IS CONCERNED</pattern><template>The race would simply be cancelled.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE WHAT HAPPENS</pattern><template>I don't understand. Why am I supposed to do this?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW THE HELL DID HE DO THAT</pattern><template>He's a nobody.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE KIDDING ME</pattern><template>Jesus. How did that happen?</template></category><category><pattern>IN HOSPITAL  THE TOUGHEST PART OF MY TREATMENT WAS THE VACUUM</pattern><template>Pumping the shit out of my lungs.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MUCH DOES SHE WEIGH</pattern><template>600 kilos.</template></category><category><pattern>LAP 58    HUNT IN THE LEAD   OH  GOD  HIS TYRES  THEY'RE BLISTERING</pattern><template>Brambilla very close behind him, closing on him all the time.   And he's trying to drive inside James Hunt.   Hunt cuts across the orange March nose.   Hunt not having that at all.</template></category><category><pattern>EARLY TO BED  EARLY TO RISE</pattern><template>All very dull, but according to the team, the best way to keep beating the goose stepper.' Is that what you were doing when I came in?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST MARRIED HEY  HEY  HEY</pattern><template>What's going on with him?</template></category><category><pattern>I CALLED THIS MEETING BECAUSE  AS ALL YOU DRIVERS KNOW  THE NÜBURGRING IS THE MOST STUPID  BARBARIC  OUTDATED AND DANGEROUS TRACK IN THE WORLD</pattern><template>You've all seen the rain that has been falling today.</template></category><category><pattern>PRE SEASON TESTING</pattern><template>You're relentless.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS AN INCREDIBLE BATTLE BETWEEN NIKI LAUDA   IN THE RED FERRARI AND JAMES HUNT   IN THE WHITE HESKETH       THE CHALLENGE OF NIKI LAUDA      LAUDA ATTACKING HUNT  HE GETS THROUGH ON THE INSIDE    GOES WIDE AT THE EXIT    HUNT IS PAST AGAIN    ONCE MORE  LAUDA TRIES TO SNEAK UP THE INSIDE    THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY SIDE BY SIDE  WHEEL TO WHEEL    SO EVENLY MATCHED    FANTASTIC BATTLE BETWEEN THESE TWO GREAT DRIVERS    HUNT IS NOW AHEAD ONCE MORE    BUT LAUDA'S COMING BACK AGAIN NOW    LAUDA ONCE MORE SNEAKS UP THE INSIDE    AND AGAIN HE RUNS WIDE</pattern><template>Again the Hesketh...    Suzy, we're ready, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>APART FROM THE REAR BRAKES ARE WORN OUT  THE FRONT RIGHT TYRE IS A BIT SOFT  WHICH EXPLAINS WHY YOU'RE WEAVING SO MUCH</pattern><template>How can you tell?</template></category><category><pattern>AH  WHAT MUSIC</pattern><template>They could never have imagined it, those pioneers who invented the automobile, that it would possess us like this, in our imaginations, our dreams.</template></category><category><pattern>AND FOR GOING ALL NIGHT AND ALL DAY AND ALL NIGHT AGAIN IN BED</pattern><template>He's a good driver, but an immortal fuck apparently.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER BETTER  PATRON</pattern><template>Have a gargle with this.</template></category><category><pattern>TEN MINUTES</pattern><template>Arsehole.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  START HER UP</pattern><template>Ah! What music!</template></category><category><pattern>FINE  THANKS</pattern><template>Well done, Superstar!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YEAH</pattern><template>I know exactly.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I DID</pattern><template>Oh, come on, James.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THANK YOU  GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>What was Regazzoni's time?</template></category><category><pattern>RULES ARE RULES</pattern><template>Yes, and rats are rats.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT QUESTIONING YOUR TASTE</pattern><template>She is a great girl, but...</template></category><category><pattern>NOT IF YOU'RE LEADING</pattern><template>Trust me, this race is all about the start.</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES HUNT AND MCLAREN HAVE CAUGHT UP A LOT WHILE YOU WERE AWAY</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS  WASN'T HE</pattern><template>Did he go two seconds faster?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S OBVIOUS</pattern><template>Look at the tyre marks.</template></category><category><pattern>CHOP CHOP  DON'T WAIT TOO LONG</pattern><template>You don't want him to do what Lauda just did.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  IT'S THE DEADLINE FOR SECURING SPONSORSHIP FOR THE FORTHCOMING FORMULA 1 SEASON</pattern><template>Yes?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD'VE TAKEN MY ADVICE</pattern><template>Fuck off. Where's Niki?</template></category><category><pattern>HUNT HAS THE PIT LANE POLE POSITION    WHICH SHOULD GIVE HIM THE BEST CHANCE   OF OUTDRAGGING LAUDA'S FERRARI    IF EVER THERE WAS A DOUBT ABOUT   WHETHER LAUDA HAD A SERIOUS CHALLENGER TO THIS SEASON    HUNT AND HIS MCLAREN HAVE CERTAINLY GIVEN US THE ANSWER   BRAZIL LAUDA WINS HUNT HAS ENGINE FAILURE GRAND PRIX SOUTH AFRICA 76  HERE IN SOUTH AFRICA  JAMES HUNT IS DETERMINED   TO MAKE AMENDS AFTER THAT DISASTROUS RETIREMENT IN BRAZIL    BUT IT'S LAUDA WHO TAKES THE FLAG HERE AT KYALAMI    JAMES HUNT COMES HOME SECOND   TO CONFIRM HIS CHAMPIONSHIP CHALLENGE AT LAST   AND SCORE HIS FIRST POINTS OF THE SEASON   THAT WIND YOU CAN FEEL IS ME BREATHING DOWN YOUR NECK</pattern><template>Next time I'll have you.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MINUTE YOU DO THAT  YOU KILL WHAT'S GOOD ABOUT THIS</pattern><template>You kill the sport.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS YOU'RE A BAD BOY</pattern><template>Alexander doesn't know what he's talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST ONE SECOND</pattern><template>Can we go, yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>AGNES' LAST BOYFRIEND WAS A BRITISH FORMULA 2 DRIVER WHO HAS A REPUTATION FOR TWO THINGS  FOR BEING A LITTLE CRAZY ON THE TRACK</pattern><template>and for going all night and all day and all night again in bed.</template></category><category><pattern>SUZY HUNT RACES TO RICHARD BURTON CIRCUIT PAUL RICARD CHAMPIONNAT DU MONDE  WE HAVEN'T SEEN THIS SORT OF INTENSITY   FROM JAMES HUNT ALL SEASON LONG    REPORTS HAVE BEEN COMING OUT OF THE MCLAREN CAMP ALL WEEK   THAT THEIR CAR IS NOW FULLY LEGAL AND FASTER THAN EVER   FRANCE HUNT WINS LAUDA RETIRES  NEVER MIND THE BLOODY WETS</pattern><template>We're still quick.  BRITISH GRAND PRIX BRANDS HATCH SUNDAY 18TH JULY 1976  Hunt has really closed the gap on Lauda   as they head into Druids.   Niki Lauda is under real pressure from James Hunt   as they go up the hill into Druids Corner.   And Hunt is in front of Lauda!   So James Hunt gets the plaudits of the crowd,   the first Briton to win a British Grand Prix   at Brands Hatch since Jim Clark in 1964.  James, at the moment you've got a terrific edge over the rest,  how have you achieved this advantage?  Big balls.</template></category><category><pattern>THE RISKS WERE TOTALLY UNACCEPTABLE</pattern><template>You were prepared to die.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT SURE THAT WAS MEANT AS A COMPLIMENT</pattern><template>When do you start testing?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY OTHER LINE  LOOK  I'LL GET BACK TO YOU</pattern><template>Peter Hunt.</template></category><category><pattern>LOTUS 59</pattern><template>1000cc. Cosworth Mae engine.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DIDN'T WANNA TELL YOU BEFORE THE RACE</pattern><template>Tell me what?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THAT BAD  HUH</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>DID WHAT</pattern><template>Jesus! You crazy bastard!</template></category><category><pattern>IN HOSPITAL  I ASKED THEM STRAIGHT  NO BULLSHIT  HOW BAD MY APPEARANCE WOULD BE</pattern><template>They said with time it would be fine.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>About the race in Spain I won.</template></category><category><pattern>ROW 2 IS MIKE BEUTTLER AND DAVE MORGAN  WITH TONY TRIMMER AND GERRY BIRRELL</pattern><template>Who's that?</template></category><category><pattern>IMPOSSIBLE</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S</pattern><template>it's the Kraut.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT'S CRAZY</pattern><template>Why so heavy?</template></category><category><pattern>AT THE FRONT</pattern><template>Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>JUST PLAIN WHITE WITH THE FLAGS</pattern><template>And racing overalls which read  Sex. Breakfast of champions.  So when do we start?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT TRUE</pattern><template>Don't worry. I will be one day.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THAT CORNER HAD YOU</pattern><template>That move was total suicide.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  NOW PUT HIM IN MY CAR AND HE'LL GO 2 SECONDS FASTER</pattern><template>Well, that's impossible.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT  BLOODY HELL  HE'S RIGHT   NO SPONSORSHIP  SUPERSTAR</pattern><template>I hope you approve.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A V12 ENGINE</pattern><template>That lump weighs 190K on its own.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  HAVE A THINK  WORK OUT YOUR PRIORITIES AND GET BACK TO ME</pattern><template>Hey, Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD HELP ANYONE WHO WANTS MORE</pattern><template>And Richard Burton, will he be able to give you more?</template></category><category><pattern>TO LET THE CONDENSATION OUT</pattern><template>It'll also let the water in.</template></category><category><pattern>BY WHOM</pattern><template>Alexander.</template></category><category><pattern>HEADING INTO THE GRAND HOTEL HAIRPIN  SECOND GEAR    TURN IN HARD  LOOKING FOR LATE APEX    GENTLE WITH THE BAR    HEADING INTO PORTIER  SECOND GEAR    CLIP THE APEX    LIGHT BRAKE  STAY IN SECOND    LOOKING FOR A GOOD EXIT    HEADING THROUGH THE TUNNEL  GRADUAL RIGHT    UP THROUGH THIRD  FOURTH  FIFTH     LS ALEXANDER AROUND</pattern><template>Yes, he was.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE BEEN WORKING ON IT ALL NIGHT</pattern><template>Put Regazzoni in the car.</template></category><category><pattern>QUICK TOKE OF THIS</pattern><template>At Crystal Palace today, James Hunt's on pole, with Austrian newcomer Niki Lauda alongside him and Dave Walker completing Row 1.</template></category><category><pattern>FORGET IT</pattern><template>Make your own friends.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU  WHAT'S YOUR NAME</pattern><template>James Simon Wallis Hunt.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY GUY TO HAVE BURNT HIS FACE AND IT BE AN IMPROVEMENT</pattern><template>Of course he didn't listen to me.   For James, one world title was enough.   He had proved what he needed to prove,   to himself and anyone who doubted him.   And two years later he retired.   When I saw him next in London seven years later,   me as champion again,   him as broadcaster,   he was barefoot on a bicycle, with a flat tyre.   Still living each day like his last.   When I heard he'd died aged 45, of a heart attack,   I wasn't surprised.   I was just sad.   People always think of us as rivals,   but he was among the very few I liked   and even fewer that I respected.   He remains the only person I envied.  Born3o.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS  HOW DID THAT HAPPEN</pattern><template>Did he buy his way in there too?</template></category><category><pattern>LAUDA TAKES A LOOK DOWN THE INSIDE         AND HE'S SOLD HIM A DUMMY    LAUDA IS THROUGH</pattern><template>He's in the lead!   Hunt will be determined to make up for that mistake.   Hunt's in Lauda's slipstream.   Lauda's not leaving any gap.   The Lotus goes for the inside.   It's an aggressive move from Hunt.   There's contact!   The leaders have spun out!</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME GIVE YOU SOME ADVICE</pattern><template>I'm all ears.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK  KID</pattern><template>Good luck, James!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  START THE BASTARD</pattern><template>Good luck, kid.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE IS A GREAT GIRL  BUT</pattern><template>Agnes' last boyfriend was a British Formula 2 driver who has a reputation for two things, for being a little crazy on the track...</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GIVE ME THE DRIVE</pattern><template>Yeah, he can be a loose canon.</template></category><category><pattern>GLOVES  PLEASE</pattern><template>I'd say we push it...</template></category><category><pattern>FORTUNATELY A FEW HANDS HAVE ALREADY GONE UP  GOOD PEOPLE</pattern><template>Jacky Ickx.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT TIME I'LL HAVE YOU</pattern><template>We'll see in Spain.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY REASON WE TOOK YOU ON IS BECAUSE YOU'RE PAYING US</pattern><template>Well, as of now, if you want me to stay, we rip up the contract, I don't pay you a cent.</template></category><category><pattern>DOC POSTLETHWAITE  OUR DESIGNER</pattern><template>How do you do?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON  YOU ASSHOLES</pattern><template>This race has gone wrong for him so far.   His championship rival, James Hunt,   is a long way up the road.   Lauda passing car after car.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE YOU  SHOULD I KNOW YOU</pattern><template>What, you don't know?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE RELENTLESS</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE BOTH A PAIR OF KIDS WHEN WE MET</pattern><template>Hot headed jerks in Formula 3.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOT EVERYTHING TO LOSE</pattern><template>Mr. Lauda, are you feeling pressure?</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES SIMON WALLIS HUNT</pattern><template>Remember it, my little Jerry friend.</template></category><category><pattern>FOLLOWING AN INQUIRY INTO THE DISQUALIFICATION   OF DRIVER JAMES HUNT FROM THE SPANISH GRAND PRIX    IT HAS BEEN DECIDED TO OVERTURN THIS DISQUALIFICATION   AND TO RESTORE HIS VICTORY AND REINSTATE HIS POINTS   JAMES</pattern><template>A few weeks ago you were out of the running completely and now you're right back in it.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M QUICKER THAN JACKY</pattern><template>But he's consistent, dependable.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  WHAT DID HE DO</pattern><template>Got himself a drive, with BRM.</template></category><category><pattern>LAUDA IS CLEARLY FURIOUS    THERE'S EVERY REASON TO EXPECT SHARP WORDS IN THE PIT    IT'S GOING TO BE VICTORY FOR HUNT    IT'S GOING TO BE AN IGNOMINIOUS DEFEAT FOR NIKI LAUDA    SO JAMES HUNT SCORES HIS THIRD MAJOR FORMULA 3 WIN   OF THE SEASON HERE  AT CRYSTAL PALACE    AFTER A DESPERATE BATTLE WITH NIKI LAUDA    LAUDA WAS UNABLE SO RESTART   AFTER HUNT'S AGGRESSIVE MOVE CAUSED THEM BOTH TO SPIN OUT   IN THE LAST LAP OF THE RACE   HARD LUCK  BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME</pattern><template>Hey, asshole!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO GIVE IT TO MY FATHER AND TELL HIM TO PUT IT ON THE MANTELPIECE AND IMAGINE IT'S A FIRST CLASS DEGREE IN MEDICINE</pattern><template>Well done, Superstar.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  OF COURSE</pattern><template>I have the better car.</template></category><category><pattern>IS JAMES HUNT</pattern><template>Superb news!</template></category><category><pattern>AND ALEXANDER  LORD HESKETH  THE TEAM'S OWNER</pattern><template>How do you do?</template></category><category><pattern>ON  CHRIST</pattern><template>I need a drive, Pete. I need you to find me a drive.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT'S ALL BULLSHIT</pattern><template>So what brings you here?</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN DO YOU START TESTING</pattern><template>Next week?</template></category><category><pattern>1 INTO THE PIT    SOME SORT OF PROBLEM  WE CAN'T IMAGINE WHAT    SO EARLY IN THE RACE   WHAT'S WRONG WITH THE CAR</pattern><template>What's wrong with the car?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN YOU TELL</pattern><template>My ass.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KILL THE SPORT</pattern><template>James!</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WE STAY ON WETS TOO</pattern><template>Niki, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>AND SINCE THE ECONOMICS OF F1 ARE NOT SO SIGNIFICANTLY DIFFERENT TO THE ECONOMICS OF F2  WELL  WE THOUGHT IF WE WERE GOING TO BE LOSING MONEY  WE MIGHT AS WELL BE DOING IT ON THE BIG ROULETTE TABLE IN F1</pattern><template>You fat, little, inbred beauty.</template></category><category><pattern>BOLOGNA  ITALY   WHERE ARE YOU GOING</pattern><template>You lot go ahead.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S LETHAL OUT THERE</pattern><template>The race is going ahead.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY HAVE YOU COME HERE  JAMES</pattern><template>I've got to get you back.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKING GOOD</pattern><template>What's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES HUNT REJOINS THE RACE IN SIXTH POSITION    THERE ARE FOUR LAPS TO GO</pattern><template>Surely no way back for the Brit.  Concentrate, Superstar.</template></category><category><pattern>TRENTO'S HALF AN HOUR'S DRIVE</pattern><template>Get in.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M THE ONLY PERSON IN HISTORY TO DO THE RING IN UNDER 7 MIN   SO  ACTUALLY  IT'S TO MY ADVANTAGE TO RACE HERE TODAY</pattern><template>Because I'm quicker than all of you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE HAD ANOTHER RETIREMENT TODAY</pattern><template>What's going wrong?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT ME</pattern><template>If I had more talent and could earn better money with something else, I would.</template></category><category><pattern>CHAMP</pattern><template>You look good, Niki.</template></category><category><pattern>I PROMISE IT'LL BE WORTH IT</pattern><template>Just keep them closed.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S CHANGED</pattern><template>It's a combination of factors, not all of which I'm prepared to discuss here.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY EVERYBODY LIKES YOU</pattern><template>Try saying that and tell me you're not jealous.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA MAKE SURE THIS THING IS LEGAL  NO DOUBTS</pattern><template>Then we'd better move the oil coolers to the old position.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK OFF  WHERE'S NIKI</pattern><template>Behind you. He made the same mistake.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MORNING</pattern><template>Clay!</template></category><category><pattern>LEVEL PLAYING FIELD NOW  MY RALLY LITTLE FRIEND</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING WRONG</pattern><template>It's dirty politics and dirty tricks, that's what's going wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>AND KEEN TO MAKE AN IMPRESSION</pattern><template>So let's see where Mr. Reutemann finishes and where I finish today.</template></category><category><pattern>AND POSSIBLY I'M THE BETTER DRIVER</pattern><template>But he's a clever guy and he's used his time well while I was lying half dead in hospital while I was lying half dead in hospital to win some points.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD</pattern><template>Pleasure.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR ESTEEMED LEAD DRIVER</pattern><template>Fitti fucking paldi.</template></category><category><pattern>INTERMITTENT HEAVY RAIN HAS BEEN FORECAST   HERE AT FUJI TODAY  ALONG WITH STRONG WINDS   AND OCCASIONAL FOG   ROLLING IN FROM THE MOUNTAIN    AND SO WITH TODAY'S JAPANESE GRAND PRIX TO COME    LAUDA'S LEAD A MERE THREE POINTS    WHAT A WAY TO FINISH THE SEASON    HUNT OR LAUDA    THE FINAL CHAPTER WILL UNFOLD WHEN WE BRING YOU EXTENDED COVERAGE     THEY'VE GOT TO CANCEL THE RACE</pattern><template>It's lethal out there.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  VISUALIZATION TECHNIQUES  MEMORISING THE CIRCUIT  IN THIS CASE MONACO  WHICH IS UP NEXT</pattern><template>Personally I've always been a great believer in getting there on the day, putting my foot down and playing chicken with everyone else.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU CALL A FRIENDLY DISAGREEMENT WITH ANOTHER DRIVER AN ACCIDENT</pattern><template>What did you disagree about?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  TRUST ME  WATCHING YOU WIN THOSE RACES  WHILE I WAS FIGHTING FOR MY LIFE</pattern><template>you were equally responsible for getting me back in the car.</template></category><category><pattern>GET ME OUT</pattern><template>Help me!</template></category></AIML>