<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern/><template>teacher with tenure.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT THAT'S EASIER SAID THAN DONE</pattern><template>You have to do it. You have no choice. Excelsior.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  TOMMY  TOMMY  YES  YES  I GOT YOUR WHOLE SHEET</pattern><template>Mom. Yeah. No, no...</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN  LET'S GO  PATTY  COME ON  PAT</pattern><template>Alright, let's see the scores for Solatano and Maxwell.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN     STOP</pattern><template>Pat!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  DO YOU FEEL THAT  THAT'S EMOTION</pattern><template>I don't feel anything.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HOW ARE THE PEOPLE YOU'RE COMPETING AGAINST</pattern><template>They're good. Some of them are professionals.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT'S FOR THE BEST</pattern><template>... but if it was me reading the signs...   That's it. Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  WHOA  WHOA  I'M NOT GONNA FUCKIN' DANCE WITH YOU</pattern><template>What are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY YOU CAME HOME</pattern><template>Embrace it! Embrace it!</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T MEAN IT AT ALL</pattern><template>I know, you say shit you don't mean all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T DISAPPEAR DOING GOD KNOWS WHAT WITH THAT TIFFANY MAXWELL</pattern><template>Dad, Dad, Dad. She's my friend. Why would you say that?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THOSE FUCKING DANCERS</pattern><template>You can give me the money now, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A FOUR POINT NINE  FOUR EIGHT  A FOUR NINE</pattern><template>That's really too bad, guys. That's a lot of fours.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE ONLY ANSWER  NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>Dolores, somebody was in my study.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  JESUS</pattern><template>It's like,  What? What day is it?  How about Trazodone?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A PERFECT THING  I'M GONNA FIND HER AND MAYBE I'LL GO IN THERE</pattern><template>We never  ... ... fuck in the shower anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S HAVE A GOOD ENDING TO THE STORY   PAT  YOU OWE US AN APOLOGY</pattern><template>Mom, for what, I can't apologize.</template></category><category><pattern>MOM  IT'S A GOOD THING</pattern><template>I'm remaking myself.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT'S THE ONE</pattern><template>Don't let them hurt your feelings.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO TELL HIM NIKKI'S GONNA BE THERE</pattern><template>We have to tell him that she's going.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF YOU TOLD NIKKI WHEN VERONICA WAS IN THE BATHROOM</pattern><template>Yes. Yes, that could work. I love that.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT NIKKI</pattern><template>Don't look up until you're halfway here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW SOMETHING  IT'S NOTHING NEW  YOUR TEAM DOES THAT ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>They get close... and then they blow it. They got an inferiority complex.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY DRINKS HAVE YOU HAD</pattern><template>I've had two vodkas. Listen, I don't know what choices you've made, but you gotta deal with it right now, okay? We're in this.</template></category><category><pattern>GODDAMN IT  I KNEW IT  IT WAS A TEST  HOW DID I DO</pattern><template>I think I did pretty well.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  YOU'RE UP TO SOMETHING  I KNOW</pattern><template>People like Tiffany, or Danny, or me, maybe we know something that you guys don't know, okay? Did you ever think about that? Maybe we understand something because we're more  We have a sixth sense. I mean, everybody's got it. Everybody's just not in touch with it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OKAY</pattern><template>I'm not okay. Don't tell anybody. Listen to me.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  MOM  CAN WE GIVE DANNY A RIDE TO NORTH PHILLY</pattern><template>What? I don't understand.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS VERY DEPRESSED AFTER TOMMY DIED  IT WAS A LOT OF PEOPLE</pattern><template>We don't have to talk about it.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  GUYS  THE BABY IS SLEEPING</pattern><template>Sorry. I don't wanna wake up the baby. Bye.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S TIFFANY  SHE LEFT</pattern><template>What do you mean, she left?</template></category><category><pattern>EXCELSIOR  EXCELSIOR  WHAT DOES THAT MEAN</pattern><template>It means you know what I'm gonna do, I'm gonna take all this negativity and use it as fuel and I'm gonna find a silver lining, that's what I'm gonna do.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER I TOLD YOU ABOUT MY BROTHER  HE HAD A JHERI CURL  AND I COULDN'T GET A JHERI CURL BECAUSE MY HAIR DIDN'T GROW LONG ENOUGH</pattern><template>I was so jealous of my brother...</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH I WAS WEARING THAT JERSEY</pattern><template>I feel like an idiot.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A MESSED UP THING</pattern><template>I'm sorry, but that's...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M THE REASON WHY TODAY HAPPENED</pattern><template>I think so. Let's talk about that.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I KNOW</pattern><template>You do.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THE ARGUING KIND</pattern><template>And the scores for Santos and Aguilar are: seven point six, seven point three, seven point four, and six point nine for an average score of seven point three.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE PEOPLE  THIS IS A HIGH  END DANCE CONTEST  I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>Do not put it as part of the parlay, Randy. Don't   They go by the Philadelphia rules.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  WOW  WOW  FASCINATING</pattern><template>Sorry. I don't wanna be mean.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  IT'S GONNA BE GREAT</pattern><template>Nikki's gonna be there. You know?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS SCARED FOR YOUR MOTHER AND YOU HURT HIM AS WELL</pattern><template>Yes, last night was a mess. Okay? And I think he probably just tried to do his best.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DIDN'T CONVERT ME TO MY MENTAL HYGIENE LAW ADMISSION STATUS WITHIN TWO THIRDS OF THE MAXIMUM LENGTH OF MY FELONY SENTENCE  SO I'M OUT  THEY HAD TO LET ME GO</pattern><template>I never understand what he's saying.</template></category><category><pattern>I BELIEVE IN YOU  PATTY  I BELIEVE IN YOU  I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT</pattern><template>So I'm gonna bet heavy on this game.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>Hey, is he messing with you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED TO PIPE DOWN</pattern><template>Everything all right?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHAT I LEARNED IN THE HOSPITAL</pattern><template>You have to do everything you can, you have to work your hardest, and if you do, if you stay positive, you have a shot at a silver lining.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY'D YOU RUN BY MY HOUSE</pattern><template>Did our little conversation get you upset last night?</template></category><category><pattern>DESEAN JACKSON  WHAT HAPPENED TO DESEAN JACKSON</pattern><template>Come on, tell me that one.</template></category><category><pattern>TIFFANY  THIS IS DANNY</pattern><template>Hello. Pat told me about you. So is the girl, that you wrote about?</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE WE SHOULD CALL THE FBI</pattern><template>Don't make fun. This is serious.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ARE YOU  YOU OKAY  GOOD  HOW ARE YOU  I'M REALLY GOOD  YEAH  THANKS</pattern><template>You looked really happy out there. Did I?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  DON'T WRITE IT UP</pattern><template>I don't want her to see this!</template></category><category><pattern>SO YEAH  I SNAPPED  I ALMOST BEAT HIM TO DEATH  BUT NOW I GET FUCKING CHASTISED FOR IT  I'M PARALLEL TO MY FATHER  I DON'T THINK SO</pattern><template>All right. Can you talk about something that you did, before or after?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S IT</pattern><template>That's it. There you go. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER  WAIT A SECOND  I DO LIKE THE IDEA OF A PARLAY</pattern><template>What? No parlay! No! No, don't do it. Don't do it.</template></category><category><pattern>UPSTAIRS  IT'S A GARAGE  I JUST RENOVATED IT  YOU KNOW  I WAS THINKING ABOUT PUTTING A BALLET BARRE HERE</pattern><template>When are you gonna give it to her?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT     YOU'RE ASKING ME  YOU'RE REALLY ASKING ME THAT QUESTION</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>FOOTBALL STAYS OUT OF THIS PLACE  SO DOES  LORD OF THE FLIES    WAIT  WAIT  NO  NO  NO  WHAT ARE YOU DOING  I'M BEHIND ON MY SYLLABUS</pattern><template>I don't give a fuck. What the hell are you doing? Hey, hey!</template></category><category><pattern>DAD'S GOT YOU SITTING HERE</pattern><template>Oh, yeah. He calls me  Jailhouse Lawyer.   Hold the remote the way you were holding it before.</template></category><category><pattern>IF ONE OF YOUR TWO SUPERVISING PHYSICIANS LOSES THEIR LICENSE  THEN YOUR WHOLE AJUDICATION IS THROWN OUT</pattern><template>How'd you know we were here?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE HERE EVERY WEEK  NO</pattern><template>Uh, Jake you better get your brother.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE MIDDLE OF THE WALL</pattern><template>We have a port in every room. Gimme an iPod.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA GO ON A TOUR NOW</pattern><template>Let's go see the house.</template></category><category><pattern>IT CAN STILL BE A DATE IF YOU ORDER RAISIN BRAN</pattern><template>It's not a date. So how's your thing going... your dancing thing?</template></category><category><pattern>TIFF  I'M SORRY  I CAN'T DO ANYTHING ELSE WITHOUT READING NIKKI'S LETTER  OKAY  IT'S JUST     IT'S IN THE BACK OF MY HEAD</pattern><template>We don't almost have it, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WANTED ME TO BE PASSIONATE AND COMPASSIONATE  AND THAT'S A GOOD THING  YOU KNOW  I JUST  LOOK  I'M MY BEST SELF TODAY  AND I THINK SHE'S HER BEST SELF TODAY  AND OUR LOVE'S GONNA BE FUCKING AMAZING</pattern><template>It's gonna be amazing, and you're gonna be amazing, and she's gonna be amazing, and you're not gonna be that guy that's gonna take advantage of a situation without offering to do something back.</template></category><category><pattern>PICK ME UP AT SEVEN THIRTY</pattern><template>Happy Halloween.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GONNA APOLOGIZE FOR THIS</pattern><template>You know what I will do? I will apologize on behalf of Ernest Hemingway, because that's who's to blame here.</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  I CAN'T  LOOK  I'M READY TO GO</pattern><template>Spend family time. Wait, you mean OCD, superstitious time?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I MEAN  I HOPE SO</pattern><template>Maybe you can teach us both, you know what I mean?</template></category><category><pattern>'CAUSE WE'RE GONNA BE BETTER THAN EVER    NIKKI  JUST PRACTICING</pattern><template>How'd Tommy die?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I ASK YOU ONE MORE QUESTION</pattern><template>Were there any women?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  LISTEN  SIR</pattern><template>He's chasing me! This guy's chasing me! Help me!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  THIS IS MY ROUTE  OKAY  JUST BACK OFF</pattern><template>This is my neighborhood.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  STOP IT  STOP IT  STOP IT</pattern><template>I can't watch my wedding video, but I CAN hear the fucking song Mom?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THE SEX PISTOLS  THE CLASH  GOT SOME CLASH</pattern><template>Oh,  West Side Story.   Yeah,  West Side Story.   It makes me peaceful.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA GIVE IT A CHIROPRACTIC ADJUSTMENT</pattern><template>Enough with awkwardness! I don't wanna walk in your house and not be able to say what I wanna say.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO  HOW YOU DOING  PAT  JESUS</pattern><template>I guess his sixth sense forgot to tell him the cops were coming.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GET WOBBLY ON ME  I'M NOT</pattern><template>We have a dance to do. We have a parlay. You gotta stay focused.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE THE ONE  YEAH  YOU'RE THE ONE  PAT</pattern><template>Superstition, Danny. I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE MEANT TO BE HERE</pattern><template>This is special. Everything happens for a reason.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T WANT TO WAKE YOU  BUT I NEEDED AN ENVELOPE</pattern><template>You didn't want to wake me?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  MISTER EXCELSIOR  YOU WANNA BE POSITIVE  BE POSITIVE  SIT DOWN</pattern><template>All right, all right.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AN EAGLES FAN</pattern><template>Well then, what's the problem? He's not goin' anywhere. Just let him finish the game, that's all. The handkerchief is working. We're killing the Seahawks, twenty seventen.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  LAST NIGHT WAS A MESS  OKAY  AND I THINK HE PROBABLY JUST TRIED TO DO HIS BEST</pattern><template>Pat, you have to have a strategy. I told you earlier.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OFF ME  DAD</pattern><template>Stop hitting him!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THANK GOD  FINALLY</pattern><template>DeSean Jackson. Yeah. Did it fit?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S SAYING YOU'RE BEING RUDE</pattern><template>How am I being rude?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  MAN</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU</pattern><template>You shut the fuck up!</template></category><category><pattern>CUCKOO BIRD'S TAKIN' OFF  DOCTOR PATEL</pattern><template>Pat! Hey! What are you doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>VERONICA DIDN'T LIKE IT</pattern><template>Veronica hates the jersey.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T  I CAN'T DO IT</pattern><template>What do you mean, you can't do it? You can't do what?</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  PAT  THAT'S ILLEGAL</pattern><template>Pat, today I'm your brother in green, not your therapist. I'm so happy to see you. How wonderful that you are here!</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD BE SO AMAZING IF YOU COULD GET A LETTER TO NIKKI FROM ME</pattern><template>I'd have to hide it from Veronica.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER THE DINNER AT RONNIE'S  SHE SAID  QUOTE   WE CAN GO TO THE BACK HOUSE AND YOU CAN FUCK ME AS LONG AS WE TURN THE LIGHTS OUT    UNQUOTE  AND SHE STILL WEARS HER WEDDING RING</pattern><template>So she's a loyal, married to a dead guy slut.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU NEED ANYTHING    MY CARD</pattern><template>Thank you. Sorry. We understand.</template></category><category><pattern>BYE  EXCELSIOR  PAT</pattern><template>Excelsior! That's my man. Lets go!</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SUB  I'LL WORK HISTORY  WHATEVER YOU WANT</pattern><template>Here, let me give you a hand.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT YOU KNOW WHAT  NO DISRESPECT  IT'S NOT PERSONAL  BUT THIS IS THE TIME TO STRIKE</pattern><template>You start snapping up commercial real estate... cheap... flip it over, you flip it over and that's when you make the money.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  CALM DOWN  THANK ABOUT IT  SEE YOU LATER</pattern><template>Pat, no. What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  COME ON  PLEASE</pattern><template>Calm down, crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>TIFFANY  WHAT'S THAT</pattern><template>What? No, no, no, no. You're crazy to give away that many points. That's ridiculous!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  WHAT IS IT  WHAT IS IT  WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>Can I say something? Do you mind? No.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT SONG REALLY PLAYING</pattern><template>We have music sometimes.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES I HEAR IT WHEN IT'S NOT EVEN PLAYING</pattern><template>Wow.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD ONE INCIDENT  ONE INCIDENT CAN CHANGE A LIFETIME</pattern><template>But I'm ready. I'm ready to take responsibility for my side of the street.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE VERY  VERY MUCH IN LOVE  OKAY  JUST LIKE YOU TWO</pattern><template>Listen, Patrick, she's gone. She's not around anymore. Nikki left.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  BEING OF SERVICE</pattern><template>Yeah. To your need. Uh huh.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  SHE MIGHT BE WITH THAT GUY</pattern><template>That, the...</template></category><category><pattern>GIMME A BREAK  GIMME ME A BREAK</pattern><template>We can't get five! Give 'em a five. Give 'em a five.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GONNA GO ANYWHERE</pattern><template>Don't get in a fight!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  AND NOW YOU'RE HOLDING THE REMOTE</pattern><template>And it's working. Your dad's a genius.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  OKAY  I WAS JUST SUGGESTING THAT MAYBE THERE'S A BETTER SCENARIO</pattern><template>Why don't you walk towards me like I'm Nikki.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM YOUR BOOKMAKING</pattern><template>Who told you that? Mom told me. Outside.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DO YOU SLEEP</pattern><template>Upstairs. It's a garage, I just renovated it. You know, I was thinking about putting a ballet barre here.</template></category><category><pattern>I WORE IT TO RONNIE'S FOR DINNER</pattern><template>Beautiful jersey. I love that jersey.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>What was that like?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE'S A FUN FACT  YOU KNOW WHERE THE TERM  OK  COMES FROM</pattern><template>No. No, I don't.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO  WHO DOESN'T HAVE AN IPOD</pattern><template>Well, I don't have an iPod.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FELT IT  I FELT IT  DON'T LIE  WE'RE NOT LIARS LIKE THEY ARE</pattern><template>I live in the addition around back, which is completely separate from my parents' house, so there's no chance of them walking in on us. I hate the fact that you wore a football jersey to dinner because I hate football, but you can fuck me if you turn the lights off, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  NO  NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>Double or nothing on the Bengals, next week? Is that what you're saying?</template></category><category><pattern>OOH  OOH  WARMER  WARMER  WARMER</pattern><template>...it's a drawer at a morgue where they pull out dead bodies and shoot them with formaldehyde.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT IT  AHH  WELL  WE GOT THAT</pattern><template>We don't want them to steal that.</template></category><category><pattern>HAPPY HALLOWEEN</pattern><template>Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  I'M DOING IT WITH MY PHYSICALITY  I'VE BEEN WORKIN' OUT  THAT'S WHAT I'M DOIN'</pattern><template>Why is he wearing a garbage bag?</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR SON WAS TRYING TO  IT'S ALL FUCKING RUINED NOW  IT'S ALL RUINED</pattern><template>No, Dad! It's all fucking ruined now! It's all fucking ruined!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T WANT TO WAKE ME</pattern><template>He didn't want to wake me.</template></category><category><pattern>DOLORES  WOULD YOU STOP HIM  JESUS</pattern><template>How could you not take that bet?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT  WE'RE NOT A PART OF IT</pattern><template>There are people, this is a high  end dance contest. I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE SAID TO SHOW HER SOMETHING  PAT  THIS DANCE CAN BE THAT SOMETHING  YOU WOULD HAVE NEVER DONE SOMETHING LIKE THIS IN A MILLION YEARS  IT SHOWS ALL KINDS OF SKILLS ON SO MANY DIFFERENT LEVELS: FOCUS  COLLABORATION  DISCIPLINE  IT'S ROMANTIC  LIKE I SAID IT WOULD BE  IT'S FOR HER</pattern><template>Thanks for the letter.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE KILLING ME  YOU'RE KILLING ME</pattern><template>Tiffany, please. She'll see how well he's doing, maybe she'll lift the restraining order.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I USE YOUR PHONE</pattern><template>Is it an emergency?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD TURN AROUND  TOO  THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH THAT</pattern><template>Yeah. You're pretty good. Mm, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T THINK I COULD'VE BEAT THE SHIT OUT OF HIM  I MEAN</pattern><template>He was scared for your mother and you hurt him as well.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MEANS YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GONNA DO  I'M GONNA TAKE ALL THIS NEGATIVITY AND USE IT AS FUEL AND I'M GONNA FIND A SILVER LINING  THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO</pattern><template>And that's no bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>MOM  NO  IT'LL BE FINE  IT'LL BE FINE</pattern><template>I guess everybody's leaving today!</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE TIME  I'LL STILL GIVE YOUR LETTER TO NIKKI  DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>Wow. I really appreciate that, Tiffany.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU'RE NOT GONNA READ THAT SHIT ON MY TIME  I CAN TELL YOU ALL ABOUT THE  LORD OF THE FLIES    IT'S A BUNCH OF BOYS ON AN ISLAND AND THEY HAVE A CONCH    THEY HAVE A SHELL     AND WHOEVER HAS THE CONCH HAS THE POWER AND THEY CAN TALK</pattern><template>And if you don't have the conch, then you don't have the power. And then there's a little chubby boy, and they call him Piggy and they're really mean, and then there's a murder. I mean, humanity is just nasty and there's no silver lining.</template></category><category><pattern>SUPERSTITION  DANNY  I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>Come sit down.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM WHY  BECAUSE HE BELIEVES IN YOU  IS THAT TRUE</pattern><template>I believe in you, Patty. I believe in you. I want you to know that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU SO UP ABOUT</pattern><template>He's very happy. I'm happy.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YEAH  RIGHT  HMM</pattern><template>I just wanted to, maybe I didn't, spend enough time with you growing up. I spent too much time with your brother. It might have made you feel worse about your behavior, but I didn't know anything, I didn't know how to handle it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT  WHAT'S THE GOOD NEWS</pattern><template>Things are looking up.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DO  YEAH  SURE  I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW  WITH THE LETTER</pattern><template>I'll bet I know what happened if only one is missing.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I WAS ON XANAX AND EFFEXOR  BUT I AGREE  I WASN'T AS SHARP  SO I STOPPED  YOU EVER TAKE KLONOPIN</pattern><template>Klonopin? Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID   JUST CUT IT THE WAY YOU CUT IT      ONCE YOU GET IN THE RIGHT FRAME OF MIND  I THINK ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE</pattern><template>I think we get, we so often get caught in this state of negativity and it's a, it's a poison like nothing else.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  NO  NO  NO  NO  YOU'RE CRAZY TO GIVE AWAY THAT MANY POINTS  THAT'S RIDICULOUS</pattern><template>I won't take that!</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  DO US A FAVOR  DON'T READ FOR A WHILE</pattern><template>What are you wearing a garbage bag for? I'm gonna go run now.</template></category><category><pattern>I USED THE INSURANCE MONEY TO BUILD THIS  I DESIGNED IT  ALL THE FLOORS ARE HARD OAK  IT HAS GOOD BOUNCE FOR DANCERS  WOW</pattern><template>I'm not that great of a dancer, but who cares? It's therapy and it's fun. And the walls are good 'cause I can play music really loud without anybody hearing.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST  JUST SORT OF COME IN  PAT  COME IN LIKE THIS  AND</pattern><template>Okay. Yeah. Can you move 'em a little bit more? Yeah, that's it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS A PLEA BARGAIN WITH THE COURTS</pattern><template>The lawyer, he instructed me, he said that what we should plead that, and then I would serve eight months and then I'd get out.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU KNOW  I DIDN'T APPROVE WHEN YOU CALLED HER AND YOU TOLD HER WHERE HE WAS RUNNING  SO SHE COULD AMBUSH HIM  I DIDN'T APPROVE OF THAT  BUT YOU DID IT ANYWAY  SO I'M DOING THIS ANYWAY  THAT'S IT</pattern><template>We're gonna tell him Nikki'll be there.</template></category><category><pattern>I START FUCKING SMASHING SHIT</pattern><template>You gotta get your marriage together.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S BETTING EVERYTHING ON THE GIANT GAME  EVERYTHING</pattern><template>All the money that he needs for the restaurant, he's betting on the Giant game.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS MY WEDDING SONG AND WHEN I HEAR IT  I GO KINDA CRAZY</pattern><template>Sometimes I hear it when it's not even playing.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  COME ON  DAD  BE NICE  COME ON  SHE'S MAKING CRABBY SNACKS AND HOMEMADES  COME ON  DAD</pattern><template>What are you so up about?</template></category><category><pattern>DEAR PAT  IT WAS VERY EMOTIONAL FOR ME TO GET YOUR LETTER  AS I'M SURE YOU CAN IMAGINE  BUT I'M GLAD YOU TOOK THE RISK OF DISCREETLY GETTING IT TO ME THROUGH TIFFANY</pattern><template>This gives us a chance to communicate while I keep the restraining order until I feel safe.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  CAN HE MAKE IT</pattern><template>I don't know yet! Can you make it next Sunday?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOKED REALLY HAPPY OUT THERE  DID I</pattern><template>Yeah. Yeah, who'd have thought, dancing?</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE SUNDAYS  I LIVE FOR SUNDAYS</pattern><template>The whole family's together. Mom makes braciole. Dad puts the jersey on.</template></category><category><pattern>I KINDA GOT THAT FEELING  YEAH</pattern><template>Goddamn it. I knew it. It was a test. How did I do?</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING</pattern><template>Let me just ask you something.</template></category><category><pattern>NANCE  THIS IS MY LUCKY DAY</pattern><template>Look at you working on a Sunday!</template></category><category><pattern>PUT ON THE JERSEY AND STAY  PLEASE</pattern><template>Please. It's important, please.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  GUYS  HOW'S IT GOING</pattern><template>Hey. Is Tiffany home? Go away.</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  LISTEN TO ME  I DIDN'T KNOW THAT  EXCELSIOR  WAS THE STATE MOTTO OF NEW YORK  OKAY</pattern><template>I didn't know, either, but now I know.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  WHOA  WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Stay back, Pat. Stay back.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  THAT WOULD BE AMAZING IF WE GOT FIVE  LET'S NOT GET AWAY  OH  COME ON  WE CAN GET A FIVE OUT OF TEN</pattern><template>Gimme a break! Gimme me a break!</template></category><category><pattern>NOT FOR DINNER</pattern><template>Look, he got us flowers.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCELSIOR  THAT'S MY MAN  LETS GO</pattern><template>Pat. Patty.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LIED TO ME  PAT</pattern><template>Danny's not allowed to leave.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THAT'S SWEET  THAT'S SWEET  PAT  THAT'S LOVELY</pattern><template>And wine.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T TELL DAD YOU WERE PICKING ME UP</pattern><template>Don't worry about that. I wanna make sure when you come out that you're okay, and she didn't say anything.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD  OH  MY GOD</pattern><template>Pat told me. He told me you should never throw a marriage out the window.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP TALKING ABOUT ME IN THIRD PERSON</pattern><template>You can take Tiffany home first.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING  COME ON  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>What are you doing to these kids?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST SEE THAT YOU MADE AN EFFORT AND I'M GONNA BE BETTER WITH MY WIFE  I'M WORKING ON THAT  I WANNA ACKNOWLEDGE HER BEAUTY</pattern><template>I never used to do that. I do that now.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IT'S A LITTLE LIE</pattern><template>There's no other way.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT THAT GUY</pattern><template>He got kicked out of that stadium he beat up so many people at Eagles games, he's on the exclusion list.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  FROM THE LOONEY BIN</pattern><template>What the fuck?! I talked to you about that already!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T TELL ME  THE COURT SAID YES  DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>Yeah, but what did the doctor say? Because the, the court listens to the doctor.</template></category><category><pattern>HEAVY  I WANT YOU TO GO TO THE GAME WITH YOUR BROTHER</pattern><template>You want me to go to the game with Jake?</template></category><category><pattern>HUH  NO  IT'S ALRIGHT</pattern><template>He's a good dude! He's a good dude.</template></category><category><pattern>EVER SINCE  EVER SINCE HE WAS WITH YOU  EVER SINCE  YOU THINK THAT I'M WHY TODAY'S HAPPENED</pattern><template>That's right, you are why today happened.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL UNDER CONTROL</pattern><template>Well... okay, okay. Congratulations.</template></category><category><pattern>UNDIAGNOSED BIPOLAR</pattern><template>Yeah. With mood swings and weird thinking brought on by severe stress, which rarely happens, thank God.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS WITH YOU  HE WAS WITH ME  WE WENT FOR A RUN</pattern><template>Really? That's crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>THE REMOTES LIKE THIS</pattern><template>Did you do this, Randy?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE YOU UP THERE  OKAY  OKAY</pattern><template>Hey, Pat, Tiffany!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVEN'T EVEN SEEN US DANCE</pattern><template>That's the parlay.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE YOU HAVE A RESTRAINING ORDER</pattern><template>What good are you, man?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE MARRIED  SO AM I</pattern><template>No, that's confusing. He's dead.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE FAITH  I HAVE FAITH</pattern><template>Excelsior belongs in this house  Dad   ... not in the State of New York. In this house.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GONNA GO YOUR WHOLE LIFE SCARED OF THAT SONG</pattern><template>It's just a song.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK IS THE MATTER WITH YOU  GIVE IT TO HER YOURSELF</pattern><template>Let me say something. You don't ever have to see me again if you just read it, alright?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY IS HE WEARING A GARBAGE BAG</pattern><template>Why are you wearing a garbage bag?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HAD TO BE HARD</pattern><template>Yeah. It's a lot to deal with, especially when you don't know what the hell is happening, which I do now. Sort of.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  YOU ARE DONE</pattern><template>It takes the light right out of your eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU'RE NOT MESSING UP THE JUJU  BUT THE JUJU IS MESSED UP BECAUSE I'M NOT WITH HIM DURING THE GAMES</pattern><template>Guess what? What?</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE I DO  DOES HE WANT ME TO GO</pattern><template>Of course he wants you to go.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  OKAY  THAT'S IT</pattern><template>Why? What is it, what is it, what is it.</template></category><category><pattern>RANDY  TELL HIM WHAT I'M DOING</pattern><template>He's betting everything on the Giant game. Everything.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOU WANT ANOTHER ONE  SURE</pattern><template>So what do you do? I'm a lawyer. Litigator, actually.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  MY SISTER IN LAW TIFFANY</pattern><template>You look nice.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  ARE YOU BEING  A TROUBLEMAKER</pattern><template>You know, you look good.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE ARE AGAIN AT THE ONE YARD LINE  DESEAN  SNATCHING DEFEAT FROM THE JAWS OF VICTORY  THERE YOU GO</pattern><template>What does that even mean, Dad?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHUT THE FUCK UP</pattern><template>Tiffany! Hey! Tiffany!</template></category><category><pattern>VERONICA HATES THE JERSEY</pattern><template>Whatever you do, watch out for that restraining order, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANTED TO  MAYBE I DIDN'T  SPEND ENOUGH TIME WITH YOU GROWING UP  I SPENT TOO MUCH TIME WITH YOUR BROTHER  IT MIGHT HAVE MADE YOU FEEL WORSE ABOUT YOUR BEHAVIOR  BUT I DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING  I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO HANDLE IT</pattern><template>I mean, that's what all this Eagles stuff is about. It's about us, spending time now. I wanna do everything I can to help you get back on your feet. That's the whole point. Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  GO SEE TANYA  GOOD IDEA</pattern><template>Okay, man, hey. I'm gonna be there, man. I want you guys to win!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU WORE A JERSEY TO DINNER</pattern><template>Isn't it awesome?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT AT ALL LIKE ME AND NIKKI</pattern><template>What are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON</pattern><template>I can't, I can't do it.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCELSIOR BELONGS IN THIS HOUSE  DAD       NOT IN THE STATE OF NEW YORK  IN THIS HOUSE</pattern><template>Dad, listen to me. I didn't know that  Excelsior  was the state motto of New York, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  CAN YOU TALK ABOUT SOMETHING THAT YOU DID  BEFORE OR AFTER</pattern><template>Yeah, about a week before the incident, I called the cops and I told them that my wife and the history guy were plotting against me by embezzling money from the local high school, which wasn't true... It was a delusion. And we later found out from the hospital that's because I'm, uh...</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T FIND MY WEDDING VIDEO  MOM  WAKE UP</pattern><template>What is it?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT RIGHT</pattern><template>You're twisting the knife right now. You get off on it!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I'M RUNNING HERE  ME TOO</pattern><template>Well then, why don't you run somewhere else?</template></category><category><pattern>OLD ENOUGH TO HAVE A MARRIAGE END AND NOT WIND UP IN A MENTAL HOSPITAL</pattern><template>Look, I had a really good time tonight and I think you're really pretty, but I'm married, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>DOES IT REALLY MATTER</pattern><template>Baby, how's it going?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE PARLAY</pattern><template>Will somebody please explain to me the parlay? Please?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WON  FORTY  FOUR SIX</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>STOP HITTING HIM</pattern><template>I'm not hitting him! He's hitting me!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  SHE SAID YOU WERE COOL  BUT YOU KNOW</pattern><template>No, I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S JUST TALK ABOUT THIS</pattern><template>Mom, just listen... Don't tou  ...</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DID YOU ORDER TEA</pattern><template>Because you ordered Raisin Bran.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  CLIFF  THAT'S NOT THE WAY YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO MEET PEOPLE  OKAY</pattern><template>You should write that down in your, I don't know your little book you write stuff down in.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  THERE SHE IS  LOOK HOW BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>What! Whats this?</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE WILL GET OVER IT</pattern><template>It'll be all good. It'll work out.</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>...it was my wedding song and when I hear it, I go kinda crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>NASTY INDIAN CURRY  THIS IS AMERICA  BABY  GO BACK TO YOUR COUNTRY</pattern><template>What, what's wrong? Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY IT TOOK SO LONG FOR ME TO CATCH UP  I JUST GOT STUCK  PAT    I WROTE THAT A WEEK AGO</pattern><template>You wrote that a week ago? Yes, I did.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  THE SILVER LINING THING IS YOURS  I'M JUST GIVING BACK YOUR WORDS TO YOU  THIS  CRAZY SAD SHIT    AS YOU CALL IT  MADE YOU A HAPPIER  CALMER PERSON WITH A BEAUTIFUL POSITIVE PHILOSOPHY OF GOING OUTDOORS  WORKING OUT  AND READING BOOKS</pattern><template>No, not the books. You said Nikki's friends with Ronnie, Veronica and Tiffany. So if you become friends with Tiffany, Nikki will think that you're a kind, generous, large hearted person, who helps people in need, who is basically thriving. So if you help Tiffany, it will be good for you.</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE COCKSUCKERS</pattern><template>Okay, you know what? I don't have her phone number. If you want, if you really want, you can call Veronica 'cause she does, but I don't want to talk to Veronica.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN</pattern><template>Huh?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE READING THE SIGNS  OH  OKAY</pattern><template>Pat! You are not a stand up guy!</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS SO JEALOUS OF MY BROTHER</pattern><template>But Wait a minute, Wait a minute. Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE ONLY WAY TO CONVEY HOW MUCH YOU'VE MISSED ME IS BY YOUR WALK  BY YOUR SLOW WALK</pattern><template>You can't talk. Only walk.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NO BULLSHIT  THAT TAKES WORK AND THAT'S THE TRUTH</pattern><template>What the fuck?!</template></category><category><pattern>I LOST ALL THAT  I BLEW IT  BUT YOU ALSO BLEW IT  WE CAN GET IT BACK</pattern><template>We're gonna get it back.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED TO DEAL WITH IT</pattern><template>Stop breaking my balls.</template></category><category><pattern>AGAINST THE COWBOYS</pattern><template>That's your team isn't it, Randy? That's his team!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THAT SETTLES THAT</pattern><template>Pat! What are you doin'?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE POOR SOCIAL SKILLS  YOU HAVE A PROBLEM</pattern><template>I have a problem? You say more inappropriate things than appropriate things. You scare people.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IF I WAS TAKING THAT  I'D BE ON THE FLOOR  DAD</pattern><template>Just stay with us. Stay for the game. Spend some family time.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT MEDS ARE YOU ON</pattern><template>Me? None. I used to be on Lithium and Seroquel and Abilify, but I don't take them anymore, no. They make me foggy and they also make me bloated.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS IT  IT'S RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>You got it. Ahh, well, we got that.</template></category><category><pattern>TIFFANY  TIFFANY AND    TOMMY</pattern><template>Yeah. Just Tiffany.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  I KNEW WHY THEY INVITED ME OVER  I KNEW IT</pattern><template>Listen, she might be with that guy.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  THAT'S MY OLD IPOD  BUT  OH  BUDDY  THANK YOU</pattern><template>That's so nice of you. Wow.</template></category><category><pattern>SPEND FAMILY TIME  WAIT  YOU MEAN OCD  SUPERSTITIOUS TIME</pattern><template>Come on, your dad needs a winner. Help him out.</template></category><category><pattern>TOMMY DIED  COPS DIE</pattern><template>How'd he die?</template></category><category><pattern>HAS ANYBODY EVER TOLD YOU HOW TOMMY DIED</pattern><template>We were married for three years and five days, and I loved him. But for the last couple months, I just wasn't into sex at all. It just felt like we were so different and I was depressed. Some of that is just me, some of it was he wanted me to have kids and I have a hard enough time taking care of myself.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S SOME KIND OF LOVE THERE  I KNOW  I USED TO SEE IT</pattern><template>You guys have a beautiful thing that got broken somewhere along the line and you gotta fix it like a chiropractor.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HE'S READY  LOOK AT HIM</pattern><template>You didn't tell Dad you were picking me up?</template></category><category><pattern>I LIKE THIS ROAD  THIS IS MY NEIGHBORHOOD</pattern><template>Oh, come on, please!</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD FOR YOU</pattern><template>And the scores for Makarov and Tretiak are: six point seven, eight point one, seven point five and six point five for an average score of seven point two.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A DANCE THING  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>It's a competition thing at the Benjamin Franklin Hotel.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A VERY UNCONVENTIONAL CHEMISTRY  IT MAKES PEOPLE FEEL AWKWARD  BUT NOT ME  SHE'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL WOMAN I'VE EVER BEEN WITH</pattern><template>Wow. It's electric between us, Okay? Yeah, we wanna change each other, but that's normal, couples wanna do that, I want her to stop dressing like she dresses, I want her to stop acting so superior to me, okay? And she wanted me to lose weight and stop my mood swings, both of which I've done.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL RUINED  YOU LITTLE FUCKING SHIT</pattern><template>No, Dad! I didn't do a fucking thing! Come on, Dad!</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT</pattern><template>Tea Be right back.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA BE PART OF IT  WE HAVE TO DO IT</pattern><template>Aren't you nervous to be lying?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ARE YOU  HEY</pattern><template>What are you doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO AVERAGE THE FOUR JUDGES' SCORES</pattern><template>Okay, score is from one to ten, right? And you guys are how good?</template></category><category><pattern>PLUS  ARE YOU LISTENING  PLUS WHATEVER THEIR SCORE IS AT THE DANCE THING  WHAT'S THAT</pattern><template>Tiffany, what's that?</template></category><category><pattern>ISN'T THAT A GOOD THING</pattern><template>You're just up, up, up.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT AN EMERGENCY</pattern><template>Yeah, kind of. What kind of emergency?</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST OF ALL  CHECK WITH THE LATEST LEGAL DEVELOPMENT</pattern><template>Well, we got a call that they did convert you to a Mental Hygiene Law admission status by the deadline of your sentence, so...</template></category><category><pattern>ASK HIM ABOUT ANY PRESIDENT  HE KNOWS 'EM ALL</pattern><template>Here's a fun fact. You know where the term  OK  comes from?</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIDN'T WANT TO WAKE ME</pattern><template>He doesn't have a problem complaining about Ernest fucking Hemingway.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T GIVE A FUCK  WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING  HEY  HEY</pattern><template>Did you just throw that outside?</template></category><category><pattern>BE MY GUEST</pattern><template>The first night that Pat and I met at my sister's, the Eagles beat the Forty Niners handily, forty to twenty six. The second time we got together we went for a run and the Phillies beat the Dodgers seven to five in the NLCS.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  JUST TIFFANY</pattern><template>What happened to Tommy?</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T  I DIDN'T  I DIDN'T  IT'S THE KIDS</pattern><template>Honestly He didn't do anything, it was all the kids.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK</pattern><template>Ronnie! Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY ABOUT THAT  GUYS</pattern><template>Dad, Dad, did the Eagles win?</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T HAVE TO TALK ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOT ALL HIS EAGLES VIDEOS AND NOT ONE VIDEO OF MY WEDDING</pattern><template>Is it here? I mean...?</template></category><category><pattern>I TOOK CARE OF THAT JERKOFF THAT WAS IN FRONT OF YOUR HOUSE</pattern><template>What? Jordie?</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  PAT</pattern><template>I looked over there! I already looked all over there!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE ENVELOPE WAS EMPTY</pattern><template>I'm sorry, you were sleeping.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT AM I GONNA DO  I'M GETTING IN SHAPE  I'M GETTING TRIM  I'M GETTING REALLY FIT FOR NIKKI</pattern><template>I'm gonna read Nikki's teaching syllabus and get my old job back.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY</pattern><template>I was very depressed after Tommy died. It was a lot of people.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANNA HAVE DINNER AT THIS DINER</pattern><template>Pick me up at seven thirty.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOU GUYS OUGHTA BE ASHAMED OF YOURSELVES</pattern><template>I used the insurance money to build this. I designed it. All the floors are hard oak. It has good bounce for dancers. Wow.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO DID THIS  WHO TOOK  WHO TOOK  WHO TOOK THE</pattern><template>the remotes like this?</template></category><category><pattern>PUT THE PHONE DOWN  PLEASE</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU COMFORTABLE</pattern><template>Veronica's not gonna like it.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE ARE STUPID  THEY  THEY  THEY  THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE SAYING</pattern><template>Yeah, that's the one.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  PLEASE  TELL ME MORE ABOUT WHAT HE SAID IN THE LETTER</pattern><template>Yeah, anything you wanna know, I'll just tell you. It was nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT IT  I GOT IT  I GOT IT</pattern><template>Let me ask you something.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  DON'T LOOK FOR NIKKI  TAKE YOUR CAMERA AND GET OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Patrick, please. Pat!</template></category><category><pattern>NOT CORRECT ABOUT THE MENTAL HYGIENE LAW  YOU'RE NOT CORRECT</pattern><template>Come on. You guys oughta be ashamed of yourselves.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Don't focus on that.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ALL RIGHT ON ALL COUNTS</pattern><template>Does anybody here happen to know what the official motto of the state of New York is on the official seal of the State of New York?</template></category><category><pattern>PATRIZIO  I FEEL TERRIBLE  YOU KNOW  YOU MADE THE BET  I WON A LOT OF MONEY  AND NOW LOOK  YOUR WHOLE FAMILY IS IN TURMOIL</pattern><template>Oh, fuck off, Randy. You love it.</template></category><category><pattern>SWEETIE  SWEETIE  HONEY  CALM DOWN</pattern><template>You're killing me. You're killing me!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  IT FLATTENS YOU OUT</pattern><template>I mean, you are done.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS MOVED TO READ ABOUT 'EXCELSIOR' AND YOUR BELIEF IN HAPPY ENDINGS  I AM ALSO MOVED BY YOUR ACT OF LOVE TO READ THE BOOKS I HAVE TAUGHT AT THE HIGH SCHOOL  I'M SORRY YOU FIND THEM SO NEGATIVE  BUT I DISAGREE  I THINK THEY ARE GREAT WORKS OF ART THAT REFLECT HOW HARD LIFE CAN BE AND THEY CAN ALSO HELP KIDS PREPARE THEMSELVES FOR THE HARDNESS OF LIFE  IN SPITE OF ALL THESE POSITIVE DEVELOPMENTS  PAT  I HAVE TO SAY IF IT'S ME READING THE SIGNS  I NEED TO SEE SOMETHING TO PROVE YOU ARE READY TO RESUME OUR MARRIAGE  OTHERWISE I FIND MYSELF THINKING THAT WE MIGHT BOTH BE BETTER OFF MOVING ON WITH OUR LIVES SEPARATELY</pattern><template>Please don't react quickly to this, but take time to think about it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  NO PARLAY  NO  NO  DON'T DO IT  DON'T DO IT</pattern><template>Pat, how do they run this dance competition?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT'S MORE AMERICAN  WHAT</pattern><template>Benjamin Franklin, that's what's more American.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE GREAT AND THEY ONLY GOT A SEVEN POINT TWO</pattern><template>This is a tough room.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU GUYS   IT'S ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Huh? No. It's alright.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BET I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED IF ONLY ONE IS MISSING</pattern><template>Either Dolores or Pat needed an envelope and one of 'em took it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK YOU DOING</pattern><template>You... hit your mother?!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOLD YOUR THERAPIST THAT YOU WERE IN A SUPERIOR MENTAL ILLNESS CATEGORY  DIDN'T YOU</pattern><template>What? Hey, calm down! Hey  Just leave me alone!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU LOVED HEARING ABOUT IT  DIDN'T YOU</pattern><template>You are afraid to be alive, you're afraid to live. You're a hypocrite.</template></category><category><pattern>I FEEL LIKE AN IDIOT</pattern><template>Are you comfortable?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH HER</pattern><template>Is that another creep? What do you want, creep? Just beat it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DO</pattern><template>I just gotta get a strategy, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS A BIPOLAR EPISODE</pattern><template>Get outta here, you little fuckin' idiot! Get outta here!</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T DO IT  TIFFANY  WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO</pattern><template>Think of something. There's this thing.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL CALL THEM  THEY'LL COME FOR YOU</pattern><template>Why would you do that? You wouldn't do that. Why would you call them?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT EXPLOSION  NO  CLIFF IS LYING  THAT'S NOT TRUE</pattern><template>He's not allowed to talk about that.</template></category><category><pattern>MOM  YEAH  NO  NO</pattern><template>...I'm just confirming.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE IT TO ME  THANK YOU  BABY  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Of all the rooms there are iPod ports in, I'm happy you brought us into the bathroom.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE I DO  JUST CHECK IN  I GOTTA GO FIND VERONICA</pattern><template>Hi, good evening. Evening.</template></category><category><pattern>IT TAKES THE LIGHT RIGHT OUT OF YOUR EYES</pattern><template>God, I bet it does.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A WHITE LIE  WHAT'S THAT MATTER  THAT'S NO BIG DEAL</pattern><template>So it's a little lie.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS DOWN  BUT YOU KNOW  SHE WANTS MORE  SO I'M GIVING HER MORE  MAN</pattern><template>Hey, you know my dad lost his pension.</template></category><category><pattern>AHH</pattern><template>Where is it? It's right here.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU WALK TOWARDS ME LIKE I'M NIKKI</pattern><template>And the only way to convey how much you've missed me is by your walk. By your slow walk.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TRYING TO KEEP YOU OUT OF TROUBLE  PLEASE</pattern><template>I have very, good news, everybody. Very good news.</template></category><category><pattern>MOM  CAN WE STOP AT THE LIBRARY  I WANNA READ NIKKI'S ENTIRE ENGLISH HIGH SCHOOL SYLLABUS</pattern><template>Mom, it's a good thing.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK I FUCKED UP THE EAGLES' JUJU  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>Ever since, ever since he was with you, ever since  You think that I'm why today's happened?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU START SNAPPING UP COMMERCIAL REAL ESTATE    CHEAP    FLIP IT OVER  YOU FLIP IT OVER AND THAT'S WHEN YOU MAKE THE MONEY</pattern><template>But the pressure... it's like...</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  IT'S ELECTRIC BETWEEN US  OKAY  YEAH  WE WANNA CHANGE EACH OTHER  BUT THAT'S NORMAL  COUPLES WANNA DO THAT  I WANT HER TO STOP DRESSING LIKE SHE DRESSES  I WANT HER TO STOP ACTING SO SUPERIOR TO ME  OKAY  AND SHE WANTED ME TO LOSE WEIGHT AND STOP MY MOOD SWINGS  BOTH OF WHICH I'VE DONE</pattern><template>I mean, people fight. Couples fight.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ABOUT A WEEK BEFORE THE INCIDENT  I CALLED THE COPS AND I TOLD THEM THAT MY WIFE AND THE HISTORY GUY WERE PLOTTING AGAINST ME BY EMBEZZLING MONEY FROM THE LOCAL HIGH SCHOOL  WHICH WASN'T TRUE    IT WAS A DELUSION  AND WE LATER FOUND OUT FROM THE HOSPITAL THAT'S BECAUSE I'M  UH</pattern><template>...undiagnosed bipolar.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE JUST UP  UP  UP</pattern><template>I don't know what that is.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M JUST DOING THIS PROJECT WITH TIFFANY AND I WANTED TO TELL HER I'M NOT GONNA BE ON TIME</pattern><template>Just don't make her an emergency, that crazy girl, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD  MM  YEAH</pattern><template>Okay, we got it, we got it. Okay. Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS SO FUCKED UP</pattern><template>Yeah, just read it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AFTER THREE O'CLOCK</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>RONNIE AND VERONICA AND I ARE GONNA SEE HER TONIGHT</pattern><template>Oh, I actually changed the first paragraph. I did this thing about Shakespeare and how it's very romantic  Mm hmm.  and that maybe in the future if she wanted to go dancing, I can be able to do that because of all the training that No, that's good, that's really good.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  GIMME A BREAK</pattern><template>I'm right here.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  I BET IT DOES</pattern><template>I'm tired. I wanna go.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS CRAZINESS WITH TIFFANY MAXWELL</pattern><template>There's no craziness.</template></category><category><pattern>WERE THERE ANY WOMEN</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK NICE</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>DECEMBER TWENTY EIGHT  LAST GAME OF THE SEASON</pattern><template>Oh, my God. Same day as the Benjamin Franklin Pairs Open Freestyle Dance Competition.</template></category><category><pattern>WEIGHT LIFTING ACCIDENT</pattern><template>That sounds like bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GONNA TALK ABOUT IT ANYMORE</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  I'M IN THERE BECAUSE OF THE COURT</pattern><template>That's the agreement that we made months ago.</template></category><category><pattern>I ASSUME YOU'RE A GOOD TEACHER</pattern><template>Yeah. I mean, I hope so.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE IT EASY  DUDE  RELAX</pattern><template>He's harassing me!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  WHAT'S WRONG  HEY</pattern><template>Whoa, whoa, what's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING'S MY PROBLEM  I'M FINE  I'M TIRED AND I WANNA GO</pattern><template>Come on, are you ready?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL    OKAY  OKAY  CONGRATULATIONS</pattern><template>Thank you. So what are you doing with yourself?</template></category><category><pattern>ME TOO</pattern><template>We'd better get back to the letter.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  THESE ARE THE TWO DAYS THAT YOU HAVE PROMISED ME AND THAT WE HAVE PREPARED TO NAIL THE BIG MOVE  IT'S NOT READY YET</pattern><template>And we don't have a move yet.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU TAKING THE PROPER DOSAGE OF YOUR MEDICATION</pattern><template>Am I taking the right dose? Of course I am.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT THAT GREAT OF A DANCER  BUT WHO CARES  IT'S THERAPY AND IT'S FUN  AND THE WALLS ARE GOOD 'CAUSE I CAN PLAY MUSIC REALLY LOUD WITHOUT ANYBODY HEARING</pattern><template>Where do you sleep?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WHAT ARE YOU DOING  SHE'S FINE  BUDDY  SHE'S WITH ME</pattern><template>She's fine? Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>PLUS YOU GOT A TIE ON</pattern><template>Don't worry about it, you're the guest of honor. You come however you wanna come.</template></category><category><pattern>UM  MAYBE I SHOULD DRIVE THEM HOME SEPARATELY</pattern><template>You can drive them both home. Now.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY  STOP  STOP  STOP  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Hey, get off of me! Shut up, shut up.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Pat!</template></category><category><pattern>MS  MECKERS</pattern><template>Oh, God! Oh, God!</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH YOURSELF</pattern><template>You know, I'm gonna start a restaurant.</template></category><category><pattern>THE THIRD TIME WE GOT TOGETHER WE HAD RAISIN BRAN IN THE DINER AND THE PHILLIES DOMINATED TAMPA BAY IN THE FOURTH GAME OF THE WORLD SERIES  TEN TO TWO</pattern><template>Oh, wow.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA GET YOUR MARRIAGE TOGETHER</pattern><template>I start breaking shit, and I hurt my hand. And   Ronnie, that's fucked up. Yeah, but it makes me feel better.</template></category><category><pattern>IS  IS THE SPEAKER HERE</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay... I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ARE YOU IN LOVE  TELL ME ABOUT THAT  THE BIG NIKKI LOVE</pattern><template>Tell me about it, I wanna understand it.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GONNA DO IT  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>You are not a stand up guy right now. If it's me reading the signs... if it's me reading the signs  If it's you reading the signs?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THERE A SPEAKER HERE</pattern><template>Is, is the speaker here?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY WERE THERE</pattern><template>Eleven.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WINE</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL</pattern><template>What happened to your face?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A BETTER GUY THAN THIS</pattern><template>I can see it in your eyes. She just texted me!</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SHOW YOU  PAT  LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT I MEAN  YOU GOTTA COME AT HER WITH A LITTLE BIT MORE SOUL  MAN</pattern><template>You should move more hips.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>The world will break your heart ten ways to Sunday, that's guaranteed.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  DAD  IT'S ALL FUCKING RUINED NOW  IT'S ALL FUCKING RUINED</pattern><template>No, Dad, Dad, Dad, don't!</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE HUNDRED FEET  YOU HEAR WHAT HE JUST SAID  YOUHAVE A RESTRAINING ORDER</pattern><template>Yeah, Dad, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST HAVE TO GIVE IT SOME TIME</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'M GLAD THAT THE SEAHAWKS ARE LOSING AND WE'RE WINNING  BUT I GOTTA TAKE DANNY MCDANIELS BACK TO BALTIMORE  ALRIGHT  HE CAN CONTEST HIS CASE FROM BALTIMORE</pattern><template>Not correct about the Mental Hygiene Law. You're not correct.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  YOU CAN'T QUIT  I'M NOT DOING THE DANCE  I'M OUT</pattern><template>Pat, calm down. Thank about it. See you later.</template></category><category><pattern>IN FACT  I'LL GIVE YOU TEN POINTS  NO  DAD  DAD</pattern><template>Dad! You have to take that bet on the Cowboys.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  IS TIFFANY HOME  GO AWAY</pattern><template>I know her. I know her, we've dated. We still date.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST HOPE YOU CAN HANDLE IT  THANK YOU</pattern><template>What was her energy when she gave it to you?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO BACK TO THE INCIDENT</pattern><template>I come home from work after I..</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STILL GOT YOURS  YEAH  I GOT MINE</pattern><template>So what, you don't talk to me? You didn't tell me you took him out.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  PATTY</pattern><template>Where have you been?</template></category><category><pattern>ANOTHER RUDE CREEP</pattern><template>Listen to what he's saying.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL FIX IT WHEN I GET BACK  FIX IT NOW</pattern><template>Get in the car, Pat. You have to go to therapy.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  HEY  WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE</pattern><template>You know, we must beat the Giants, my brother.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FINE</pattern><template>Come on, it's gonna be great.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE</pattern><template>I just see that you made an effort and I'm gonna be better with my wife, I'm working on that. I wanna acknowledge her beauty.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE PRESSURE    IT'S LIKE</pattern><template>You okay?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST RAN BY MY HOUSE</pattern><template>I like to run by myself, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE  GOTTA BE MAKING A LOT OF PAPER TO DO THAT</pattern><template>Yeah, we're doing all right, man. I can't complain.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER ALL OF THE GOOD STUFF THAT WE HAVE HERE</pattern><template>Of course I do. Just check in. I gotta go find Veronica.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HAVE ERNEST HEMINGWAY CALL US AND APOLOGIZE TO US  TOO</pattern><template>Why didn't you run with me? Huh!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MAY NOT HAVE EXPERIENCED THE SHIT THAT I DID</pattern><template>But you loved hearing about it, didn't you?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  NO  NO  WE HAVEN'T  WE HAVEN'T EVEN FINISHED THE SALAD YET  OR THE DUCK  I MADE THE FIRE AND ICE CAKE</pattern><template>I said I'm tired. Are you gonna walk me home or what?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN HELPING POP WITH THE RESTAURANT 'CAUSE HE NEEDS TO HAVE A LEGITIMATE BUSINESS  HE NEEDS A TAX RETURN  WITH ALL THE MONEY THAT HE'S MAKING WITH HIS BOOKMAKING  THEY'RE GONNA COME AFTER HIM  AND THEN IT LOOKS LIKE I'M MAKING  I'M GONNA MAKE PARTNER AT THE FIRM</pattern><template>Well, I don't even know what to say to you anymore. You lost your wife, I'm getting engaged, and I wanna be able to tell you about those kind of things. You lost your house, I'm getting a new house. You lost your job, things are going great for me at the firm.</template></category><category><pattern>UH HUH</pattern><template>Cool, man. Wow, you lost a lot of weight. I almost didn't recognize you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  NO  NO  NO  NO  I'M MARRIED</pattern><template>Oh, great, a married creep. I'm her friend.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A SMALL THING  SIT DOWN  COME ON</pattern><template>I'm making crabby snacks and homemades.</template></category><category><pattern>HE GOT KICKED OUT OF THAT STADIUM HE BEAT UP SO MANY PEOPLE AT EAGLES GAMES  HE'S ON THE EXCLUSION LIST</pattern><template>I had one incident. One incident can change a lifetime.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M MARRIED</pattern><template>So am I!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOSER  YOU LOSER</pattern><template>I'm not a loser.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST GOT FIRED  ACTUALLY</pattern><template>Oh, really? How?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE YOU WEARING A GARBAGE BAG</pattern><template>To sweat.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN  SHE LEFT</pattern><template>She left. What do you think! Where is she?</template></category><category><pattern>I MUST ADMIT YOU SOUND TERRIFIC AND I'M HAPPY THAT YOU ARE FEELING SO POSITIVE AND BECOMING A MORE LOVING AND CARING MAN  WHICH I ALWAYS KNEW YOU WERE</pattern><template>I was moved to read about 'Excelsior' and your belief in happy endings. I am also moved by your act of love to read the books I have taught at the high school. I'm sorry you find them so negative, but I disagree. I think they are great works of art that reflect how hard life can be and they can also help kids prepare themselves for the hardness of life. In spite of all these positive developments, Pat, I have to say if it's me reading the signs, I need to see something to prove you are ready to resume our marriage. Otherwise I find myself thinking that we might both be better off moving on with our lives separately.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MM HMM  IT'S REALLY GENEROUS</pattern><template>You know, being of service.</template></category><category><pattern>OH   WEST SIDE STORY    YEAH   WEST SIDE STORY    IT MAKES ME PEACEFUL</pattern><template>Maria, I just met a girl named Maria...   Right, right, right.</template></category><category><pattern>I COME HOME AND WHAT'S PLAYING BUT THE SONG FROM MY WEDDING</pattern><template>The song that you so charmingly played out here today for us.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T  I DON'T FEEL GOOD WHEN I'M ON THEM  MOM  I DON'T FEEL GOOD</pattern><template>I'm so much clearer without them. Mom, they make me bloated.</template></category><category><pattern>WE KNOW ALL ABOUT THE EXPLOSION AT THE PSYCHIATRIST'S OFFICE</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID WHO DIE</pattern><template>Hey, Tiffany! This is Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE THEY SO EXCITED ABOUT A FIVE</pattern><template>How are you? You okay? Good. How are you? I'm really good. Yeah, thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LETTER TO NIKKI</pattern><template>Probably tonight. Really?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I BELIEVE IN AMERICA'S TEAM BUT IF I WIN THAT BET  I WIN YOUR BOOK  YOU'RE OUT OF ACTION  YOU GET NO RESTAURANT  NO NOTHING</pattern><template>I like it. No. No, Patrizio  I believe in the Eagles, I believe in my son, I'll take the action. I'll take it.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OFF OF ME  GET OFF</pattern><template>You're harassing me!</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SAY SOMETHING  YOU DON'T EVER HAVE TO SEE ME AGAIN IF YOU JUST READ IT  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>This is so fucked up.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST TOLD ME OUTSIDE  MOM  WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>Five minutes ago, we were walking up the stairs, you said,  Don't say anything, but Dad lost his job and he's bookmaking.   Why, Dolores? Why did you say that to him? He has the wrong idea.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  BUT THAT'S</pattern><template>You can call me Cliff, please.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU LOSE A LOT OF WEIGHT</pattern><template>I did, yeah. I did. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S GOOD NOW  YES  IT IS</pattern><template>Wait, you're going the wrong way!</template></category><category><pattern>BASICALLY   WAS I SOME PERCENTAGE NOT COOL</pattern><template>No, she said you were cool, but you know.</template></category><category><pattern>PATTY  DON'T LOOK FOR NIKKI</pattern><template>Ms. Meckers!</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'LL TAKE THAT FUCKING CAMERA AND I'M GONNA BREAK IT OVER YOUR FUCKIN' HEAD  THEN I'M GONNA COME BACK AND INTERVIEW YOU ABOUT WHAT IT'S LIKE TO GET THAT FUCKIN' CAMERA BROKEN OVER YOUR HEAD</pattern><template>Youwa..., what are you laughing about?</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'</pattern><template>I gotta go, man.</template></category><category><pattern>TOMMY WOULD NEVER DO IT WITH ME AND I MISSED IT EVERY SINGLE YEAR</pattern><template>Well, Tommy's dead, so he's not gonna fucking do it.</template></category><category><pattern>DESEAN JACKSON  DESEAN JACKSON</pattern><template>Oh, you wore a jersey to dinner.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT EMBARRASSED</pattern><template>No. I'd love to go to the game, too, but as you know, I'm banned from the stadium. 'Cause I'd love to see us beat the Giants and take a lot of money from this asshole.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT'S A LOT TO DEAL WITH  ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL IS HAPPENING  WHICH I DO NOW  SORT OF</pattern><template>Pat, you have to take your medication.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE GOOD  BETTER THAN YOU  A LOT BETTER</pattern><template>A lot better. So if I was to say you only have to score five, I would be really very generous, right?</template></category><category><pattern>EXCEPT FOR A MINOR INCIDENT AT THE DOCTOR'S OFFICE</pattern><template>And the so called incident with the weights.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO TOLD YOU THAT  MOM TOLD ME  OUTSIDE</pattern><template>I did not. No, I didn't.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT DID NOT SAY THAT</pattern><template>He didn't say that.</template></category><category><pattern>NIKKI'S GONNA BE THERE  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Everything's gonna come together.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID I'M TIRED  ARE YOU GONNA WALK ME HOME OR WHAT</pattern><template>You mean me?</template></category><category><pattern>BY    HAVING SEX WITH EVERYBODY IN THE OFFICE</pattern><template>Everybody?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  LET'S GET BACK TO THE LETTER</pattern><template>What if you told Nikki when Veronica was in the bathroom?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S IT  THERE YOU GO  I'M SORRY  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TELL YOU  I KNOW YOU DON'T WANNA LISTEN TO YOUR FATHER  I DIDN'T LISTEN TO MINE BUT I'M TELLING YOU  YOU GOTTA PAY ATTENTION TO THE SIGNS  WHEN LIFE REACHES OUT WITH A MOMENT LIKE THIS  IT'S A SIN IF YOU DON'T REACH BACK  I'M TELLING YOU  IT'S A SIN IF YOU DON'T REACH BACK  AND IT'LL HAUNT YOU FOR THE REST OF YOUR DAYS LIKE A CURSE  YOU'RE FACING A BIG CHALLENGE IN YOUR LIFE RIGHT NOW  AT THIS VERY MOMENT  RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>That girl loves you, she really loves you. And I don't know if Nikki ever did, but she sure as hell doesn't love you right now.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  YOU WERE SLEEPING</pattern><template>I didn't want to wake you, but I needed an envelope.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GET OFF ON IT  IF NOT  THEN PROVE IT  PROVE IT</pattern><template>Yeah, prove it, prove it!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  RANDY  DON'T YOU BELIEVE IN AMERICA'S TEAM</pattern><template>Yeah, I believe in America's Team but if I win that bet, I win your book, you're out of action, you get no restaurant, no nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I DID PRETTY WELL</pattern><template>Yeah, she said you were cool, basically.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S HARASSING ME</pattern><template>Hey, hey, stop, stop. Stop, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S FUCKING NUTS  WHEN YOU STARTED SPENDING TIME WITH HER  IT ALL FELL APART  THIS IS THE FUCKING REASON RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>You think I fucked up the Eagles' juju, don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST GONNA READ IT OUT LOUD  OKAY  BECAUSE IF SHE SAYS ANYTHING THAT'S  YOU KNOW  IS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A RESTRAINING ORDER ON THIS GUY</pattern><template>I know, I have a stupid sense of humor.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU DO THIS  RANDY</pattern><template>No, I don't touch them. As a matter of fact, I don't know why you need so many.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST CONFIRMING  OKAY</pattern><template>Wait, wait, wait, wait.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOUR DAD NEEDS A WINNER  HELP HIM OUT</pattern><template>Come on. I can't. It's the Seahawks.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK</pattern><template>Sweetie, sweetie. Honey, calm down.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  NIKKI  WHAT'S ALL THIS ABOUT NIKKI</pattern><template>Pan from the framed photo of Jake on foyer wall, to Jake on the stairs above.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL THEN  WHY DON'T YOU RUN SOMEWHERE ELSE</pattern><template>There's a fucking ton of roads to run in! What are you trying to do?</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO TALK RIGHT NOW  WHEN YOU MAKE A SERIOUS COMMITMENT TO SOMEBODY  IT IS NOT COOL TO NOT SHOW UP</pattern><template>Wait a second, I tried to call, my God, what's happening, I called..., but I tried to call you, Tiffany, I  Oh, really? Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I DO   AN INTERVIEW FOR A SCHOOL PROJECT ON MENTAL ILLNESS  NO</pattern><template>It's for a school project!</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  PEOPLE FIGHT  COUPLES FIGHT</pattern><template>We would fight, we wouldn't talk for a couple weeks. That's normal. She always wanted the best for me.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WHAT'S THIS</pattern><template>What? I thought you were doing it.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY  HEY  GET OFF ME</pattern><template>What are you doing? Come on. What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU GOTTA MAKE SURE IT GETS MENDED  AND YOU'RE GETTIN' IN THE WAY OF THAT RIGHT NOW  OKAY</pattern><template>Because she's sensitive and she's smart, she's artistic. This is a great girl and you gotta be respectful of that. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>Where's my wedding video?</template></category><category><pattern>HMM</pattern><template>Did you invite him?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T</pattern><template>What do you mean, you can't?</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM NO  IT'S NOT OKAY  IT'S NOT OKAY  YOU GOTTA ASK</pattern><template>Do not go in my study or I will eat you!  It's not funny, it's not funny.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUWA     WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING ABOUT</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULDN'T ACTUALLY CALL THE RESTRAINING ORDER  MY THING    BUT GETTING BACK WITH NIKKI IS  AND I'VE BEEN DOING PRETTY WELL</pattern><template>Except for a minor incident at the doctor's office.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  YOU HAVE TO TAKE YOUR MEDICATION</pattern><template>I can't, Mom. I can't.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  THEN I'M NOT GIVING HER YOUR FUCKING LETTER</pattern><template>Wait a second! But you promised you would do this.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I ALREADY DID DO SOMETHING FOR YOU  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>I took care of that jerkoff that was in front of your house.</template></category><category><pattern>BABY  HOW'S IT GOING</pattern><template>Great, great.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FELL APART  WHAT ARE YOU FUCKING TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>Your son was trying to  It's all fucking ruined now. It's all ruined.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE WASN'T ON THE HUNDRED DOLLAR BILL  NOBODY        WOULD EVEN KNOW WHO HE IS</pattern><template>What are you doing? No, no, no, no.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA FIND HER  I KNOW  MOM  I KNOW</pattern><template>Hey, WHAT are you doing? She's fine, buddy, she's with me.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON BREATH  THERE'S NO SONG PLAYING  THERE'S NO SONG</pattern><template>That's it.</template></category><category><pattern>BE QUIET  SHUT UP  YOU ALREADY DID ENOUGH  RANDY  WHAT DO YOU SAY</pattern><template>My birds, Benjamin Franklin's team favored by one and a half points.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S IN THE ENVELOPE</pattern><template>Yeah, what are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD  I'M GONNA GO HOME AND WRITE THE LETTER RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Can I at least finish my tea?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS SPECIAL  EVERYTHING HAPPENS FOR A REASON</pattern><template>That's why you came home.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TIRED  I WANNA GO</pattern><template>No. No, no, no, no. We haven't, we haven't even finished the salad yet, or the duck. I made the Fire and Ice cake.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>SLOW DOWN  RAISIN BRAN</pattern><template>Hey, come on. Look, I don't think you're crazy, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  IS THIS FOR ME</pattern><template>Yeah. Well, that's my old iPod, but  Oh, buddy, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  JAILHOUSE LAWYER  COME ON  LET'S COME BACK AND SIT DOWN THE WAY YOU WERE BEFORE</pattern><template>What a treat! Whoa, whoa, whoa.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M WORRIED ABOUT THE BET</pattern><template>Holy shit.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S REALLY TOO BAD  GUYS  THAT'S A LOT OF FOURS</pattern><template>...and and a five point four for an average score of.. five point zero.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A POSITIVE GUY  OKAY</pattern><template>You just have to give it some time.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SOLID  I'M SOLID NOW</pattern><template>You fell apart! What are you fucking talking about?!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA TAKE THAT AS A SILVER DEVELOPMENT  NANCY</pattern><template>A silver development!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST LOOKING OUT FOR YOU  I'M JUST LOOKING OUT FOR YOU  SHE'S UNSTABLE</pattern><template>What's wrong with your marriage?</template></category><category><pattern>I DID MY RESEARCH  WELL  I GOTTA SAY  I'M IMPRESSED</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU OKAY  RONNIE CALLED  HEY  IS THAT MAKE UP ON YOUR SHIRT</pattern><template>I don't know, Mom.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  LISTEN  I'M SORRY THAT I DIDN'T COME SEE YOU DOWN AT THE HOSPITAL</pattern><template>You know how those places creep me out, and the firm's been expanding.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS FOR THE LETTER</pattern><template>I'll see you tomorrow, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU BEING A PUNK ON HALLOWEEN WITH THESE KIDS</pattern><template>You wanna go back to Baltimore?</template></category><category><pattern>I GO TO A LOT OF THERAPY  RONNIE</pattern><template>What are you trying to say?</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  PAT TOLD ME ABOUT YOU  SO IS THE GIRL  THAT YOU WROTE ABOUT</pattern><template>Yeah. What? He wrote about me? I'm  the girl ?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FOR A SCHOOL PROJECT</pattern><template>Don't pay any attention.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE SCORES FOR MAKAROV AND TRETIAK ARE: SIX POINT SEVEN  EIGHT POINT ONE  SEVEN POINT FIVE AND SIX POINT FIVE FOR AN AVERAGE SCORE OF SEVEN POINT TWO</pattern><template>They were great and they only got a seven point two.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE SO CALLED INCIDENT WITH THE WEIGHTS</pattern><template>Yeah. That was a thing with my parents. I wish I could just explain it all in a letter to Nikki because it was minor and I could just explain it and let her know that I'm actually not out of control and that I'm actually doing really well.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M FUCKED UP  WHAT CAN I TELL YOU  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>You're Tommy's widow, right?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT IT  IT</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO SEE THE HOUSE</pattern><template>Come on, let's go for the tour.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST A SONG</pattern><template>Don't make it a monster.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT OKAY  I'VE BEEN ASSIGNED TO YOUR CASE  SO YOU'RE GONNA BE SEEING A LOT OF ME  DO YOURSELF A FAVOR  RESPECT THE RESTRAINING ORDER  OKAY</pattern><template>Five hundred feet. You hear what he just said? Youhave a restraining order.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA JUST EXPLAIN TO YOU SOMETHING  I MEAN  YOU KNOW WHAT I'M DOING  HONEY  THIS EVERYTHING  LIKE THIS</pattern><template>I got this, it all corresponds.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THAT  THAT'S NOT RICK D'ANGELO  IS IT  THAT'S HIM</pattern><template>Is he the guy who's having the problem?</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO BEAT THE VIKINGS BY THREE  I'M GIVIN' YOU A SIX  WHICH IS VERY GENEROUS AFTER THE BEATING YOU JUST TOOK  SO WHAT ARE WE DOIN'  WHAT ARE WE TALKIN' ABOUT HERE</pattern><template>I'd like to do another parlay if we make it to the next round, that's all.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  DAD  I DIDN'T DO A FUCKING THING  COME ON  DAD</pattern><template>You loser! You loser!</template></category><category><pattern>GET IN THE CAR  PAT  YOU HAVE TO GO TO THERAPY</pattern><template>I don't wanna go to therapy.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW AM I BEING RUDE</pattern><template>Oh, you know. You know. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT THE ONE THAT JUST GOT OUT OF THAT HOSPITAL IN BALTIMORE</pattern><template>I'm not the big slut!</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING'S FINE  PATRICK  I'M MORE CONCERNED ABOUT YOU THAN ANYTHING ELSE</pattern><template>Good, Dad. Good.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT GIRL LOVES YOU  SHE REALLY LOVES YOU  AND I DON'T KNOW IF NIKKI EVER DID  BUT SHE SURE AS HELL DOESN'T LOVE YOU RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>I'm telling you, don't fuck this up.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S BULLSHIT  THAT'S NOT TRUE  DON'T SAY THAT</pattern><template>You get off on it! If not, then prove it. Prove it.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE STOP TALKING ABOUT ALL THE STUFF THAT'S GOOD FOR YOU AND BAD FOR HIM  JUST  YOU KNOW  LEAVE IT ALONE  WE'RE WATCHING THE GAME</pattern><template>You know what, I'm just gonna, I'm just gonna, I'm just gonna stop talking. I'm gonna shut my mouth.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S VERY  VERY MANIC INDEED</pattern><template>That's the parlay. Shake on it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A THING  IT'S A THING</pattern><template>It's a, it's a dance thing.</template></category><category><pattern>SO AM I</pattern><template>What the fuck are you doing? Your husband's dead!</template></category><category><pattern>GIRL  YOU GOTTA MOVE YOUR JUNK</pattern><template>I gotta get out of here. I gotta go see this girl, Tanya.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT ASHAMED OF IT</pattern><template>Let the whole neighborhood wake up! I... don't care!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST CAME BY TO SAY HI  TO LET YOU KNOW I'M READY TO COME BACK TO WORK</pattern><template>You shouldn't be here.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT MY EYES  LOOK AT HOW CLEAR THEY ARE</pattern><template>I'm not a complainer anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A SERIOUS SITUATION ON OUR HANDS  YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>We gotta beat the Giants if we wanna have a chance of getting into the division, any chance of playing in the playoffs. Do you realize that?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YEAH  YOU GOT THE STRANGLERS</pattern><template>You love The Stranglers.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WOULD YOU JUST LEAVE ME ALONE</pattern><template>Wait a second! I have one more letter for you to read, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THAT  WHAT THE</pattern><template>What are you doing here, man?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE CRAZY</pattern><template>I'm not the one that just got out of that hospital in Baltimore.</template></category><category><pattern>RONNIE  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Okay, it's a little true. But if you think she still hates you, you're wrong because why would she tell me to invite you to dinner?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU THE NUMBER</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE TWISTING THE KNIFE RIGHT NOW  YOU GET OFF ON IT</pattern><template>That's bullshit! That's not true! Don't say that!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD SHE DO THAT  WAS IT A TEST</pattern><template>I kinda got that feeling, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT WAS JUST THE WAY I WANTED IT  BUT HE CUT IT BACK TOO FAR</pattern><template>He cut this side back too far trying to even it up. I didn't tell him to do that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE</pattern><template>Well, Martin Van Buren, the eighth president of the United States of America, is from Kinderhook, New York...</template></category><category><pattern>ISN'T THE MARKET DOWN  THOUGH</pattern><template>It is down, but you know, she wants more, so I'm giving her more, man.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  I DON'T</pattern><template>Where?</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  I NEED TO ASK YOU SOMETHING</pattern><template>Tomorrow can I spend half the day with you and half the day at the Eagles game?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  WHATS THIS</pattern><template>Everything good? Mm hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT  YOU SEEM LIKE YOU'RE A TOUGH GIRL TO ME  WHY DON'T YOU JUST DO THINGS ON YOUR OWN</pattern><template>I always get myself in these fucking situations. I give everything to other people and nobody ever, I never... I don't get what I want, okay? I'm not my sister.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WAIT A MINUTE  WAIT A MINUTE  HELLO</pattern><template>Yeah! It looks great now. You like it?</template></category><category><pattern>I TOOK IT TOO FAR</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  PAT  COME ON  A LITTLE BIT MORE SOUL  BLACK IT UP  PAT</pattern><template>Black it up ? You know damn well what it means.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN  YOU CAN'T</pattern><template>I don't have the controls. I'm sorry, I  Did Doctor Timbers put you up to this?</template></category><category><pattern>BARTENDER  BARTENDER  CAN I GET A VODKA  PLEASE</pattern><template>So, you want another one? Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY IS SHE A SLUT</pattern><template>After the dinner at Ronnie's, she said, quote,  We can go to the back house and you can fuck me as long as we turn the lights out.   Unquote. And she still wears her wedding ring.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WROTE THAT A WEEK AGO  YES  I DID</pattern><template>You let me lie to you for a week? I was trying to be romantic.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A JOKE</pattern><template>It's a... fireplace.</template></category><category><pattern>TEA BE RIGHT BACK</pattern><template>You look nice.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE ARE GONNA MAKE IT TO THE NEXT ROUND  WE'RE GONNA BEAT</pattern><template>No, that was me that did that. No that was me.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIED</pattern><template>Tommy died? Cops die.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>Hey, what's up?</template></category><category><pattern>PAT</pattern><template>Mom!</template></category><category><pattern>MOM  FOR WHAT  I CAN'T APOLOGIZE</pattern><template>I'm not gonna apologize for this.</template></category><category><pattern>BENJAMIN FRANKLIN  THE FOUNDER OF OUR COUNTRY  HERE IN PHILADELPHIA</pattern><template>You mean the guy with the... ... little glasses and the long scraggly hair?</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  I DON'T WANNA WAKE UP THE BABY  BYE</pattern><template>Listen, I haven't dated since before my marriage so I don't really remember how this works.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  DAD  GOOD</pattern><template>Okay, the question, the big question, is what are you gonna do with yourself?</template></category><category><pattern>I ALWAYS GET MYSELF IN THESE FUCKING SITUATIONS  I GIVE EVERYTHING TO OTHER PEOPLE AND NOBODY EVER  I NEVER    I DON'T GET WHAT I WANT  OKAY  I'M NOT MY SISTER</pattern><template>Alright, well, ask for you. What can I do for you?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GONNA BE AMAZING  AND YOU'RE GONNA BE AMAZING  AND SHE'S GONNA BE AMAZING  AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE THAT GUY THAT'S GONNA TAKE ADVANTAGE OF A SITUATION WITHOUT OFFERING TO DO SOMETHING BACK</pattern><template>So think about the dance thing.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  YOU SAY SHIT YOU DON'T MEAN ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>All the time. I'll still give your letter to Nikki, don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YOU DO</pattern><template>No, I don't.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LET'S START SIMPLE  START AT THAT CORNER  WALK TOWARDS ME</pattern><template>Walk across the room.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD WRITE THAT DOWN IN YOUR  I DON'T KNOW YOUR LITTLE BOOK YOU WRITE STUFF DOWN IN</pattern><template>I'm sorry about that song. I just wanted to see if it was still a trigger for you.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW VERONICA STILL HATES ME  THAT'S NOT TRUE</pattern><template>Yes, it is. Nikki always said that  Ronnie's wife keeps his social calendar where she keeps his balls, in her purse.   That's not true.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OVER HERE</pattern><template>DeSean Jackson's in the house!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS SCARED  ABOUT WHAT  DID SHE TELL YOU</pattern><template>Try to stay positive.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  GOOD EVENING  EVENING</pattern><template>Check in? How many dancers are there?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A  IT'S A DANCE THING</pattern><template>It's a dance thing, all right.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE IN LOVE AND WE'RE MARRIED</pattern><template>It's completely different.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT HE'S GOTTA DO THIS THING  HE CAN'T BE A QUITTER</pattern><template>He cannot be a quitter.</template></category><category><pattern>HUH  ANYBODY  DO YOU  DO YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Excelsior.   Look it up.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TOUCH THEM  DON'T TOUCH THEM</pattern><template>I didn't even touch 'em. Why are you..., don't blame me.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WHAT</pattern><template>My tea. Can I finish it?</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  PATRIZIO  DON'T  IT'S TOXIC</pattern><template>I have faith, I have faith.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT THE LIGHTNING WITH THE KITE  HE STOOD IN THE STORM WITH A KITE</pattern><template>If he wasn't on the hundred dollar bill, nobody... ... would even know who he is.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  EXCELSIOR  LISTEN  I HAVE A LETTER I WANT YOU TO GIVE NIKKI  OKAY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A COURT ORDER AGAINST YOU</pattern><template>five hundred feet. Listen to me!</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T WATCH MY WEDDING VIDEO  BUT I CAN HEAR THE FUCKING SONG MOM</pattern><template>What the fuck you doing?!</template></category><category><pattern>IS HE THE GUY WHO'S HAVING THE PROBLEM</pattern><template>People are stupid. They, they, they, they don't know what they're saying.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OFF</pattern><template>Take it easy. Dude, relax.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T YOU BELIEVE IN AMERICA'S TEAM</pattern><template>Yeah, Randy, don't you believe in America's Team?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE RIGHT  MAN  YOU'RE RIGHT  YOU'RE RIGHT  EAGLES  BABY  YEAH  LET'S GO</pattern><template>What the fuck? What's that smell?</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  I'M NOT GONNA BE A PART OF THIS  RANDY  RANDY  YOU'RE A SICKNESS  YOU'RE A FUCKING SICKNESS  RANDY  I'M OUT</pattern><template>Pat, you can't quit. I'm not doing the dance. I'm out.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WAS AT THE DOOR</pattern><template>Who was that, Dad?</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN WITH ALL HIS FRIENDS  WITH ALL HIS FRIENDS  HE TRUSTS YOU</pattern><template>He's not embarrassed?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER EVERYTHING</pattern><template>I want you to remember all of the good stuff that we have here.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT A BAD THING</pattern><template>No, I think, it's a good thing.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  MOM</pattern><template>What happened over there?</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  PERSONALLY  I THINK IT'S A STUPID BET  AS A MATTER OF FACT  I THINK IT'S RIDICULOUS TO BET ALL THAT DOUGH FOR THE RESTAURANT ON A GAME</pattern><template>Randy. I just hope you heard what I said. It's like a family business, it's our family endeavor. We all stick together on this.</template></category><category><pattern>I COME HOME FROM WORK AFTER I</pattern><template>fight with Nancy, the high school ... principal.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE YOU GO</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>EACH DANCER IS SCORED ON A SCALE OF ONE TO TEN  TEN BEING THE HIGHEST</pattern><template>You have to average the four judges' scores.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK THAT I'M CRAZIER THAN YOU</pattern><template>Because, well, we're different, I mean  Oh, my God. Ugh. You're killing me.</template></category><category><pattern>BENJAMIN FRANKLIN  THAT'S WHAT'S MORE AMERICAN</pattern><template>Benjamin Franklin?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY  WAIT A SECOND  WHAT ARE YOU DOING  WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>How come you weren't outside?</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU JUST THROW THAT OUTSIDE</pattern><template>What? You're not gonna read that shit on my time. I can tell you all about the  Lord of the Flies.   It's a bunch of boys on an island and they have a conch... they have a shell ... and whoever has the conch has the power and they can talk.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT THE BOOKS  YOU SAID NIKKI'S FRIENDS WITH RONNIE  VERONICA AND TIFFANY  SO IF YOU BECOME FRIENDS WITH TIFFANY  NIKKI WILL THINK THAT YOU'RE A KIND  GENEROUS  LARGE HEARTED PERSON  WHO HELPS PEOPLE IN NEED  WHO IS BASICALLY THRIVING  SO IF YOU HELP TIFFANY  IT WILL BE GOOD FOR YOU</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU</pattern><template>Is that...? You're asking me, you're really asking me that question?</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA READ IT OUT LOUD</pattern><template>Okay. Sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SO MUCH CLEARER WITHOUT THEM  MOM  THEY MAKE ME BLOATED</pattern><template>I don't like the way it makes me look.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOVE IT  VON  BECAUSE THEN YOU CAN BE THE GOOD ONE  JUST SAY IT</pattern><template>No... I don't. I don't. I just wanted to have a nice, I just wanted to have a nice dinner. Oh, God.</template></category><category><pattern>COME SIT DOWN</pattern><template>Don't disappear doing God knows what with that Tiffany Maxwell.</template></category><category><pattern>NIKKI REPLIED TO YOUR LETTER</pattern><template>But you can't read it until after you nail the big move. Go.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAW THE WAY YOU WERE LOOKING AT ME  PAT</pattern><template>You felt it, I felt it, don't lie. We're not liars like they are.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW COME YOU WEREN'T OUTSIDE</pattern><template>What the hell's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>SO I'M GONNA BET HEAVY ON THIS GAME</pattern><template>You understand? Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE HE WANTS YOU TO GO</pattern><template>He told you that? He told me, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE WRITES ANOTHER ENDING</pattern><template>She dies, Dad! I mean, the world's hard enough as it is, guys. It's fucking hard enough as it is.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T DRINK TOO MUCH  DON'T HIT ANYBODY  YOU'LL BE FINE</pattern><template>Yeah. I'm solid.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FUCKING IDIOT  YOU SPIKE THE BALL ON THE ONE YARD LINE  WHO IS THIS   WHO'S THIS</pattern><template>We need to talk right now! When you make a serious commitment to somebody, it is not cool to not show up!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS MY NEIGHBORHOOD</pattern><template>You just ran by my house.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT ALLOWED TO TALK ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>Jesus Christ, who's that?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  I THINK IT WOULD BE WISE IF WE SPENT FATHER SON TIME  READING ABOUT THE EAGLES  TALKING ABOUT THEM  JUST TO STRENGTHEN THE GOOD LUCK THING THAT YOU'RE IN</pattern><template>Okay. Yeah? Right. Hmm?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA GET IT BACK</pattern><template>It's all gonna be better now.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  STOP IT</pattern><template>Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOVE IT WHEN I HAVE PROBLEMS</pattern><template>You love it, Von, because then you can be the good one. Just say it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED TO TOMMY</pattern><template>He died.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  A LOT WENT DOWN</pattern><template>People will get over it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO GO  IT'S PART OF THE DEAL</pattern><template>You can't live with us and not go.</template></category><category><pattern>OH GOD  RANDY  I THOUGHT THEY WERE AMERICA'S TEAM</pattern><template>Don't you believe in America's Team?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW COULD YOU NOT TAKE THAT BET</pattern><template>Even with the ten points I give you, that's an insane spread to your advantage. Cowboys are cowards. And I'll bet you're such a coward, you won't take the ten.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S EVERYBODY MAKING A JOKE OUT OF THIS FOR</pattern><template>Dolores, you are so beautiful!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON MAN WHAT YOU GONNA DO ABOUT THAT SONG</pattern><template>You gonna go your whole life scared of that song?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW YOU DO</pattern><template>You do? Yeah, sure. I'll see you tomorrow? With the letter?</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE DON'T REACT QUICKLY TO THIS  BUT TAKE TIME TO THINK ABOUT IT</pattern><template>I'm glad you're doing so well. Love, Nikki.   I think I'm done for today, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH YOU'D WATCH THESE GAMES WITH ME SO WE COULD TALK  WE COULD GET INTO THINGS</pattern><template>So would you, would you just come downstairs and talk to me and Randy now?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  HEY  CALM DOWN  HEY  JUST LEAVE ME ALONE</pattern><template>Can I just explain myself, please?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  OUR MARRIAGE</pattern><template>we're very, very much in love, okay? Just like you two.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH   EXCELSIOR    OH PAT</pattern><template>Not that I give a fuck about football or about your superstitions, but if it's me reading the signs, I don't send the Eagles guy whose personal motto is  Excelsior,   to a fucking Giants game, especially when he's already in a legal situation.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YES  THAT COULD WORK  I LOVE THAT</pattern><template>Oh, my God, I'm gonna go home and write the letter right now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE AN ASSHOLE  YOU ARE AN ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Get off of me! Get off!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  TOMMY'S DEAD  SO HE'S NOT GONNA FUCKING DO IT</pattern><template>Would you please! I don't have a filter when I talk.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  YOU HAVE TO HAVE A STRATEGY  I TOLD YOU EARLIER</pattern><template>You need to recognize these feelings coming to you, otherwise you will be sent back to Baltimore. So when you get these feelings, you need to get to a quieter place, and be at peace with yourself, however you can.</template></category><category><pattern>HE CUT THIS SIDE BACK TOO FAR TRYING TO EVEN IT UP  I DIDN'T TELL HIM TO DO THAT</pattern><template>I said,  Just cut it the way you cut it...   Once you get in the right frame of mind, I think anything's possible.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T EVEN HAVE A PHONE</pattern><template>They won't let me make any calls.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING FOR ME  YOU SAID  YOU SAID IF I WROTE A LETTER  YOU'D GET IT TO NIKKI  I KNOW  THAT WAS THE SET UP</pattern><template>Because I do this time after time after time, I do all this shit for other people and then I wake up and, and I'm empty, I have nothing!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T BE HAPPY ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>Who told you you can't be happy?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S MORE AMERICAN THAN A COWBOY</pattern><template>You know what's more American? What?</template></category><category><pattern>I LIKE IT  NO  NO  PATRIZIO  I BELIEVE IN THE EAGLES  I BELIEVE IN MY SON  I'LL TAKE THE ACTION  I'LL TAKE IT</pattern><template>Dad! Patrizio, don't! It's toxic!</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE SHE JUST NEEDS A FRIEND AND SHE THOUGHT IF SHE OFFERS YOU SEX  IT WILL BE EASIER FOR YOU TO BECOME FRIENDS WITH HER</pattern><template>She said she's not a whore anymore, but she likes that part of herself along with all the other parts of herself and can I say the same?</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  PATRICK  SHE'S GONE  SHE'S NOT AROUND ANYMORE  NIKKI LEFT</pattern><template>What are you doing, Dad? You know what?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A DANCE THING  OKAY  THERE'S NOTHING MORE TO IT  DAD  I SWEAR</pattern><template>Listen, I need to ask you something.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK SO  LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>Be my guest.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  FOR  OH  MAYBE THREE HOURS  PLUS</pattern><template>Everything's good, everything's good, yeah. I got you, you're all down. No, Randy, he's complaining. You know he lost a lot of money. He's moaning and groaning. The restaurant's happening because of Randy, so everything's good.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY FAULT  PAT DIDN'T KNOW</pattern><template>Pat didn't know. He's my friend, so he was rootin' for me. I'm havin' a disagreement with the hospital, but we're working it out.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT FBI  COME ON  LET'S TAKE A LOOK  I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT THIS IS</pattern><template>I'm gonna just explain to you something. I mean, you know what I'm doing, honey. This everything, like this.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GOD  OH  GOD</pattern><template>Nance! This is my lucky day!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TELLING YOU  DON'T FUCK THIS UP</pattern><template>I love you, Dad.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS JUST A VERY GENERAL LETTER</pattern><template>Cool. She's fine. She is my friend with an  F.   A capital  F.   For  friend.   Hey, can I see what you guys are doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST CONFIRMING</pattern><template>I'm just confirming. Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I THINK  IT'S A GOOD THING</pattern><template>Don't drink too much. Don't hit anybody. You'll be fine.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY TO GET HIM TO SHOW</pattern><template>What's that? Oh, what's that?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE ON THEIR WAY TO THE PLAYOFFS</pattern><template>Where's Tiffany?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT    A CALL ASKING TO</pattern><template>...check on this house. Pat Solatano?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT YOUR JOB</pattern><template>I just got fired, actually.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I USED TO THINK THAT YOU WERE THE BEST THING THAT EVER HAPPENED TO ME  BUT NOW I THINK THAT YOU MIGHT MAYBE BE THE WORST THING AND I'M SORRY THAT I EVER MET YOU</pattern><template>Good for you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH JERSEY</pattern><template>DeSean Jackson.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK OF EVERYTHING EVERYONE DID FOR ME AND I FEEL LIKE    A VERY LUCKY GUY</pattern><template>We have to beat the Vikings by three. I'm givin' you a six, which is very generous after the beating you just took. So what are we doin', what are we talkin' about here?</template></category><category><pattern>DESEAN JACKSON</pattern><template>DeSean Jackson is the man.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  JAKE YOU BETTER GET YOUR BROTHER</pattern><template>Cuckoo bird's takin' off. Doctor Patel!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN TAKE TIFFANY HOME FIRST</pattern><template>You love it when I have problems.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A PROBLEM  YOU SAY MORE INAPPROPRIATE THINGS THAN APPROPRIATE THINGS  YOU SCARE PEOPLE</pattern><template>I tell the truth. But you're mean.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO OTHER WAY</pattern><template>You know, we gotta leave a trail of bread crumbs so that he can live his life without ruining it.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME ABOUT IT  I WANNA UNDERSTAND IT</pattern><template>We have a very unconventional chemistry, it makes people feel awkward, but not me. She's the most beautiful woman I've ever been with.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I THINK   OH  THAT'S KINDA SWEET  SHE'S IN THE SHOWER</pattern><template>What a perfect thing. I'm gonna find her and maybe I'll go in there.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A SECOND  I HAVE ONE MORE LETTER FOR YOU TO READ  OKAY</pattern><template>What the fuck is the matter with you? Give it to her yourself!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S TRUE LOVE</pattern><template>Yeah, that's when I had long hair.</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T TAKE THAT</pattern><template>However, wait a second. I do like the idea of a parlay.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T  MOM  I CAN'T</pattern><template>I will call them. They'll come for you.</template></category><category><pattern>THIRTY TWO GIGABYTES  HOW MANY SONGS IS THAT  SEVEN THOUSAND</pattern><template>Oh, yeah, you got The Stranglers.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A CONFORMIST  YOU'RE A LIAR</pattern><template>I opened up to you and you judged me.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T ALMOST HAVE IT  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>I just hope you can handle it. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GUYS HAVE A BEAUTIFUL THING THAT GOT BROKEN SOMEWHERE ALONG THE LINE AND YOU GOTTA FIX IT LIKE A CHIROPRACTOR</pattern><template>You gotta give it a chiropractic adjustment.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW WHO HIS TEAM IS  WHEN IS THE GAME</pattern><template>December twenty eight, last game of the season.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE VERY  GOOD NEWS  EVERYBODY  VERY GOOD NEWS</pattern><template>What's that? What's the good news?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  I HAVE A STUPID SENSE OF HUMOR</pattern><template>That's not a good thing to do.</template></category><category><pattern>SORT OF LIKE ME</pattern><template>Sort of like you ? I hope to God she didn't tell Nikki that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WAS THAT  DAD</pattern><template>It was that kid with the camera.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE SCORES FOR SANTOS AND AGUILAR ARE: SEVEN POINT SIX  SEVEN POINT THREE  SEVEN POINT FOUR  AND SIX POINT NINE FOR AN AVERAGE SCORE OF SEVEN POINT THREE</pattern><template>Three, two, one! Philadelphia beats Dallas!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  MOM  YOU OKAY</pattern><template>I am out on a limb for you with the courts right now.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  IT'S A TELEVISION  IT'S A COMPUTER SCREEN  NOPE</pattern><template>Just keep going, keep going, keep going.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>Sort of how you are. It's fine, relax.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  COME ON  LOOK  I DON'T THINK YOU'RE CRAZY  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Yes, you do.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME</pattern><template>I'm good with a hammer. You want me to fix something? A deal is a deal.</template></category><category><pattern>TIFFANY  HEY  TIFFANY</pattern><template>Slow down, Raisin Bran.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW YOU DOING  JAKE  GOOD  YOU LOOK LIKE SCHWARZENEGGER IN HIS PRIME</pattern><template>Didn't I say you wouldn't recognize him?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT ENCOURAGES HIM  TIFFANY  YOU SHOULDN'T DO IT</pattern><template>Couldn't you say the same about you and Nikki?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  RANDY  JAKE  WHAT DO WE GOT</pattern><template>Dallas just tied with another field goal, three three.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  WELL  ASK FOR YOU  WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU</pattern><template>I can't do it. Tiffany, what do you want me to do?</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD CALL NIKKI</pattern><template>I'm actually gonna give you one of my iPods. I have an old one.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD YOU TELL ME THAT  YOU KNOW HE BROKE UP MY MARRIAGE</pattern><template>What, are you being, a troublemaker?</template></category><category><pattern>THINK OF SOMETHING  THERE'S THIS THING</pattern><template>There's a thing, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW SIT UP  AND DANNY'S THE GOOD LUCK CHARM</pattern><template>Danny's from you. This is your house, so it comes down to you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT'S NO BULLSHIT</pattern><template>That's no bullshit. That takes work and that's the truth.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA PRETEND THAT YOU DIDN'T JUST ASK ME THAT</pattern><template>Why? These are the two days that you have promised me and that we have prepared to nail the big move. It's not ready yet.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>No, no, no, listen, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS READING</pattern><template>Please. Do us a favor, don't read for a while.</template></category><category><pattern>DID OUR LITTLE CONVERSATION GET YOU UPSET LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>Hey, this is my route, okay? Just back off.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I SAY SOMETHING  DO YOU MIND  NO</pattern><template>You sure? Just say it. Say it.</template></category><category><pattern>SORT OF LIKE YOU   I HOPE TO GOD SHE DIDN'T TELL NIKKI THAT</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER UNDERSTAND WHAT HE'S SAYING</pattern><template>Okay, jailhouse lawyer, come on, let's come back and sit down the way you were before.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  I HAVEN'T DATED SINCE BEFORE MY MARRIAGE SO I DON'T REALLY REMEMBER HOW THIS WORKS</pattern><template>How what works?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  PAT  TIFFANY</pattern><template>Hey. What a glorious, beautiful occasion, man.</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK THIS OUT  WE JUST REDID THE WHOLE THING</pattern><template>Wow!</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T HAVE THE CONTROLS  I'M SORRY  I  DID DOCTOR TIMBERS PUT YOU UP TO THIS</pattern><template>Is there a speaker here?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT CALMING DOWN  I DON'T GIVE A FUCK WHO HEARS  I'M NOT CALMING DOWN</pattern><template>Anybody can wake up!</template></category><category><pattern>DANNY'S FROM YOU  THIS IS YOUR HOUSE  SO IT COMES DOWN TO YOU</pattern><template>You're the one. Yeah, you're the one, Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT OF PEOPLE  MY UNCLE  TOO</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST KEEP GOING  KEEP GOING  KEEP GOING</pattern><template>It's a brick oven, it's a brick oven. It's a light. It's a...</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN ARE YOU GONNA GIVE IT TO HER</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>OH YEAH  HE'S FINE NOW  YOU WANNA SEND HIM BACK TO BALTIMORE</pattern><template>We know all about the explosion at the psychiatrist's office.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE BET</pattern><template>I'm worried about the bet.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T FOCUS ON THAT</pattern><template>I would call Nikki.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY ABOUT WHAT I SAID IN THE DINER</pattern><template>I know. I know you didn't mean it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WOULD FIGHT  WE WOULDN'T TALK FOR A COUPLE WEEKS  THAT'S NORMAL  SHE ALWAYS WANTED THE BEST FOR ME</pattern><template>She wanted me to be passionate and compassionate. And that's a good thing. You know? I just, look, I'm my best self today, and I think she's her best self today, and our love's gonna be fucking amazing.</template></category><category><pattern>I FEEL LIKE I'M GETTING CRUSHED AND  CRUSHED BY WHAT</pattern><template>Everything. The family, the baby, the job, the fucking dicks at work, and it's like, you know, like I'm trying to do this, you know, and, and, and I'm like... suffocating.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>Dad, I'm in there because of the court.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S OKAY  EVERYTHING IS OKAY  WE'RE FINE  THANK YOU  WE APPRECIATE IT  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT WILL BE</pattern><template>I'm gonna take that as a silver development, Nancy!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  WE GOTTA LEAVE A TRAIL OF BREAD CRUMBS SO THAT HE CAN LIVE HIS LIFE WITHOUT RUINING IT</pattern><template>No. I don't approve. You can't do it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE YOU GIVING ME SUCH A HARD TIME</pattern><template>No, I'm not giving you a hard time.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  SHIT  THE ASIAN INVASION</pattern><template>They're here every week! No!</template></category><category><pattern>LL OF A SUDDEN I SEE THE DVD PLAYER  AND ON THE D</pattern><template>...</template></category><category><pattern>CALM DOWN  CRAZY</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>What's in that envelope?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE</pattern><template>I just came by to say hi, to let you know I'm ready to come back to work.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  I REALLY APPRECIATE THAT  TIFFANY</pattern><template>I know you do.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SAY SOMETHING  I GOTTA SAY SOMETHING</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT  OH  WHAT'S THAT</pattern><template>We have to tell him Nikki's gonna be there.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A SILVER LINING</pattern><template>Good luck.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I ALSO MENTIONED HOW GENEROUS IT IS  WHAT I'M DOING FOR YOU</pattern><template>Yeah. Mm hmm. It's really generous.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  I'M OUT</pattern><template>Here we are again at the one yard line. DeSean, snatching defeat from the jaws of victory. There you go.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU</pattern><template>I knew it the minute I met you.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  NOT MY BROTHER  HEY  HEY  HEY</pattern><template>Break it up or you'll be arrested!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT WAS ME THAT DID THAT  NO THAT WAS ME</pattern><template>That was me. I played the Jack.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT  YOU DON'T TALK TO ME  YOU DIDN'T TELL ME YOU TOOK HIM OUT</pattern><template>Well, he's ready. Look at him.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  BUT LISTEN TO ME  THIS IS TOXIC  DAD  DAD  DAD  THIS IS TOXIC  YOU SHOULDN'T BE DOING THIS  YOU SHOULDN'T BE DOING  RANDY  WHAT DO YOU SAY</pattern><template>Be quiet, shut up. You already did enough. Randy, what do you say?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT DRIVES ME CRAZY  AND YES  I WAS NEGATIVE  YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THAT I LOVED IT  NIKKI  BUT I DID</pattern><template>I just didn't appreciate it, or you, before.   Come on. Time to go.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP THAT  HEY  HEY  HEY  STOP  STOP  STOP</pattern><template>Listen, a lot of envelopes go in and out of my office every day after games with a lot of cash in 'em. So show some respect for what I do.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FATHER EXPECTS TO SPEND TIME WITH YOU  PAT</pattern><template>Football stays out of this place, so does  Lord of the Flies.   Wait, wait, no, no, no, what are you doing? I'm behind on my syllabus.</template></category><category><pattern>AREN'T YOU NERVOUS TO BE LYING</pattern><template>Yeah. A little bit.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU'RE OUT OUT</pattern><template>Uh huh.</template></category><category><pattern>DOUBLE OR NOTHING ON THE BENGALS  NEXT WEEK  IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING</pattern><template>Against the Cowboys.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  ARE YOU FUCKING NUTS</pattern><template>Pat, the silver lining thing is yours. I'm just giving back your words to you. This  crazy sad shit,   as you call it, made you a happier, calmer person with a beautiful positive philosophy of going outdoors, working out, and reading books.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU  LET HIM STAY  PLEASE</pattern><template>I don't know what the hell you're talking about  the handkerchief .</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT DOING IT  DO IT  NO  THAT'S STUPID</pattern><template>No walk, no letter. Walk to me like I'm Nikki, come on. Do it. I'm Nikki. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S YOUR TEAM ISN'T IT  RANDY  THAT'S HIS TEAM</pattern><template>I know who his team is. When is the game?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DON'T HAVE AN IPOD</pattern><template>I don't even have a phone.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A COMPETITION THING AT THE BENJAMIN FRANKLIN HOTEL</pattern><template>Tommy would never do it with me and I missed it every single year.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GONNA MAKE THAT  THAT  THAT CONNECTION THAT YOU'RE MAKING WITH DESEAN JACKSON  IT DOESN'T MATTER ANYMORE OKAY  JUST BECAUSE I HAVE THE FUCKING JERSEY ON</pattern><template>I'm not gonna do it. I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>MARIA  I JUST MET A GIRL NAMED MARIA      RIGHT  RIGHT  RIGHT</pattern><template>And then when I'm angry, which is a lot these days, I go to the garage... Metallica... Megadeth.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN WITH THE TEN POINTS I GIVE YOU  THAT'S AN INSANE SPREAD TO YOUR ADVANTAGE  COWBOYS ARE COWARDS  AND I'LL BET YOU'RE SUCH A COWARD  YOU WON'T TAKE THE TEN</pattern><template>Plus, are you listening, plus whatever their score is at the dance thing. What's that?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANT US TO BE FRIENDS</pattern><template>Did you hear what I said?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HOW YOU DOIN'  IS TIFFANY HERE</pattern><template>What do you want with her?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT THE BIG SLUT</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WITH MOOD SWINGS AND WEIRD THINKING BROUGHT ON BY SEVERE STRESS  WHICH RARELY HAPPENS  THANK GOD</pattern><template>And then the shower incident happened and that's when everything snapped, so I then realized that, oh, wow, I've been dealing with this my whole life. And without any supervision I've been doing it all on my own with no help and basically I've been white knuckling it this whole time.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU KNOW WHAT HE SAYS TO ME   YOU SHOULD PROBABLY GO    THAT'S WHAT HE SAYS TO ME</pattern><template>So yeah, I snapped. I almost beat him to death. But now I get fucking chastised for it? I'm parallel to my father? I don't think so.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE THERE IN A MINUTE</pattern><template>That's true love.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE HARASSING ME</pattern><template>Hey, hey!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I'M TOMMY'S CRAZY WHORE WIDOW  MINUS THE WHORE THING FOR THE MOST PART</pattern><template>You're a funny girl. You wanna get a drink sometime?</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME ONE THING  WOULD YOU LIKE TO BE A GUY WHO GOES BACK TO JAIL OR TO THE HOSPITAL  HMM  SO TAKE YOUR MEDICATION AND IF YOU DO FINE  WE'LL REDUCE THEM</pattern><template>Nikki's waiting for me to get in shape and get my life in order, and then she's gonna be with me. And that's better than any medication.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO TELL HIM THAT SHE'S GOING</pattern><template>But that's a lie! It's a white lie.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S CHASING ME  THIS GUY'S CHASING ME  HELP ME</pattern><template>Sit down!</template></category><category><pattern>TEACHER WITH TENURE</pattern><template>And you know what he says to me?  You should probably go.   That's what he says to me.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES NIKKI STILL WORK HERE</pattern><template>You know I can't tell you that.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE  HELP ME  HELP ME</pattern><template>You can't tell Nikki about this, Officer.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T LOOK UP UNTIL YOU'RE HALFWAY HERE</pattern><template>Yes. Do you feel that? That's emotion.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'D LOVE TO GO TO THE GAME  TOO  BUT AS YOU KNOW  I'M BANNED FROM THE STADIUM  'CAUSE I'D LOVE TO SEE US BEAT THE GIANTS AND TAKE A LOT OF MONEY FROM THIS ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Listen, personally, I think it's a stupid bet. As a matter of fact, I think it's ridiculous to bet all that dough for the restaurant on a game.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE OUR HOUSE  I'M REALLY EXCITED ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS WHEN I WAS AN X RAY TECHNICIAN WITH MY ADD AND MY ANXIETY  I HAD A LOT OF ACCESS TO MEDICATION AND I TOOK ADVANTAGE OF IT  THAT'S WHEN MY HAIR WAS LONG  TOO</pattern><template>But my hair only grew when I was older. When I was younger, my hair didn't grow because my brother...</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS CHRIST  WHO'S THAT</pattern><template>Keep an eye on him.</template></category><category><pattern>MM HMM</pattern><template>Oh... my God. Nikki hated when I talked like this.</template></category><category><pattern>ISN'T IT GREAT</pattern><template>Tremendous.</template></category><category><pattern>DOCTOR'S WAITING  LET'S GO</pattern><template>I'll be there in a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK THAT MAKES ME A CRIMINAL  ANYWAY ONE NIGHT AFTER DINNER  HE DROVE TO VICTORIA'S SECRET AT KING OF PRUSSIA MALL AND GOT SOME LINGERIE TO GET SOMETHING GOING  AND ON THE WAY BACK  HE STOPPED ON 76 TO HELP A GUY WITH A FLAT TIRE AND HE GOT HIT BY A CAR AND KILLED  AND THE VICTORIA'S SECRET BOX WAS STILL IN THE FRONT SEAT  THAT'S A FEELING</pattern><template>Whoa! Slow down. What?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  IS HE MESSING WITH YOU</pattern><template>No, no. No, this was just a joke. This is a joke I started.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL RIGHT  YOU JUST DO YOUR BEST  YOU HAVE NO CHOICE</pattern><template>That's not true at all. You just can't.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST BRAGGING ABOUT YOU  CAN'T I BRAG ABOUT MY LITTLE SISTER</pattern><template>Don't talk about me in the third person.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS CHRIST  WAS IT LIKE    OLDER WOMEN  A SEXY TEACHER WHO WANTS TO SEDUCE YOU  MADE ME SIT ON HER LAP AND DO THINGS  YEAH</pattern><template>What? You sat on her lap?</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE YOU'RE OKAY WITH VERONICA'S SISTER COMING OVER</pattern><template>You okay with that? Who?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T LET TIFFANY GET YOU IN TROUBLE</pattern><template>Pat, you're up to something, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT  THE</pattern><template>Oh, no way!</template></category><category><pattern>MY TEA  CAN I FINISH IT</pattern><template>Wait a minute. Did Veronica tell Nikki about our dinner?</template></category><category><pattern>BRAVO  IT'S A TRIGGER  I'M NOT GONNA TAKE ANY MEDS  I SHOULD JUST TELL YOU THAT RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>No, You have to take medicine.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW</pattern><template>The third time we got together we had Raisin Bran in the diner and the Phillies dominated Tampa Bay in the fourth game of the World Series, ten to two.</template></category><category><pattern>MOM  JUST LISTEN    DON'T TOU</pattern><template>...</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN SEE IT IN YOUR EYES  SHE JUST TEXTED ME</pattern><template>Hey! Hey, wait a second! What are you doing? What happened?</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE YOU CAN TEACH US BOTH  YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN</pattern><template>And I also mentioned how generous it is, what I'm doing for you.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH ALL MY CRAZY SAD SHIT</pattern><template>What, are you fucking nuts?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT  DAD</pattern><template>You haven't even seen us dance!</template></category><category><pattern>AND NIKKI WOULDN'T LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Especially after all the shit you just told me.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT  YEAH  THAT'S THE BIND WE'RE IN</pattern><template>I mean, I think it would be wise if we spent father son time, reading about the Eagles, talking about them, just to strengthen the good luck thing that you're in.</template></category><category><pattern>PAN FROM THE FRAMED PHOTO OF JAKE ON FOYER WALL  TO JAKE ON THE STAIRS ABOVE</pattern><template>A restraining order is nothing to fool with, bro. Holy shit, look at you! You are fit! You look absolutely amazing. You feel good?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S WHAT'S MEANT TO BE  YOU OKAY</pattern><template>Don't get wobbly on me. I'm not.</template></category><category><pattern>THE NEXT TIME WE WENT FOR A RUN THE EAGLES BEAT THE FALCONS  TWENTY  SEVEN TO FOURTEEN</pattern><template>Wow.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I'M READY  I'M READY TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR MY SIDE OF THE STREET</pattern><template>She just needs to take responsibility for hers.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT ANOTHER CREEP  WHAT DO YOU WANT  CREEP  JUST BEAT IT</pattern><template>Whoa, no, no, no. No, I'm married.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO SHARE THIS</pattern><template>Why did you order Raisin Bran?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY</pattern><template>He's harassing me!</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN GET A LETTER TO NIKKI  I SEE HER SOMETIMES WITH MY SISTER</pattern><template>It would be so amazing if you could get a letter to Nikki from me.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  YOU GUYS ARE STILL IN TOUCH WITH NIKKI  RIGHT</pattern><template>Does Veronica still talk to Nikki?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  TIFFANY'S BEEN DOING THIS DANCE THING FOR YEARS AND SHE'S REAL GOOD AT IT  SHE'S GONNA BE COMPETING AT THE BEN FRANKLIN HOTEL</pattern><template>Oh, really? My wife loves dance. Nikki loves dance.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HOW DID HE DIE</pattern><template>How did who die?</template></category><category><pattern>SURE</pattern><template>I'll see you next Sunday.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I MAKE A LOT OF MONEY  WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE IF I DO THIS OR THAT</pattern><template>It's a small thing. Sit down. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S LIKE MY THERAPY  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>When I'm with Nikki, I'm never gonna do stuff like that...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ALL  YOU STAY HERE AND WATCH THE GAME WITH ME</pattern><template>The birds are better when Pat is with me. We settled that.</template></category><category><pattern>NIKKI SOLD THE HOUSE  SHE LEFT</pattern><template>Didn't your mother tell you that?</template></category><category><pattern>HE DOESN'T HAVE A PROBLEM ASKING FOR HIS WEDDING VIDEO  BE NICE  IT'S GAME DAY  I'M MAKIN CRABBY SNACKS AND HOMEMADES</pattern><template>Yeah, come on, Dad, be nice. Come on, she's making crabby snacks and homemades. Come on, Dad!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR FACE</pattern><template>Weight lifting accident.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO DO IT  YOU HAVE NO CHOICE  EXCELSIOR</pattern><template>Yeah, Excelsior. Listen, I have a letter I want you to give Nikki, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE SEEING YOU  RIGHT  OUTSIDE THE OFFICE</pattern><template>Pat, Pat. That's illegal!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GREAT  A MARRIED CREEP  I'M HER FRIEND</pattern><template>We go running. Have you guys not seen us? I took her to the diner.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY WEDDING  IT'S MY WEDDING VIDEO</pattern><template>Pat! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!</template></category><category><pattern>THEN DON'T FUCKING DO THIS</pattern><template>Don't talk to me like that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS HER ENERGY WHEN SHE GAVE IT TO YOU</pattern><template>She was intrigued, excited, and a little scared.</template></category><category><pattern>BAD COMBINATION</pattern><template>Yeah. On top of an anxiety disorder.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE HAVE BEEN NO GAMES SINCE PAT AND I HAVE BEEN REHEARSING EVERY DAY AND IF PAT HAD BEEN WITH ME LIKE HE WAS SUPPOSED TO  HE WOULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN IN A FIGHT  HE WOULDN'T BE IN TROUBLE  MAYBE THE EAGLES BEAT THE NEW YORK GIANTS</pattern><template>She's making a lot of sense, Pop.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD ARE SCARED  I GOTTA COME IN</pattern><template>How are we doing in here, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>PAT WAS A HISTORY SUB AT THE HIGH SCHOOL  TIFFANY</pattern><template>Ask him about any president, he knows 'em all.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID  YEAH  I DID  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Get away from me! Get away!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT TRUE AT ALL  YOU JUST CAN'T</pattern><template>Ronnie, Ronnie, Ronnie!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I'M SORRY  I'M SORRY  OKAY  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>But I can only do it if I have a partner... and now I'm about to miss it for another year.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCELSIOR    LOOK IT UP</pattern><template>Yeah,  Excelsior.   Oh Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>I looked in here, but this is all your sewing shit up here, for your sewing and everything.</template></category><category><pattern>DESEAN JACKSON  YEAH  DID IT FIT</pattern><template>I wore it to Ronnie's for dinner.</template></category><category><pattern>DUDE  YOU'RE FINE  I LIKE THAT JERSEY</pattern><template>I wish I was wearing that jersey.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN'T GET FIVE  GIVE 'EM A FIVE  GIVE 'EM A FIVE</pattern><template>We can do a five.</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  YOU HAVE TO TAKE THAT BET ON THE COWBOYS</pattern><template>Dolores, would you stop him? Jesus!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOOK THAT STUPID PARLAY THING  AND NOW HE WON'T DO THE DANCE AND IT WAS VERY CONSTRUCTIVE FOR HIM  AND YOU RUINED IT</pattern><template>There's only one way to get him to show.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE NOT A STAND UP GUY RIGHT NOW  IF IT'S ME READING THE SIGNS    IF IT'S ME READING THE SIGNS  IF IT'S YOU READING THE SIGNS</pattern><template>You're reading the signs? Oh, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>VD PLAYER IS THE CD AND IT'S PLAYING OUR WEDDING SONG  AND THEN I LOOK DOWN AND I SEE MY WIFE'S</pattern><template>...panties on the ground and then  ...I look up and I see her naked in the shower...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU WOULD DO IT</pattern><template>I'd have to be careful. I'm already on thin ice with my family, you should hear how I lost my job.</template></category><category><pattern>OF ALL THE ROOMS THERE ARE IPOD PORTS IN  I'M HAPPY YOU BROUGHT US INTO THE BATHROOM</pattern><template>I can play music for the baby in any room.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HOW YOU DOING</pattern><template>So, Pat, what's this I hear about you just gettin' out?</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT PUT IT AS PART OF THE PARLAY  RANDY  DON'T   THEY GO BY THE PHILADELPHIA RULES</pattern><template>Each dancer is scored on a scale of one to ten, ten being the highest.</template></category><category><pattern>HONESTLY HE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING  IT WAS ALL THE KIDS</pattern><template>Let's go, clear out, nothing going on here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD MOVE MORE HIPS</pattern><template>Just, just sort of come in, Pat, come in like this. And...</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  TODAY I'M YOUR BROTHER IN GREEN  NOT YOUR THERAPIST  I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU  HOW WONDERFUL THAT YOU ARE HERE</pattern><template>Hey, Jake this is Cliff.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOOKED IN HERE  BUT THIS IS ALL YOUR SEWING SHIT UP HERE  FOR YOUR SEWING AND EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Did you put it up here?</template></category><category><pattern>TRAZODONE</pattern><template>Oh, it flattens you out.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANTED TO CLARIFY SOMETHING</pattern><template>I just want us to be friends.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS THAT LIKE</pattern><template>Hot.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HOW IT WORKS  THAT'S A POSITIVE  POSITIVE VIBE</pattern><template>I made a commitment to Tiffany about a project, and we have a very important part of it that we have to go over on Sunday, and it's good for me, Dad. It's making me disciplined and focused, and it's, it's..., I never would've thought this, but it's a good thing.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT  PAT SOLATANO AND TIFFANY MAXWELL</pattern><template>You know, I used to think that you were the best thing that ever happened to me, but now I think that you might maybe be the worst thing and I'm sorry that I ever met you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT SUPERSTITIOUS  THAT'S A SMALL THING THAT I DO</pattern><template>If I make a lot of money, what's the difference if I do this or that?</template></category><category><pattern>ELEVEN</pattern><template>Wow.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA PAY FOR IT  DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT</pattern><template>From your bookmaking?</template></category><category><pattern>FORGET THE ENTIRE FUCKING IDEA  'CAUSE THAT MUST HAVE BEEN FUCKING CRAZY BECAUSE I AM SO MUCH CRAZIER THAN YOU</pattern><template>Keep your voice down.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WHY DON'T YOU THINK ABOUT WHEN THE EAGLES BEAT THE SEAHAWKS  FOURTEEN TO SEVEN</pattern><template>He was with you? He was with me. We went for a run.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BETTER  I JUST WANT TO LET YOU KNOW  I'M BETTER NOW  OKAY</pattern><template>I'm better. I feel good. I feel so good. Look at my eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>I MADE A COMMITMENT TO TIFFANY ABOUT A PROJECT  AND WE HAVE A VERY IMPORTANT PART OF IT THAT WE HAVE TO GO OVER ON SUNDAY  AND IT'S GOOD FOR ME  DAD  IT'S MAKING ME DISCIPLINED AND FOCUSED  AND IT'S  IT'S     I NEVER WOULD'VE THOUGHT THIS  BUT IT'S A GOOD THING</pattern><template>What is this thing you're doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE  I'VE BEEN PLANNING THIS FOREVER  I LOVE OUR HOUSE</pattern><template>I love our house. I'm really excited about it.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ON TOP OF AN ANXIETY DISORDER</pattern><template>That was when I was an X ray technician with my ADD and my anxiety. I had a lot of access to medication and I took advantage of it. That's when my hair was long, too.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT BAD  DOCTOR JONES  BUT I DON'T THINK I'M GONNA BLOW IT WITH NIKKI BECAUSE TIFFANY'S A SLUT</pattern><template>Why is she a slut?</template></category><category><pattern>PATTY</pattern><template>It's probably in the attic.</template></category><category><pattern>DIDN'T YOUR MOTHER TELL YOU THAT</pattern><template>Let me tell you something. You don't know anything about my marriage, okay, Dad?</template></category><category><pattern>PULL THE CURTAIN BACK AND THERE'S THE FUCKING HISTORY</pattern><template>...</template></category><category><pattern>TIFFANY  PLEASE  SHE'LL SEE HOW WELL HE'S DOING  MAYBE SHE'LL LIFT THE RESTRAINING ORDER</pattern><template>Oh, my God. Oh, my God.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT  YOU'RE THE GUEST OF HONOR  YOU COME HOWEVER YOU WANNA COME</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY I'M LATE</pattern><template>It's fine.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT IN YOUR HAND</pattern><template>It's a... see?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WANTS ME TO HAVE   ALL THIS EAGLES INFORMATION</pattern><template>It's his living. Um, tell Dad thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M NOT GIVING YOU A HARD TIME</pattern><template>I don't know how to act with you when you do this shit.</template></category><category><pattern>I WENT BY YOUR PARENTS' HOUSE LOOKING FOR YOU AND THEY TOLD ME YOU WAS OVER HERE</pattern><template>Danny, this is Tiffany.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY I DIDN'T VISIT YOU IN THE HOSPITAL  YOU KNOW  WORK'S OUT OF CONTROL  YOU KNOW  SHE HAD THE BABY  I'M REALLY GLAD YOU'RE BACK</pattern><template>I missed you. I really need someone to talk to. You gotta come see the baby.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS</pattern><template>Are you taking the proper dosage of your medication?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NICE  THAT'S NICE</pattern><template>Well, thank God, finally.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT THE FUCK UP</pattern><template>Fuck you!</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T EVEN TOUCH 'EM  WHY ARE YOU     DON'T BLAME ME</pattern><template>Who did this? Who took, who took, who took the...</template></category><category><pattern>I COME HOME  WHAT DO I SEE  I WALK IN THE DOOR AND I SEE UNDERWEAR AND PIECES OF CLOTHING AND A GUY'S PANTS WITH HIS BELT IN IT  AND I WALK UP THE STAIRS  AND ALL</pattern><template>...ll of a sudden I see the DVD player, and on the D  ...</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  THAT WAS A GREAT SYNOPSIS</pattern><template>I still need to read it, though.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN PLAY MUSIC FOR THE BABY IN ANY ROOM</pattern><template>Can you play  Ride the Lightning  by Metallica?</template></category><category><pattern>THE WHOLE FAMILY'S TOGETHER  MOM MAKES BRACIOLE  DAD PUTS THE JERSEY ON</pattern><template>We're all watching the game.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S PROBABLY IN THE ATTIC</pattern><template>Are you going in my study?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M OUT  IT'S OFFICIAL  MAN</pattern><template>They didn't convert me to my Mental Hygiene Law admission status within two thirds of the maximum length of my felony sentence, so I'm out. They had to let me go.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MAKE IT A MONSTER</pattern><template>Come on breath! There's no song playing. There's no song.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I MESSED UP THE EAGLES' JUJU</pattern><template>No, you're not messing up the juju, but the juju is messed up because I'm not with him during the games.</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME HOME</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I KNOW  I SAW TWO SEVEN FOUR</pattern><template>I just wanted to tell you the number.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS ME  I PLAYED THE JACK</pattern><template>So you put the bread crumbs, the garlic in the steak and you roll it up with the toothpicks?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU GOING IN MY STUDY</pattern><template>It feels to me like you wanna hide my wedding video.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M NOT GONNA TAKE ANY MEDICINE  IT MAKES ME FOGGY  NO  YOU WILL HAVE TO TAKE MEDICATION</pattern><template>I don't want any meds, Doctor.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE YOU ORDERED RAISIN BRAN</pattern><template>I ordered Raisin Bran because I didn't want there to be any mistaking this for a date.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'D YOU DO  WHAT HAPPENED  DAD  WHAT THE FUCK HAPPENED  DAD</pattern><template>The birds lose, I lose a fuckin' fortune, a fortune to Randy!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S LIKE   WHAT  WHAT DAY IS IT   HOW ABOUT TRAZODONE</pattern><template>Trazodone!</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE  IT'S JUST NOT RIGHT  LUMPING YOU AND I TOGETHER  I MEAN  IT'S JUST WRONG</pattern><template>And Nikki wouldn't like that.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE DIES  DAD  I MEAN  THE WORLD'S HARD ENOUGH AS IT IS  GUYS  IT'S FUCKING HARD ENOUGH AS IT IS</pattern><template>Can't somebody say,  Hey, let's be positive?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>I'll bring him back right away.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  AND THE COURT SAID  THE COURT LISTENS TO THE DOCTOR  THE DOCTOR  DAD  RELAX  THE COURT SAID IT'S FINE  OKAY  LET IT GO</pattern><template>Don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK  I GOTTA WRITE THIS UP</pattern><template>Come on, don't write it up!</template></category><category><pattern>RONNIE  RONNIE  RONNIE</pattern><template>I hope you're okay with Veronica's sister coming over.</template></category><category><pattern>SORT OF HOW YOU ARE  IT'S FINE  RELAX</pattern><template>What do you mean? How am I? What does that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TALK TO ME LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Well then, don't behave this way.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW WHAT WORKS</pattern><template>I saw the way you were looking at me, Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE AFRAID TO BE ALIVE  YOU'RE AFRAID TO LIVE  YOU'RE A HYPOCRITE</pattern><template>You're a conformist. You're a liar.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D TOMMY DIE</pattern><template>What about your job?</template></category><category><pattern>EITHER DOLORES OR PAT NEEDED AN ENVELOPE AND ONE OF 'EM TOOK IT</pattern><template>That's the only answer. No, no, no.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE SAID SHE'S NOT A WHORE ANYMORE  BUT SHE LIKES THAT PART OF HERSELF ALONG WITH ALL THE OTHER PARTS OF HERSELF AND CAN I SAY THE SAME</pattern><template>Can you?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I GOT YOU AN IPOD</pattern><template>Whoa! Is this for me?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  MOM  HAVE YOU SEEN HER</pattern><template>You gotta find her. I know, Mom, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE TOLD YOU WHAT TO DO</pattern><template>Mm hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>IT FEELS TO ME LIKE YOU WANNA HIDE MY WEDDING VIDEO</pattern><template>Please stop yelling!</template></category><category><pattern>WE GO RUNNING  HAVE YOU GUYS NOT SEEN US  I TOOK HER TO THE DINER</pattern><template>She's not here.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT SONG  I JUST WANTED TO SEE IF IT WAS STILL A TRIGGER FOR YOU</pattern><template>Bravo. It's a trigger. I'm not gonna take any meds, I should just tell you that right now.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WHAT A GLORIOUS  BEAUTIFUL OCCASION  MAN</pattern><template>Yeah, yeah. All right, buddy, I'll see you. Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES ANYBODY HERE HAPPEN TO KNOW WHAT THE OFFICIAL MOTTO OF THE STATE OF NEW YORK IS ON THE OFFICIAL SEAL OF THE STATE OF NEW YORK</pattern><template>Huh? Anybody? Do you? Do you know?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S PLAYING AND I DON'T THINK ANYTHING OF IT  WHICH IS ODD  'CAUSE I SHOULD HAVE</pattern><template>I come home, what do I see? I walk in the door and I see underwear and pieces of clothing and a guy's pants with his belt in it, and I walk up the stairs, and all...</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT'S WORKING  YOUR DAD'S A GENIUS</pattern><template>Now sit up. And Danny's the good luck charm?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  OFFICER</pattern><template>If you need anything... my card.</template></category><category><pattern>CALM DOWN  PAT</pattern><template>I'm not calming down! I don't give a fuck who hears, I'm not calming down!</template></category><category><pattern>TRY TO STAY POSITIVE</pattern><template>I'm just gonna read it out loud, okay? Because if she says anything that's, you know, is that too much to ask?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BRING HIM BACK RIGHT AWAY</pattern><template>You lied to me, Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>ESPECIALLY AFTER ALL THE SHIT YOU JUST TOLD ME</pattern><template>You think that I'm crazier than you.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D HE DIE</pattern><template>Please, don't bring it up.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT THAT I GIVE A FUCK ABOUT FOOTBALL OR ABOUT YOUR SUPERSTITIONS  BUT IF IT'S ME READING THE SIGNS  I DON'T SEND THE EAGLES GUY WHOSE PERSONAL MOTTO IS  EXCELSIOR    TO A FUCKING GIANTS GAME  ESPECIALLY WHEN HE'S ALREADY IN A LEGAL SITUATION</pattern><template>Unbelievable. Wow. How did you know all that stuff?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SHE SAID YOU WERE COOL  BASICALLY</pattern><template>Basically ? Was I some percentage not cool?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU WEARING A GARBAGE BAG FOR  I'M GONNA GO RUN NOW</pattern><template>Wait, wait, wait. You have to fix this window.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE GOTTA TAKE YOUR MEDICATION</pattern><template>Why don't you just take your medication?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SOLID  I WAS SOLID AT THE GAME  DAD</pattern><template>I'm solid, I'm solid now.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN WHEN I'M ANGRY  WHICH IS A LOT THESE DAYS  I GO TO THE GARAGE    METALLICA    MEGADETH</pattern><template>I start fucking smashing shit.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  REALLY  MY WIFE LOVES DANCE  NIKKI LOVES DANCE</pattern><template>Why do you have to talk about me like that?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT AN IDEA  COME GET SOME  PAT  COME GET SOME</pattern><template>Shuffle back, shuffle back.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  I KNOW YOU DIDN'T MEAN IT</pattern><template>I didn't mean it at all.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>I thought you were gonna read it out loud.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD  SAME DAY AS THE BENJAMIN FRANKLIN PAIRS OPEN FREESTYLE DANCE COMPETITION</pattern><template>Oh God. Randy, I thought they were America's Team.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE WAS PART OF A CLUB  A MEN'S CLUB  CALLED OLD KINDERHOOK</pattern><template>And if you were cool, you were in the club, they'd say,  That guy's OK.   'Cause he was in the Old Kinderhooks.</template></category><category><pattern>OH</pattern><template>...and he was part of a club, a men's club, called Old Kinderhook.</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK ON THIS HOUSE  PAT SOLATANO</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY TONIGHT  REALLY</pattern><template>Ronnie and Veronica and I are gonna see her tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A    FIREPLACE</pattern><template>In the middle of the wall?</template></category><category><pattern>BEAUTIFUL JERSEY  I LOVE THAT JERSEY</pattern><template>Veronica didn't like it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T WANT THEM TO STEAL THAT</pattern><template>You still got yours? Yeah, I got mine.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEBODY TOOK AN ENVELOPE</pattern><template>Maybe we should call the FBI.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE'RE DOING ALL RIGHT  MAN  I CAN'T COMPLAIN</pattern><template>Isn't the market down, though?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE SHE BRINGS ME DOWN  MAN  SHE JUST BRINGS ME DOWN</pattern><template>You have to change. You're not gonna throw the marriage away.</template></category><category><pattern>DEAR TIFFANY</pattern><template>... I know you wrote the letter.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  MY MOM GOT THIS GAP OUTFIT SHE WANTS ME TO WEAR  BUT I WANNA WEAR A JERSEY THAT MY BROTHER  JAKE  GOT ME FROM THE EAGLES</pattern><template>Which jersey?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WHAT'S UP</pattern><template>Sorry I'm late.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT HIM TO GET USED TO THE ROUTINE HERE</pattern><template>Eight months is already long enough.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS DEFENDING HIS BROTHER</pattern><template>You fucking idiot! You spike the ball on the one yard line, Who is this?! Who's this?!</template></category><category><pattern>NO    I DON'T  I DON'T  I JUST WANTED TO HAVE A NICE  I JUST WANTED TO HAVE A NICE DINNER  OH  GOD</pattern><template>What is your problem?!</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Who was at the door?</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME THINK ABOUT THAT  WAIT A MINUTE</pattern><template>Well, why don't you think about when the Eagles beat the Seahawks, fourteen to seven.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT A GOOD THING TO DO</pattern><template>Well, I'm fucked up. What can I tell you? I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING YOU CAN  YOU HAVE TO WORK YOUR HARDEST  AND IF YOU DO  IF YOU STAY POSITIVE  YOU HAVE A SHOT AT A SILVER LINING</pattern><template>Work on a strategy, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO CHANGE  YOU'RE NOT GONNA THROW THE MARRIAGE AWAY</pattern><template>There's some kind of love there. I know, I used to see it.</template></category><category><pattern>VERONICA'S NOT GONNA LIKE IT</pattern><template>Get over here.</template></category><category><pattern>HI</pattern><template>Here you go.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>So I know.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE YOU NEXT SUNDAY</pattern><template>Now, you guys are still in touch with Nikki, right?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE GOOD  SOME OF THEM ARE PROFESSIONALS</pattern><template>They're good? Better than you? A lot better.</template></category><category><pattern>HE CANNOT BE A QUITTER</pattern><template>You took that stupid parlay thing, and now he won't do the dance and it was very constructive for him, and you ruined it.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  IT'S IMPORTANT  PLEASE</pattern><template>What are you up to, Pat? Nothing, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF THING</pattern><template>It's a thing, it's a thing.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN ROOKIE OF THE YEAR</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU PUT IT IN HERE  IT MAKES NO SENSE FOR YOU TO PUT IT IN HERE</pattern><template>Patty, what are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I HAD A REALLY GOOD TIME TONIGHT AND I THINK YOU'RE REALLY PRETTY  BUT I'M MARRIED  OKAY</pattern><template>You're married? So am I.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A MINUTE  ARE YOU AN EAGLES FAN OR ARE YOU NOT AN EAGLES FAN</pattern><template>I'm an Eagles fan.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING  DO YOU CALL HIM WHEN YOU'RE LONELY</pattern><template>That encourages him, Tiffany. You shouldn't do it.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU KNOW  YOU KNOW  COME ON</pattern><template>Sometimes it's okay with girls like this, they wanna have fun and sometimes     it's not because they got a broken wing, and they're hurt, and they're an easy target. And in this case, in this particular case, I think that wing is being fixed.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU UNDERSTAND  YEAH</pattern><template>Heavy. I want you to go to the game with your brother.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE LIVES ON THIS SIDE OF TOWN</pattern><template>Yeah, go see Tanya. Good idea.</template></category><category><pattern>ME  NONE  I USED TO BE ON LITHIUM AND SEROQUEL AND ABILIFY  BUT I DON'T TAKE THEM ANYMORE  NO  THEY MAKE ME FOGGY AND THEY ALSO MAKE ME BLOATED</pattern><template>Yeah, I was on Xanax and Effexor, but I agree, I wasn't as sharp, so I stopped. You ever take Klonopin?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE  MAN</pattern><template>If one of your two supervising physicians loses their license, then your whole ajudication is thrown out.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOVE ME  YEAH  I DO</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE WE SHOULD CHANGE THE SUBJECT</pattern><template>I don't mind it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING  DAD  YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>Excelsior. Excelsior. What does that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  YOU LOOK GOOD</pattern><template>Did you lose a lot of weight?</template></category><category><pattern>FIGHT WITH NANCY  THE HIGH SCHOOL     PRINCIPAL</pattern><template>I come home and what's playing but the song from my wedding.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  MY FRIEND RONNIE'S HAVING THIS PARTY ON SUNDAY NIGHT AND IT'S LIKE A REAL HOITY TOITY THING AND HIS WIFE  VERONICA'S A REAL STICKLER FOR</pattern><template>I don't know, my mom got this Gap outfit she wants me to wear, but I wanna wear a jersey that my brother, Jake, got me from the Eagles.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  YOU ARE NOT A STAND UP GUY</pattern><template>Pat! I told you not to push it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  WE MUST BEAT THE GIANTS  MY BROTHER</pattern><template>I'm not supposed to be seeing you, right? Outside the office?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT THIS  IT ALL CORRESPONDS</pattern><template>Dad, I borrowed one of your envelopes.</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK IN  HOW MANY DANCERS ARE THERE</pattern><template>What?! Nikki? Nikki.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>Because, it's just not right, lumping you and I together, I mean, it's just wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT OKAY  DON'T TELL ANYBODY  LISTEN TO ME</pattern><template>I feel like I'm getting crushed and  Crushed by what?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO  CLEAR OUT  NOTHING GOING ON HERE</pattern><template>Come on man what you gonna do about that song?</template></category><category><pattern>STOP IT</pattern><template>Hey, hey, hey, get off me!</template></category><category><pattern>GO BACK TO SLEEP  THE PARTY'S OVER  SHOW'S OVER</pattern><template>...this is not a reflection of where I'm at. You can't... please, you can't tell her any of this You can't tell Nikki about this.</template></category><category><pattern>BLACK IT UP   YOU KNOW DAMN WELL WHAT IT MEANS</pattern><template>I got an idea. Come get some, Pat. Come get some.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BIRDS ARE BETTER WHEN PAT IS WITH ME  WE SETTLED THAT</pattern><template>Relax, we're gonna do fine, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  ARE THEY</pattern><template>You know what, I knew why they invited me over. I knew it.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A THING  OKAY</pattern><template>What kind of thing?</template></category><category><pattern>RAISIN BRAN  MILK</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUTTA HERE  YOU LITTLE FUCKIN' IDIOT  GET OUTTA HERE</pattern><template>Someone, help me! Help me!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE NIKKI'S TEACHING THAT BOOK TO THE KIDS</pattern><template>I mean the whole time   let me just break it down for you   the whole time you're rooting for this Hemingway guy to survive the war and to be with the woman that he loves, Catherine Barkley...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE TOMMY'S WIDOW  RIGHT</pattern><template>Yes, I'm Tommy's crazy whore widow, minus the whore thing for the most part.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE TODAY WE WILL    I</pattern><template>...pull the curtain back and there's the fucking history...</template></category><category><pattern>COULDN'T YOU SAY THE SAME ABOUT YOU AND NIKKI</pattern><template>It's not at all like me and Nikki.</template></category><category><pattern>MOM</pattern><template>I can't find my wedding video. Mom, wake up.</template></category><category><pattern>WALK ACROSS THE ROOM</pattern><template>Can we do something else besides the dance deal?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOTTA BEAT THE GIANTS IF WE WANNA HAVE A CHANCE OF GETTING INTO THE DIVISION  ANY CHANCE OF PLAYING IN THE PLAYOFFS  DO YOU REALIZE THAT</pattern><template>I didn't realize that. Yeah, that's the bind we're in.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  THIS WAS JUST A JOKE  THIS IS A JOKE I STARTED</pattern><template>There's a restraining order on this guy.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TIFFANY  BY THE WAY</pattern><template>What is this craziness with Tiffany Maxwell?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM OUT ON A LIMB FOR YOU WITH THE COURTS RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>It's my fault. Pat didn't know.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO CRAZINESS</pattern><template>I told you who she was, I was doing this thing with her. We had a conversation!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DID YOU ORDER RAISIN BRAN</pattern><template>Why did you order tea?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NOW YOU LIKE HER  DAD</pattern><template>I have to say I do. Yup.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T TALK  ONLY WALK</pattern><template>I'm not doing it. Do it. No. That's stupid.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT'S WHEN I HAD LONG HAIR</pattern><template>People say I talk about my hair too much.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE ALL WATCHING THE GAME</pattern><template>Yeah, it drives me crazy, and yes, I was negative. You didn't even know that I loved it, Nikki, but I did.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS  DANCING WITH THE STARS</pattern><template>Well, you knew that. Maybe you should've scouted 'em.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT JUST A MINUTE</pattern><template>...Put the phone down, please.</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  DAD  DID THE EAGLES WIN</pattern><template>The Eagles won, forty four six!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I CAN ONLY DO IT IF I HAVE A PARTNER    AND NOW I'M ABOUT TO MISS IT FOR ANOTHER YEAR</pattern><template>Whoa, whoa, whoa, I'm not gonna fuckin' dance with you.</template></category><category><pattern>DESEAN JACKSON IS THE MAN</pattern><template>Well, that settles that.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT IT</pattern><template>Up next, ladies and gentlemen please welcome Pat Solatano, Jr. and Tiffany Maxwell.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T TELL NIKKI ABOUT THIS  OFFICER</pattern><template>Look, I gotta make out a report.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED TO RECOGNIZE THESE FEELINGS COMING TO YOU  OTHERWISE YOU WILL BE SENT BACK TO BALTIMORE  SO WHEN YOU GET THESE FEELINGS  YOU NEED TO GET TO A QUIETER PLACE  AND BE AT PEACE WITH YOURSELF  HOWEVER YOU CAN</pattern><template>Yeah, but that's easier said than done.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I DO THIS TIME AFTER TIME AFTER TIME  I DO ALL THIS SHIT FOR OTHER PEOPLE AND THEN I WAKE UP AND  AND I'M EMPTY  I HAVE NOTHING</pattern><template>What are you talking about? You seem like you're a tough girl to me. Why don't you just do things on your own?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT IS  NIKKI ALWAYS SAID THAT  RONNIE'S WIFE KEEPS HIS SOCIAL CALENDAR WHERE SHE KEEPS HIS BALLS  IN HER PURSE    THAT'S NOT TRUE</pattern><template>Ronnie! What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK   I TALKED TO YOU ABOUT THAT ALREADY</pattern><template>I told you guys   It's all right.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HERS</pattern><template>What's hers? Are you joking?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY WAY YOU COULD MEET MY CRAZY           WAS BY DOING SOMETHING CRAZY YOURSELF  THANK YOU</pattern><template>I love you.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU PLAY  RIDE THE LIGHTNING  BY METALLICA</pattern><template>Pat was a history sub at the high school, Tiffany.</template></category><category><pattern>SHH  SHH  WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT  I'M NOT GONNA HIDE THIS</pattern><template>You need to deal with it.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S INTERESTING</pattern><template>You know, Tiffany's been doing this dance thing for years and she's real good at it. She's gonna be competing at the Ben Franklin Hotel.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER YOU DO  WATCH OUT FOR THAT RESTRAINING ORDER  OKAY</pattern><template>Don't let Tiffany get you in trouble.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  JUST READ IT</pattern><template>Dear Tiffany...</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT LOOKS GREAT NOW  YOU LIKE IT</pattern><template>No, It's good now. Yes, it is.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  TWO THINGS  WE GOTTA WATCH THAT BUBBLE SCREEN FOR FUCKIN' MANNING IN THE BACKFIELD AND WE GOTTA MAKE SURE WE KNOCK THE RECEIVERS ON THEIR ASS ON THE LINE OF SCRIMMAGE</pattern><template>You can say that again.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU SAT ON HER LAP</pattern><template>Mm hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YEAH  ALL RIGHT  BUDDY  I'LL SEE YOU  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>Wish me luck, man.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK HE ENDS IT THERE</pattern><template>No! He writes another ending.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE  I GOTTA GO SEE THIS GIRL  TANYA</pattern><template>She lives on this side of town.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I'M SORRY  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>I was a big slut, but I'm not anymore. There's always gonna be a part of me that's sloppy and dirty, but I like that, with all the other parts of myself. Can you say the same about yourself, fucker?!</template></category><category><pattern>BREAK IT UP OR YOU'LL BE ARRESTED</pattern><template>What'd you do? What happened? Dad  What the fuck happened? Dad.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  FUCK OFF  RANDY  YOU LOVE IT</pattern><template>You live for this shit. You've been betting against my father for years.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST DIDN'T APPRECIATE IT  OR YOU  BEFORE    COME ON  TIME TO GO</pattern><template>I lost all that. I blew it. But you also blew it. We can get it back.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WOULD YOU  WOULD YOU JUST COME DOWNSTAIRS AND TALK TO ME AND RANDY NOW</pattern><template>Randy, tell him what I'm doing.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU'RE HERE ON GAME DAY</pattern><template>I'm out. It's official, man.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT GO IN MY STUDY OR I WILL EAT YOU   IT'S NOT FUNNY  IT'S NOT FUNNY</pattern><template>What's everybody making a joke out of this for?</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE YOU THINK THAT NIKKI'S NOT AROUND AND TIFFANY'S AN ATTRACTIVE GIRL AND IF YOU GET DRAWN TOWARDS TIFFANY  YOU WILL SPOIL YOUR CHANCES OF GETTING NIKKI BACK TO YOU</pattern><template>Not bad, Doctor Jones. But I don't think I'm gonna blow it with Nikki because Tiffany's a slut.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I HEARD YOU WENT TO YOUR OLD HOUSE AND THE SCHOOL</pattern><template>It's not okay. I've been assigned to your case, so you're gonna be seeing a lot of me. Do yourself a favor. Respect the restraining order, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUDGE EVERYBODY  YOU'RE THE ONE WHO HAS A MESSED UP MARRIAGE</pattern><template>I'm just looking out for you, I'm just looking out for you. She's unstable.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BUT THEN PEOPLE WERE GETTING INTO FIGHTS IN THE PARKING LOT AT WORK  AND IN THE BATHROOM    AND THE BOSS CALLED ME IN TO HIS OFFICE AND TRIED TO PIN IT ALL ON ME  SO I ACCUSED HIM OF HARASSMENT AND THEN THEY FIRED ME  SENT ME HOME AND PUT ME ON SOME MEDS</pattern><template>I get it. The song that was playing when my wife...</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS INTRIGUED  EXCITED  AND A LITTLE SCARED</pattern><template>She was scared? About what? Did she tell you?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE GOT A CALL THAT THEY DID CONVERT YOU TO A MENTAL HYGIENE LAW ADMISSION STATUS BY THE DEADLINE OF YOUR SENTENCE  SO</pattern><template>Wait a minute. Are you an Eagles fan or are you not an Eagles fan?</template></category><category><pattern>LEAVE THE FUCKING INDIANS ALONE  STAY HERE  STAY HERE</pattern><template>I'm not gonna go anywhere.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU HAD IT TOGETHER  YOU WERE SOLID</pattern><template>I am solid. I was solid at the game, Dad.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA STOP WITH THESE CRAZY THEORIES</pattern><template>He's a cop. What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A GOOD DUDE  HE'S A GOOD DUDE</pattern><template>Oh, shit! The Asian invasion!</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO WHAT HE'S SAYING  WHAT'S HE SAYING</pattern><template>He's saying you're being rude.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE IN THIS HOUSE  PLEASE SHOW SOME RESPECT FOR WHAT I DO</pattern><template>And we should spend time together anyway.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY</pattern><template>I'm just saying   Am I messed up?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SO THEY PUT ME ON MEDICATION  WHICH I FEEL ASHAMED OF</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>PATRIZIO  STOP IT  AND RANDY  DON'T YOU TAKE THE BET</pattern><template>In fact, I'll give you ten points. No, Dad! Dad!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HERS  ARE YOU JOKING</pattern><template>Let's go back to the incident.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST STAY WITH US  STAY FOR THE GAME  SPEND SOME FAMILY TIME</pattern><template>Dad, I can't. Look, I'm ready to go.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  TAKING A LITTLE BIT TOO MANY OR SOMETHING</pattern><template>No, if I was taking that, I'd be on the floor, Dad.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A DRAWER AT A MORGUE WHERE THEY PULL OUT DEAD BODIES AND SHOOT THEM WITH FORMALDEHYDE</pattern><template>Where would the body go, though?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALLY  YOU REALLY WANNA GO RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Yes, I really wanna go! It's been great.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE SAY I TALK ABOUT MY HAIR TOO MUCH</pattern><template>And it was just the way I wanted it, but he cut it back too far.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE SHOULD SPEND TIME TOGETHER ANYWAY</pattern><template>I'm trying to keep you out of trouble, please.</template></category><category><pattern>RANDY  I JUST HOPE YOU HEARD WHAT I SAID  IT'S LIKE A FAMILY BUSINESS  IT'S OUR FAMILY ENDEAVOR  WE ALL STICK TOGETHER ON THIS</pattern><template>That's how it works. That's a positive, positive vibe.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LET ME LIE TO YOU FOR A WEEK  I WAS TRYING TO BE ROMANTIC</pattern><template>You love me? Yeah, I do.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID YOU GUYS WAS HELPING EACH OTHER OUT AND YOU WERE NICE AND HAD A MOUTH ON YOU  THAT YOU WERE MOUTHY  BUT  WHOA  WHOA  THAT'S ENOUGH</pattern><template>No, please, tell me more about what he said in the letter.</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE HUNDRED FEET  LISTEN TO ME</pattern><template>...and I'll take that fucking camera and I'm gonna break it over your fuckin' head, then I'm gonna come back and interview you about what it's like to get that fuckin' camera broken over your head!</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS</pattern><template>How many were there?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  MAN  HEY  I'M GONNA BE THERE  MAN  I WANT YOU GUYS TO WIN</pattern><template>Bye! Excelsior, Pat!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GLAD YOU'RE DOING SO WELL  LOVE  NIKKI    I THINK I'M DONE FOR TODAY  OKAY</pattern><template>She said to show her something, Pat. This dance can be that something. You would have never done something like this in a million years. It shows all kinds of skills on so many different levels: focus, collaboration, discipline. It's romantic, like I said it would be. It's for her.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  GET INTO THE END ZONE  DUMMY  # I MEAN  HE CELEBRATES BEFORE HE'S EVEN IN</pattern><template>You know something? It's nothing new. Your team does that all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU UP TO  PAT  NOTHING  COME ON</pattern><template>What's in the envelope?</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE ME BACK TO THE HOSPITAL  BUT TAKE PAT HOME  HE'S FINE  TRUST ME  YOU'LL SEE  HE'S FINE  IT'S MY FAULT</pattern><template>Mom, can we stop at the library? I wanna read Nikki's entire English high school syllabus.</template></category><category><pattern>COOL  MAN  WOW  YOU LOST A LOT OF WEIGHT  I ALMOST DIDN'T RECOGNIZE YOU</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A SECOND  I TRIED TO CALL  MY GOD  WHAT'S HAPPENING  I CALLED     BUT I TRIED TO CALL YOU  TIFFANY  I  OH  REALLY  YES</pattern><template>I told you I was gonna split my time with my dad and you, and my dad was pulling me in one direction. Doctor Patel, Ronnie  Well, that sounds great, Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S SO NICE OF YOU  WOW</pattern><template>Thirty two gigabytes. How many songs is that? Seven thousand.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT GOOD ARE YOU  MAN</pattern><template>Why did you have this overwhelming urgency to see your wedding video last night?</template></category><category><pattern>ENOUGH WITH AWKWARDNESS  I DON'T WANNA WALK IN YOUR HOUSE AND NOT BE ABLE TO SAY WHAT I WANNA SAY</pattern><template>You're right, man. You're right, you're right, Eagles, baby! Yeah! Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  IT'S A LITTLE TRUE  BUT IF YOU THINK SHE STILL HATES YOU  YOU'RE WRONG BECAUSE WHY WOULD SHE TELL ME TO INVITE YOU TO DINNER</pattern><template>Hmm?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS THAT KID WITH THE CAMERA</pattern><template>Good luck. I gotta write this up.</template></category><category><pattern>GET IN HERE  PLEASE  I NEED YOU</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS YOUR WIFE</pattern><template>You're crazy!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE JUST NEEDS TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR HERS</pattern><template>What's hers?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S NOT INTO BREAKING THE LAW  WHICH THIS LETTER WOULD DEFINITELY BE DOING</pattern><template>But you would do it?</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT DO YOU DO  I'M A LAWYER  LITIGATOR  ACTUALLY</pattern><template>Oh, the arguing kind.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OKAY WITH THAT  WHO</pattern><template>Veronica's sister.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  I THOUGHT YOU WERE DOING IT</pattern><template>Oh, I thought you were doing it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU STOP JUDGING PEOPLE</pattern><template>You judge everybody. You're the one who has a messed up marriage.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST THE CRAZY SLUT WITH A DEAD HUSBAND</pattern><template>Forget it!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU WANT ME TO PROVE IT  HOW'S HE GONNA PROVE IT</pattern><template>By giving them the chance to win back everything, double or nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN AM I GONNA GET A PHONE</pattern><template>You'll get a phone in due time.</template></category><category><pattern>BY GIVING THEM THE CHANCE TO WIN BACK EVERYTHING  DOUBLE OR NOTHING</pattern><template>No, no, no, no, no, no, no.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A MINUTE  WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>What makes the Cowboys America's Team?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT ME TO GO TO THE GAME WITH JAKE</pattern><template>Of course I do. Does he want me to go?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S BEAUTIFUL  AND VERONICA WANTS TO MAKE DINNER FOR YOU</pattern><template>Congratulations on the baby, but I'm not buying the invitation.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I'M SOLID</pattern><template>This is my little brother Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T WANT NIKKI TO THINK THAT I WAS ASSOCIATED WITH THAT KIND OF SEXUAL BEHAVIOR BECAUSE I'VE NEVER DONE ANYTHING LIKE THAT  OKAY</pattern><template>You may not have experienced the shit that I did.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>The letter to Nikki.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN THE SHOWER INCIDENT HAPPENED AND THAT'S WHEN EVERYTHING SNAPPED  SO I THEN REALIZED THAT  OH  WOW  I'VE BEEN DEALING WITH THIS MY WHOLE LIFE  AND WITHOUT ANY SUPERVISION I'VE BEEN DOING IT ALL ON MY OWN WITH NO HELP AND BASICALLY I'VE BEEN WHITE KNUCKLING IT THIS WHOLE TIME</pattern><template>That had to be hard.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL FIX ALL THIS  OKAY</pattern><template>That was a messed up thing you did, Doctor Patel. Alright!</template></category><category><pattern>I STILL NEED TO READ IT  THOUGH</pattern><template>Who's that? What the...?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA HAVE A BOWL OF YOUR RAISIN BRAN</pattern><template>Great!</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS THING YOU'RE DOING</pattern><template>Yeah, what is it? What is this project, hon?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FUCKING LOSER</pattern><template>You ruined everything!</template></category><category><pattern>HANDKERCHIEF  YEAH</pattern><template>That's OCD. That's crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>OH    MY GOD  NIKKI HATED WHEN I TALKED LIKE THIS</pattern><template>Made me feel like such a pervert.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW YOU WROTE THE LETTER</pattern><template>The only way you could meet my crazy...    ... was by doing something crazy yourself. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT THE PHONE DOWN  YOU GOTTA</pattern><template>Wait just a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AND A FIVE POINT FOUR FOR AN AVERAGE SCORE OF   FIVE POINT ZERO</pattern><template>Sorry about that, guys.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  GET OFF OF ME  SHUT UP  SHUT UP</pattern><template>Stop it.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD YOU PLEASE TURN IT OFF</pattern><template>I can't.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DON'T</pattern><template>You told your therapist that you were in a superior mental illness category, didn't you?</template></category><category><pattern>PAT TOLD ME  HE TOLD ME YOU SHOULD NEVER THROW A MARRIAGE OUT THE WINDOW</pattern><template>Pat did not say that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DO YOU HAVE TO TALK ABOUT ME LIKE THAT</pattern><template>I'm just bragging about you. Can't I brag about my little sister?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WHAT YOU WANNA DO</pattern><template>I didn't, I didn't, I didn't  It's the kids!</template></category><category><pattern>GIMME YOUR IPOD</pattern><template>Give it to me. Thank you, baby, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEEMED TO HAVE TROUBLE LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>Let me just set the record straight about last night.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  I DON'T KNOW HOW THEY FUCKING SCORE  WE'RE PARTICIPATING</pattern><template>We're not, we're not a part of it.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT YOU WORKING ON A SUNDAY</pattern><template>How are you? Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A MEDICATION PROBLEM  BUT HE'S FINE NOW</pattern><template>Oh yeah? He's fine now? You wanna send him back to Baltimore?</template></category><category><pattern>KLONOPIN  YEAH</pattern><template>Right? Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>GUESS WHAT  WHAT</pattern><template>Nikki replied to your letter.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUFFLE BACK  SHUFFLE BACK</pattern><template>Girl, you gotta move your junk.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS YOU'RE GOOD    LUCK  HONEY</pattern><template>What's that in your hand?</template></category><category><pattern>MISTER SOLATANO  I GOT A LOT OF CALLS</pattern><template>People in the neighborhood are scared. I gotta come in.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A DANCE TO DO  WE HAVE A PARLAY  YOU GOTTA STAY FOCUSED</pattern><template>I'm focused. Okay, let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANNA GO TO THERAPY</pattern><template>You have to go. It's part of the deal.</template></category><category><pattern>WISH ME LUCK  MAN</pattern><template>Excelsior!</template></category><category><pattern>TREMENDOUS</pattern><template>Yeah, man, I'm, I'm thinking of redoing it again.</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE  OPEN UP</pattern><template>Mister Solatano, I got a lot of calls.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YEAH  WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT  DANCING</pattern><template>You look incredible. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FATHER WANTED YOU TO HAVE THIS</pattern><template>He wants me to have   all this Eagles information.</template></category><category><pattern>HUH</pattern><template>We got a serious situation on our hands, you know that.</template></category><category><pattern>VERONICA'S SISTER</pattern><template>Tiffany. Tiffany and... Tommy?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL GIVE YOU THREE MORE</pattern><template>Patrizio, stop it! And Randy, don't you take the bet!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE PARLAY  SHAKE ON IT</pattern><template>You know what? I'm not gonna be a part of this. Randy, Randy, you're a sickness. You're a fucking sickness, Randy. I'm out.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'D BETTER GET BACK TO THE LETTER</pattern><template>Yeah, let's get back to the letter.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA WIN TWO BETS OR YOU LOSE THE WHOLE THING  FOR PAT SR  TO WIN  THE BIRDS GOTTA BEAT THE COWBOYS PLUS PAT AND TIFFANY GOTTA GET AT LEAST A FIVE AT THE DANCE</pattern><template>That's very, very manic indeed.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I'M SORRY  OKAY    I'M SORRY</pattern><template>I'll fix all this, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>SIT DOWN</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I could just write you a letter and you could just let me have five minutes, explaining how much better I'm doing.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS HIS SIXTH SENSE FORGOT TO TELL HIM THE COPS WERE COMING</pattern><template>I'm taking him back to the hospital.</template></category><category><pattern>HOT</pattern><template>Jesus Christ. Was it like... older women, a sexy teacher who wants to seduce you  Made me sit on her lap and do things? Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU CAN'T READ IT UNTIL AFTER YOU NAIL THE BIG MOVE  GO</pattern><template>Tiff, I'm sorry. I can't do anything else without reading Nikki's letter, okay? It's just..., it's in the back of my head.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED OVER THERE</pattern><template>When am I gonna get a phone?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  SHE'S A MESS  YOU GOTTA BE CAREFUL  SHE GOES TO A LOT OF THERAPY</pattern><template>I go to a lot of therapy, Ronnie.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP IT  STOP IT  STOP IT</pattern><template>What's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M FOCUSED  OKAY  LET'S GO</pattern><template>Look at the dancers. You see them? Shit.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA TELL HIM NIKKI'LL BE THERE</pattern><template>You gotta be part of it. We have to do it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WON'T LET ME MAKE ANY CALLS</pattern><template>They think I'm gonna call Nikki.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T FEEL ANYTHING</pattern><template>Has anybody ever told you how Tommy died?</template></category><category><pattern>LET THE WHOLE NEIGHBORHOOD WAKE UP  I    DON'T CARE</pattern><template>Pat! Stop it!</template></category><category><pattern>SIT DOWN  WE'RE SEVEN MINUTES IN  NO SCORE  COME ON  HELP TURN THE JUJU AROUND</pattern><template>I don't believe in juju, Dad.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT MY HAIR ONLY GREW WHEN I WAS OLDER  WHEN I WAS YOUNGER  MY HAIR DIDN'T GROW BECAUSE MY BROTHER</pattern><template>Remember I told you about my brother, he had a Jheri curl, and I couldn't get a Jheri curl because my hair didn't grow long enough.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MAKE FUN  THIS IS SERIOUS</pattern><template>What FBI? Come on, let's take a look. I'll show you what this is.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WOW</pattern><template>Let me think about that. Wait a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>DALLAS JUST TIED WITH ANOTHER FIELD GOAL  THREE THREE</pattern><template>I'm worried about the bet.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FIRST NIGHT THAT PAT AND I MET AT MY SISTER'S  THE EAGLES BEAT THE FORTY NINERS HANDILY  FORTY TO TWENTY SIX  THE SECOND TIME WE GOT TOGETHER WE WENT FOR A RUN AND THE PHILLIES BEAT THE DODGERS SEVEN TO FIVE IN THE NLCS</pattern><template>She's right, Dad.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SOUNDS LIKE BULLSHIT</pattern><template>Why'd you run by my house?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>Stop it!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT'S CONFUSING  HE'S DEAD</pattern><template>Wait, what?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  SIT DOWN</pattern><template>Sit down.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE YOU IN A LITTLE BIT</pattern><template>I'll see you up there, okay? Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS MY DOCTOR  CLIFF</pattern><template>Look, two things. We gotta watch that bubble screen for fuckin' Manning in the backfield and we gotta make sure we knock the receivers on their ass on the line of scrimmage.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU SHUT UP  OKAY</pattern><template>How many drinks have you had?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL GET A PHONE IN DUE TIME</pattern><template>What happened?</template></category><category><pattern>THE BIRDS LOSE  I LOSE A FUCKIN' FORTUNE  A FORTUNE TO RANDY</pattern><template>What the fuck did you do?! You fucking lost it!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S UP</pattern><template>I don't, I don't feel good when I'm on them, Mom. I don't feel good.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN THE WHOLE TIME   LET ME JUST BREAK IT DOWN FOR YOU   THE WHOLE TIME YOU'RE ROOTING FOR THIS HEMINGWAY GUY TO SURVIVE THE WAR AND TO BE WITH THE WOMAN THAT HE LOVES  CATHERINE BARKLEY</pattern><template>It's four o'clock in the morning, Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU'RE SO UP  UP  UP  UP</pattern><template>Isn't that a good thing?</template></category><category><pattern>PAT DIDN'T KNOW  HE'S MY FRIEND  SO HE WAS ROOTIN' FOR ME  I'M HAVIN' A DISAGREEMENT WITH THE HOSPITAL  BUT WE'RE WORKING IT OUT</pattern><template>Take me back to the hospital, but take Pat home, he's fine. Trust me. You'll see, he's fine. It's my fault.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM</pattern><template>Nothing's my problem! I'm fine. I'm tired and I wanna go.</template></category><category><pattern>AS MY FRIEND DANNY WOULD SAY I GOT NOTHING BUT LOVE FOR YOU  BROTHER</pattern><template>That's right. That's right.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE MARRIED FOR THREE YEARS AND FIVE DAYS  AND I LOVED HIM  BUT FOR THE LAST COUPLE MONTHS  I JUST WASN'T INTO SEX AT ALL  IT JUST FELT LIKE WE WERE SO DIFFERENT AND I WAS DEPRESSED  SOME OF THAT IS JUST ME  SOME OF IT WAS HE WANTED ME TO HAVE KIDS AND I HAVE A HARD ENOUGH TIME TAKING CARE OF MYSELF</pattern><template>I don't think that makes me a criminal. Anyway one night after dinner, he drove to Victoria's Secret at King of Prussia Mall and got some lingerie to get something going. And on the way back, he stopped on 76 to help a guy with a flat tire and he got hit by a car and killed. And the Victoria's Secret box was still in the front seat. That's a feeling.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WROTE ABOUT YOU  ALL RIGHT  WHAT'D HE SAY</pattern><template>He said you guys was helping each other out and you were nice and had a mouth on you, that you were mouthy, but  Whoa, whoa, that's enough.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>I gotta rethink this whole thing. I didn't trust it before, but I gotta say, now I do.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  I'M JUST GONNA  I'M JUST GONNA  I'M JUST GONNA STOP TALKING  I'M GONNA SHUT MY MOUTH</pattern><template>As my friend Danny would say I got nothing but love for you, brother.</template></category><category><pattern>DANNY  THIS IS TIFFANY</pattern><template>Tiffany, this is Danny.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ANYTHING YOU WANNA KNOW  I'LL JUST TELL YOU  IT WAS NOTHING</pattern><template>It was just a very general letter.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ACTUALLY GONNA GIVE YOU ONE OF MY IPODS  I HAVE AN OLD ONE</pattern><template>Gimme your iPod.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I COULD JUST WRITE YOU A LETTER AND YOU COULD JUST LET ME HAVE FIVE MINUTES  EXPLAINING HOW MUCH BETTER I'M DOING</pattern><template>There's a court order against you...</template></category><category><pattern>THEY THINK I'M GONNA CALL NIKKI</pattern><template>Don't worry about it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW HOW THOSE PLACES CREEP ME OUT  AND THE FIRM'S BEEN EXPANDING</pattern><template>I've been helping Pop with the restaurant 'cause he needs to have a legitimate business. He needs a tax return. With all the money that he's making with his bookmaking, they're gonna come after him. And then it looks like I'm making, I'm gonna make partner at the firm.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT  GREAT</pattern><template>We're gonna go on a tour now.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE WOULD THE BODY GO  THOUGH</pattern><template>It's a joke!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I'M GONNA START A RESTAURANT</pattern><template>It's gonna be a cheesesteak place.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  I DON'T UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>Mom, no, it'll be fine. It'll be fine.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT  YOU ARE WHY TODAY HAPPENED</pattern><template>I'm the reason why today happened?</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIDN'T SAY THAT</pattern><template>He said it several times, Tiffany, and this is his chance.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SURE  JUST SAY IT  SAY IT</pattern><template>No, please. I think Pat, you should be facing Tiffany.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GONNA FIGHT</pattern><template>Hey, not my brother! Hey, hey, hey!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  A LITTLE BIT</pattern><template>But it's for the best.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN DO A FIVE</pattern><template>What are you talking about, Dad?</template></category><category><pattern>ANYBODY CAN WAKE UP</pattern><template>I'm not ashamed of it!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN DRIVE THEM BOTH HOME  NOW</pattern><template>Stop talking about me in third person.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY  THAT'S CRAZY</pattern><template>There have been no games since Pat and I have been rehearsing every day and if Pat had been with me like he was supposed to, he wouldn't have gotten in a fight, he wouldn't be in trouble, maybe the Eagles beat the New York Giants.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN ME</pattern><template>Yeah, you. Are you gonna walk me home?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT  I WANNA MAKE SURE WHEN YOU COME OUT THAT YOU'RE OKAY  AND SHE DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING</pattern><template>You didn't tell me? The court said yes. Don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  I'M SORRY  HOW'D THAT HAPPEN</pattern><template>Does it really matter?</template></category><category><pattern>DANNY WAS IN FOR ASSAULT BECAUSE OF CRYSTAL METH AND ALCOHOL</pattern><template>Bad combination.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GET IN A FIGHT</pattern><template>I'm not gonna fight.</template></category><category><pattern>EIGHT MONTHS IS ALREADY LONG ENOUGH</pattern><template>Hey, Mom. Can we give Danny a ride to North Philly?</template></category><category><pattern>DANNY'S NOT ALLOWED TO LEAVE</pattern><template>All right, Mom, just hold on a sec.</template></category><category><pattern>NO WALK  NO LETTER  WALK TO ME LIKE I'M NIKKI  COME ON  DO IT  I'M NIKKI  COME ON</pattern><template>You're not Nikki.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A FUCKING TRAITOR</pattern><template>What's more American than a cowboy?</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE WHEN DO COPS HAVE CARDS</pattern><template>Tell me one thing. Would you like to be a guy who goes back to jail or to the hospital? Hmm? So take your medication and if you do fine, we'll reduce them.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WHAT IS IT  WHAT IS THIS PROJECT  HON</pattern><template>It's a dance thing, okay? There's nothing more to it, Dad. I swear.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TAKING HIM BACK TO THE HOSPITAL</pattern><template>What? No, no, he passed his thing, right?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT HITTING HIM  HE'S HITTING ME</pattern><template>I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  DON'T BRING IT UP</pattern><template>No, how did he die?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE     NO  SHE MIGHT BE WITH HIM  SHE'S AFRAID OF YOU</pattern><template>She doesn't want to talk to you.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE DOESN'T WANT TO TALK TO YOU</pattern><template>No way, Dad. You mean, Doug Culpepper?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I CAN'T BEGIN TO EXPLAIN THAT   OR THE CRAZINESS INSIDE MYSELF AND EVERYBODY ELSE  BUT GUESS WHAT</pattern><template>Sunday is my favorite day again.</template></category><category><pattern>MY BIRDS  BENJAMIN FRANKLIN'S TEAM FAVORED BY ONE AND A HALF POINTS</pattern><template>I'll give you three more.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR A SECOND  I'LL WATCH THE BEGINNING OF THE GAME</pattern><template>He says you're good... luck, honey.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE   YOU SEE THAT</pattern><template>You're meant to be here!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A BRICK OVEN  IT'S A BRICK OVEN  IT'S A LIGHT  IT'S A</pattern><template>Ooh, ooh, warmer, warmer, warmer.</template></category><category><pattern>TECHNICALLY  YOU CAN TAKE HIM OUT AGAINST OUR RECOMMENDATION  BUT YOU ASSUME A LOT OF LIABILITY IN THE EYES OF THE COURT</pattern><template>And he's just getting used to the routine here.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  I DON'T WANNA BE MEAN</pattern><template>I know. I know, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>I ORDERED RAISIN BRAN BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT THERE TO BE ANY MISTAKING THIS FOR A DATE</pattern><template>It can still be a date if you order Raisin Bran.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T BELIEVE IN JUJU  DAD</pattern><template>Come on, Mister Excelsior. You wanna be positive? Be positive. Sit down.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF IT WAS ME READING THE SIGNS      THAT'S IT  OKAY</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  I'M NOT TELLING THE TRUTH</pattern><template>Um, maybe I should drive them home separately?</template></category><category><pattern>COOL  SHE'S FINE  SHE IS MY FRIEND WITH AN  F    A CAPITAL  F    FOR  FRIEND    HEY  CAN I SEE WHAT YOU GUYS ARE DOING</pattern><template>Yeah. Okay. That's it?</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU  DAD</pattern><template>Hey! Would you just leave me alone?!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN WHEN I WAS AT HIS HOUSE  IT'S LIKE A CIRCUS OVER THERE</pattern><template>Shh, shh. What are you talking about? I'm not gonna hide this.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIKE TO RUN BY MYSELF  OKAY</pattern><template>Me too.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T LET THEM HURT YOUR FEELINGS</pattern><template>Pat, don't look for Nikki! Take your camera and get out of here!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANTED TO GIVE YOU MY CARD TO GIVE TO HER</pattern><template>Another rude creep.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE A LOT OF REPORTS FROM YOUR NEIGHBORS  WE GOT A LOT OF PHONE CALLS</pattern><template>Nikki is being manipulated and controlled. You have to talk to her.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YEAH  CAN YOU MOVE 'EM A LITTLE BIT MORE  YEAH  THAT'S IT</pattern><template>Move 'em a bit more.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIVE IN THE ADDITION AROUND BACK  WHICH IS COMPLETELY SEPARATE FROM MY PARENTS' HOUSE  SO THERE'S NO CHANCE OF THEM WALKING IN ON US  I HATE THE FACT THAT YOU WORE A FOOTBALL JERSEY TO DINNER BECAUSE I HATE FOOTBALL  BUT YOU CAN FUCK ME IF YOU TURN THE LIGHTS OFF  OKAY</pattern><template>How old are you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN THE GUY WITH THE        LITTLE GLASSES AND THE LONG SCRAGGLY HAIR</pattern><template>What about the lightning with the kite? He stood in the storm with a kite.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID YOU LOSE YOUR JOB</pattern><template>By... having sex with everybody in the office.</template></category><category><pattern>AM I TAKING THE RIGHT DOSE  OF COURSE I AM</pattern><template>Okay. Taking a little bit too many or something?</template></category><category><pattern>BRO  GET OFF OF ME</pattern><template>He's harassing me!</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  SLOW DOWN  WHAT</pattern><template>Your father wanted you to have this.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING  THE FAMILY  THE BABY  THE JOB  THE FUCKING DICKS AT WORK  AND IT'S LIKE  YOU KNOW  LIKE I'M TRYING TO DO THIS  YOU KNOW  AND  AND  AND I'M LIKE    SUFFOCATING</pattern><template>Holy shit.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK DID YOU DO   YOU FUCKING LOST IT</pattern><template>I thought you said you had it together! You were solid!</template></category><category><pattern>WE SUCK  WE DON'T SUCK  PAT'S A BEGINNER  I'M OKAY  WE'RE HAPPY JUST TO BE GOING THERE</pattern><template>And how are the people you're competing against?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  TIFFANY  THIS IS PAT</pattern><template>Pat, my sister in law Tiffany.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT  THAT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>That's nice. That's nice.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LIVE FOR THIS SHIT  YOU'VE BEEN BETTING AGAINST MY FATHER FOR YEARS</pattern><template>Is that right?</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  NOT NOW</pattern><template>Would you put it in here? It makes no sense for you to put it in here.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S NOT CRAZY    I'LL JUST BORROW JAKE'S PHONE  IT'S TOO BAD YOU CAN'T COME IN TO THE STADIUM  BUT I KNOW YOU WERE KICKED OUT  YOU KNOW  FOR BEATING EVERYBODY UP  GUESS WE'RE NOT THAT DIFFERENT  HUH  DAD</pattern><template>That a bad thing?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU RUINED EVERYTHING</pattern><template>He was defending his brother!</template></category><category><pattern>SO SHE'S A LOYAL  MARRIED TO A DEAD GUY SLUT</pattern><template>Maybe she just needs a friend and she thought if she offers you sex, it will be easier for you to become friends with her.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  ARE YOU READY</pattern><template>You really, you really wanna go right now?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN  HOW AM I  WHAT DOES THAT MEAN</pattern><template>Sort of like me.</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  DAD  DAD  SHE'S MY FRIEND  WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT</pattern><template>Oh, she's a mess. You gotta be careful. She goes to a lot of therapy.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE STOP YELLING</pattern><template>I'm not yelling, Mom, I'm just frustrated because I should have my fucking wedding video!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S IN THAT ENVELOPE</pattern><template>Guys, I'm beating the song! I'm on the scoreboard!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M MAKING CRABBY SNACKS AND HOMEMADES</pattern><template>You see?! You see that?!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT   NIKKI  NIKKI</pattern><template>Oh, Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEVER          FUCK IN THE SHOWER ANYMORE</pattern><template>Maybe today we will.   I...</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S INSANITY  HE SPIKES THE BALL AT THE ONE YARD LINE  THE ONE FUCKING YARD LINE</pattern><template>I mean, get into the end zone, dummy. # I mean, he celebrates before he's even in!</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE 'EM A BIT MORE</pattern><template>You could turn around, too, there's nothing wrong with that.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT WHAT DID THE DOCTOR SAY  BECAUSE THE  THE COURT LISTENS TO THE DOCTOR</pattern><template>Yeah, and the court said  The court listens to the doctor, the doctor  Dad, relax. The court said it's fine, okay? Let it go.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GO IN MY STUDY</pattern><template>Dad, not now!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT A LOSER</pattern><template>You fucking loser!</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU WHO SHE WAS  I WAS DOING THIS THING WITH HER  WE HAD A CONVERSATION</pattern><template>She's fucking nuts! When you started spending time with her, it all fell apart. This is the fucking reason right here.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D LIKE TO DO ANOTHER PARLAY IF WE MAKE IT TO THE NEXT ROUND  THAT'S ALL</pattern><template>But we are gonna make it to the next round. We're gonna beat...</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT HERE  I MEAN</pattern><template>Patty!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S PREGNANT  AND THEY ESCAPE UP INTO THE MOUNTAINS AND THEY'RE GONNA BE HAPPY  AND THEY'RE GONNA BE DRINKING WINE AND THEY DANCE</pattern><template>they both like to dance with each other, there's scenes of them dancing, which was boring, but I liked it, because they were happy.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  HOW DO THEY SCORE IT AND EVERYTHING</pattern><template>I don't know, I don't know how they fucking score! We're participating.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SONG THAT YOU SO CHARMINGLY PLAYED OUT HERE TODAY FOR US</pattern><template>That's playing and I don't think anything of it. Which is odd, 'cause I should have.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  PAT  WHAT'S THIS I HEAR ABOUT YOU JUST GETTIN' OUT</pattern><template>Yeah, from the looney bin!</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I GOTTA MAKE OUT A REPORT</pattern><template>No, no! No!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A TREAT  WHOA  WHOA  WHOA</pattern><template>Dad's got you sitting here?</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE LIKE TIFFANY  OR DANNY  OR ME  MAYBE WE KNOW SOMETHING THAT YOU GUYS DON'T KNOW  OKAY  DID YOU EVER THINK ABOUT THAT  MAYBE WE UNDERSTAND SOMETHING BECAUSE WE'RE MORE  WE HAVE A SIXTH SENSE  I MEAN  EVERYBODY'S GOT IT  EVERYBODY'S JUST NOT IN TOUCH WITH IT</pattern><template>Oh, no. How you doing, Pat? Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOST A LOT OF WEIGHT  I'VE BEEN READING YOUR BOOKS AND  I HAVE A POSITIVE ATTITUDE  I'M ON MEDICATION  I'M IN THERAPY</pattern><template>Where's Tiffany? She left.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DID YOU HAVE THIS OVERWHELMING URGENCY TO SEE YOUR WEDDING VIDEO LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>Oh, I don't know, because I'm married and I haven't seen my wife in eight and a half months?</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER  ON THE OTHER HAND  HAD NO TROUBLE SLAPPING THE SHIT OUT OF ME LAST NIGHT  WHICH I DID NOT RETURN 'CAUSE I COULD'VE KILLED HIM AND I DIDN'T  HE'S SIXTY FIVE YEARS OLD</pattern><template>You don't think I could've beat the shit out of him? I mean...</template></category><category><pattern>TIFFANY  I'M NOT GONNA DO A DANCE WITH YOU</pattern><template>All right, then I'm not giving her your fucking letter.</template></category><category><pattern>TIFFANY  WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT  WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU CAN'T GIVE THE LETTER TO NIKKI  BECAUSE WHAT AM I GETTING IN RETURN</pattern><template>What are you doing for me? You said! You said if I wrote a letter, you'd get it to Nikki. I know. That was the set up.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL WORK FULL TIME  HALF TIME</pattern><template>I'll sub, I'll work history, whatever you want.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  YOU'RE GOING THE WRONG WAY</pattern><template>What? Are you sure about that?</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME WALK YOU DOWN TO YOUR CAR</pattern><template>You're a better guy than this.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST SIT DOWN  COME ON  I WANT YOU TO WATCH THE GAME WITH ME</pattern><template>I'm not superstitious. That's a small thing that I do.</template></category><category><pattern>RELAX  WE'RE GONNA DO FINE  OKAY</pattern><template>I'll see you in a little bit.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING GOOD  MM HMM</pattern><template>Ahh.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU  ARE YOU GONNA WALK ME HOME</pattern><template>You have poor social skills. You have a problem.</template></category><category><pattern>STUPID FUCKING BOOK</pattern><template>I just can't believe Nikki's teaching that book to the kids.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GREAT FOR ALL OF THEM  BUT ALL OF THEM DIDN'T MAKE A COMMITMENT TO ME IN RETURN FOR MY HELP</pattern><template>I'm Tiffany, by the way.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A FUCKING TON OF ROADS TO RUN IN  WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO</pattern><template>I like this road. This is my neighborhood.</template></category><category><pattern>DESEAN JACKSON'S IN THE HOUSE</pattern><template>You mean rookie of the year?</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  I TOLD YOU NOT TO PUSH IT</pattern><template>Yeah, but he's gotta do this thing. He can't be a quitter.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOVE THE STRANGLERS</pattern><template>Oh, the Sex Pistols. The Clash. Got some Clash.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP AN EYE ON HIM</pattern><template>Is this a bipolar episode?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOUR MARRIAGE</pattern><template>Nothing's wrong!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU KNOW MY DAD LOST HIS PENSION</pattern><template>I'm sorry, man.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP BREAKING MY BALLS</pattern><template>Oh! I got you an iPod.</template></category><category><pattern>DIDN'T I SAY YOU WOULDN'T RECOGNIZE HIM</pattern><template>So, listen, I'm sorry that I didn't come see you down at the hospital.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN WE DO SOMETHING ELSE BESIDES THE DANCE DEAL</pattern><template>Are you fucking kidding me?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT  WAIT  YOU HAVE TO FIX THIS WINDOW</pattern><template>I'll fix it when I get back. Fix it now.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D HAVE TO HIDE IT FROM VERONICA</pattern><template>She's not into breaking the law, which this letter would definitely be doing.</template></category><category><pattern>'CAUSE YOU THINK VERONICA STILL HATES YOU</pattern><template>I know Veronica still hates me. That's not true.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  FORGET I OFFERED TO HELP YOU</pattern><template>Forget the entire fucking idea. 'Cause that must have been fucking crazy because I am so much crazier than you.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T LIKE THE WAY IT MAKES ME LOOK</pattern><template>You've gotta take your medication.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S HIS LIVING  UM  TELL DAD THANKS</pattern><template>Your father expects to spend time with you, Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK INCREDIBLE  THANK YOU</pattern><template>You lost a lot of weight. I've been reading your books and, I have a positive attitude. I'm on medication, I'm in therapy.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  THERE'S A POSSIBILITY  AND I WANT YOU TO BE PREPARED FOR IT  THAT SHE MAY NOT RETURN  TRUE LOVE IS ABOUT LETTING HER GO AND SEEING IF SHE RETURNS  IN THE MEANTIME  IF YOU LISTEN TO THAT SONG  I DON'T WANT YOU TO FALL APART  SO GET A STRATEGY  OKAY  YOU NEED ONE</pattern><template>Let me say something, I gotta say something.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I'M WITH NIKKI  I'M NEVER GONNA DO STUFF LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Whoa, Nikki? What's all this about Nikki?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WE GOT IT  WE GOT IT  OKAY  OKAY</pattern><template>Come on, Pat, come on. A little bit more soul. Black it up, Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT MAKES THE COWBOYS AMERICA'S TEAM</pattern><template>Because we are, we're America's Team.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU PUT THE BREAD CRUMBS  THE GARLIC IN THE STEAK AND YOU ROLL IT UP WITH THE TOOTHPICKS</pattern><template>Yeah. For, oh, maybe three hours, plus.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S OCD  THAT'S CRAZY</pattern><template>What OCD? I want my son to watch the game with me, so sue me.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S MAKING A LOT OF SENSE  POP</pattern><template>That's all right on all counts.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU FORGIVE  ARE YOU ANY GOOD AT THAT</pattern><template>You seemed to have trouble last night.</template></category><category><pattern>BENJAMIN FRANKLIN</pattern><template>Benjamin Franklin. The founder of our country, here in Philadelphia.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO SAY I DO  YUP</pattern><template>Patrizio, I feel terrible, you know? You made the bet, I won a lot of money, and now look, your whole family is in turmoil.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S FINE  YEAH</pattern><template>Why don't you shut up, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>DOLORES  YOU ARE SO BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>Stop that! Hey, hey, hey, stop, stop, stop!</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW</pattern><template>I'm not gonna talk about it anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S MY WEDDING VIDEO</pattern><template>It's after three o'clock!</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU INVITE HIM</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>GUESS WHAT IT IS</pattern><template>Oh, it's a television. It's a computer screen. Nope.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO TOOK ONE OF MY ENVELOPES</pattern><template>Somebody took an envelope.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SCORE IS FROM ONE TO TEN  RIGHT  AND YOU GUYS ARE HOW GOOD</pattern><template>We suck. We don't suck. Pat's a beginner, I'm okay, we're happy just to be going there.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS EVERYBODY'S LEAVING TODAY</pattern><template>Hello, Mrs. S. An honor to finally meet you. Pat told me all about you, how God made you rich in character, and you're the mighty oak that holds the household together, and not to mention the lasagna you make on game day when the Birds play.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOOD WITH A HAMMER  YOU WANT ME TO FIX SOMETHING  A DEAL IS A DEAL</pattern><template>I know. Okay. I was just suggesting that maybe there's a better scenario.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  LET ME GIVE YOU A HAND</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I'm being rude.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BETTER  I FEEL GOOD  I FEEL SO GOOD  LOOK AT MY EYES</pattern><template>Look at my eyes. Look at how clear they are.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE IN WHAT</pattern><template>Next, Pat Solatano and Tiffany Maxwell.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT I WILL DO  I WILL APOLOGIZE ON BEHALF OF ERNEST HEMINGWAY  BECAUSE THAT'S WHO'S TO BLAME HERE</pattern><template>Yeah, have Ernest Hemingway call us and apologize to us, too.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU    HIT YOUR MOTHER</pattern><template>No, no, no, no, no!</template></category><category><pattern>HE DOESN'T HAVE A PROBLEM COMPLAINING ABOUT ERNEST FUCKING HEMINGWAY</pattern><template>He doesn't have a problem asking for his wedding video  Be nice. It's game day! I'm makin crabby snacks and homemades.</template></category><category><pattern>DANNY  YOU'RE OUT OF THE HOSPITAL</pattern><template>And you're here on game day?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA READ NIKKI'S TEACHING SYLLABUS AND GET MY OLD JOB BACK</pattern><template>Nikki sold the house. She left.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  DAD  I KNOW</pattern><template>Thank you, Officer.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A MINUTE  DID VERONICA TELL NIKKI ABOUT OUR DINNER</pattern><template>Why would she do that? Was it a test?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  JORDIE</pattern><template>Let me ask you something. Do you call him when you're lonely?</template></category><category><pattern>PATRICK  PLEASE  PAT</pattern><template>Patty! Don't look for Nikki!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT'S A LIE  IT'S A WHITE LIE</pattern><template>It's a white lie, what's that matter? That's no big deal.</template></category><category><pattern>WE USED TO WORK TOGETHER  JUST GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>I just wanted to give you my card to give to her.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID</pattern><template>Why are you giving me such a hard time?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A COP  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>It's a medication problem, but he's fine now.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES VERONICA STILL TALK TO NIKKI</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>TOMORROW CAN I SPEND HALF THE DAY WITH YOU AND HALF THE DAY AT THE EAGLES GAME</pattern><template>I'm gonna pretend that you didn't just ask me that.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU I WAS GONNA SPLIT MY TIME WITH MY DAD AND YOU  AND MY DAD WAS PULLING ME IN ONE DIRECTION  DOCTOR PATEL  RONNIE  WELL  THAT SOUNDS GREAT  PAT</pattern><template>That's great for all of them, but all of them didn't make a commitment to me in return for my help.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOOKED OVER THERE  I ALREADY LOOKED ALL OVER THERE</pattern><template>Calm down, Pat.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M THE REASON  I DON'T THINK SO</pattern><template>Yeah, Tommy, Tommy, yes, yes. I got your whole sheet.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I'M OUT</pattern><template>Yeah? You're out out?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE DOING A DANCE THING ANYWAY FOR GOD'S SAKE</pattern><template>I want you to remember everything.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST DON'T MAKE HER AN EMERGENCY  THAT CRAZY GIRL  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>She's not crazy... I'll just borrow Jake's phone. It's too bad you can't come in to the stadium, but I know you were kicked out, you know, for beating everybody up. Guess we're not that different, huh, Dad?</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  MRS  S  AN HONOR TO FINALLY MEET YOU  PAT TOLD ME ALL ABOUT YOU  HOW GOD MADE YOU RICH IN CHARACTER  AND YOU'RE THE MIGHTY OAK THAT HOLDS THE HOUSEHOLD TOGETHER  AND NOT TO MENTION THE LASAGNA YOU MAKE ON GAME DAY WHEN THE BIRDS PLAY</pattern><template>Danny was in for assault because of crystal meth and alcohol.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW YET  CAN YOU MAKE IT NEXT SUNDAY</pattern><template>Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  REALLY  HOW</pattern><template>I mean, I'm sorry. How'd that happen?</template></category><category><pattern>I GET IT  THE SONG THAT WAS PLAYING WHEN MY WIFE</pattern><template>was in the shower with the history teacher...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT IN YOUR FATHER'S STUDY</pattern><template>Don't go in my study.</template></category><category><pattern>THINK ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Well, I already did do something for you, you know.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  NO  NO  HE PASSED HIS THING  RIGHT</pattern><template>First of all, check with the latest legal development.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>Why are they so excited about a five?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT WAS A THING WITH MY PARENTS  I WISH I COULD JUST EXPLAIN IT ALL IN A LETTER TO NIKKI BECAUSE IT WAS MINOR AND I COULD JUST EXPLAIN IT AND LET HER KNOW THAT I'M ACTUALLY NOT OUT OF CONTROL AND THAT I'M ACTUALLY DOING REALLY WELL</pattern><template>I can get a letter to Nikki. I see her sometimes with my sister.</template></category><category><pattern>PATTY  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>He's got all his Eagles videos and not one video of my wedding!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  JESUS</pattern><template>What the fuck?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN WE HAVE ONE CONVERSATION WITHOUT YOU REMINDING ME THAT MY GODDAMN HUSBAND IS DEAD</pattern><template>Yes, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay, I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  PROVE IT  PROVE IT</pattern><template>How do you want me to prove it? How's he gonna prove it?</template></category><category><pattern>ISN'T IT AWESOME</pattern><template>Not for dinner.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOTTA RETHINK THIS WHOLE THING  I DIDN'T TRUST IT BEFORE  BUT I GOTTA SAY  NOW I DO</pattern><template>Oh, now you like her, Dad?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T STAY  COME ON  I MADE A MISTAKE  I SHOULDN'T HAVE WORN THIS</pattern><template>Dude, you're fine. I like that jersey.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST BE NICE  JUST BE NICE</pattern><template>Wow, wow, wow. Fascinating.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  I KNOW  I KNOW</pattern><template>What meds are you on?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S VERY HAPPY  I'M HAPPY</pattern><template>No, you're so up, up, up, up.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY TO YOU ANYMORE  YOU LOST YOUR WIFE  I'M GETTING ENGAGED  AND I WANNA BE ABLE TO TELL YOU ABOUT THOSE KIND OF THINGS  YOU LOST YOUR HOUSE  I'M GETTING A NEW HOUSE  YOU LOST YOUR JOB  THINGS ARE GOING GREAT FOR ME AT THE FIRM</pattern><template>Maybe stop talking about all the stuff that's good for you and bad for him. Just, you know, leave it alone. We're watching the game.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT  THE HANDKERCHIEF</pattern><template>And I'm glad that the Seahawks are losing and we're winning, but I gotta take Danny McDaniels back to Baltimore, alright? He can contest his case from Baltimore.</template></category><category><pattern>I TELL THE TRUTH  BUT YOU'RE MEAN</pattern><template>What? I'm not telling the truth?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN  YOU CAN'T DO IT  YOU CAN'T DO WHAT</pattern><template>I can't give the letter to Nikki.</template></category><category><pattern>GUYS  I'M BEATING THE SONG  I'M ON THE SCOREBOARD</pattern><template>I'm playing down field! I feel great!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SONG IS KILLING ME</pattern><template>Could you please turn it off?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE LEFT  WHAT DO YOU THINK  WHERE IS SHE</pattern><template>Let me tell you, I know you don't wanna listen to your father, I didn't listen to mine but I'm telling you, you gotta pay attention to the signs. When life reaches out with a moment like this, it's a sin if you don't reach back. I'm telling you, it's a sin if you don't reach back, and it'll haunt you for the rest of your days like a curse. You're facing a big challenge in your life right now, at this very moment, right here.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING  YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT MY MARRIAGE  OKAY  DAD</pattern><template>All right? Our marriage...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T  DO YOU</pattern><template>No. But then people were getting into fights in the parking lot at work, and in the bathroom... and the boss called me in to his office and tried to pin it all on me. So I accused him of harassment and then they fired me, sent me home and put me on some meds.</template></category><category><pattern>I MISSED YOU  I REALLY NEED SOMEONE TO TALK TO  YOU GOTTA COME SEE THE BABY</pattern><template>She's beautiful. And Veronica wants to make dinner for you.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS MY LITTLE BROTHER PAT</pattern><template>Hey, how you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>PATTY  PATTY  ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS WE HAVE TO MAKE A FIVE</pattern><template>That's all. You stay here and watch the game with me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE  I'VE CALLED HER  I'VE TEXTED HER</pattern><template>I still haven't heard back.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED OF YOURSELF  WE'RE IN PHILADELPHIA  WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU</pattern><template>You're a fucking traitor.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW IT THE MINUTE I MET YOU</pattern><template>I'm sorry it took so long for me to catch up. I just got stuck. Pat.   I wrote that a week ago.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN</pattern><template>Those cocksuckers!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT OCD  I WANT MY SON TO WATCH THE GAME WITH ME  SO SUE ME</pattern><template>Just sit down, come on. I want you to watch the game with me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING  YOUR HUSBAND'S DEAD</pattern><template>Where is your wife?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHAT I BELIEVE TO BE TRUE</pattern><template>This is what I learned in the hospital.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU PUT IT UP HERE</pattern><template>What about in your father's study?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TALK ABOUT ME IN THE THIRD PERSON</pattern><template>Please, gimme a break.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T PAY ANY ATTENTION</pattern><template>Who's that? That's not Rick D'Angelo, is it? That's him.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  THAT'S WHAT ALL THIS EAGLES STUFF IS ABOUT  IT'S ABOUT US  SPENDING TIME NOW  I WANNA DO EVERYTHING I CAN TO HELP YOU GET BACK ON YOUR FEET  THAT'S THE WHOLE POINT  YEAH</pattern><template>I wish you'd watch these games with me so we could talk, we could get into things.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN GIVE ME THE MONEY NOW  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Patty, Patty, all we have to do is we have to make a five.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT  YOU WOULDN'T DO THAT  WHY WOULD YOU CALL THEM</pattern><template>What's up?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  KIND OF  WHAT KIND OF EMERGENCY</pattern><template>Well, I'm just doing this project with Tiffany and I wanted to tell her I'm not gonna be on time.</template></category><category><pattern>HE TOLD YOU THAT  HE TOLD ME  YES</pattern><template>Even with all his friends? With all his friends. He trusts you.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  A LOT OF ENVELOPES GO IN AND OUT OF MY OFFICE EVERY DAY AFTER GAMES WITH A LOT OF CASH IN 'EM  SO SHOW SOME RESPECT FOR WHAT I DO</pattern><template>Yeah, I know. I saw two seven four.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  NO  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Pat. I'm out.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES IT'S OKAY WITH GIRLS LIKE THIS  THEY WANNA HAVE FUN AND SOMETIMES     IT'S NOT BECAUSE THEY GOT A BROKEN WING  AND THEY'RE HURT  AND THEY'RE AN EASY TARGET  AND IN THIS CASE  IN THIS PARTICULAR CASE  I THINK THAT WING IS BEING FIXED</pattern><template>And you gotta make sure it gets mended. And you're gettin' in the way of that right now, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANNA GO BACK TO BALTIMORE</pattern><template>Is that what you wanna do?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  BUT MY DAD OPENED UP TO ME AND IT WAS REALLY BEAUTIFUL AND I WANNA BE OF SERVICE TO HIM  OKAY</pattern><template>And he's worried that the juju from the Eagles is being fucked up and he's concerned that it's because I'm spending time with you.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS GIVES US A CHANCE TO COMMUNICATE WHILE I KEEP THE RESTRAINING ORDER UNTIL I FEEL SAFE</pattern><template>I must admit you sound terrific and I'm happy that you are feeling so positive and becoming a more loving and caring man, which I always knew you were.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  TELL ME THAT ONE</pattern><template>It's insanity. He spikes the ball at the one yard line. The one fucking yard line.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT HER TO SEE THIS</pattern><template>It's okay, everything is okay. We're fine, thank you, we appreciate it. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU KNOW WHAT  I DON'T HAVE HER PHONE NUMBER  IF YOU WANT  IF YOU REALLY WANT  YOU CAN CALL VERONICA 'CAUSE SHE DOES  BUT I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO VERONICA</pattern><template>Why don't you wanna talk to Veronica?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW WHEN I RUN</pattern><template>I wanted to clarify something.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  MOM  JUST HOLD ON A SEC</pattern><template>Let's just talk about this.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A    SEE</pattern><template>Handkerchief? Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S TIFFANY</pattern><template>I don't know, Mom. Have you seen her?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL GONNA BE BETTER NOW</pattern><template>I'm better now and I hope you are, too. And I'm gonna appreciate...   Hey, I'll be there in a minute, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>TO SWEAT</pattern><template>Sit down. We're seven minutes in, no score. Come on, help turn the juju around.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU PLEASE  I DON'T HAVE A FILTER WHEN I TALK</pattern><template>Can we have one conversation without you reminding me that my goddamn husband is dead?</template></category><category><pattern>THE EAGLES WON  FORTY FOUR SIX</pattern><template>They won, forty  four six!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW YOU GONNA PAY FOR IT</pattern><template>I'm gonna pay for it, don't worry about it.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S RIGHT  DAD</pattern><template>The next time we went for a run the Eagles beat the Falcons, twenty  seven to fourteen.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOOD  HOW'S YOUR RESTRAINING ORDER</pattern><template>I wouldn't actually call the restraining order  my thing,   but getting back with Nikki is, and I've been doing pretty well.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO THESE KIDS</pattern><template>Are you being a punk on Halloween with these kids?</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID IT SEVERAL TIMES  TIFFANY  AND THIS IS HIS CHANCE</pattern><template>You gotta give him a chance.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU KNEW THAT  MAYBE YOU SHOULD'VE SCOUTED 'EM</pattern><template>Look at those fucking dancers!</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE MINUTES AGO  WE WERE WALKING UP THE STAIRS  YOU SAID   DON'T SAY ANYTHING  BUT DAD LOST HIS JOB AND HE'S BOOKMAKING    WHY  DOLORES  WHY DID YOU SAY THAT TO HIM  HE HAS THE WRONG IDEA</pattern><template>Everything's fine, Patrick. I'm more concerned about you than anything else.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW I CAN'T TELL YOU THAT</pattern><template>But Doug Culpepper is still here.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T MIND IT</pattern><template>You don't, do you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE HAD TWO VODKAS  LISTEN  I DON'T KNOW WHAT CHOICES YOU'VE MADE  BUT YOU GOTTA DEAL WITH IT RIGHT NOW  OKAY  WE'RE IN THIS</pattern><template>We're in what?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T LIVE WITH US AND NOT GO</pattern><template>Is that song really playing?</template></category><category><pattern>RONNIE  PAT</pattern><template>There he is! He's back!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA UNDERSTAND ME  YOU WANNA GO BACK  WELL THEN  STOP THIS</pattern><template>Then don't fucking do this.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING'S GONNA COME TOGETHER</pattern><template>It's what's meant to be. You okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T KNOW  EITHER  BUT NOW I KNOW</pattern><template>I know, but listen to me, this is toxic. Dad, Dad, Dad, this is toxic, you shouldn't be doing this, you shouldn't be doing  Randy, what do you say...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE</pattern><template>I'll work full time, half time.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW OLD ARE YOU</pattern><template>Old enough to have a marriage end and not wind up in a mental hospital.</template></category><category><pattern>AS SOON AS YOU LEFT  THE REDSKINS THREW A TRICK PLAY  A PITCH OUT TO RANDAL EL</pattern><template>Andy Reid wastes a timeout challenging it, loses the challenge, loses the game.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WHAT  HE WROTE ABOUT ME  I'M  THE GIRL</pattern><template>He wrote about you, all right. What'd he say?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I REALLY WANNA GO  IT'S BEEN GREAT</pattern><template>Okay, guys, the baby is sleeping!</template></category><category><pattern>I'D HAVE TO BE CAREFUL  I'M ALREADY ON THIN ICE WITH MY FAMILY  YOU SHOULD HEAR HOW I LOST MY JOB</pattern><template>How did you lose your job?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I JUST EXPLAIN MYSELF  PLEASE</pattern><template>I didn't want Nikki to think that I was associated with that kind of sexual behavior because I've never done anything like that, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>SO THINK ABOUT THE DANCE THING</pattern><template>Danny, you're out of the hospital?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE SHE'S SENSITIVE AND SHE'S SMART  SHE'S ARTISTIC  THIS IS A GREAT GIRL AND YOU GOTTA BE RESPECTFUL OF THAT  COME ON</pattern><template>Let me walk you down to your car.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE'S JUST GETTING USED TO THE ROUTINE HERE</pattern><template>I don't want him to get used to the routine here.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT DOUG CULPEPPER IS STILL HERE</pattern><template>Why would you tell me that? You know he broke up my marriage.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S NOT HERE</pattern><template>Hi, guys. How's it going?</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  HOW DO THEY RUN THIS DANCE COMPETITION</pattern><template>I mean, how do they score it and everything?</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE'S WORRIED THAT THE JUJU FROM THE EAGLES IS BEING FUCKED UP AND HE'S CONCERNED THAT IT'S BECAUSE I'M SPENDING TIME WITH YOU</pattern><template>Oh, I messed up the Eagles' juju?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YEAH  HE CALLS ME  JAILHOUSE LAWYER    HOLD THE REMOTE THE WAY YOU WERE HOLDING IT BEFORE</pattern><template>Okay. And now you're holding the remote?</template></category><category><pattern>I DID NOT  NO  I DIDN'T</pattern><template>You just told me outside, Mom, what are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME JUST SET THE RECORD STRAIGHT ABOUT LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>Hurting my mother was a mistake and I hate myself for it, and I hate my illness and I want to control it.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS A MESSED UP THING YOU DID  DOCTOR PATEL  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>That's a messed up thing.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING'S WRONG</pattern><template>You should have seen when I was at his house. It's like a circus over there.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT YELLING  MOM  I'M JUST FRUSTRATED BECAUSE I SHOULD HAVE MY FUCKING WEDDING VIDEO</pattern><template>Pat! Pat!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  MARTIN VAN BUREN  THE EIGHTH PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA  IS FROM KINDERHOOK  NEW YORK</pattern><template>Oh.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  JAKE THIS IS CLIFF</pattern><template>This is my doctor, Cliff.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN'T SOMEBODY SAY   HEY  LET'S BE POSITIVE</pattern><template>Let's have a good ending to the story?  Pat, you owe us an apology.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BETTER NOW AND I HOPE YOU ARE  TOO  AND I'M GONNA APPRECIATE      HEY  I'LL BE THERE IN A MINUTE  OKAY</pattern><template>Doctor's waiting. Let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU HAVE TO TAKE MEDICINE</pattern><template>No, I'm not gonna take any medicine. It makes me foggy  No, you will have to take medication.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'D YOU KNOW WE WERE HERE</pattern><template>I went by your parents' house looking for you and they told me you was over here.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU WANNA TALK TO VERONICA</pattern><template>Because she brings me down, man! She just brings me down.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I AT LEAST FINISH MY TEA</pattern><template>Wait, what?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  PLEASE  I THINK PAT  YOU SHOULD BE FACING TIFFANY</pattern><template>Let me show you, Pat, let me show you what I mean. You gotta come at her with a little bit more soul, man.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I'M BEING RUDE</pattern><template>I got it. I got it. I got it.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  SORRY  WE UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>Since when do cops have cards?</template></category><category><pattern>A RESTRAINING ORDER IS NOTHING TO FOOL WITH  BRO  HOLY SHIT  LOOK AT YOU  YOU ARE FIT  YOU LOOK ABSOLUTELY AMAZING  YOU FEEL GOOD</pattern><template>How you doing, Jake? Good. You look like Schwarzenegger in his prime.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST SAYING   AM I MESSED UP</pattern><template>Why don't you stop judging people?</template></category><category><pattern>CH THE STEERING        WHEEL</pattern><template>Pat, this whole thing was a mistake.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S COMPLETELY DIFFERENT</pattern><template>How are you in love? Tell me about that. The big Nikki love.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE DON'T HAVE A MOVE YET</pattern><template>I know, but my dad opened up to me and it was really beautiful and I wanna be of service to him, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF YOU DON'T HAVE THE CONCH  THEN YOU DON'T HAVE THE POWER  AND THEN THERE'S A LITTLE CHUBBY BOY  AND THEY CALL HIM PIGGY AND THEY'RE REALLY MEAN  AND THEN THERE'S A MURDER  I MEAN  HUMANITY IS JUST NASTY AND THERE'S NO SILVER LINING</pattern><template>Wow. That was a great synopsis.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  I LIKE TO RUN ALONE  WILL YOU STOP</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU JUST TAKE YOUR MEDICATION</pattern><template>Come on, I'm doing it with my physicality. I've been workin' out, that's what I'm doin'.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'D I SAY  SHE DOESN'T  SHE DOESN'T DO THAT ANYMORE</pattern><template>I'm sorry about what I said in the diner.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  I CAN'T  IT'S THE SEAHAWKS</pattern><template>Put on the jersey and stay, please.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE HE IS  HE'S BACK</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FOUR O'CLOCK IN THE MORNING  PAT</pattern><template>...and he does. He does. He survives the war, after getting blown up he survives it, and he escapes to Switzerland with Catherine. But now Catherine's pregnant. Isn't that wonderful?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DIDN'T YOU RUN WITH ME  HUH</pattern><template>I was reading.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  HE GOT US FLOWERS</pattern><template>Oh, that's sweet. That's sweet, Pat. That's lovely.</template></category><category><pattern>CONGRATULATIONS ON THE BABY  BUT I'M NOT BUYING THE INVITATION</pattern><template>'Cause you think Veronica still hates you?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SORRY</pattern><template>Dear Pat, It was very emotional for me to get your letter, as I'm sure you can imagine, but I'm glad you took the risk of discreetly getting it to me through Tiffany.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT  WAIT  WAIT</pattern><template>Can I do.. an interview for a school project on mental illness? No.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M REMAKING MYSELF</pattern><template>DeSean Jackson. What happened to DeSean Jackson?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS A BIG SLUT  BUT I'M NOT ANYMORE  THERE'S ALWAYS GONNA BE A PART OF ME THAT'S SLOPPY AND DIRTY  BUT I LIKE THAT  WITH ALL THE OTHER PARTS OF MYSELF  CAN YOU SAY THE SAME ABOUT YOURSELF  FUCKER</pattern><template>Can you forgive? Are you any good at that?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DON'T TOUCH THEM  AS A MATTER OF FACT  I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU NEED SO MANY</pattern><template>Hey, there she is! Look how beautiful!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL BE ALL GOOD  IT'LL WORK OUT</pattern><template>Yes! It will be!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN  DAD</pattern><template>I'm not gonna make that, that, that connection that you're making with DeSean Jackson. It doesn't matter anymore okay? Just because I have the fucking jersey on...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK  WHAT'S THAT SMELL</pattern><template>Nasty Indian curry! This is America, baby! Go back to your country!</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME JUST ASK YOU SOMETHING</pattern><template>Does Nikki still work here?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DON'T APPROVE  YOU CAN'T DO IT</pattern><template>Well, you know, I didn't approve when you called her and you told her where he was running, so she could ambush him. I didn't approve of that, but you did it anyway, so I'm doing this anyway. That's it.</template></category><category><pattern>GRAPES OF WRATH  AND WATCHING FOOTBALL WITH YOUR DAD</pattern><template>Tiffany, I'm not gonna do a dance with you.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCELSIOR</pattern><template>Wait, what's this?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN CALL ME CLIFF  PLEASE</pattern><template>Yeah, well, Cliff, that's not the way you're supposed to meet people, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>NIKKI'S WAITING FOR ME TO GET IN SHAPE AND GET MY LIFE IN ORDER  AND THEN SHE'S GONNA BE WITH ME  AND THAT'S BETTER THAN ANY MEDICATION</pattern><template>Pat, there's a possibility, and I want you to be prepared for it, that she may not return. True love is about letting her go and seeing if she returns. In the meantime, if you listen to that song, I don't want you to fall apart. So get a strategy, okay? You need one.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I ACTUALLY CHANGED THE FIRST PARAGRAPH  I DID THIS THING ABOUT SHAKESPEARE AND HOW IT'S VERY ROMANTIC  MM HMM   AND THAT MAYBE IN THE FUTURE IF SHE WANTED TO GO DANCING  I CAN BE ABLE TO DO THAT BECAUSE OF ALL THE TRAINING THAT NO  THAT'S GOOD  THAT'S REALLY GOOD</pattern><template>I assume you're a good teacher.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY BOTH LIKE TO DANCE WITH EACH OTHER  THERE'S SCENES OF THEM DANCING  WHICH WAS BORING  BUT I LIKED IT  BECAUSE THEY WERE HAPPY</pattern><template>You think he ends it there?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT A COMPLAINER ANYMORE</pattern><template>I'm a positive guy. Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF YOU WERE COOL  YOU WERE IN THE CLUB  THEY'D SAY   THAT GUY'S OK    'CAUSE HE WAS IN THE OLD KINDERHOOKS</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>THINGS ARE LOOKING UP</pattern><template>Oh, are they?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE  WELL  WE'RE DIFFERENT  I MEAN  OH  MY GOD  UGH  YOU'RE KILLING ME</pattern><template>You know what? Forget I offered to help you.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER USED TO DO THAT  I DO THAT NOW</pattern><template>'Cause we're gonna be better than ever... Nikki. Just practicing.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING  NO  NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>Don't touch them, don't touch them.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW HOW TO ACT WITH YOU WHEN YOU DO THIS SHIT</pattern><template>You wanna have dinner at this diner?</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE MUSIC SOMETIMES</pattern><template>That song is killing me.</template></category><category><pattern>I STILL HAVEN'T HEARD BACK</pattern><template>We used to work together  Just get the hell out of here...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO WAY</pattern><template>She..., no, she might be with him. She's afraid of you.</template></category><category><pattern>TREMENDOUS  TREMENDOUS</pattern><template>Isn't it great?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  PRETTY COOL  RIGHT</pattern><template>That's interesting.</template></category><category><pattern>ANDY REID WASTES A TIMEOUT CHALLENGING IT  LOSES THE CHALLENGE  LOSES THE GAME</pattern><template>You're in this house, please show some respect for what I do.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I DON'T KNOW  BECAUSE I'M MARRIED AND I HAVEN'T SEEN MY WIFE IN EIGHT AND A HALF MONTHS</pattern><template>Maybe you think that Nikki's not around and Tiffany's an attractive girl and if you get drawn towards Tiffany, you will spoil your chances of getting Nikki back to you?</template></category><category><pattern>THE LAWYER  HE INSTRUCTED ME  HE SAID THAT WHAT WE SHOULD PLEAD THAT  AND THEN I WOULD SERVE EIGHT MONTHS AND THEN I'D GET OUT</pattern><template>It's all under control.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  ARE YOU KIDDING ME  SUNDAYS</pattern><template>I love Sundays. I live for Sundays.</template></category><category><pattern>EMBRACE IT  EMBRACE IT</pattern><template>I'm the reason? I don't think so.</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  I BORROWED ONE OF YOUR ENVELOPES</pattern><template>I hope that's not a problem No, it's not okay. It's not okay. You gotta ask.</template></category><category><pattern>I START BREAKING SHIT  AND I HURT MY HAND  AND   RONNIE  THAT'S FUCKED UP  YEAH  BUT IT MAKES ME FEEL BETTER</pattern><template>It's like my therapy, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>WILL SOMEBODY PLEASE EXPLAIN TO ME THE PARLAY  PLEASE</pattern><template>You gotta win two bets or you lose the whole thing. For Pat Sr. to win, the birds gotta beat the Cowboys plus Pat and Tiffany gotta get at least a five at the dance.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I THOUGHT YOU WERE DOING IT</pattern><template>We're doing a dance thing anyway for God's sake.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOTTA GO  MAN</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>STAY BACK  PAT  STAY BACK</pattern><template>Leave the fucking Indians alone. Stay here, stay here!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>We're in love and we're married.</template></category><category><pattern>GET AWAY FROM ME  GET AWAY</pattern><template>I'm better. I just want to let you know, I'm better now. Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A FUNNY GIRL  YOU WANNA GET A DRINK SOMETIME</pattern><template>What'd I say? She doesn't, she doesn't do that anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  LET'S SEE THE SCORES FOR SOLATANO AND MAXWELL</pattern><template>We have a four point nine, four eight, a four nine...</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THE DANCERS  YOU SEE THEM  SHIT</pattern><template>Hey, Randy, Jake. What do we got?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T GIVE THE LETTER TO NIKKI</pattern><template>Tiffany, what are you talking about? What do you mean you can't give the letter to Nikki? Because what am I getting in return?</template></category><category><pattern>NIKKI IS BEING MANIPULATED AND CONTROLLED  YOU HAVE TO TALK TO HER</pattern><template>Hey, sit down.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT ANY MEDS  DOCTOR</pattern><template>Look, I am not the explosion guy, okay? My father is the explosion guy.</template></category><category><pattern>NO WAY  DAD  YOU MEAN  DOUG CULPEPPER</pattern><template>Put the phone down. You gotta...</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  LET'S GO FOR THE TOUR</pattern><template>I've, I've been planning this forever. I love our house.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN</pattern><template>I'm just the crazy slut with a dead husband!</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE MONEY THAT HE NEEDS FOR THE RESTAURANT  HE'S BETTING ON THE GIANT GAME</pattern><template>Tell him why. Because he believes in you. Is that true?</template></category><category><pattern>DOLORES  SOMEBODY WAS IN MY STUDY</pattern><template>Who took one of my envelopes?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A TOUGH ROOM</pattern><template>Got it.</template></category><category><pattern>UNBELIEVABLE  WOW  HOW DID YOU KNOW ALL THAT STUFF</pattern><template>I did my research. Well, I gotta say, I'm impressed.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT A DATE  SO HOW'S YOUR THING GOING    YOUR DANCING THING</pattern><template>It's good. How's your restraining order?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE WE ARE  WE'RE AMERICA'S TEAM</pattern><template>You should be ashamed of yourself. We're in Philadelphia, what's the matter with you?</template></category><category><pattern>WORK ON A STRATEGY  OKAY</pattern><template>Hey, my friend Ronnie's having this party on Sunday night and it's like a real hoity toity thing and his wife, Veronica's a real stickler for...</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO WHAT HE'S SAYING</pattern><template>Listen to what he's saying. What's he saying?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M PLAYING DOWN FIELD  I FEEL GREAT</pattern><template>Hey, how you doin'? Is Tiffany here?</template></category><category><pattern>FORGET IT</pattern><template>Shut the fuck up.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL THEN  WHAT'S THE PROBLEM  HE'S NOT GOIN' ANYWHERE  JUST LET HIM FINISH THE GAME  THAT'S ALL  THE HANDKERCHIEF IS WORKING  WE'RE KILLING THE SEAHAWKS  TWENTY SEVENTEN</pattern><template>What's the matter with you? Let him stay, please!</template></category><category><pattern>MADE ME FEEL LIKE SUCH A PERVERT</pattern><template>Maybe we should change the subject.</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME BACK  MAN</pattern><template>Yeah, I'm out.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MISSUS SOLATANO  MISTER SOLATANO  I'M OFFICER KEOGH</pattern><template>I work this beat. Look, I heard about the restraining order.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD  HEY</pattern><template>Are you okay? Ronnie called. Hey, is that make up on your shirt?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE AGREEMENT THAT WE MADE MONTHS AGO</pattern><template>It was a plea bargain with the courts.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HAPPENING</pattern><template>Oh, my God. Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW  OKAY</pattern><template>Can I use your phone?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  TO YOUR NEED  UH HUH</pattern><template>All right, let's start simple. Start at that corner, walk towards me.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Just be nice. Just be nice.</template></category><category><pattern>PAT  THIS WHOLE THING WAS A MISTAKE</pattern><template>I'm sorry, Mom. You okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST GOTTA GET A STRATEGY  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Me too.</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT BETTER  SO IF I WAS TO SAY YOU ONLY HAVE TO SCORE FIVE  I WOULD BE REALLY VERY GENEROUS  RIGHT</pattern><template>No, no, that would be amazing if we got five. Let's not get away  Oh, come on, we can get a five out of ten!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ARE WE DOING IN HERE  HUH</pattern><template>There are a lot of reports from your neighbors, we got a lot of phone calls.</template></category><category><pattern>PANTIES ON THE GROUND AND THEN     I LOOK UP AND I SEE HER NAKED IN THE SHOWER</pattern><template>...and I think,  Oh, that's kinda sweet, she's in the shower.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL THEN  DON'T BEHAVE THIS WAY</pattern><template>I got... a call asking to...</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GONNA BE A CHEESESTEAK PLACE</pattern><template>How you gonna pay for it?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW HER  I KNOW HER  WE'VE DATED  WE STILL DATE</pattern><template>What are you doing here? I've called her, I've texted her.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA GIVE HIM A CHANCE</pattern><template>Bartender! Bartender, can I get a vodka, please?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I AM NOT THE EXPLOSION GUY  OKAY  MY FATHER IS THE EXPLOSION GUY</pattern><template>I'm not that guy.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE DOES  HE DOES  HE SURVIVES THE WAR  AFTER GETTING BLOWN UP HE SURVIVES IT  AND HE ESCAPES TO SWITZERLAND WITH CATHERINE  BUT NOW CATHERINE'S PREGNANT  ISN'T THAT WONDERFUL</pattern><template>She's pregnant. And they escape up into the mountains and they're gonna be happy, and they're gonna be drinking wine and they dance...</template></category><category><pattern>I WORK THIS BEAT  LOOK  I HEARD ABOUT THE RESTRAINING ORDER</pattern><template>And I heard you went to your old house and the school.</template></category><category><pattern>SUNDAY IS MY FAVORITE DAY AGAIN</pattern><template>I think of everything everyone did for me and I feel like... a very lucky guy.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MAN  I'M  I'M THINKING OF REDOING IT AGAIN</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT FLIRTING WITH YOU</pattern><template>Oh, I didn't think you were.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  DAD  DAD  DAD  DON'T</pattern><template>It's all ruined, you little fucking shit!</template></category><category><pattern>HURTING MY MOTHER WAS A MISTAKE AND I HATE MYSELF FOR IT  AND I HATE MY ILLNESS AND I WANT TO CONTROL IT</pattern><template>My father, on the other hand, had no trouble slapping the shit out of me last night, which I did not return 'cause I could've killed him and I didn't. He's sixty five years old.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THE QUESTION  THE BIG QUESTION  IS WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO WITH YOURSELF</pattern><template>What am I gonna do? I'm getting in shape, I'm getting trim, I'm getting really fit for Nikki.</template></category><category><pattern>A SILVER DEVELOPMENT</pattern><template>That's a silver lining!</template></category><category><pattern>I OPENED UP TO YOU AND YOU JUDGED ME</pattern><template>You are an asshole. You are an asshole!</template></category><category><pattern>WAS IN THE SHOWER WITH THE HISTORY TEACHER</pattern><template>I heard about that.</template></category><category><pattern>THREE  TWO  ONE  PHILADELPHIA BEATS DALLAS</pattern><template>They are on their way to the playoffs.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WORLD WILL BREAK YOUR HEART TEN WAYS TO SUNDAY  THAT'S GUARANTEED</pattern><template>And I can't begin to explain that   or the craziness inside myself and everybody else, but guess what?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY GET CLOSE    AND THEN THEY BLOW IT  THEY GOT AN INFERIORITY COMPLEX</pattern><template>Wait a minute, what are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE GET  WE SO OFTEN GET CAUGHT IN THIS STATE OF NEGATIVITY AND IT'S A  IT'S A POISON LIKE NOTHING ELSE</pattern><template>...technically, you can take him out against our recommendation, but you assume a lot of liability in the eyes of the court.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY SHIT</pattern><template>Is this  Dancing with the Stars ?</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A PORT IN EVERY ROOM  GIMME AN IPOD</pattern><template>Who, who doesn't have an iPod?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A SECOND  BUT YOU PROMISED YOU WOULD DO THIS</pattern><template>Think about it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO TOLD YOU YOU CAN'T BE HAPPY</pattern><template>It's all right. You just do your best, you have no choice.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS NOT A REFLECTION OF WHERE I'M AT  YOU CAN'T    PLEASE  YOU CAN'T TELL HER ANY OF THIS YOU CAN'T TELL NIKKI ABOUT THIS</pattern><template>You need to pipe down.</template></category><category><pattern>UP NEXT  LADIES AND GENTLEMEN PLEASE WELCOME PAT SOLATANO  JR  AND TIFFANY MAXWELL</pattern><template>Damn. Let's go, Patty! Come on, Pat!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOUR SCHEDULE IS SO BUSY</pattern><template>Grapes of Wrath  and watching football with your dad?</template></category></AIML>