<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>ANYTHING MORE ON DUPREE'S CAR</pattern><template>Nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THE DIRECTOR ON THE PHONE AND HAVE OUR JET AT THE TARMAC AT LAX IN HALF AN HOUR</pattern><template>Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO DIED AND HAD THEIR BODIES DUMPED IN THE LAKE</pattern><template>The other has severe hypothermia, possible dementia, and will probably be a multiple amputee by week's end.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S ACTUALLY THE HEAD OF CARDIOLOGY AT STOCKHOLM UNIVERSITY</pattern><template>Primo wants Israel's heart.  Heart?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT HAS TO BE HANDLED BY MY STAFF  SIR</pattern><template>How long have you been working here?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE BEEN HERE FOR 16 HOURS</pattern><template>It's pretty dead.  Thank you, Captain Obvious.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO KNOWS  LOCKE HAS BEEN WITH THE LAWYERS FROM JUSTICE SINCE YESTERDAY AFTERNOON</pattern><template>Israel's manager is acting as his attorney. That's what's holding things up.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  SON  I'M DOING ALL THIS TO SAVE HELLER</pattern><template>So you send us in there, bugles blaring, and when it bottoms out, we're the last to know!</template></category><category><pattern>SUPPOSEDLY A SPECIALIST   HE'S HAD A SUSTAINED ARRHYTHMIC EPISODE  SEVERE CARDIAC DISTRESS</pattern><template>He's actually the head of cardiology at Stockholm University.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YEAH  HEY  YOU'RE GOOD TO GO IN</pattern><template>Hey, man.</template></category><category><pattern>I LEAVE MESSAGE</pattern><template>I know you left a message.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID ONE FOR    I WAS ON ONE FOR SIX MONTHS</pattern><template>I gained, like, 20, 25 pounds.</template></category><category><pattern>FORGET IT  YOU WON'T GET A SIGNAL IN HERE</pattern><template>You'll have to wait.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU</pattern><template>Motherfuck! Motherfucker!</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS AN EMERGENCY</pattern><template>Let's hope not.</template></category><category><pattern>DOG PILE OF PISS POOR PHYSIQUE ON TOP OF A SMALL COCK AND HEREDITARY ALCOHOLISM</pattern><template>I appreciate it!</template></category><category><pattern>URINE IS GOOD FOR YOUR SKIN</pattern><template>My grandmother...</template></category><category><pattern>STRONG ARM ROBBERY</pattern><template>Get in the van, man!</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING STINKS HERE</pattern><template>Call San Francisco.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS GOOD  THOUGH  WHAT YOU'RE TELLING ME  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>I need to hear this stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T FUCKING HEAR YOU</pattern><template>How bad?</template></category><category><pattern>EI ESTRAGO    THE PLAGUE    WHEN HE WAS CAUGHT BY THE SAS IN BELFAST    AND IN PRISON  HE CHEWED OFF HIS FINGERTIPS TO THE BONE   WHY DON'T YOU HAVE MAINTENANCE DO IT</pattern><template>Do what, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GET OVER TO THE LAKE</pattern><template>You find out whatever you can.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S 'CAUSE YOU'RE 12 YEARS OLD</pattern><template>Yeah, well, then, who gives a shit?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  WE'RE NOT TOGETHER  NO</pattern><template>Come on, baby. Don't be shy.</template></category><category><pattern>ESPECIALLY THE KIND OF LOYALTY WHERE AN OTHERWISE SENSIBLE MOTHERFUCKER LIKE MYSELF PUT HIS OWN BEST INTERESTS ASIDE</pattern><template>That's why you're my man.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S ONE OF THE BEST HEART SURGEONS IN THE WORLD    THE ACTUAL CONTRACT WENT TO LAZLO SOOT    THE MAN WHO ESCAPED THE PENTHOUSE YESTERDAY     DON'T SHOOT ME</pattern><template>...in disguise.   He was hired by Sparazza to neutralize Israel's entourage.   Dr. Ingstrom was here to perform the surgery.  And as father and son, they are blood compatible.</template></category><category><pattern>SO IF YOU THINK I'M GONNA LET YOUR LITTLE PUNK ASS WITH THE DIRT I DONE</pattern><template>Listen to me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT INCENTIVE IS THERE TO TRACK HIM ON SOMETHING AS SMALL TIME AS A FUCKING SKIP TRACE</pattern><template>I take it you're not going.</template></category><category><pattern>SHAR  SHAR SEVEN   I'M PINCHED    BRING SOME HEAVY SHIT   FIRE FROM THE SKY  MY COUNT</pattern><template>Bet.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  YOU GOT CLICKS</pattern><template>Anything?   No, nothing on my end.   So, how we looking?</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY  WE GOT EACH OTHER</pattern><template>That's all the love we ever gonna need.   Feel me?   You feel me, girl?  Oh, wait a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>A GULFSTREAM IS WAITING AT THE REAGAN NATIONAL AIRPORT TO TRANSPORT YOU TO LAKE TAHOE</pattern><template>And I'll be flying to Los Angeles to finalize Israel's deal.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  I LIVE IN A VAN</pattern><template>What does that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOU GOT THE SEMEN  OKAY  YOU'VE GOT THE HUMAN EJACULATE THAT'S BEEN ALLOWED TO SOAK IN FOR  LIKE  7 HOURS  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Work its way into the fabric fucking fibers...</template></category><category><pattern>REMOVING A SLIGHT PIECE OF BONE IN MY CHIN  I WILL ALTER MY JAW LINE</pattern><template>Eventually, he reached the rank of capo inside the Carlotta crime family,   but due to some internal slipup, his cover was compromised.   Primo Sparazza was given the contract to kill him.  Sparazza is a bit of a specter.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  HELLO  IS ANYONE THERE</pattern><template>I need to speak to security right away.   This is Special Agent Donald Carruthers of the FBI.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE WANTED TO KNOW</pattern><template>Yeah, he's here right now.</template></category><category><pattern>EXPLAIN IT NOW</pattern><template>Go back to Washington.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DON'T NEED MEDICAL ATTENTION</pattern><template>Tell me what's going on.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  DON'T KEEP IT BY THE WATER EITHER</pattern><template>Don't even let it rub shoulders with the other bottle.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN HE GETS HIS DICK WET</pattern><template>Strong arm robbery.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  IF HE'S GONNA RUN  HE'S GONNA RUN NOW  SO WE GOT TO GO</pattern><template>I'm gonna call security and make sure the whole place is locked down.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T DO YOUR MAN DOWNSTAIRS</pattern><template>I found him like that.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE GO</pattern><template>What incentive is there to track him on something as small time as a fucking skip trace?</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAMPAIGNING LIKE NIGGAS AIN'T HOT</pattern><template>We hot.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW I'M PLAYING WITH YOUR PRETTY ASS</pattern><template>Let me ask you a question.</template></category><category><pattern>FOUR YEARS</pattern><template>About six years.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF PERSONNEL</pattern><template>Right now?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BETRAYED US THE WAY YOU BETRAYED THEM</pattern><template>You fucking asshole!</template></category><category><pattern>FBI  YOU GOTTA GET UP THERE  GOT TO GO</pattern><template>Get these hotel guests out in the hallway there.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THAT SPARAZZA'S HAD MAJOR ELECTIVE PLASTIC SURGERY</pattern><template>Fifteen of them. Right?</template></category><category><pattern>WEST TOWER  NOMAD     ALL RIGHT  HOLD ON</pattern><template>Just lay still for a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT TO ORDER WITHOUT</pattern><template>No, no, we cool.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WHY DON'T YOU JUST CHILL FOR NOW</pattern><template>Whatever.</template></category><category><pattern>SAME GUYS WHO HIRED ME  HIS FORMER LAW FIRM</pattern><template>He walked out the door after he made bail.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT  I NEED YOU TO UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>It's time for you to get on a jet back to DC and make no further inquiry into this matter.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STAY WITH ME</pattern><template>Stay with me.</template></category><category><pattern>IMAGINE THAT</pattern><template>I'm pretty much a pantywaist.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS WHAT IT IS    BULLSHIT  IT ISN'T</pattern><template>Listen...  I am not... I don't know how to say it any fucking louder, Morrie.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MENTION OF THIS MYSTERIOUS SWEDE</pattern><template>There's no Swedish hit man on anyone's radar.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF THEM IS A FED</pattern><template>Hello, did you hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>$50 000</pattern><template>ISRAEL: $50,000 for this fucking suite?</template></category><category><pattern>ABSOLUTELY</pattern><template>Hello? Hello? Is anyone there?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAD US FOR THAT</pattern><template>You ain't never made no real beef on your own.</template></category><category><pattern>A JUMBO JET OUT OF THE SKY</pattern><template>Blast down the moon?</template></category><category><pattern>SURE DO   WHAT THE FUCK</pattern><template>What the fuck are you trying to shoot?</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU THOUGHT OLD MAN PRIMO COULD TWIST YOUR SHIT UP   WAIT TILL YOU SEE WHAT I'M ABOUT TO DO HERE   I DON'T BELIEVE THIS</pattern><template>Battery's completely dead.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY TIME AN OPERATIVE FAILED  OR WAS PERCEIVED TO HAVE FAILED  HE WAS BLACKBALLED</pattern><template>Look at what happened to Ness.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK SO</pattern><template>I know so.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THEN  PUNK</pattern><template>No, it was not made clear to me.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE SOME RESPECT  COME ON</pattern><template>STEVE ON RADIO: We have some activity here.  Why don't you speak a little louder, Steve?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU STUCK ON STUPID OR SOMETHING  I KNOW  YOU RODE A LITTLE BUS TO SCHOOL</pattern><template>Hey, man, stop using that fucking lotion, man.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>You shot me.</template></category><category><pattern>SIXTEEN STATE AND FEDERALLY FUNDED AGENCIES RUNNING CONCURRENT CRIMINAL PROBES  ON SELECT MEMBERS OF LA COSA NOSTRA    LOCKE: WITH ISRAEL BEING THE TARGET OF VIRTUALLY EVERY ONE    HIS TESTIMONY HAS THE POTENTIAL OF BLOWING THE LID   OFF OF WHAT'S LEFT OF LA COSA NOSTRA IN THIS COUNTRY    THAT ALONE WARRANTS TOTAL IMMUNITY FROM PROSECUTION   AND A VANISHING ACT WITH THE WITNESS PROTECTION PROGRAM   THE WIRETAPS ON SERNA AND PADICHE  MENTION OF ISRAEL'S HEART</pattern><template>Well, that corroborates what we already know.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS THE LIE THAT I TELL YOUR EYES</pattern><template>Making the magic happen in the moment, in that split second, but seeing behind this motherfucker and knowing that it's all bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>A PROCEDURE KNOWN AS RHINOPLASTY WILL REDUCE THE SIZE OF MY NOSE</pattern><template>If you add facial hair to the equation, gentlemen, you have a face that looks nothing like mine, and more importantly, nothing like a federal agent's.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY PULLED IT</pattern><template>Wait, wait. What do you mean?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT CAR</pattern><template>Dupree's car. '89 Cadillac Sedan DeVille.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FINGERS ARE CUT OFF</pattern><template>Poor me.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>Urine is good for your skin.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY THINK HE'S  LIKE  A MYSTIC</pattern><template>You know, something special.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I AM  I WOULD ADVISE YOU TO LOWER YOUR WEAPON  SIR</pattern><template>You're investigating those murders out at the lake, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>DO WHAT  SIR</pattern><template>Shut the elevator down.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHAT HE WOUND UP DOING WAS SPLITTING THE FAMILY INTO DUAL FACTIONS</pattern><template>Sparazza on one side, Israel on the other.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK   DEPUTY  I NEED YOU</pattern><template>I need you to lock down...</template></category><category><pattern>DUPREE WAS GOING IN AS SECURITY</pattern><template>Yep.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE SPEND THE NIGHT</pattern><template>Come on, baby, look.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I SAID DYING  NOT DEAD   SHIT</pattern><template>Shit, girl.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SAYING WE'RE GONNA HIT WHOEVER'S BETWEEN US AND ISRAEL  THAT'S HOW I'M ON IT</pattern><template>I ain't trying to dead the whole floor and I don't want to be killing no women.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID YOU SAY TO MECKLEN ON THE LITTLE MOTHERFUCKING MACHINE</pattern><template>That you were returning his call and you were very, very concerned.</template></category><category><pattern>I MIGHT JUST BORROW THIS FOR A LITTLE WHILE</pattern><template>MESSNER: Your IFB working?  No, that's why we're on walkies.</template></category><category><pattern>OR HE STILL FUCKING WITH THAT LITTLE LIGHT SKINNED GIRL   I AIN'T TRYING TO BREAK A SWEAT OFF OF THAT MOTHERFUCKER</pattern><template>Yeah, fuck that nigga, man.</template></category><category><pattern>NO PROBLEM</pattern><template>Great, that's good.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN ON RADIO: DO A SWEEP ON CAMERA THREE  MAYBE WE CAN PICK HIM UP   BILL  CAN I SPEAK TO YOU PRIVATELY</pattern><template>If you get a chance...  Gary? Let's get our personnel up on the catwalk over 12.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO TAKE HIM TO</pattern><template>Okay, gentlemen, let's get him up on the roof.</template></category><category><pattern>FEMALE REPORTER:    THE TWO MEN WERE SLAIN HERE EARLIER TODAY    AS AUTHORITIES SPECULATE AS TO THE APPARENT DISAPPEARANCE OF A THIRD    THE NAME OF ONE VICTIM IS BEING WITHHELD    BUT THE OTHER VICTIM IN BEING IDENTIFIED AS JACK DUPREE     OH  SHIT  GODDAMN IT</pattern><template>Son of a fucking bitch! Fuck!</template></category><category><pattern>NOBODY GETS NEAR THE CRIME SCENE</pattern><template>Make it happen, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>WORK ITS WAY INTO THE FABRIC FUCKING FIBERS</pattern><template>If you like, I send out.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU'RE ON SOME BULLSHIT</pattern><template>But I can shape it, I can shift it, I can make it as real as this room.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT A FUCKING HEART TRANSPLANT</pattern><template>You're gonna kill Israel to save Sparazza.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GO UP IN THERE AD LIBBING AND SHIT  IT'S YOUR ASS</pattern><template>What are we talking on the split?</template></category><category><pattern>NESS AND THE UNTOUCHABLES TOOK DOWN CAPONE</pattern><template>Heller got shot and killed.</template></category><category><pattern>CLOSE YOUR EYES</pattern><template>Don't make this face the last thing you ever see.</template></category><category><pattern>WERE THESE UNIFORMS RECOVERED</pattern><template>No, we're still looking.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE OKAY</pattern><template>No, no. Stay awake.</template></category><category><pattern>BRING HIM UP HERE</pattern><template>We gotta get packed up.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE ALL SISTERS EVERYWHERE  BLACK  WHITE  BROWN AND YELLOW  PUT OUR SHIT DOWN ONE TIME  A UNIFIED FRONT  YOU KNOW  THE FEMALE RACE  MOBILIZED  BABY  MOVING AS ONE  YOU FEEL ME</pattern><template>I'm gonna need a minibar key, too.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT LOOKS LIKE SOME FUCKHEAD SHOT HIS LOAD ON A $12 000 CALFSKIN JACKET</pattern><template>The twist is it's my $12,000 calfskin jacket!</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  PLEASE  PLEASE  RAPE HIM IF IT'S POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Punch him in the seat or something, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I NEED YOU TO CHILL</pattern><template>I need you to call the florist.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKES A LOT OF SPACE</pattern><template>Did you cook up this little construction thing?</template></category><category><pattern>HOES GOTTA GO</pattern><template>Get them out of here.</template></category><category><pattern>SPARAZZA ON ONE SIDE  ISRAEL ON THE OTHER</pattern><template>The infighting that followed drew the interest of every investigative body   operating under the canopy of the federal government.  This is it, right here.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  CHRIST</pattern><template>I will maintain a slight limp.   My accent will be a regional Calabrese.  My birthplace, Cosenza, Italy.</template></category><category><pattern>SUPPOSEDLY  A SPECIALIST</pattern><template>And he ain't coming cheap.   So I'm thinking we jump,   get to Israel before the Swede can, we're in a power position.   We grab him...</template></category><category><pattern>WALK WITH ME</pattern><template>Okay, so obviously, we got a man posing as one of us.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT HELLER WAS A DOUBLE OP</pattern><template>He worked for the OSS before joining the Bureau in its heyday.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STAY DOWN  YOU STAY DOWN</pattern><template>Do you hear what I'm saying?</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY THE DIRECTOR HIMSELF</pattern><template>He asked that you contact him immediately.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  THEY DON'T KNOW WHERE HE'S FROM  HOW LONG HE'S BEEN IN THE GAME    OR EVEN WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE    BUT WHEN SOOT DECIDES TO MOVE ON SOMEBODY    THEY'RE THE LAST ONES TO SEE IT COMING    DUPREE: SO  THERE IT IS   THE BOND ON BUDDY ISRAEL EXPIRES IN 18 HOURS</pattern><template>After that, it's a jump ball.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS  GOD</pattern><template>Dog pile of piss poor physique on top of a small cock and hereditary alcoholism.</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT</pattern><template>Drop that goddamn gun now or you're a dead man!</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ISN'T A FUCKING LAUNDRY DETERGENT OR DRY CLEANING PRODUCT KNOWN TO MAN THAT WILL GET THAT CLEAN</pattern><template>Some shit, suffice it to say, just don't wash out!</template></category><category><pattern>THE SECURITY IN PLACE IS SOLELY TO PRESERVE FLOOR INTEGRITY</pattern><template>And who else has access to the floor, Bill?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW BAD</pattern><template>Mortal.</template></category><category><pattern>MALE REPORTER: THE VEHICLE REGISTERED IN MR  DUPREE'S NAME   HAS BEEN RECOVERED IN THE PARKING LOT OF THE NOMAD HOTEL AND CASINO   DON  IF YOU CAN HEAR THIS  I'M IN THE HOTEL  NORTH SIDE</pattern><template>IVY: I changed lives for you.  You ain't never had to wash another man's blood off, dig it out of your fingernails.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  DON'T SHOOT ME</pattern><template>Don't shoot me, please!</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT TO KEEP HIM IN THAT PENTHOUSE</pattern><template>ACOSTA: I'd like to take a look at the penthouse.  No, I'm sorry, the penthouse is currently under construction.</template></category><category><pattern>THREE DAYS STARING AT SPARAZZA'S HOUSE</pattern><template>This guy's got hookers up there fistfighting.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'D YOU GET THESE</pattern><template>Same place that rents to the guards.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU CAN HEAR ME  GIRL  I CAN'T SEE SHIT FROM WHERE I AM</pattern><template>I'm moving down for a better sight line.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT DIDN'T SEEM ODD TO YOU</pattern><template>I mean, I thought they gave it to him so he could...</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT TO GO  BUZZY   HE SAID ONE MILLION</pattern><template>One million.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT THE FUCK UP</pattern><template>Hey, bitch!</template></category><category><pattern>HOTEL LOCKED DOWN AT ALL</pattern><template>I couldn't tell you that right now, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST REMEMBER IT'S MORE OF A RESCUE THAN A RAMPAGE  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Hey, come on, man.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE WORKED VICE  LIKE  6 YEARS</pattern><template>Is that right?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST TOLD ME YOUR GRANDMA SAID THAT PISS IS GOOD FOR YOUR SKIN</pattern><template>Have some respect. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>SPECIAL AGENT GERALD DIEGO  FEDERAL BUREAU OF INVESTIGATION  SAN FRANCISCO FIELD OFFICE</pattern><template>We're conducting a series of impromptu inspections for the Nevada Gaming Commission, and I'd like to speak with your head of security.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD UP  HOLD UP</pattern><template>I'm getting all kinds of shit over this scanner.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WERE NO OTHER AGENTS</pattern><template>Our agents are landing here now.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER THAT  IT'S A JUMP BALL</pattern><template>Who posted the bond?</template></category><category><pattern>SO MANY PEOPLE ARE DEAD</pattern><template>I need you to return to Washington.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  NOW I'M PRAYING HE PUTS UP A FIGHT</pattern><template>Please! Please, please, rape him if it's possible!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT IS</pattern><template>It's filling up your lungs right now.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT'S ALL RIGHT THOUGH</pattern><template>That's cool.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO LOCK DOWN</pattern><template>I need you to limit physical activity...</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THE HO TRAIN JUST ARRIVED</pattern><template>Damn! Four skank ass bitches.</template></category><category><pattern>APPRECIATE IT</pattern><template>Get your dick beaters off it.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS NOT A FUCKING SWAP MEET  ALL RIGHT  MORRIE</pattern><template>I'm not giving up my boys and you fucking know that.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I WHACK ANYBODY</pattern><template>Who am I gonna whack?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU HEAR ME  I'M HIT</pattern><template>Oh, shit.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S NOT ANTAGONIZE THIS ANY MORE  OKAY</pattern><template>If we push this, they are gonna revoke your protective status  and that nullifies any agreement we got.</template></category><category><pattern>COFFEE</pattern><template>No, no, thanks, darling.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WAS</pattern><template>The other agent.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR REAL  BRING YOUR ASS DOWN HERE  SHIT</pattern><template>What the fuck?</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  DID YOU HEAR ME</pattern><template>Did you hear what I said?   I said one of them has got a FBI badge.  Wait a minute, wait a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  WE'LL GET OUR HANDS ON THOSE WHEN WE GET INSIDE</pattern><template>Basically, there's two security levels, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  GRANDMA'S BIG HELPER BOY</pattern><template>Nana, Nana. Nana?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ACTING LIKE Y'ALL ON SUNDIAL  Y'ALL NEED TO BE ON STOPWATCH</pattern><template>Damn it. I didn't realize how fucked up I was till I just saw your ass, girl.</template></category><category><pattern>HUH  RIGHT THERE  AND THEN PADLOCK IT AND THEN YOU PUT THE CHAIN ON IT</pattern><template>That's a new one I'm working on.</template></category><category><pattern>STEP OUT OF THE ELEVATOR</pattern><template>Are these feds fake or real?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT BITCH ASS FED GET IN THE WAY  RIP  NIGGA</pattern><template>Fucking Kevlar, the way I had to stitch it, this shit is itchy as hell.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU FUCKING NUTS</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOT TO BE FRUSTRATING</pattern><template>Copy that. We got her now.  No guests, though, on the penthouse?</template></category><category><pattern>I AIN'T NO FUCKING CLEANING LADY  DAWG</pattern><template>For real. Bring your ass down here. Shit.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THEY RELOCATED HIM TO NEVADA AND MADE HIM THE HEAD OF THE LAS VEGAS COSA NOSTRA</pattern><template>Water.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  WE'RE COVERING SOME VERY SENSITIVE MATERIAL HERE  AND I'VE GOT TO SAFEGUARD MYSELF  SO IF YOU COULD JUST SHOW ME YOUR ID AGAIN  GET YOUR CLEARANCE</pattern><template>Of course, great.</template></category><category><pattern>MESSNER</pattern><template>Listen. Hold it. I need to speak with Locke.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ON THE WAY UP TO THE PENTHOUSE</pattern><template>Lester!</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN     I AM NOT    I DON'T KNOW HOW TO SAY IT ANY FUCKING LOUDER  MORRIE</pattern><template>I am not giving up my boys.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME ISOLATE THE</pattern><template>Never mind! Just get in there.</template></category><category><pattern>MMM HMM</pattern><template>Them are left over after my hysterectomy, so they'd be a few years old.</template></category><category><pattern>MY NAME IS VITOLI</pattern><template>How can I be of assistance?  Vitoli!</template></category><category><pattern>DIRECTOR LOCKE</pattern><template>He's had a sustained arrhythmic episode, severe cardiac distress.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT</pattern><template>Well, yeah, hey, you're good to go in.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KEEP EATING THIS CRAP</pattern><template>MESSNER: Well, that's my problem, though.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THAT CORROBORATES WHAT WE ALREADY KNOW</pattern><template>Sparazza's health is in rapid decline and before he dies, he is demanding the heart of his sworn enemy.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY GOT A IMPOSTOR</pattern><template>Some fool with a fake badge.  You think it might be that motherfucker that Loretta was telling us about? Soot?</template></category><category><pattern>DID HE GIVE YOU A NAME</pattern><template>Spanish something.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  IS ANYONE THERE  HELLO   IS THAT BLOOD</pattern><template>Yes, it is.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  BABY  LOOK</pattern><template>We could break down now...  Shit, girl.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  FUCK YOU  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Fuck you and this fucking wig 'cause this shit is getting on my nerves.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU</pattern><template>Get in here!</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE AGENTS FROM THAT ERA  THEY'RE DEAD AND GONE  SO HISTORY DEFAULTED TO FABLE</pattern><template>Until now.</template></category><category><pattern>GET ME A MEDIC</pattern><template>I need a medic.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK</pattern><template>Get me a medic!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THESE PHONES ARE HARDWIRED DIRECTLY TO MAINTENANCE  BUT ONCE WE REACH THE PENTHOUSE  I CAN CALL DOWN</pattern><template>I'll have the elevators taken offline, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE ABOUT THREE MILES FROM THE NOMAD NOW</pattern><template>SERNA ON TAPE: So do this in the next day or so, get to Israel before the Swede can,   we're in a power position.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE PISSED ON YOUR FACE</pattern><template>Get the fuck out of here.</template></category><category><pattern>GIRL  WHERE ARE YOU</pattern><template>God damn it, Georgia!</template></category><category><pattern>DISMANTLED MOST OF THE ORGANIZED CRIME    THIS IS THE ONLY WAY TO TRULY INFILTRATE ORGANIZED CRIME</pattern><template>His superiors were convinced that he had gone rogue, swapped allegiances,  so they gave the order to terminate his cover.   All this time, we were told that it was Sparazza that killed Heller,   when it was us, the FBI.   And we didn't kill him.   He survived.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OTHER AGENT</pattern><template>He said he was here to do some inspections.</template></category><category><pattern>PRETTY MUCH</pattern><template>You were here hunting the man named Israel, weren't you?</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT MESSNER  WE RECOVERED THE CAR</pattern><template>What car?</template></category><category><pattern>SHH  SHUT UP  WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SHOUT FOR</pattern><template>Shh, my ass!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE BEEN LOOKING TO RENOVATE THAT AREA OF OUR HOTEL FOR SOME TIME NOW</pattern><template>The security in place is solely to preserve floor integrity.</template></category><category><pattern>IF IT GIVES YOU ANY COMFORT  YOU KNOW  I WAS GOING IN THERE TO ACT A FOOL  BABY</pattern><template>Straight rocking heat, slaying niggas, man.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE WERE WORRIED ABOUT THE DUST AND DEBRIS FROM THE WORK GOING ON UP THERE RUINING THE CAMERAS</pattern><template>So you shut them off?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BELIEVE IN LOYALTY  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>Do I believe in loyalty?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  ENOUGH SAID</pattern><template>REED: Hi, Jack. Great, good, super. Come on in.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOUR GUY GONNA CALL</pattern><template>That's what's happening.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  HE WAS WEARING ONE OF OUR JACKETS</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT A DECISION HAS BEEN MADE</pattern><template>And we're required to abide by it, regardless of our personal feelings.</template></category><category><pattern>SO DON'T FEEL SO BAD  CHIEF</pattern><template>Oh, damn.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT IT   YOU SHUT THEM OFF</pattern><template>Yes. I mean, no, we...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M HIT</pattern><template>We need a medic!</template></category><category><pattern>CRAZY  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Wall to wall felony offenses.</template></category><category><pattern>ACCOUNT FOR HIM</pattern><template>What's your name, baby girl?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  OKAY  OKAY</pattern><template>Now, I'm a registered nurse and this was my bath not a half hour ago.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MILLION</pattern><template>One million, plus the fucking heart.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  I'M PREPARED TO DISMISS YOUR BEHAVIOR  AND IN LIGHT OF WHAT'S HAPPENED  I UNDERSTAND IT</pattern><template>I really do, and I'm truly sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>YEP</pattern><template>I'm gonna go over to the hotel.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>Special Agent Donald Carruthers, FBI.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER MIND  JUST GET IN THERE</pattern><template>Get in there and pin that girl!</template></category><category><pattern>SON OF A FUCKING BITCH  FUCK</pattern><template>MALE REPORTER: The vehicle registered in Mr. Dupree's name   has been recovered in the parking lot of the Nomad Hotel and Casino.  Don, if you can hear this, I'm in the hotel, north side.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  THEN  WHEN THEM TRICKS HIT THE LOBBY  I WANT YOU TO HOLLER AT ME</pattern><template>I'm gonna meet them on their way up, blend in real nice.   Once I'm inside, I'm puttin' chrome to Israel's head and backing out hot.   Anybody get gully, you know.  I'm gonna grip and rip.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR REAL</pattern><template>Your boy very well might have been one of them.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WE'RE STILL LOOKING</pattern><template>Fuck!  Deputy? I need you...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M IN THE SECURITY ROOM   ARE YOU ANYWHERE NEAR THE PENTHOUSE</pattern><template>No, no.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THEM FELLAS  THE ONES THAT WAS SHOT AND TOSSED INTO THE LAKE</pattern><template>Them police officers, too?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKS VERY GOOD    FUCKING THRILLED TO HEAR IT    SO  THIS SIT DOWN  YOU MUST HAVE FELT IT FROM THEM THEN  HUH    COLD BLOOD  SID  DEAD EYES    OKAY  YEAH  GOOD</pattern><template>So you're at the hotel.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU CONTACTED AGENT CARRUTHERS</pattern><template>Yeah, cell reception up here is terrible, but until you or I speak with him, he's the SAC and he's the guy I answer to...</template></category><category><pattern>NORTH ELEVATOR DOOR'S OPEN</pattern><template>Possible aggression inside.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF YOUR WHALES</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK THAT'S GONNA WORK</pattern><template>And why?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE THE FUCK VITOLI AT</pattern><template>The fuck do you mean? I ain't trying to clean this shit up myself, dawg.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  JUST ONE SECOND</pattern><template>Just hang on, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I MEAN  HE HAD THE BADGE AND EVERYTHING</pattern><template>And when you saw him later, he was wearing one of your security jackets.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY ARE BRICKING US</pattern><template>All right?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  IT'S BITCHES LIKE THAT THE REASON WHY NIGGAS DON'T PAY OUR SPECIES ANY MIND</pattern><template>They don't respect us!</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WE'RE SUPPOSED TO GO IN THERE  BUST ON THIS PUNK AND REMOVE HIS HEART</pattern><template>Is that for real?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WORKED FOR THE OSS BEFORE JOINING THE BUREAU IN ITS HEYDAY</pattern><template>He was the first operative assigned with infiltrating the mob.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  IF YOU LIKE  I'LL TAKE YOUR VERBAL RESIGNATION RIGHT HERE  RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Do you want your career to end here, now, like this?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T SAY THIS TO BE SELF DEPRECATING</pattern><template>I just, you know, don't have much of an opinion of myself. I'd much rather be like you guys.</template></category><category><pattern>FAGGOT ASS REDNECK</pattern><template>What'd you say?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GIVE US YOUR KEYS AND GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  THEN</pattern><template>You know, up here in heaven, it's beautiful.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GOOD WORK</pattern><template>Good fucking work.</template></category><category><pattern>LOVELY</pattern><template>So, I spoke to Loretta this morning.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TO GET TO YOUR PENTHOUSE LEVEL IMMEDIATELY</pattern><template>Well, I'm headed there right now. Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>Well, they dug it up in archives as part of the Sparazza investigation.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS THE FIRST OPERATIVE ASSIGNED WITH INFILTRATING THE MOB</pattern><template>Fake identity, falsified backgrounds, everything that is now standard operating procedure,  Heller implemented way back when.  ...your attention to these overlays, I'll show you exactly what I meant when I said,  Change my face.  And as a result, his undercover work was highly successful.</template></category><category><pattern>SAME PLACE THAT RENTS TO THE GUARDS</pattern><template>All right, there's a shift change at 9:00 a.m.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  BITCHY BITCH</pattern><template>You open the fucking door.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU DUMPED US IN THE LAKE</pattern><template>Pretty much.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU'RE DESCRIBING NOW IS A MUCH LARGER MOVEMENT</pattern><template>Messner?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHAT ABOUT ACCESS CARDS  PASSKEYS</pattern><template>Yeah, well, we'll get our hands on those when we get inside.</template></category><category><pattern>IT DON'T MATTER WHAT YOU WANTED</pattern><template>It's what you did.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLLIS ELMORE</pattern><template>Vegas resident.</template></category><category><pattern>BUDDY WANTS YOU NOW UP TOP</pattern><template>Where are you, you big nut?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO LIMIT PHYSICAL ACTIVITY</pattern><template>Is that clear?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M CONFISCATING IT</pattern><template>FBI.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE THEY DOING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Dying.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ASKED THAT YOU CONTACT HIM IMMEDIATELY</pattern><template>Should we inform Messner and Carruthers?</template></category><category><pattern>CORRECT</pattern><template>Well, enough said.</template></category><category><pattern>LESTER</pattern><template>Fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T FUCK    WHAT THE</pattern><template>Where you going?</template></category><category><pattern>ODDS ARE THEY'RE GONNA GET INTO SOME SHIT    MIGHT HAVE TO PUT PEOPLE DOWN   THESE GUYS AREN'T FUCKING AROUND</pattern><template>PADICHE: Well, just so I get a quote in my head, how much is the Swede getting?   That's the punch line.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE PASQUALE ACOSTA</pattern><template>Blood money mercenary.</template></category><category><pattern>ZOOM BACK IN AND STAY THERE</pattern><template>STEVE: He is on the phone.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE ON RADIO: WE HAVE SOME ACTIVITY HERE   WHY DON'T YOU SPEAK A LITTLE LOUDER  STEVE</pattern><template>Just keep it fucking down.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I BE OF ASSISTANCE   MY NAME IS VITOLI</pattern><template>How can I be of assistance?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA GET TO ISRAEL BEFORE THEY DO</pattern><template>I don't think that's gonna work.</template></category><category><pattern>JIMMY  CUFF HIM</pattern><template>Put him in...</template></category><category><pattern>FORTY FIVE A PIECE FOR YOU TWO</pattern><template>Ten percent finder's fee for me.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>A six man security force plus Vitoli, our executive butler, so seven men, total.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WAS AFTER SOME FOOL NAMED ISRAEL</pattern><template>Damn, girl, you're gonna make a nigga fall hard.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID HE WAS FROM SAN FRANCISCO</pattern><template>Did he give you a name?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE DONE    THEY'RE YANKING US  BUDDY    THEY KILLED US</pattern><template>They killed us.  Three minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HIS BAIL BOND BOBBING AROUND UP THERE OUT AT THE LAKE</pattern><template>Rip, hand to God, you got nothing to worry about with this.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I GUESS YOUR FRIEND DON'T WANT TO HEAR THIS</pattern><template>Hollis? Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  WHERE IS HE</pattern><template>WATTERS: He's dead.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOLD ME TO HAND DELIVER</pattern><template>Where did this come from?</template></category><category><pattern>THE SWEDE'S BEEN DISPATCHED    HE'S FLYING HIMSELF    ALL RIGHT  DAMN  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>So he's headed to Tahoe then, huh?   Yeah. We're in a bit of a footrace right now, Buzzy.   It's a matter of who outhustles who, you know?   We just got to get to Israel first.   It's getting done, Sid.   We got to get him, Buzz.</template></category><category><pattern>DIALOGUE HOT  DIALOGUE HOT   EVERYBODY OFF THE WALKIES NOW</pattern><template>Everybody off air.</template></category><category><pattern>MESSNER: WELL  THAT'S MY PROBLEM  THOUGH</pattern><template>I don't gain weight. I tried.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SHE MIGHT BE MISSING SOME WORK</pattern><template>Oh, hell, no! This is nice.</template></category><category><pattern>HAS ANYONE ELSE SEEN THIS</pattern><template>Only the Director himself.</template></category><category><pattern>THREE OF THEM</pattern><template>Same skank mom, different deadbeat dads.</template></category><category><pattern>GET HIM BACK UP HERE</pattern><template>We gotta...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'D YOU SAY TO MECKLEN</pattern><template>What I've always been saying, let's make the fucking deal.</template></category><category><pattern>GO  GO  GO</pattern><template>Vegas lounge act turns legitimate thug.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALIZE THAT YOU'RE DOING THIS TO SAVE SPARAZZA</pattern><template>No, son. I'm doing all this to save Heller.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE FEELING IT  YOU'RE FEELING IT  COME ON</pattern><template>Outstanding! Get it up there!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FORGOT YOUR HAT</pattern><template>Get your hands off me, asshole!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S YOUR GUY</pattern><template>Right here.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S COOL</pattern><template>It's just some little casino inspection.</template></category><category><pattern>A SIX MAN SECURITY FORCE PLUS VITOLI  OUR EXECUTIVE BUTLER  SO SEVEN MEN  TOTAL</pattern><template>You have an executive butler on the floor?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  HOLD ON</pattern><template>Wait a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>So you made another deal, didn't you?</template></category><category><pattern>YO  GET OUT OF HERE  HUGO  MAN</pattern><template>He working with them people, Hugo!</template></category><category><pattern>SERNA: BUZZY  BUZZ    YEAH  IT'S ME</pattern><template>All right, you got clicks?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  YOU HAVE TO KEEP YOUR EYE ON EVERYTHING</pattern><template>And everybody all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ROLL OF THE CINNAMON</pattern><template>That looks like jizz.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CALLED THE RIGHT BITCHES FOR THIS ONE  MAN</pattern><template>You see? Write that shit down.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING HAPPENED AT TABLE 14   TABLE 12</pattern><template>I got it.  You shut them off.</template></category><category><pattern>MORE DUCT  COME ON  MORE DUCT</pattern><template>A little more duct.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  OKAY</pattern><template>What's up?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  SHIT  I'M SHOT</pattern><template>Georgia!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BITCH</pattern><template>You forgot your hat!</template></category><category><pattern>SPARAZZA INTRODUCED ISRAEL TO THE LIFE    GAVE HIM HIS FIRST BIG BREAK ONSTAGE  BROUGHT HIM UP THROUGH THE RANKS   AND ISRAEL PLAYED THE SITUATION VERY SHREWDLY</pattern><template>Slowly amassing the loyalties of Sparazza's top men,   with the idea of toppling the throne.  You know, I've seen some stupid moves, but...</template></category><category><pattern>YO  CALM DOWN</pattern><template>Don't tell me to fucking calm down!</template></category><category><pattern>MY DEBRIEFING</pattern><template>Your debriefing? Your debriefing will be handled in DC, like I told you.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE'S COUSIN  SOME ZIP OFF THE BOAT FROM NAPLES   ZIP OFF THE BOAT</pattern><template>Let's get pros.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  JUST WAIT TILL WE GET OUTSIDE</pattern><template>Let go of me!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL HANDLE THE REST OF IT</pattern><template>You all right, Hugo?</template></category><category><pattern>SAME YEAR THAT SPARAZZA SUPPOSEDLY MURDERED FREEMAN HELLER</pattern><template>I'd like to show you exactly what I meant when I said,  Change my face.  Using the latest techniques in cosmetic surgery, I will have my ears pinned back.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE WHO KNOW HOW TO BEHAVE   THIS THING'S GONNA BLOW UP HUGE</pattern><template>You know, there's a pair of broads I think might be very good for this.  Which broads?</template></category><category><pattern>I REALLY DO  AND I'M TRULY SORRY</pattern><template>But a decision has been made.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED A MEDIC</pattern><template>Somebody get him out of there!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE RELIABLE</pattern><template>They're good? What?   Two of the best.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCKING STOP IT</pattern><template>Yeah!</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S ON THE PHONE    AGENT 1: I GOT SOME MOVEMENT IN THERE   RICKY  PAN TO THE RIGHT AND ZOOM IN</pattern><template>Okay, we got him.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE STAY OFF THE WALKIES</pattern><template>Buzzy, I'm upstairs.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  HOLD UP  HOLD UP</pattern><template>What I got here is a Gerald Diego.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MUCH LONGER YOU THINK</pattern><template>Who knows? Locke has been with the lawyers from Justice since yesterday afternoon.</template></category><category><pattern>SPANISH SOMETHING</pattern><template>It was Diego or Garcia.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THEM OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT MESSNER IS ON HIS WAY IN</pattern><template>Agent Messner.</template></category><category><pattern>HASN'T BEEN SEEN SINCE</pattern><template>If this Israel really is the great white whale of snitches, then what are we doing messing with the mob, who are, correct me if I'm wrong, but I think they're going to pour boxes of bullets into his ass?</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT 1: HEY  YO  MIKE  WHERE ARE YOU  MAN</pattern><template>I can't see you now.  Are you nervous?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE AN EXECUTIVE BUTLER ON THE FLOOR</pattern><template>Just in terms of the men that are up there now, my team, serving lunch and dinner and just generally doing upkeep.</template></category><category><pattern>SAME SKANK MOM  DIFFERENT DEADBEAT DADS</pattern><template>They're used for that suicide style, kamikaze shit.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER</pattern><template>Would you like two beds in your room?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT SOME HANDLOADS UP HERE READY TO PUT SOME NIGGAS OUT</pattern><template>Trust me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'D YOU SAY</pattern><template>Not you.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WENT DEEP COVER IN 1940</pattern><template>He could have ripped the Mafia apart.  But I firmly believe...</template></category><category><pattern>GET BACK HERE</pattern><template>We'll handle the rest of it.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU SPEND YOUR LIFE PULLING RABBITS OUT OF HATS AND SAWING PEOPLE IN HALF  ANYTHING SEEMS POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Israel wanted to touch something real, something dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU GET A CHANCE     GARY  LET'S GET OUR PERSONNEL UP ON THE CATWALK OVER 12</pattern><template>I don't like the rolls that table's been getting.</template></category><category><pattern>DYING</pattern><template>So, them fellas, the ones that was shot and tossed into the lake?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THESE BITCHES ON A PERMANENT SMOKE BREAK OR WHAT</pattern><template>Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS NAME IS SOOT  LAZLO SOOT</pattern><template>A lot of folks want this white boy clapped.</template></category><category><pattern>WALK  LET'S GO</pattern><template>You're going to tell me why no call was made to inform us that the Israel situation had been altered.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I FORGOT</pattern><template>I don't remember what you said. What?</template></category><category><pattern>WANT TO GO GRAB SOMETHING TO EAT</pattern><template>Yeah. Any word on this Swede?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SORRY ABOUT THAT BOY</pattern><template>His mama abandoned him going on a year now and his daddy, my boy Dale, he's over at the Reno Washoe Correctional Facility.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL MAINTAIN A SLIGHT LIMP    MY ACCENT WILL BE A REGIONAL CALABRESE   MY BIRTHPLACE  COSENZA  ITALY</pattern><template>That's him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT FLOOR ARE THEY ON</pattern><template>I don't know right now.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME SHIT  SUFFICE IT TO SAY  JUST DON'T WASH OUT</pattern><template>Do you want my apology?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  NOW LET'S GET A TACTICAL TEAM ASSEMBLED</pattern><template>We're going up.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLER GOT SHOT AND KILLED</pattern><template>The bad guys beat him.  Worse, Sparazza walked.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT MY FUCKING FACE</pattern><template>You just figure that out?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU A COLOSSAL FUCKING IDIOT</pattern><template>I am, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU  PUSSY</pattern><template>Hey, we did that dance, bitch. Kick rocks.</template></category><category><pattern>I FORGIVE YOU  DARWIN</pattern><template>Shoot, I appreciate that, man.</template></category><category><pattern>I BET YOU YOUR DICK IS DISINTEGRATING AS WE SPEAK  PLAYER</pattern><template>Stupid ass motherfucker.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS GUY'S GOT HOOKERS UP THERE FISTFIGHTING</pattern><template>Look at all you're missing.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A RECEIPT OUT OF HIS POCKET    IT WAS FOR A UNIFORM RENTAL</pattern><template>What kind of uniform?   The receipt was partially destroyed by the lake water.  What kind of uniforms?</template></category><category><pattern>FREELANCED FOR THE CIA    NOTED FOR HIS LEGENDARY TORTURE TECHNIQUES    WHEN HE WAS CAUGHT BY THE SAS IN NORTHERN IRELAND    IN PRISON HE CHEWED OFF HIS FINGERTIPS TO THE BONES    SO HE COULDN'T BE PRINTED OR ID'D BY INTERPOL   IS IT POSSIBLE THAT HE COULD BE INVOLVED IN THIS</pattern><template>A million dollar hit fee would draw some huge flies.</template></category><category><pattern>AND A PATERNITY SUIT  JUST TO  YOU KNOW  ROUND OUT THE PORTFOLIO THERE</pattern><template>And not one single criminal charge laid against him.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU ALL RIGHT  SON</pattern><template>You need some medical attention?</template></category><category><pattern>END OF FUCKING SONG       ON THAT PARTICULAR ISSUE  PALLY   I'VE BEEN COHABITATING WITH THESE PEOPLE FOR THE LAST 30 HOURS</pattern><template>These are the premier prick cocksuckers of all time.</template></category><category><pattern>'CAUSE I'M GONNA KILL THE ONE THAT AIN'T   STOP THE ELEVATOR</pattern><template>Stop the elevator.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE IF YOU ARE  IT'S CERTAINLY NOT COMING UP HERE IN THE VAN AND WE'D CERTAINLY LIKE TO SEE WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>We've been here for 16 hours.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TAKE EVERY HAS BEEN ACTOR IN HOLLYWOOD  THEY HAVEN'T BEEN CUT THIS MUCH</pattern><template>Easy.</template></category><category><pattern>IN DISGUISE    HE WAS HIRED BY SPARAZZA TO NEUTRALIZE ISRAEL'S ENTOURAGE    DR  INGSTROM WAS HERE TO PERFORM THE SURGERY   AND AS FATHER AND SON  THEY ARE BLOOD COMPATIBLE</pattern><template>You're talking about a transplant, aren't you?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BUT YOU NEED TO BRING YOUR ASS DOWN HERE AND HELP ME OUT  HUGO  FOR REAL</pattern><template>I ain't cleaning all this shit up myself, man.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  DON'T SHOOT</pattern><template>FBI. You gotta get up there! Got to go!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT YOUR CAR</pattern><template>No, I...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CALL MECKLEN</pattern><template>I got the machine.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT CLEAR ON THE TABLE</pattern><template>Is it table... I'm at 12.   I don't know what you're seeing right now, Bill.  It's a little blue haired lady. I'm looking at her right now. Table 12!</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THE OVERHEADS NECESSARY</pattern><template>Turn the overheads off! Now!</template></category><category><pattern>IF THE SITUATION'S CHANGED  I NEED TO HEAR IT FROM HIM</pattern><template>You Messner?</template></category><category><pattern>GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME  ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Take your shit, bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE AT THE HOTEL</pattern><template>Everything's all right?   It's quiet.   So, you're not seeing anything?   No signs of trouble, nobody lurking, no threats? Nothing?   Absolutely no.</template></category><category><pattern>DR  INGSTROM  THE SWEDE  IS NOT A HIRED KILLER</pattern><template>Supposedly a specialist.  He's had a sustained arrhythmic episode, severe cardiac distress.</template></category><category><pattern>CHECKMATE  KIDDO</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TABLE 12   TABLE 12  OKAY</pattern><template>I need somebody over at table 12.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  COME IN</pattern><template>Hold him there till we get somebody up.  Where is Carruthers and Messner?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE'RE REQUIRED TO ABIDE BY IT  REGARDLESS OF OUR PERSONAL FEELINGS</pattern><template>Feelings that might run contrary to the collective good.</template></category><category><pattern>A LITTLE MORE DUCT</pattern><template>That's how we do!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE OUT OF YOUR FUCKING MIND</pattern><template>You fucked up...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT UP  G</pattern><template>Speak, come on. Speak up.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S VERY DIFFICULT TO EXPLAIN EVERYTHING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Much larger matters loom.</template></category><category><pattern>GO BACK TO WASHINGTON</pattern><template>There he goes!</template></category><category><pattern>MY HUSBAND  BILL  COMMITTED SUICIDE BY HANGING ABOUT NINE MONTHS BACK</pattern><template>And ever since then, little Boogie there has been man of the house.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA MEET THEM ON THEIR WAY UP  BLEND IN REAL NICE    ONCE I'M INSIDE  I'M PUTTIN' CHROME TO ISRAEL'S HEAD AND BACKING OUT HOT    ANYBODY GET GULLY  YOU KNOW   I'M GONNA GRIP AND RIP</pattern><template>I got some handloads up here ready to put some niggas out.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FIGMENT OF PRIMO SPARAZZA BECAME FLESH AND BLOOD    AND FREEMAN HELLER WAS NO MORE   NOW  THE BRASS WANTED HELLER'S OP REMOVED FROM OFFICIAL RECORDS  SO THEY BURIED IT COMPLETELY AND THEY WROTE HELLER OFF</pattern><template>All the agents from that era, they're dead and gone, so history defaulted to fable.</template></category><category><pattern>REPEAT  ON THE SEVENTH FLOOR  OFFICERS DOWN</pattern><template>Let me isolate the...</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  AS YOU SAID  YOU GOT TO KEEP YOUR EYE ON EVERYTHING AT ALL TIMES</pattern><template>Well, we were worried about the dust and debris from the work going on up there ruining the cameras.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR CALL</pattern><template>Now, I'm prepared to dismiss your behavior. And in light of what's happened, I understand it.</template></category><category><pattern>OVER THE YEARS  THE SERIOUS CRIMES WITH WHICH HE WAS THOUGHT TO BE INVOLVED WITH  INCLUDING HELLER'S MURDER  COULD NEVER BE TRACED BACK TO HIM</pattern><template>A dedicated viciousness and slavish devotion to mob doctrine  had Sparazza's star on the rise.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME  LISTEN   THE DEAL IS OFF IN FIVE MINUTES UNLESS THEY GIVE US SOMETHING</pattern><template>MECKLEN: I don't know what to say to you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN</pattern><template>I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE A LOOK AT THAT</pattern><template>Hollis Elmore.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GIVING US UP TO THE FEDS  HUGO</pattern><template>Yo, get out of here, Hugo, man!</template></category><category><pattern>IT CAUSES ALZHEIMER'S</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>PATERNITY SUIT</pattern><template>Just for fun?</template></category><category><pattern>I COULDN'T TELL YOU THAT RIGHT NOW  SIR</pattern><template>Hugo, what the fuck is wrong with you, man?</template></category><category><pattern>SHOULD WE INFORM MESSNER AND CARRUTHERS</pattern><template>No. Things have changed.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT RIGHT</pattern><template>Four.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO</pattern><template>I'm gonna get to Israel before they do.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT OTHER AGENT</pattern><template>There were no other agents.</template></category><category><pattern>GRAB THEM SUITS AND THE CAR</pattern><template>And pitch them poor fellas in the lake.</template></category><category><pattern>BILL</pattern><template>MAN: Oh, my God, I need an ambulance for Bill!</template></category><category><pattern>SYKES: I AIN'T NEVER HEARD OF HIM</pattern><template>WATTERS: Me, neither.  Then listen up, 'cause he may wind up being your main competition.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK THEM  YOU KNOW   THESE GUYS GOT BALLS</pattern><template>Let me tell you.</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH HIM</pattern><template>You're okay.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN TO TELL ME THAT NOBODY NOTICED ANYONE GETTING OUT OF A CADILLAC THAT LOOKED LIKE A WIFFLE BALL</pattern><template>I know.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED SOME MEDICAL ATTENTION</pattern><template>No, I don't need medical attention.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING DOWN</pattern><template>I'll bet you are.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THINGS HAVE CHANGED</pattern><template>Get the Director on the phone and have our jet at the tarmac at LAX in half an hour.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S PRETTY DEAD   THANK YOU  CAPTAIN OBVIOUS</pattern><template>All right well, just stay awake, guys.</template></category><category><pattern>ACOSTA: I'D LIKE TO TAKE A LOOK AT THE PENTHOUSE   NO  I'M SORRY  THE PENTHOUSE IS CURRENTLY UNDER CONSTRUCTION</pattern><template>MAN ON RADIO: Do a sweep on camera three. Maybe we can pick him up.  Bill, can I speak to you privately?</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAS A HISTORY OF TAKING ON TOUGH KILLS  AND HE'S CERTAINLY NOT ALONE</pattern><template>Who else?</template></category><category><pattern>GET MR  ISRAEL UP ON THE ROOF</pattern><template>He's traveling back with us.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT WHAT</pattern><template>Look at the collar on that coat. What does that look like? That stain?</template></category><category><pattern>PUT HER DOWN  PUT HER DOWN AND GET UP AGAINST THE WALL RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Show me your hands.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  NO  I DON'T WANT TO SIT  EXPLAIN IT</pattern><template>It's very difficult to explain everything right now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WOULD'VE</pattern><template>Hell, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW HOW BAD THIS IS  SHIT</pattern><template>That shit probably got through that Kevlar.</template></category><category><pattern>AUTOMATED VOICE: PLEASE REMAIN CALM   NOW THAT'S THE POWER  THERE</pattern><template>Elevator service has been temporarily suspended and will resume momentarily.   Please remain calm.   Elevator service has been temporarily suspended and will resume momentarily.  Well, let's get on it, then.</template></category><category><pattern>AND BONES IT</pattern><template>Huh? Right there, and then padlock it and then you put the chain on it.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT TABLE    I'M AT 12    I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE SEEING RIGHT NOW  BILL   IT'S A LITTLE BLUE HAIRED LADY  I'M LOOKING AT HER RIGHT NOW  TABLE 12</pattern><template>She is killing it, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>PARKING STRUCTURE AT THE NOMAD</pattern><template>Are the overheads necessary?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  NEVER BEEN CAUGHT</pattern><template>No criminal record.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE IF THEY</pattern><template>You know, he was wearing one of our jackets.</template></category><category><pattern>PLUS THE HEART</pattern><template>And Buddy Israel.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A RISK WE TAKE</pattern><template>Yeah, empty pockets.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE WE CLEAR  AGENT MESSNER</pattern><template>We're clear.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE HERE HUNTING THE MAN NAMED ISRAEL  WEREN'T YOU</pattern><template>Is that who you was here for? Israel?</template></category><category><pattern>WE WAIT ANY LONGER  SOMEONE GONNA DEAD THIS FOOL</pattern><template>MESSNER: Then we lose our witness.  And we lose our case.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TAKE THE CAR</pattern><template>You get over to the lake.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  HOLD IT  I NEED TO SPEAK WITH LOCKE</pattern><template>Get him on the phone.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I'VE ASSEMBLED A TEAM NOW</pattern><template>We're gonna go in, we're gonna get this guy, and everyone is gonna leave the theater grinning.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED MEDICAL ASSISTANCE</pattern><template>I got multiple officers down.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR AGENTS ARE LANDING HERE NOW</pattern><template>There was nobody here.</template></category><category><pattern>MAMA'S GOT YOUR BACK</pattern><template>Mama's got your back, baby.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I BET YOU GUYS GOT A BUNCH OF STORIES  RIGHT  I DON'T</pattern><template>I grew up soft with the private schools and little blazers, you know, and...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  THANKS  DARLING</pattern><template>Lovely.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE GOOD  WHAT    TWO OF THE BEST</pattern><template>They hit those Chinamen, took out the big triad.   These girls are worth every penny. I'll call Loretta.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT SHOT TWICE</pattern><template>I think I accidentally shot and killed my boy today.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  BUDDY STARTS MAKING FRIENDS</pattern><template>The connected kind.   He's doing the Sinatra thing.  Becomes the unofficial mob mascot.</template></category><category><pattern>GET IN THE VAN NOW</pattern><template>Go! Go! Go!</template></category><category><pattern>MUCH LARGER MATTERS LOOM</pattern><template>I'm sorry to hear about Carruthers.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT THREE COMING DOWN NOW   GO  MOVE  MOVE</pattern><template>Forgive me.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN  WHAT THE FUCK WAS YOU THINKING  BAREBACKING THEM BITCHES  HUGO</pattern><template>I bet you your dick is disintegrating as we speak, player!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE IS KILLING IT  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>I want you to keep an eye on her! That's all!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  AGENT CARRUTHERS</pattern><template>Do you know where he is?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT  AND THE MENTION OF THIS MYSTERIOUS SWEDE MAKES THE CONTRACT ON ISRAEL ALL THE MORE REAL</pattern><template>SYKES: How real?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING UP</pattern><template>Okay, we need to get these elevators powered up.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TELL ME TO FUCKING CALM DOWN</pattern><template>That's all they're gonna give us.</template></category><category><pattern>THEM POLICE OFFICERS  TOO</pattern><template>Mmm hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOW THEM YOUR ID WITH THE LETTERS  FBI  IN ALL CAPS  IT'S INSTANT COMPLIANCE</pattern><template>I've seen it happen a hundred times.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT 60 YEARS OF AMASSED INTEL</pattern><template>Do you have any idea of how valuable that is?</template></category><category><pattern>NO CRIMINAL RECORD</pattern><template>It's possible.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BETRAYED US</pattern><template>Stop pointing...</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT  WHAT DO YOU MEAN</pattern><template>What do you mean, man?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE HANDLES BOTH OF THEM    ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Odds are they're gonna get into some shit.   Might have to put people down.  These guys aren't fucking around.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  Y'ALL GOT SICK LEAVE</pattern><template>'Cause one of your hoes just got fucked up!</template></category><category><pattern>A LITTLE BLUE HAIRED LADY THERE WHO'S ROLLED ABOUT 14 TIMES  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Something happened at table 14?  Table 12!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOU FUCKER</pattern><template>WATTERS: Forget it. It's done.  Hey, quit saying that, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT WAS NOT MADE CLEAR TO ME</pattern><template>This is the first I'm hearing of it.</template></category><category><pattern>GO AHEAD    NOW  WHAT I HEARD DOWNSTAIRS IS THEY GOT A GUY  SOME SWEDE   SWEDE</pattern><template>You know a Swede?</template></category><category><pattern>CLEAR THE VALET AREA    FUCK  COME ON</pattern><template>AGENT: Left side of the building's sealed off.  Goddamn. Can you hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TELL YOU</pattern><template>These guys got some balls.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOING TO CUT HIS HEART OUT</pattern><template>His heart?</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN DO WE GET CONCERNED</pattern><template>We don't get concerned.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I BE OF ASSISTANCE    MY NAME IS VITOLI</pattern><template>How can I be of assistance?  My name is Vitoli.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED A MEDIC</pattern><template>Fuck!</template></category><category><pattern>THEM ARE LEFT OVER AFTER MY HYSTERECTOMY  SO THEY'D BE A FEW YEARS OLD</pattern><template>I'm not gay because I have a beard.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  RUN BOTH THOSE NAMES THROUGH THE DC DATABASE</pattern><template>Something stinks here.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  SIR</pattern><template>Hotel locked down at all?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SHIT PROBABLY GOT THROUGH THAT KEVLAR</pattern><template>It's on the way up to the penthouse.</template></category><category><pattern>I CANNOT DISCUSS IT</pattern><template>You can and you will.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  I THOUGHT THEY GAVE IT TO HIM SO HE COULD</pattern><template>Walk with me.</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR TO GOD  MY GRANDMOTHER TOLD ME</pattern><template>She said... She did, 'cause when I used to get a zit or something, she said...</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  HOLLIS  COME ON IN</pattern><template>So, Jack, he tells me you guys a couple of ex cops?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S EMBARRASSING</pattern><template>All right. Cut it out.</template></category><category><pattern>CARRUTHERS: I'M TELLING YOU SOMETHING     YOU'VE GOT TO BE CAREFUL WHEN YOU'RE DOING YOUR STAKEOUTS</pattern><template>I did one for... I was on one for six months.</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL'S MANAGER IS ACTING AS HIS ATTORNEY  THAT'S WHAT'S HOLDING THINGS UP</pattern><template>So I want to be in that penthouse a half a second after this deal is done.</template></category><category><pattern>MOTHERFUCK  MOTHERFUCKER</pattern><template>You're out of your fucking mind!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE DISGUSTING</pattern><template>Come on, don't keep it by the water either.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A SHAME THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN</pattern><template>What was you doing here, anyway?</template></category><category><pattern>LITTLE ANGEL BUTT</pattern><template>I feel like you're eyeballing me, dawg!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Maybe, but that's very unlikely.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT ONLY ESSENTIAL TO OUR CASE   HE IS OUR CASE</pattern><template>And understand that if an attempt is made on his life, it'll be made by those of the strictest professional caliber.</template></category><category><pattern>BET</pattern><template>Oh, my God.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER YOU THINK  WHATEVER</pattern><template>You must be out of your fucking mind.</template></category><category><pattern>Y'ALL PEELED SOME SERIOUS CAPS  WORD TRAVELS</pattern><template>So, we're supposed to go in there, bust on this punk and remove his heart.</template></category><category><pattern>SPECIAL AGENT DONALD CARRUTHERS  FBI</pattern><template>I need to get to your penthouse level immediately.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WE DID THAT DANCE  BITCH  KICK ROCKS</pattern><template>Goddamn!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOT ME</pattern><template>And you murdered my friends.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HOLLIS</pattern><template>Rip Reed.</template></category><category><pattern>BIG SPENDER  COME ON</pattern><template>No, no.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THESE FEDS FAKE OR REAL</pattern><template>I don't know!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WE NEED TO GET THESE ELEVATORS POWERED UP</pattern><template>All right, maintenance, I need somebody to power up these elevators immediately.</template></category><category><pattern>THE JUSTICE LAWYERS SIGN OFF</pattern><template>Yeah, that's happening.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT YOU WERE RETURNING HIS CALL AND YOU WERE VERY  VERY CONCERNED</pattern><template>Wow, that's fantastic work, man.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS CALL IT</pattern><template>Strapped? Well, so, they got guns.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  UP HERE IN HEAVEN  IT'S BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO RETURN TO WASHINGTON</pattern><template>You'll be debriefed in the days to come.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DID YOU FIND IT</pattern><template>Parking structure at the Nomad.</template></category><category><pattern>AND RUPERT REED  ONE OF THE FIRM'S PARTNERS  HAS LEARNED OF HIS WHEREABOUTS</pattern><template>And he's dispatched a local bondsman by the name of Jack Dupree  to pick him up and return him to Las Vegas.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S YOUR NAME  BABY GIRL</pattern><template>Georgia.</template></category><category><pattern>CALL SAN FRANCISCO</pattern><template>See if they...</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT: AM I ON THE SPEAKERPHONE</pattern><template>Yeah, go, go, go, go.   We got an ID pending on a Jack Dupree.   He's a bail bondsman out of Las Vegas, Nevada.  Did you recover anything from his person?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WENT THIS WAY  PLEASE  DON'T SHOOT ME  DON'T SHOOT</pattern><template>Please! Don't shoot.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY GRANDMOTHER</pattern><template>You just told me your grandma said that piss is good for your skin.</template></category><category><pattern>GEORGIA  WHERE ARE YOU</pattern><template>I can't fucking hear you.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT ABOUT A HANDFUL OF DEAL POINTS AND THEN WE'RE GETTING CLOSE</pattern><template>What are you shaking for, man?</template></category><category><pattern>PUNCH HIM IN THE SEAT OR SOMETHING  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Hit him in the brown.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CONNECTED KIND    HE'S DOING THE SINATRA THING   BECOMES THE UNOFFICIAL MOB MASCOT</pattern><template>Can I whack anybody?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  Y'ALL</pattern><template>We did the damn thing.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  DOCTOR  THANK YOU</pattern><template>You know, just make it sound good.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WE NEED TO HANDLE IT NOW</pattern><template>You are instructed to get out...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY</pattern><template>What I've been saying.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR FUCKING MIND</pattern><template>My guy is dead.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WHO'S THIS</pattern><template>Take a look at that.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK</pattern><template>Godspeed.</template></category><category><pattern>VITOLI NOT ANSWER THE PHONE</pattern><template>Go down there and get him.</template></category><category><pattern>I PROBABLY WOULD'VE BUSTED ON YOU  TOO</pattern><template>What a shame that would have been.</template></category><category><pattern>DO I BELIEVE IN LOYALTY</pattern><template>Especially the kind of loyalty where an otherwise sensible motherfucker like myself put his own best interests aside...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M PRETTY MUCH A PANTYWAIST</pattern><template>I don't say this to be self deprecating.</template></category><category><pattern>CLEAR THE WAY HERE</pattern><template>Clear the way.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST GET UP IN THERE AND DO YOUR THING  BABY GIRL</pattern><template>Mama's got your back.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA CALL SECURITY AND MAKE SURE THE WHOLE PLACE IS LOCKED DOWN</pattern><template>We got to keep him in that penthouse.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T ELECTIVE</pattern><template>It was undertaken to save his life.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD FUCKING WORK</pattern><template>I love it.</template></category><category><pattern>PADICHE: WELL  JUST SO I GET A QUOTE IN MY HEAD  HOW MUCH IS THE SWEDE GETTING    THAT'S THE PUNCH LINE</pattern><template>You ready?  Here's the punch line.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU AIN'T NEVER MADE NO REAL BEEF ON YOUR OWN</pattern><template>Shit, as light in the ass as you are, bet you ain't never had to make nothing more than a fucking fist your whole life.</template></category><category><pattern>(FEEDBACK WHINING)   (RADIO CHATTERING)  THAT'S BETTER</pattern><template>Yeah, much.</template></category><category><pattern>GO DOWN THERE AND GET HIM</pattern><template>Go down there!</template></category><category><pattern>IF WORD HITS THE STREET THAT THERE'S A MILLION DOLLAR BOUNTY   FOR BUDDY FUCKING ISRAEL    YOU'RE GONNA HAVE EVERY FUCKING HIT MAN IN THE FREE WORLD LOOKING FOR HIM    WE GOT TO MOVE QUICKLY</pattern><template>No more tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  EMPTY POCKETS</pattern><template>Empty pockets paid for by the lives of our own people.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BUREAU BETRAYED US</pattern><template>Wake up.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING PRETTY IN LIPSTICK AND EYELINER THAT CAN SUCK A FUCKING COCK</pattern><template>Shh! Shut up. What do you have to shout for?</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE PUSH THIS  THEY ARE GONNA REVOKE YOUR PROTECTIVE STATUS  AND THAT NULLIFIES ANY AGREEMENT WE GOT</pattern><template>And that is mate.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HOT</pattern><template>And they losing a whole floor's worth of business, saying it's under construction.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M HEADED THERE RIGHT NOW  SURE</pattern><template>Is this an emergency?</template></category><category><pattern>GET IN HERE</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE TALKING TO THE KID</pattern><template>We need about two minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME MY PURSE</pattern><template>Shut the fuck up!</template></category><category><pattern>MESSNER: YOUR IFB WORKING   NO  THAT'S WHY WE'RE ON WALKIES</pattern><template>Jurisdiction's a nightmare right now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW OF A SWEDE</pattern><template>Nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T TALK VERY LOUD</pattern><template>Primo's downstairs.   I've been sitting by this phone for 20 fucking hours.   Now listen to me, Buzzy.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENING</pattern><template>Hey, yo, Beanie.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO PLAY BALL   NO  I DON'T HAVE TO DO SHIT  WHICH INCLUDES COOPERATING WITH THESE FUCKERS  UNTIL I GET WHAT I WANT</pattern><template>Listen to me.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Are you fucking nuts?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL</pattern><template>As a female, that shit right there don't get you?</template></category><category><pattern>THESE TWO DUDES JUST SITTING IN THE ELEVATOR  ALL SHOT UP</pattern><template>Whatever it was, it got way past words.</template></category><category><pattern>NO MORE TOMORROW</pattern><template>I got to go, Buzzy.  He said one million.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M GONNA GET IT FOR YOU</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST  YOU KNOW  DON'T HAVE MUCH OF AN OPINION OF MYSELF  I'D MUCH RATHER BE LIKE YOU GUYS</pattern><template>You know, bar fighters and big, swinging dicks, taking care of shit.</template></category><category><pattern>I FOUND HIM LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Whether you believe me or not, you know, that ain't even the least bit important right now.</template></category><category><pattern>WATTERS: HE'S DEAD</pattern><template>No, I said dying, not dead.  Shit.</template></category><category><pattern>MECKLEN'S GONNA CALL ANY SECOND  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>All right? You with me?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT DEFINITELY SOUNDS LIKE GUNSHOTS  AND I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT'S COMING FROM</pattern><template>It's your IFB, man.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THEY'RE HEADED STRAIGHT TO YOU</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  WE COOL</pattern><template>Coffee?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN'T YOU CONTACT YOUR PEOPLE WITH THAT</pattern><template>No, these phones are hardwired directly to maintenance, but once we reach the penthouse, I can call down.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE</pattern><template>Girl, where are you?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT IN THERE</pattern><template>Hello? Great. Come on in.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THEY DUG IT UP IN ARCHIVES AS PART OF THE SPARAZZA INVESTIGATION</pattern><template>That Sparazza had major elective plastic surgery?</template></category><category><pattern>BLAST DOWN THE MOON</pattern><template>Any of these niggas make one false move, these bitches taking dirt naps.</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL'S AWAKE</pattern><template>There was apparently a fight with some prostitutes, but he wasn't involved.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  YOU ALL WANT THIS</pattern><template>Hell, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW I HAD TO BRING BIG MAMA THROUGH</pattern><template>You got the .50 up?</template></category><category><pattern>THESE GUYS WANT HIM BAD</pattern><template>Ladies and gentlemen, there's a guy,   he is one of the biggest stars in the world.   And we are thrilled to have him stop by.   And he's won all kinds of awards.   He has won Entertainer of the Year   every year in Las Vegas for the last five years.   Ladies and gentlemen, would you give a big round of applause,   a big Las Vegas welcome, to a great Las Vegas star   and his name is Mr. Buddy Israel!   Come on out here!   DUPREE: Buddy  Aces  Israel.  Card sharp. Illusionist.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS REAL NICE  PLAY IT UP</pattern><template>What you doing, girl?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I CAN SHAPE IT  I CAN SHIFT IT  I CAN MAKE IT AS REAL AS THIS ROOM</pattern><template>That's why I'm valuable here, Ivy. And that is why you are not.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  JACK  HE TELLS ME YOU GUYS A COUPLE OF EX COPS</pattern><template>Yeah, we worked vice, like, 6 years.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD</pattern><template>SYKES: Bring it.  Get the fuck down!</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SORRY</pattern><template>I love you. I never wanted it to be like this.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA BREAK UP  SPLIT APART  BLEND IN WITH THEM AND RECONNOITER AT THE HOTEL</pattern><template>Come here! Get over here!</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAD ONE OF HIS MEN CALL A MADAM FOR ANOTHER GROUP OF GIRLS</pattern><template>We're getting robbed here, man.</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT  GIRL</pattern><template>One of them is a fed.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  LIKE AN ACTUAL FIGHT</pattern><template>They...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>Mortal.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WENT FROM BEYONC TO BIGFOOT IN LESS THAN SIX FUCKING HOURS</pattern><template>Fuck you, pussy!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA GO OVER TO THE HOTEL</pattern><template>You take the car.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  MAN</pattern><template>Where the fuck Vitoli at?</template></category><category><pattern>THE TWIST IS IT'S MY $12 000 CALFSKIN JACKET</pattern><template>So, you got the semen, okay, you've got the human ejaculate that's been allowed to soak in for, like, 7 hours! All right?</template></category><category><pattern>WATER</pattern><template>What's his connection to Israel?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THE ATTENTION WE GETTIN'  MAN</pattern><template>We campaigning like niggas ain't hot.</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE TIME VEGAS SHOWMAN OF THE YEAR</pattern><template>The wiseguys, for some fucking reason, love him.</template></category><category><pattern>EYES  EYELIDS  JAW</pattern><template>You take every has been actor in Hollywood, they haven't been cut this much.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE EVER THREW ANY BLOWS</pattern><template>Still to this day, never punched in the face.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY GETTING THE HAIRY EYEBALL OFF THAT GUY</pattern><template>No, no. No, no.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I CANNOT DISCLOSE ANYTHING MORE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>So many people are dead.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WAY IT WORKS  GIRL</pattern><template>Y'all peeled some serious caps. Word travels.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'S JUST AT THE WRONG PLACE AT THE WRONG TIME</pattern><template>So don't feel so bad, chief.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GONNA BE REAL INCOGNITO GOING IN LIKE THAT</pattern><template>This is real brilliant.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU MURDERED MY FRIENDS</pattern><template>Yeah, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TO GET YOUR HEAD OF SECURITY RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>He's not picking up the extension.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE SEEN IT HAPPEN A HUNDRED TIMES</pattern><template>Special Agent Gerald Diego, Federal Bureau of Investigation, San Francisco Field Office.</template></category><category><pattern>AS A FEMALE  THAT SHIT RIGHT THERE DON'T GET YOU</pattern><template>Okay, it's bitches like that the reason why niggas don't pay our species any mind!</template></category><category><pattern>GET DOWN</pattern><template>Put your fucking hands in the air!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  I'M A REGISTERED NURSE AND THIS WAS MY BATH NOT A HALF HOUR AGO</pattern><template>Whoopsie.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  COME ON  MAN</pattern><template>You know I had to bring big mama through.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHEN YOU SAW HIM LATER  HE WAS WEARING ONE OF YOUR SECURITY JACKETS</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO AM I GONNA WHACK</pattern><template>Stop it. Stop it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A WANNABE    LIKE MOST WANNABES  HE STARTS FUCKING UP FAST AND PICKING UP SPEED   ARE YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME</pattern><template>Are you fucking kidding me?</template></category><category><pattern>A DONALD CARRUTHERS</pattern><template>Which one of them is for real?</template></category><category><pattern>MECKLEN: I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY TO YOU</pattern><template>It is what it is.   Bullshit! It isn't!</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TO HEAR THIS STUFF</pattern><template>Little boosts.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S FINE</pattern><template>He's giving us up to the feds, Hugo!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW I WOULDN'T</pattern><template>...hand me to the feds like your last chip...</template></category><category><pattern>SYKES: HOW REAL</pattern><template>How about six figures for that fool?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TO GET DEPUTY DIRECTOR LOCKE ON A HARD LINE AS SOON AS POSSIBLE</pattern><template>All right, done.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  THAT'S FANTASTIC WORK  MAN</pattern><template>You have the wisdom of a 6,000 or 7,000 year old man.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>Please, Sharice!</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  ANYWAY  I BELIEVE WE HAD A RETAINER FOR SERVICES RENDERED</pattern><template>$50,000.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>Mr. Israel!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GO IN AND PULL HIM OUT</pattern><template>That heart shit?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I</pattern><template>I'm confiscating it.</template></category><category><pattern>THE INFIGHTING THAT FOLLOWED DREW THE INTEREST OF EVERY INVESTIGATIVE BODY   OPERATING UNDER THE CANOPY OF THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT   THIS IS IT  RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Presently, we have...</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT  WAIT  WAIT  WAIT</pattern><template>I'm getting some fucked up feedback off of that earpiece.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE THE SOLE PASS AND RELIEVE ALL OF THE PERSONNEL MYSELF PERSONALLY</pattern><template>Now, if we can just see your ID...</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT: MAROON   WITH MAROON  THAT'S NOMAD SECURITY</pattern><template>Were these uniforms recovered?</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT OF FOLKS WANT THIS WHITE BOY CLAPPED</pattern><template>Word is Soot is working for one of them.</template></category><category><pattern>HE COULD HAVE RIPPED THE MAFIA APART   BUT I FIRMLY BELIEVE</pattern><template>Dismantled most of the organized crime ...this is the only way to truly infiltrate organized crime.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW YOU DOING  PETE</pattern><template>Hello. Rip Reed.</template></category><category><pattern>SERNA ON TAPE: SO DO THIS IN THE NEXT DAY OR SO  GET TO ISRAEL BEFORE THE SWEDE CAN    WE'RE IN A POWER POSITION</pattern><template>All right, we'll be awaiting word.  All right, we got time.</template></category><category><pattern>OFFICER</pattern><template>Hugo, what's happening, man?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  JUST MAKE IT SOUND GOOD</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Okay, come on, sit down.</template></category><category><pattern>I AIN'T TRYING TO DEAD THE WHOLE FLOOR AND I DON'T WANT TO BE KILLING NO WOMEN</pattern><template>No matter how they make their living.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE  MOVE  HURRY</pattern><template>Clear the valet area.   Fuck. Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>FAST AS WE CAN GET YOU THERE</pattern><template>We wait any longer, someone gonna dead this fool.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Israel rolled!</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  SHARICE</pattern><template>Oh, shit! I'm shot!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK LIKE A DAMN MUPPET</pattern><template>And don't let your bitch cut your hair no more, dawg.</template></category><category><pattern>STUPID ASS MOTHERFUCKER</pattern><template>Now, what the fuck is wrong with you, man?</template></category><category><pattern>THE WISEGUYS  FOR SOME FUCKING REASON  LOVE HIM</pattern><template>They think he's, like, a mystic.</template></category><category><pattern>EASY</pattern><template>Crazy, you know.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHAT DID MECKLEN HAVE TO SAY</pattern><template>They're getting close, man.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN WE BRING THIS OFF    HEY  WE KEEP OUR MOUTH SHUT  PLAY THE PART  NOBODY SUSPECTS A THING    THE OLD MAN'S ON THE FADE  BUZZY</pattern><template>Fuck them, you know.  These guys got balls.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING  AND I MEAN EVERYTHING IS RIDING ON THIS    WE'RE GONNA GET ISRAEL</pattern><template>Trust me.   HUGO ON RECORDER: You open the fucking door.   AGENT: I'm sorry, sir.  But this is eyes only.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU ADD FACIAL HAIR TO THE EQUATION  GENTLEMEN  YOU HAVE A FACE THAT LOOKS NOTHING LIKE MINE  AND MORE IMPORTANTLY  NOTHING LIKE A FEDERAL AGENT'S</pattern><template>Oh, Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE YOU GOING</pattern><template>You call Mecklen?</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID THE SHIT MIGHT GET HOT AND MIGHT GET HEAVY</pattern><template>I said,  Cool. 'Cause I got two of the hottest,  heaviest bitches alive.  Like who?</template></category><category><pattern>COME HERE  COME HERE</pattern><template>Bitches like that make me weep for what could be.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WHO YOU WAS HERE FOR  ISRAEL</pattern><template>I guess we both got beat out then, didn't we?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE JUST MEAT FOR MALE CONSUMPTION</pattern><template>Pieces of ass and pussy.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTIME  ANYTIME  FAG</pattern><template>I am sorry about that boy.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WORKING WITH THEM PEOPLE  HUGO</pattern><template>It's all bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>What floor are they on, Ricky?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST HANG ON  SIR</pattern><template>Where'd you get these?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO  WHAT  YOUR PHONE BROKE OR WHAT</pattern><template>Buddy wants you now up top.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS LISTED AS MAROON IN COLOR    CARRUTHERS: MAROON</pattern><template>AGENT: Maroon.  With maroon, that's Nomad security.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS RECONSTRUCTIVE</pattern><template>Look at the date of the first procedure.</template></category><category><pattern>WROTE A BUNCH OF BAD CHECKS</pattern><template>My husband, Bill, committed suicide by hanging about nine months back.</template></category><category><pattern>MY ASSOCIATE  MR  SERNA  I CAN GET HIM ON THE PHONE AND IF YOU COULD JUST SPEAK TO HIM AND TELL HIM YOUR PLAN</pattern><template>Your plans.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  ISRAEL'S MANAGER  A MAN BY THE NAME OF MORRIS MECKLEN   HAS GUARANTEED US THAT ISRAEL WILL ENTER INTO PROTECTIVE CUSTODY   ONCE THE GOVERNMENT HAS APPROVED HIS DEAL    NOW  WE'VE BEEN MONITORING MECKLEN'S PHONE CALLS   AND WE'VE LEARNED THAT ISRAEL IS AT THE PENTHOUSE LEVEL OF THE NOMAD HOTEL AND CASINO IN LAKE TAHOE  NEVADA</pattern><template>The high roller suite?</template></category><category><pattern>COUPLE OF THINGS</pattern><template>The hangers on, his posse, you know, they're all strapped or packing heat, whatever the phrase is.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S YOUR CREW</pattern><template>Hey, fuck you. All right.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A 35 PERSON EMPLOYEE CONTINGENT THAT GOES AT 9:00 IN THE MORNING</pattern><template>We're gonna break up, split apart, blend in with them and reconnoiter at the hotel.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE SAID    SHE DID  'CAUSE WHEN I USED TO GET A ZIT OR SOMETHING  SHE SAID</pattern><template>She pissed on your face?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GETTING ALL KINDS OF SHIT OVER THIS SCANNER</pattern><template>Just chill for a second.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST PICKING UP THEIR SIGNAL</pattern><template>We need Nomad hotel security to lock down the elevators immediately.  Girl. Please don't tell me this motherfucker just went off.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  CUT IT OUT</pattern><template>Two security levels.</template></category><category><pattern>IS HE GONNA SHOW YOU WHERE ALL THE BODIES ARE BURIED</pattern><template>Or is his ultimate worth bullshit?</template></category><category><pattern>MAN ON TAPE RECORDER: SAY YOUR NAME  THEN SAY   HOW CAN I BE OF ASSISTANCE     VITOLI: I DON'T UNDERSTAND    I DIDN'T ASK FOR YOUR UNDERSTANDING    I ASKED FOR YOUR NAME  FOLLOWED BY THE PHRASE     HOW CAN I BE OF ASSISTANCE     MY NAME IS VITOLI</pattern><template>How can I be of assistance?   Bravo.   (GUN FIRING)   My name is Vitoli.</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT MESSNER</pattern><template>What's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>EVENTUALLY  HE REACHED THE RANK OF CAPO INSIDE THE CARLOTTA CRIME FAMILY    BUT DUE TO SOME INTERNAL SLIPUP  HIS COVER WAS COMPROMISED    PRIMO SPARAZZA WAS GIVEN THE CONTRACT TO KILL HIM   SPARAZZA IS A BIT OF A SPECTER</pattern><template>Over the years, the serious crimes with which he was thought to be involved with, including Heller's murder, could never be traced back to him.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS COUNTRYMEN HAVE DUBBED HIM THE MORE DUBIOUS  EI ESTRAGO      THE PLAGUE     AMERICAN EDUCATED  FLUENT IN OVER A DOZEN LANGUAGES</pattern><template>Freelanced for the CIA.   Noted for his legendary torture techniques.   When he was caught by the SAS in Northern Ireland,   in prison he chewed off his fingertips to the bones,   so he couldn't be printed or ID'd by Interpol.  Is it possible that he could be involved in this?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S ASLEEP</pattern><template>I'm trying to wake this bitch up! Man!</template></category><category><pattern>HELLER'S OP PREDATED THE SECOND WORLD WAR</pattern><template>About 60 years of amassed intel.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S HOPE NOT</pattern><template>I'm going down.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WANT MY APOLOGY</pattern><template>Only if you really, truly mean it.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT  THAT'S GOOD</pattern><template>You're feeling it, you're feeling it. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCKING ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Watch it. Watch it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF UNIFORMS</pattern><template>It was listed as maroon in color.   CARRUTHERS: Maroon?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  CELL RECEPTION UP HERE IS TERRIBLE  BUT UNTIL YOU OR I SPEAK WITH HIM  HE'S THE SAC AND HE'S THE GUY I ANSWER TO</pattern><template>REPORTER: As to the identity of the two bodies...  Look, in less than an hour, you're gonna have 40 to 50 odd field agents arriving in Lake Tahoe without the slightest clue as to why.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WALKED OUT THE DOOR AFTER HE MADE BAIL</pattern><template>Hasn't been seen since.</template></category><category><pattern>DO ME A FAVOR  WILL YOU</pattern><template>Will you tell me what that is?</template></category><category><pattern>AND PLEASE  FOR ME  WILL YOU DO ONE THING</pattern><template>Get out of my fucking sight.</template></category><category><pattern>HELPS ALLAY MY FEARS</pattern><template>I pass that peace of mind along to my partners.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE IT HAPPEN  OKAY</pattern><template>Dupree was going in as security.</template></category><category><pattern>STRAPPED</pattern><template>I don't know what you guys call it.</template></category><category><pattern>COME HERE  GET OVER HERE</pattern><template>You stay down! You stay down!</template></category><category><pattern>IF I NEEDED YOUR CAR AND ME AND MY BROTHERS WERE WANTED BY THE LAW  I WOULD'VE KILLED YOU TO GET IT  TOO</pattern><template>You would've?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OPEN THE FUCKING DOOR</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>A FED  LIKE FBI</pattern><template>Yeah. That's all right though.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION</pattern><template>You heard from that nigga, Keith?</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD HIM THERE TILL WE GET SOMEBODY UP   WHERE IS CARRUTHERS AND MESSNER</pattern><template>Carruthers is dead.</template></category><category><pattern>LOCKE: SUICIDE OF SOME SORT</pattern><template>You know, troubles with the law. Drugs.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN BOUNCE OUT  CHILL FOR A LITTLE BIT   SHOOT A LITTLE CRAPS</pattern><template>Maybe spend the night.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE GETTING CLOSE  MAN</pattern><template>Got about a handful of deal points and then we're getting close.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WANT EVERYBODY</pattern><template>Ivy, Beanie, Hugo, the works.</template></category><category><pattern>A MONSTER THAT THE BUREAU BUILT</pattern><template>You tell me something, is he the Rosetta Stone that's going to blow the lid off the last 60 years?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FILLING UP YOUR LUNGS RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>In less than a minute, you're gonna asphyxiate and pass out.</template></category><category><pattern>GEORGIA</pattern><template>You know you saved this black man.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YO  IS THIS MADAME ALEX</pattern><template>Hey, y'all got sick leave?</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID    I SAID ONE OF THEM HAS GOT A FBI BADGE   WAIT A MINUTE  WAIT A MINUTE</pattern><template>Hold up, hold up.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M MOVING DOWN FOR A BETTER SIGHT LINE</pattern><template>I got officers down.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S ISRAEL</pattern><template>What are you doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>PUT HIM IN</pattern><template>Take him to the service exit. It's quick.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GETTING SOME FUCKED UP FEEDBACK OFF OF THAT EARPIECE</pattern><template>(FEEDBACK WHINING)   (RADIO CHATTERING)  That's better?</template></category><category><pattern>VICE</pattern><template>Four, six, five. They didn't teach you how to count, I guess, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT SIX FIGURES FOR THAT FOOL</pattern><template>How's that love?</template></category><category><pattern>HELL  YEAH</pattern><template>We's just at the wrong place at the wrong time.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEBODY GOT A EARPIECE</pattern><template>You just picking up their signal.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU AND THIS FUCKING WIG 'CAUSE THIS SHIT IS GETTING ON MY NERVES</pattern><template>I'm on my way out.  I'm going to just chill in the hallway until they come up in the elevator.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS TOUGH</pattern><template>I don't know... This...</template></category><category><pattern>MESSNER'S UNACCOUNTED FOR</pattern><template>Account for him!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>Where's Israel?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  JUST THE MENTION IN THAT PHONE CALL</pattern><template>There's no Swedish hit man on anyone's radar.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAY THIS FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART  RETIRE</pattern><template>Douchebag.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN WORKING HERE</pattern><template>Bill?</template></category><category><pattern>HIS HEART</pattern><template>Jesus, what for?   He's been snitching to the world.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL NOT BE A PROBLEM</pattern><template>No problem.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HANGERS ON  HIS POSSE  YOU KNOW  THEY'RE ALL STRAPPED OR PACKING HEAT  WHATEVER THE PHRASE IS</pattern><template>Strapped.</template></category><category><pattern>AND DON'T LET YOUR BITCH CUT YOUR HAIR NO MORE  DAWG</pattern><template>It look like she put a bowl on that shit, man. Damn.</template></category><category><pattern>(MECKLEN CRYING)   THEY REVOKED THE DEAL   THEY REVOKED THE DEAL</pattern><template>They pulled it.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE HE'S THAT GOOD</pattern><template>You know, never been caught.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL BE PRIMO SPARAZZA</pattern><template>Now, gentlemen, I understand that this is a dramatic approach.</template></category><category><pattern>SAY WHAT</pattern><template>Three men were ambushed and shot.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE YOU UP HERE SOMEDAY</pattern><template>You think so?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S TALKING TO SOMEONE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Just keep zooming in.   SERNA: Buzz.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WE GOT HIM</pattern><template>We got him. We got him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU TRYING TO SHOOT</pattern><template>A jumbo jet out of the sky?</template></category><category><pattern>CINNAMON ROLL  THE CINNAMON</pattern><template>The roll of the cinnamon?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT IS MATE</pattern><template>Checkmate, kiddo.</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT  OKAY  YOU'RE RIGHT</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S UP</pattern><template>You believe in loyalty, don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT'S HAPPENING</pattern><template>Look, if he's gonna run, he's gonna run now, so we got to go!</template></category><category><pattern>WAKE UP</pattern><template>You betrayed us...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT LOOKS LIKE JIZZ</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>BITCHES LIKE THAT MAKE ME WEEP FOR WHAT COULD BE</pattern><template>If we all sisters everywhere, black, white, brown and yellow, put our shit down one time, a unified front, you know, the female race, mobilized, baby, moving as one! You feel me?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I KNOW</pattern><template>And you dumped us in the lake.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WOULDN'T TELL ME WHY</pattern><template>We're done.   They're yanking us, Buddy.   They killed us.</template></category><category><pattern>HELL  NO</pattern><template>You didn't do that, dawg.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HIS CONNECTION TO ISRAEL</pattern><template>Sparazza introduced Israel to the life.   Gave him his first big break onstage, brought him up through the ranks.  And Israel played the situation very shrewdly.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT BEEF  YOU GOT BEEF</pattern><template>You want some of this? Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT YOU</pattern><template>What? I live in a van.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>Make it make sense.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID   COOL  'CAUSE I GOT TWO OF THE HOTTEST   HEAVIEST BITCHES ALIVE   LIKE WHO</pattern><template>Like Pasquale Acosta.</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL'S DEAL WITH THE GOVERNMENT WAS TOSSED OUT</pattern><template>We are now trying to rehabilitate him, so we can attempt a transplant.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE IT MAKE SENSE</pattern><template>They are father and son.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME FOOL WITH A FAKE BADGE   YOU THINK IT MIGHT BE THAT MOTHERFUCKER THAT LORETTA WAS TELLING US ABOUT  SOOT</pattern><template>Wait. Hold up, hold up.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT    ISRAEL'S IN THE PENTHOUSE NOW  RIGHT    YEAH  I GUESS HE'S BEEN HOLED UP THERE FOR A WEEK OR SO    HOW ARE WE ON TIME</pattern><template>The Swede's been dispatched.   He's flying himself.   All right, damn, all right.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT EXACTLY LOW PROFILE  IS THIS</pattern><template>No, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE'S DISPATCHED A LOCAL BONDSMAN BY THE NAME OF JACK DUPREE  TO PICK HIM UP AND RETURN HIM TO LAS VEGAS</pattern><template>It's very simple, gentlemen.</template></category><category><pattern>LET GO OF MY ARM</pattern><template>Shut up! Fuck off!</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE IT</pattern><template>His little criminal foray shines a floodlight on the entire Carlotta organization.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ON MY WAY OUT   I'M GOING TO JUST CHILL IN THE HALLWAY UNTIL THEY COME UP IN THE ELEVATOR</pattern><template>And you let me know, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>He's all right. Tell him.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  DON'T EVEN THINK I'M TOUCHING MY MAN'S COAT THAT I KNOW YOU NUTTED ALL OVER  YOU NO AIMING ASS</pattern><template>Man, what the fuck was you thinking, barebacking them bitches, Hugo?</template></category><category><pattern>SPEAK  COME ON  SPEAK UP</pattern><template>Bitch, I'm about to ball this.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT GOT SQUAT FUCKED  SHOT TO SHIT  SLASHED AND BURNED    WHAT HAPPENED    WELL  THE TREMOR BROTHERS GO RIP SHIT RIOT ON THE WHOLE FUCKING PLACE    SEVEN DEAD  28 WOUNDED    JUST TO GET THIS ONE FUCKING GUY    IN THE COURSE OF THE MELEE  ONE OF THEM GETS SHOT IN THE NECK  HE PASSES OUT    ANOTHER ONE CATCHES BLOWBACK FROM A JAMMED PIECE    HE'S TEMPORARILY BLINDED    THIRD ONE GETS A BULLET LODGED IN HIS BACK  HE CAN'T WALK    THEY'RE SPEED FREAK  NEO NAZI ASSHOLES WHO READ AND RECITE   MEIN KAMPF LIKE IT WAS MOTHER GOOSE   THEY'RE MEANER THAN SHIT  THEY'RE DUMBER THAN HELL AND THESE MOTHERFUCKERS WILL GO MEGATON AT THE DROP OF A HAT</pattern><template>SYKES: I ain't never heard of him.</template></category><category><pattern>I GREW UP SOFT WITH THE PRIVATE SCHOOLS AND LITTLE BLAZERS  YOU KNOW  AND</pattern><template>Everyone talked things out, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>FATE JUST UP AND FUCKS YOU FOR NO GOOD REASON</pattern><template>You know?</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL'S LAWYERS WERE LEFT HOLDING THE BAG AFTER HE SKIPPED BAIL</pattern><template>And Rupert Reed, one of the firm's partners, has learned of his whereabouts.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT PRICK  LOCKE</pattern><template>He just smashed everything.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR  GO AHEAD</pattern><template>We're about three miles from the Nomad now.</template></category><category><pattern>WATTERS: ME  NEITHER   THEN LISTEN UP  'CAUSE HE MAY WIND UP BEING YOUR MAIN COMPETITION</pattern><template>His name is Soot. Lazlo Soot.</template></category><category><pattern>RIP REED</pattern><template>Hello, Hollis. Come on in.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T COSMETIC</pattern><template>It was reconstructive.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS THE DEPUTY DIRECTOR</pattern><template>That prick, Locke.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SO OBVIOUSLY  WE GOT A MAN POSING AS ONE OF US</pattern><template>Make your team aware, but do it quietly. Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY TO HEAR ABOUT CARRUTHERS</pattern><template>He's a good man.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HO TRAIN HAS LEFT THE STATION</pattern><template>Yeah, they're headed straight to you.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING ON MY END</pattern><template>The line's clean.   STEVE: Do you guys have any signal out there?  Yeah, we got it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST FIGURE THAT OUT</pattern><template>Get that gun out of my spine or engage the safety, please.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT THE GUNS DOWN</pattern><template>He's got nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>GODSPEED</pattern><template>Good day, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOING TO CLIP ISRAEL    CLIP</pattern><template>He's gonna kill him?  Buddy Israel?</template></category><category><pattern>SHH  MY ASS</pattern><template>She's asleep!</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO CALL THE FLORIST</pattern><template>When your guy gonna call?</template></category><category><pattern>CLEAR</pattern><template>Floor's secure, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT CLICKS    PADICHE: CLICKS  NO</pattern><template>Nothing on my end.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING  AGENT MESSNER</pattern><template>Walk. Let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE FIRST I'M HEARING OF IT</pattern><template>Have you contacted Agent Carruthers?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW    THIS</pattern><template>I don't know how you do this.</template></category><category><pattern>REED: HI  JACK  GREAT  GOOD  SUPER  COME ON IN</pattern><template>Good to see you.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BAD GUYS BEAT HIM   WORSE  SPARAZZA WALKED</pattern><template>How much longer you think?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST CLEAR THEM DOWN THE HALL</pattern><template>Make room. Make room, please.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T HELP HIM HERE</pattern><template>We have to take him to...</template></category><category><pattern>DROP THAT GODDAMN GUN NOW OR YOU'RE A DEAD MAN</pattern><template>Jesus Christ. Beanie's dead.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT WHAT HAPPENED TO NESS</pattern><template>Ness and the Untouchables took down Capone.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  GREAT  COME ON IN</pattern><template>Sorry about that.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE LIKE THAT HE LIKES</pattern><template>Pussy.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP POINTING</pattern><template>...Deputy Director Locke.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THIS ISRAEL REALLY IS THE GREAT WHITE WHALE OF SNITCHES  THEN WHAT ARE WE DOING MESSING WITH THE MOB  WHO ARE  CORRECT ME IF I'M WRONG  BUT I THINK THEY'RE GOING TO POUR BOXES OF BULLETS INTO HIS ASS</pattern><template>Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>EMPTY POCKETS PAID FOR BY THE LIVES OF OUR OWN PEOPLE</pattern><template>You're blowing this way out of proportion.</template></category><category><pattern>DUPREE'S CAR  '89 CADILLAC SEDAN DEVILLE</pattern><template>Where did you find it?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WE GOT RIGHT NOW IS A NUMBER AND A NAME</pattern><template>Buddy Israel.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T EVEN BLAME PRIMO    YOU KNOW  HE'S OLD SCHOOL SICILIAN</pattern><template>This is how they hate.   Now, big concern for me, at least, we crew up.   Let's not fuck around.</template></category><category><pattern>'CAUSE ONE OF YOUR HOES JUST GOT FUCKED UP</pattern><template>Yeah, she might be missing some work.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO GO IN  GET MY HEATING PAD  GET MY BLANKET</pattern><template>Nana, not during training.</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT: SHOTS FIRED</pattern><template>West tower. Nomad...  All right, hold on.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE YOU  YOU BIG NUT</pattern><template>Vitoli!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE ALMOST HOME</pattern><template>These two are down.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S IN THE BACK  JOE</pattern><template>Joe.</template></category><category><pattern>ALZHEIMER'S  YOU GET ALZHEIMER'S IF YOU'RE USING ANTIPERSPIRANT WITH ALUMINUM</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I forgot.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN: OH  MY GOD  I NEED AN AMBULANCE FOR BILL</pattern><template>I'm in the security room.  Are you anywhere near the penthouse?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M GONNA GO INTO KENTUCKY AND TAKE FORT KNOX WITH A FUCKING SLINGSHOT  AND AFTER THAT I'M GONNA GO INTO HELL AFTER HITLER</pattern><template>Would you please find your fangs, you fucking coward, and get with this?</template></category><category><pattern>HIS SUPERIORS WERE CONVINCED THAT HE HAD GONE ROGUE  SWAPPED ALLEGIANCES   SO THEY GAVE THE ORDER TO TERMINATE HIS COVER    ALL THIS TIME  WE WERE TOLD THAT IT WAS SPARAZZA THAT KILLED HELLER    WHEN IT WAS US  THE FBI    AND WE DIDN'T KILL HIM    HE SURVIVED</pattern><template>But the injuries he sustained  required constant surgery, forever altering his features.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS A</pattern><template>No, no.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  SADLY  THIS IS IT</pattern><template>You know, it's disgusting.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR</pattern><template>Officer!</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THE COLLAR ON THAT COAT  WHAT DOES THAT LOOK LIKE  THAT STAIN</pattern><template>I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO SECURITY LEVELS</pattern><template>The one we're going in under the guise of is general hotel security.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  I WAS EAVESDROPPING  SO LET ME LAY THIS THING OUT NEAT    ALL RIGHT  I'M LISTENING</pattern><template>Go ahead.   Now, what I heard downstairs is they got a guy. Some Swede.  Swede.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN LATER I SAW HIM GET ON THE ELEVATOR WITH THE OTHER AGENT</pattern><template>Wait, hold on.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY OFF AIR</pattern><template>You got clicks?   PADICHE: Clicks? No.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE HE GOES</pattern><template>No, don't shoot me!</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE YOUR SHIT  BITCH</pattern><template>Thanks, Paul.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S HAD A SUSTAINED ARRHYTHMIC EPISODE  SEVERE CARDIAC DISTRESS</pattern><template>I can't help him here.</template></category><category><pattern>NANA  NANA  NANA</pattern><template>Grandma will get it. Go on.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF UNIFORM    THE RECEIPT WAS PARTIALLY DESTROYED BY THE LAKE WATER   WHAT KIND OF UNIFORMS</pattern><template>What kind of uniforms?</template></category><category><pattern>SMALL WORLD</pattern><template>All right, enough grab assing, goddamn it!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG WITH YOU  MAN</pattern><template>Hugo!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M IN HERE</pattern><template>Ivy's trying to kill me!</template></category><category><pattern>BUDDY ISRAEL   BUDDY ISRAEL</pattern><template>They got a guy. Some Swede.</template></category><category><pattern>HUGO  YOU HIT</pattern><template>No! No, no, no!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S UP  I'M WORKING</pattern><template>Yeah, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING    NO  NOTHING ON MY END    SO  HOW WE LOOKING</pattern><template>Looks very good.   Fucking thrilled to hear it.   So, this sit down, you must have felt it from them then, huh?   Cold blood, Sid. Dead eyes.   Okay, yeah, good.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MAKE THIS FACE THE LAST THING YOU EVER SEE</pattern><template>Am I really dying?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT'S ALL GOOD  RIGHT</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>TRUTH IS  BUDDY DON'T KNOW THE FUCKING BALL FROM THE BOUNCE   WHAT DO YOU GOT</pattern><template>He's a wannabe.   Like most wannabes, he starts fucking up fast and picking up speed.  Are you fucking kidding me?</template></category><category><pattern>BITCH  I'M ABOUT TO BALL THIS</pattern><template>Okay, then. Punk.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE ELEVATOR</pattern><template>More duct. Come on, more duct.</template></category><category><pattern>GET YOUR ASS UP</pattern><template>Put your clothes on, girl.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT TO LAY SOMETHING OUT  THOUGH</pattern><template>You go up in there ad libbing and shit, it's your ass.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T EVEN LET IT RUB SHOULDERS WITH THE OTHER BOTTLE</pattern><template>Do you know what?</template></category><category><pattern>JOE</pattern><template>Joe, are you guys seeing anything?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S YOUR IFB  MAN</pattern><template>Somebody got a earpiece.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM NOT SHELLING OUT THIS KIND OF BREAD FOR THIS SHITHOLE  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>This is a junior suite in Vegas. So, fuck this and the fucking animal kingdom.</template></category><category><pattern>DID SOME HOME INVASION  SODOMY TORTURE TYPE STUFF</pattern><template>Wrote a bunch of bad checks.</template></category><category><pattern>MY GUY IS DEAD</pattern><template>You're starting to piss me off.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK IT</pattern><template>Okay, now let's get a tactical team assembled.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO POSTED THE BOND</pattern><template>Same guys who hired me, his former law firm.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT ALL THAT</pattern><template>Shit gets wild and crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>BLAH  BLAH  BLAH</pattern><template>And a paternity suit, just to, you know, round out the portfolio there.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYONE TALKED THINGS OUT  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>No one ever threw any blows.</template></category><category><pattern>AND BUDDY ISRAEL</pattern><template>Holy shit.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE AMORAL  RUTHLESS AND WITHOUT RESTRAINT   THEY MUST NOT SUCCEED</pattern><template>PADICHE: Sid.   SERNA: Yeah, Buzzy, I just got a call from the mansion.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T REMEMBER WHAT YOU SAID  WHAT</pattern><template>Fucking asshole.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE BEEN THROUGH THAT ALREADY</pattern><template>Well, then quit acting like someone took a shit in your cereal bowl, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I GOT HERE IS A GERALD DIEGO</pattern><template>A Donald Carruthers.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ISRAEL LIKES PUSSY</pattern><template>And we like that he likes...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK</pattern><template>Get out of the way.</template></category><category><pattern>GONNA GO DOWN AND GET VITOLI</pattern><template>Get him back up here.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST ONE BED  PLEASE</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  THEN  WHO GIVES A SHIT</pattern><template>Can I get you something to drink?</template></category><category><pattern>WE DID THE DAMN THING</pattern><template>Now proceed to the front in an orderly fashion, or how the fuck y'all want to, but get the fuck going.</template></category><category><pattern>SHARICE</pattern><template>Can you hear me? I'm hit.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S PERSONNEL STATIONED AT BOTH ENDS OF THAT HALLWAY 24 HOURS A DAY</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>HUGO</pattern><template>So, what did Mecklen have to say?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  FUCK THIS</pattern><template>LOCKE: Suicide of some sort.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU DO THIS</pattern><template>I mean, you have to keep your eye on everything.</template></category><category><pattern>FEELINGS THAT MIGHT RUN CONTRARY TO THE COLLECTIVE GOOD</pattern><template>And that, I need you to understand.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER IT WAS  IT GOT WAY PAST WORDS</pattern><template>What are they doing right now?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MURDERED BEANIE</pattern><template>Put the guns down.</template></category><category><pattern>AND UNDERSTAND THAT IF AN ATTEMPT IS MADE ON HIS LIFE  IT'LL BE MADE BY THOSE OF THE STRICTEST PROFESSIONAL CALIBER</pattern><template>They are amoral, ruthless and without restraint.  They must not succeed.</template></category><category><pattern>FLOOR'S SECURE  SIR</pattern><template>Okay, come in.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  SKILLS  SKILLS</pattern><template>Fucking stop it.</template></category><category><pattern>NOBODY GETS IN THE HOTEL</pattern><template>Nobody gets near the crime scene.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST SOME LITTLE CASINO INSPECTION</pattern><template>Don't trip.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO</pattern><template>Get them to the elevator.</template></category><category><pattern>BASICALLY  THERE'S TWO SECURITY LEVELS  OKAY</pattern><template>You got your casino floor, count room surveillance, then you got your general security.</template></category><category><pattern>SECURE THESE SUSPECTS</pattern><template>I need medical assistance.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT THE GUN DOWN</pattern><template>I didn't do your man downstairs.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL OVER THE AIR HERE</pattern><template>They got a impostor.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU'RE FBI</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL HAVE TO GO ALL THE WAY AROUND TO THE OTHER SIDE</pattern><template>Clear the way here.</template></category><category><pattern>MAMA'S GOT YOUR BACK  BABY</pattern><template>SERNA: Buzzy? Buzz?   Yeah, it's me.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE: SERNA JUST PICKED UP THE HOUSE PHONE    AGENT 2: HE'S ON THE PHONE NOW  HE IS ON THE PHONE</pattern><template>He's on the phone.   AGENT 1: I got some movement in there.  Ricky, pan to the right and zoom in.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU  I NEVER WANTED IT TO BE LIKE THIS</pattern><template>You know that.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  ISRAEL</pattern><template>I'm in here!</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT MULTIPLE OFFICERS DOWN</pattern><template>Watch him.</template></category><category><pattern>THREE MEN WERE AMBUSHED AND SHOT</pattern><template>Two died and had their bodies dumped in the lake.</template></category><category><pattern>MOTHERFUCK YOU</pattern><template>Fuck you!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON</pattern><template>How about we put a gun to your head?</template></category><category><pattern>ARSON  GRAND LARCENY</pattern><template>Blah, blah, blah.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW SO</pattern><template>Small world.</template></category><category><pattern>I TAKE IT YOU'RE NOT GOING</pattern><template>No, I'm gonna go into Kentucky and take Fort Knox with a fucking slingshot, and after that I'm gonna go into hell after Hitler.</template></category><category><pattern>AN EMERGENCY SHUTDOWN OF OUR ENTIRE ELEVATED LIFT SYSTEM  SIR</pattern><template>No. That has to be handled by my staff, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU COULD JUST TELL ME WHO HAS ACCESS TO THE FLOOR  I THINK WE COULD</pattern><template>I have the sole pass and relieve all of the personnel myself personally.</template></category><category><pattern>PUSSY</pattern><template>Correct.</template></category><category><pattern>PRIMO'S DOWNSTAIRS    I'VE BEEN SITTING BY THIS PHONE FOR 20 FUCKING HOURS    NOW LISTEN TO ME  BUZZY</pattern><template>He's going to clip Israel.   Clip?</template></category><category><pattern>NANA  NOT DURING TRAINING</pattern><template>Okay, Grandma's big helper boy?</template></category><category><pattern>FAKE IDENTITY  FALSIFIED BACKGROUNDS  EVERYTHING THAT IS NOW STANDARD OPERATING PROCEDURE   HELLER IMPLEMENTED WAY BACK WHEN      YOUR ATTENTION TO THESE OVERLAYS  I'LL SHOW YOU EXACTLY WHAT I MEANT WHEN I SAID   CHANGE MY FACE   AND AS A RESULT  HIS UNDERCOVER WORK WAS HIGHLY SUCCESSFUL</pattern><template>Using the latest techniques in cosmetic surgery, I will have my ears pinned back.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THE FUCK OUT OF THE CAR</pattern><template>Come on. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  STEP BACK  STEP BACK</pattern><template>Come on...</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT THE BUREAU KNOWS HE KILLED HELLER</pattern><template>Then why not go after him for that?</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH ONE OF THEM IS FOR REAL</pattern><template>'Cause I'm gonna kill the one that ain't.  Stop the elevator.</template></category><category><pattern>BAG THEM AND GET SOME MORE ON DECK  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>All right, y'all.</template></category><category><pattern>RICKY  THIS IS AGENT MESSNER</pattern><template>Tell him exactly what happened, nice and slow.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS  PAUL</pattern><template>Israel's awake.</template></category><category><pattern>GET HIM OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Jimmy, cuff him.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IT IS  THERE IT IS</pattern><template>You called the right bitches for this one, man.</template></category><category><pattern>TEN PERCENT FINDER'S FEE FOR ME</pattern><template>So, what's the time frame?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONE WE'RE GOING IN UNDER THE GUISE OF IS GENERAL HOTEL SECURITY</pattern><template>They're basically in charge of standing around the lobby with their dicks in their hands, you know what I mean?</template></category><category><pattern>WATTERS: FORGET IT  IT'S DONE   HEY  QUIT SAYING THAT  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Girl, I just saw muzzle flashes coming from that suite.</template></category><category><pattern>I AIN'T VALUABLE</pattern><template>I am sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE INVESTIGATING THOSE MURDERS OUT AT THE LAKE  HUH</pattern><template>Say what?</template></category><category><pattern>POOR ME</pattern><template>Warren, go and practice your nunchakus now.</template></category><category><pattern>GIRL  I JUST SAW MUZZLE FLASHES COMING FROM THAT SUITE</pattern><template>That's probably where you heard the shots earlier.</template></category><category><pattern>MURDER  OF COURSE  EXTORTION</pattern><template>Arson. Grand larceny.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT IT  WE GOT 'EM  WE GOT 'EM</pattern><template>What do you mean?</template></category><category><pattern>THESE TWO ARE DOWN</pattern><template>What the fuck is going on?</template></category><category><pattern>RIP  HAND TO GOD  YOU GOT NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT WITH THIS</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE WE TALKING ON THE SPLIT</pattern><template>Forty five a piece for you two.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FUCKING ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Okay, if you like, I'll take your verbal resignation right here, right now.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BILL  YOU SAID THERE'S SOME SITUATION ON 12</pattern><template>It's table 12?  Table 12. Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS ILLUSION  IVY</pattern><template>That is the lie that I tell your eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL TAKE CARE OF THAT</pattern><template>Hey, Boogie!</template></category><category><pattern>NOT YOU</pattern><template>Some assholes on the elevator.</template></category><category><pattern>PRESENTLY  WE HAVE</pattern><template>Sixteen state and federally funded agencies running concurrent criminal probes  on select members of La Cosa Nostra.   LOCKE: With Israel being the target of virtually every one.   His testimony has the potential of blowing the lid   off of what's left of La Cosa Nostra in this country.   That alone warrants total immunity from prosecution   and a vanishing act with the Witness Protection Program.  The wiretaps on Serna and Padiche, mention of Israel's heart?</template></category><category><pattern>HOLLIS  COME ON</pattern><template>Get the fuck out of the car.</template></category><category><pattern>FOUR  SIX  FIVE  THEY DIDN'T TEACH YOU HOW TO COUNT  I GUESS  HUH</pattern><template>But I bet you guys got a bunch of stories, right? I don't.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S JUST FOR FLAVOR</pattern><template>Now, I'm still trying to get the down low from this cat Padiche.</template></category><category><pattern>DEAL WITH THE PATIENTS</pattern><template>All right, Doctor, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT UNDERSTOOD  AGENT MESSNER</pattern><template>Are we clear, Agent Messner?</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER  MAN</pattern><template>We can bounce out, chill for a little bit.  Shoot a little craps.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T EXPLAIN EVERYTHING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>No, I...</template></category><category><pattern>GET HIM ON THE PHONE</pattern><template>If the situation's changed, I need to hear it from him.</template></category><category><pattern>SELL ME OFF LIKE A FUCKING FIELD NIGGA</pattern><template>You know I wouldn't.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY I'M VALUABLE HERE  IVY  AND THAT IS WHY YOU ARE NOT</pattern><template>I ain't valuable?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GONNA KILL HIM   BUDDY ISRAEL</pattern><template>Now, I was eavesdropping, so let me lay this thing out neat.   All right, I'm listening.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY YOU'RE MY MAN</pattern><template>'Cause outside a goddamn dog, that kind of loyalty, my kind of shit, don't get no more dedicated or devout.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHERE HE IS</pattern><template>No. He wanted to know...</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU LET ME KNOW  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>You just get up in there and do your thing, baby girl.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HIGH ROLLER SUITE</pattern><template>No, that's the last place they'd look.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOTTA PACK UP</pattern><template>We gotta pack it up now.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF THEM IS BULLSHIT</pattern><template>It's all over the air here.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I'VE BEEN SAYING</pattern><template>I need to get your head of security right now.</template></category><category><pattern>MENTION OF ISRAEL'S HEART</pattern><template>He's one of the best heart surgeons in the world.   The actual contract went to Lazlo Soot,   the man who escaped the penthouse yesterday...  Don't shoot me!</template></category><category><pattern>GET ME A FUCKING MEDIC</pattern><template>Where's that medic?</template></category><category><pattern>WE COULD BREAK DOWN NOW     SHIT  GIRL</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT</pattern><template>Some mob fossil?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT ME</pattern><template>What's up? I'm working.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I MEAN  NO  WE</pattern><template>There's personnel stationed at both ends of that hallway 24 hours a day.</template></category><category><pattern>I PASS THAT PEACE OF MIND ALONG TO MY PARTNERS</pattern><template>All right. Look up. Hey, man.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE WAY OF THE WORLD</pattern><template>The way it's always gonna be.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I BE OF ASSISTANCE</pattern><template>My name is Vitoli.</template></category><category><pattern>CLEAR THE WAY</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BET YOU ARE</pattern><template>Faggot ass redneck.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ANY WORD ON THIS SWEDE</pattern><template>No, just the mention in that phone call.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S IN LAKE TAHOE ON THE NEVADA SIDE</pattern><template>We got to lay something out, though.</template></category><category><pattern>USING THE LATEST TECHNIQUES IN COSMETIC SURGERY  I WILL HAVE MY EARS PINNED BACK</pattern><template>Removing a slight piece of bone in my chin, I will alter my jaw line.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE BLOWING THIS WAY OUT OF PROPORTION</pattern><template>Are you out of your fucking mind?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A GOOD MAN</pattern><template>Director Locke?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST LAY STILL FOR A MINUTE</pattern><template>Let me figure out...</template></category><category><pattern>THEN LATER  WHEN I SAW HIM GET ON THE ELEVATOR WITH CARRUTHERS</pattern><template>This man identified himself as a federal agent?</template></category><category><pattern>CALL THE FLORIST</pattern><template>No, I need you to chill.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY GOT A GUY  SOME SWEDE</pattern><template>Swede?  Any word on this Swede?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEBODY GET HIM OUT OF THERE</pattern><template>I fucked up.</template></category><category><pattern>CINNAMON ROLL</pattern><template>cinnamon roll? The cinnamon.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE THE WISDOM OF A 6 000 OR 7 000 YEAR OLD MAN</pattern><template>That's fantastic.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MILLION  PLUS THE FUCKING HEART</pattern><template>Plus the heart.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT THE MACHINE</pattern><template>What did you say?</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T GET CONCERNED</pattern><template>We'll see movement on this soon.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL SEE MOVEMENT ON THIS SOON</pattern><template>All right? We just got to knock off a few more hours.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WILLIAM</pattern><template>We're all dying.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  SHIT</pattern><template>I don't know how bad this is. Shit.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T GAIN WEIGHT  I TRIED</pattern><template>That's 'cause you're 12 years old.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  DONE</pattern><template>Come on, step back, step back.</template></category><category><pattern>IVY'S TRYING TO KILL ME</pattern><template>Motherfuck you!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE INSTRUCTED TO GET OUT</pattern><template>What are you doing, Agent Messner?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S TRAVELING BACK WITH US</pattern><template>I can't explain everything right now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE STARTING TO PISS ME OFF</pattern><template>The Bureau betrayed us.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE EXACTLY AND ONLY WHAT I CHOOSE TO SHOW YOU</pattern><template>That is illusion, Ivy.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'S THAT LOVE</pattern><template>Bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>LET GO OF ME</pattern><template>Let go of my arm!</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF THE WAY</pattern><template>Fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MUCH</pattern><template>What you hearing right now?</template></category><category><pattern>FOUR</pattern><template>Four years.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT SOME OF THIS  YEAH</pattern><template>What? What?</template></category><category><pattern>STOP IT  STOP IT</pattern><template>Now he's got connections.</template></category><category><pattern>INITIATE ALL CLEAR</pattern><template>Clear.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TRYING TO WAKE THIS BITCH UP  MAN</pattern><template>Come here! Come here!</template></category><category><pattern>AND EVERYBODY ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>Yeah, it can be a chore.</template></category><category><pattern>Y'ALL REALLY LET HOOCHIES LIKE THAT STAY UP IN HERE</pattern><template>I mean, 'cause y'all must be burning sheets by the ton.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WANTED FELON HERE  BUDDY ISRAEL  LITTLE RICK SPRINGFIELD  I GUESS</pattern><template>And his bail bond bobbing around up there out at the lake.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THESE HOTEL GUESTS OUT IN THE HALLWAY THERE</pattern><template>Just clear them down the hall.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED HERE</pattern><template>I'm sorry, I cannot disclose anything more right now.</template></category><category><pattern>LITTLE BOOSTS</pattern><template>Helps allay my fears.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL BE DEBRIEFED IN THE DAYS TO COME</pattern><template>Explain it now.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOW ME YOUR FUCKING HANDS</pattern><template>Drop the gun down or I'll fucking drain you.</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN  FOUR SKANK ASS BITCHES</pattern><template>That's your crew.</template></category><category><pattern>GET IT FUCKING DONE   LISTEN TO ME  KID</pattern><template>Let's not antagonize this any more, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD DAY  SIR</pattern><template>Hey, baby.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WHY NOT GO AFTER HIM FOR THAT</pattern><template>Heller was buried by the agency.</template></category><category><pattern>COPY THAT  WE GOT HER NOW   NO GUESTS  THOUGH  ON THE PENTHOUSE</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT OFFICERS DOWN</pattern><template>Repeat, on the seventh floor, officers down.</template></category><category><pattern>PUSHY</pattern><template>Pussy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW A SWEDE</pattern><template>You know of a Swede?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS UNDERTAKEN TO SAVE HIS LIFE</pattern><template>Look at the work he's had done.</template></category><category><pattern>HAND ME TO THE FEDS LIKE YOUR LAST CHIP</pattern><template>Whatever you think, whatever...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GAY BECAUSE I HAVE A BEARD</pattern><template>My fingers are cut off.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Are you all right, son?</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT: LEFT SIDE OF THE BUILDING'S SEALED OFF   GODDAMN  CAN YOU HEAR ME</pattern><template>Get this shit off!</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW</pattern><template>Where's your guy?</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP  FUCK OFF</pattern><template>That's gonna be real incognito going in like that.</template></category><category><pattern>VITOLI</pattern><template>Come on, bitchy bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING TO WORK THIS OUT AND LIVE  OR WE GONNA KEEP DOING THE SAME SHIT WE'VE BEEN DOING</pattern><template>I ain't got no problem with you or your Bureau, so I think you're better off just moving on and letting us be.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HOW WE DO</pattern><template>Now, okay, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE INSTRUCTED TO TAKE ISRAEL INTO PROTECTIVE CUSTODY</pattern><template>That's a two man operation.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>It don't matter what you wanted.</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH IT  WATCH IT</pattern><template>Watch who your superior is, pal.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HIT THOSE CHINAMEN  TOOK OUT THE BIG TRIAD    THESE GIRLS ARE WORTH EVERY PENNY  I'LL CALL LORETTA</pattern><template>She handles both of them.   All right.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TOUGH  HUH</pattern><template>This is tough.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU KIDDING</pattern><template>I thought you were gonna go...</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TO SPEAK TO SECURITY RIGHT AWAY    THIS IS SPECIAL AGENT DONALD CARRUTHERS OF THE FBI</pattern><template>Hello? Is anyone there? Hello?  Is that blood?</template></category><category><pattern>GET THEM TO THE ELEVATOR</pattern><template>GIRL: Fuck you!</template></category><category><pattern>A DEDICATED VICIOUSNESS AND SLAVISH DEVOTION TO MOB DOCTRINE  HAD SPARAZZA'S STAR ON THE RISE</pattern><template>So they relocated him to Nevada and made him the head of the Las Vegas Cosa Nostra.</template></category><category><pattern>IVY  BEANIE  HUGO  THE WORKS</pattern><template>This is not a fucking swap meet, all right, Morrie?</template></category><category><pattern>GET THE PHONE  IT'S PROBABLY MECKLEN  GET VITOLI UP HERE AND START CLEANING</pattern><template>All right?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GET PROS</pattern><template>People who know how to behave.  This thing's gonna blow up huge.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TIRED</pattern><template>I ain't no fucking cleaning lady, dawg.</template></category><category><pattern>NO FORMER WITNESS AGAINST THE MOB HAS BEEN AS CRUCIAL OR AS IMPORTANT  AS BUDDY  ACES  ISRAEL</pattern><template>He's not only essential to our case,  he is our case.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE INJURIES HE SUSTAINED  REQUIRED CONSTANT SURGERY  FOREVER ALTERING HIS FEATURES</pattern><template>So he assumed the identity of his alter ego.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD DAMN IT  GEORGIA</pattern><template>Just say something!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  ONE OF THEM IS NOT</pattern><template>One of them is bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA SLIP IN WITH THE DAYTIME GUYS WHEN THEY GO ON</pattern><template>But what about access cards, passkeys?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S FANTASTIC</pattern><template>We don't have to fill up the whole blackboard after all.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY OF THESE NIGGAS MAKE ONE FALSE MOVE  THESE BITCHES TAKING DIRT NAPS</pattern><template>I ain't trying to be up here all day.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT PICKING UP THE EXTENSION</pattern><template>I know that.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOW ME YOUR HANDS</pattern><template>Show me your fucking hands!</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING TO DRINK</pattern><template>You're disgusting.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR DEBRIEFING  YOUR DEBRIEFING WILL BE HANDLED IN DC  LIKE I TOLD YOU</pattern><template>No, we need to handle it now.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU SAYING THAT JUST BECAUSE ME AND BABY GIRL HERE GOT A REP ON THE RISE  YOU KNOW  WE CHIPPED SOME NAILS ON SOME NIGGAS  THEY WANT US TO GO IN AND DROP THIS MAFIOSO MOTHERFUCKER</pattern><template>The way it works, girl.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKING THE MAGIC HAPPEN IN THE MOMENT  IN THAT SPLIT SECOND  BUT SEEING BEHIND THIS MOTHERFUCKER AND KNOWING THAT IT'S ALL BULLSHIT</pattern><template>Yeah, you're on some bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T LIKE PUNK BITCHES EYEBALLING ME</pattern><template>You got beef? You got beef?</template></category><category><pattern>CRAZY MOTHERFUCKERS UP THERE  HUH  GEE WHIZ</pattern><template>Just give us your keys and get the fuck out of here.</template></category><category><pattern>I VERY SORRY</pattern><template>Are you a colossal fucking idiot?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST SAY SOMETHING</pattern><template>Mother...</template></category><category><pattern>HIS MAMA ABANDONED HIM GOING ON A YEAR NOW AND HIS DADDY  MY BOY DALE  HE'S OVER AT THE RENO WASHOE CORRECTIONAL FACILITY</pattern><template>Got some clarity issues.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU GUYS HAVE ANY TRANSMISSION    HE'S ON THE PHONE   QUIET  QUIET  WE GOT IT</pattern><template>He's talking to someone right now.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS  I'LL TELL YOU  ENGINEERING THIS KIND OF PLAY AGAINST SPARAZZA  GOING TO THESE LENGTHS THAT THESE TWO GUYS ARE GOING  THEY'RE PLAYING SOME LONG ODDS</pattern><template>Coffee? Anything?</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL'S OBVIOUSLY PAID THEM OFF</pattern><template>We're not gonna have any trouble with the hotel staff.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  ENOUGH GRAB ASSING  GODDAMN IT</pattern><template>Grab them suits and the car.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I TELL YOU WHAT</pattern><template>That bitch ass fed get in the way, RIP, nigga.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  LADIES  GET UP</pattern><template>Beans.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE ARE THE PREMIER PRICK COCKSUCKERS OF ALL TIME</pattern><template>And I feel beaten by them. I feel bloodied.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  GENTLEMEN  I UNDERSTAND THAT THIS IS A DRAMATIC APPROACH</pattern><template>He went deep cover in 1940.</template></category><category><pattern>WE JUST WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON   YOU GOT SOME SULTAN</pattern><template>One of your whales.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  WHAT'S WRONG  WHAT   MAN  FUCKING SECURITY'S SHUTTING DOWN THE ELEVATORS IN YOUR BUILDING</pattern><template>AUTOMATED VOICE: Please remain calm.  Now that's the power, there.</template></category><category><pattern>TRUST ME</pattern><template>Just remember it's more of a rescue than a rampage, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HEART SHIT</pattern><template>That's just for flavor.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>(MECKLEN CRYING)   They revoked the deal.  They revoked the deal.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THAT GUN OUT OF MY SPINE OR ENGAGE THE SAFETY  PLEASE</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ELSE  HE DRINKS  YOU KNOW  SELF MEDICATES</pattern><template>Total clich.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW HE'S GOT CONNECTIONS</pattern><template>He's got pull.  So he starts to make plays.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS GUY  HE'S A STRUNG OUT  WASHED UP  HAS BEEN  JERK  SNITCH  FUCKING DRUNK  SEVEN LAYER LOSER</pattern><template>Right. Now I'm praying he puts up a fight!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>That your car?</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE'S HEADED TO TAHOE THEN  HUH    YEAH  WE'RE IN A BIT OF A FOOTRACE RIGHT NOW  BUZZY    IT'S A MATTER OF WHO OUTHUSTLES WHO  YOU KNOW    WE JUST GOT TO GET TO ISRAEL FIRST    IT'S GETTING DONE  SID    WE GOT TO GET HIM  BUZZ</pattern><template>Everything, and I mean everything is riding on this.   We're gonna get Israel.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING</pattern><template>You mean to tell me that nobody noticed anyone getting out of a Cadillac that looked like a wiffle ball?</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT  AS LIGHT IN THE ASS AS YOU ARE  BET YOU AIN'T NEVER HAD TO MAKE NOTHING MORE THAN A FUCKING FIST YOUR WHOLE LIFE</pattern><template>Ivy...</template></category><category><pattern>TO WHAT  INCINERATE</pattern><template>Hugo!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BOOGIE</pattern><template>I need you to go in, get my heating pad, get my blanket.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  GO  GO  GO  GO    WE GOT AN ID PENDING ON A JACK DUPREE    HE'S A BAIL BONDSMAN OUT OF LAS VEGAS  NEVADA   DID YOU RECOVER ANYTHING FROM HIS PERSON</pattern><template>We got a receipt out of his pocket.   It was for a uniform rental.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEBODY JUST DEADED ISRAEL'S ASS  IT'S A WRAP   I AIN'T COME ALL THIS WAY JUST TO PACK IT UP BECAUSE YOU THINKING SOMETHING UP</pattern><template>Whatever, man.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GETTING ROBBED HERE  MAN</pattern><template>Seriously.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  COME ON  SIT DOWN</pattern><template>Please, no, I don't want to sit. Explain it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID HE WAS HERE TO DO SOME INSPECTIONS</pattern><template>Then later, when I saw him get on the elevator with Carruthers...</template></category><category><pattern>TRUST ME    HUGO ON RECORDER: YOU OPEN THE FUCKING DOOR    AGENT: I'M SORRY  SIR   BUT THIS IS EYES ONLY</pattern><template>They told me to hand deliver.</template></category><category><pattern>AND PITCH THEM POOR FELLAS IN THE LAKE</pattern><template>And y'all follow me over to the hotel.</template></category><category><pattern>HAS MECKLEN CALLED</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE GO  HERE WE GO</pattern><template>Zoom back in and stay there.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE SHOT</pattern><template>Now, Buddy starts making friends.</template></category><category><pattern>MESSNER: SO IT'S A CONFIRMED DOUBLE HOMICIDE    CARRUTHERS: NOBODY FROM SECURITY IS PICKING UP THE LINE   GUNSHOT VICS  DUMPED IN THE LAKE  MAYBE AN HOUR COLD</pattern><template>You're on speakerphone.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FIND OUT WHATEVER YOU CAN</pattern><template>What are you gonna do?</template></category><category><pattern>IF I'M ASKING YOU WHAT YOU SAID TO MECKLEN  ASSUME THE SHIT IS RHETORICAL</pattern><template>Assume I already know.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE WE DON'T NEED TO BRING ANY MORE SHIT DOWN ON OUR HEADS</pattern><template>I'm saying we're gonna hit whoever's between us and Israel. That's how I'm on it.</template></category><category><pattern>CARRUTHERS: WHAT  NOW</pattern><template>The old man's in bed.   The nurse is in there, and then Serna is somewhere in the house.  Who's in the back?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T USE DEODORANT</pattern><template>Look at you.</template></category><category><pattern>SWEDE   ANY WORD ON THIS SWEDE</pattern><template>...the mention of this mysterious Swede.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU SEE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>You see exactly and only what I choose to show you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>You stay with me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY I AND MY FRIEND AND PARTNER  WHOSE BODY IS GOING INTO A FURNACE TOMORROW  WERE NEVER FUCKING CONTACTED</pattern><template>I cannot discuss it.</template></category><category><pattern>FIFTEEN SEPARATE PROCEDURES SINCE 1952</pattern><template>Same year that Sparazza supposedly murdered Freeman Heller.</template></category><category><pattern>WHETHER YOU BELIEVE ME OR NOT  YOU KNOW  THAT AIN'T EVEN THE LEAST BIT IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>We're going to work this out and live, or we gonna keep doing the same shit we've been doing.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE YOUR TEAM AWARE  BUT DO IT QUIETLY  OKAY</pattern><template>Fuck it.</template></category><category><pattern>PREPARE TO MOVE</pattern><template>North elevator door's open.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK THAT'S BEEN OPENED SINCE MY HUSBAND DIED</pattern><template>I might just borrow this for a little while.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY RECOGNIZE THE SKILLS</pattern><template>Now, you all want this?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HE'S HERE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>We're talking to the kid.</template></category><category><pattern>GO DOWN THERE</pattern><template>Come on. Let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT'S THE LAST PLACE THEY'D LOOK</pattern><template>Israel's lawyers were left holding the bag after he skipped bail.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR ATTITUDE IS FUCKING HORRIBLE</pattern><template>It's embarrassing.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  BABY  DON'T BE SHY</pattern><template>Just one bed, please.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DOESN'T HAVE A FRIEND IN THE WORLD  WE GOT TO MOVE</pattern><template>Son of a bitch.</template></category><category><pattern>LOCKE: PASQUALE ACOSTA    BLOOD MONEY MERCENARY</pattern><template>EI Estrago.   The Plague.   When he was caught by the SAS in Belfast.   And in prison, he chewed off his fingertips to the bone.  Why don't you have maintenance do it?</template></category><category><pattern>GOT SOME CLARITY ISSUES</pattern><template>Did some home invasion, sodomy torture type stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE ASSUMED THE IDENTITY OF HIS ALTER EGO</pattern><template>The figment of Primo Sparazza became flesh and blood,   and Freeman Heller was no more.  Now, the brass wanted Heller's op removed from official records, so they buried it completely and they wrote Heller off.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED NOMAD HOTEL SECURITY TO LOCK DOWN THE ELEVATORS IMMEDIATELY   GIRL  PLEASE DON'T TELL ME THIS MOTHERFUCKER JUST WENT OFF</pattern><template>Man, these fools.</template></category><category><pattern>HUGO  WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG WITH YOU  MAN</pattern><template>What, you stuck on stupid or something? I know. You rode a little bus to school.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOOPSIE</pattern><template>We'll take care of that.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MILLION FLAT   HOLY SHIT</pattern><template>If word hits the street that there's a million dollar bounty   for Buddy fucking Israel,   you're gonna have every fucking hit man in the free world looking for him.   We got to move quickly.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA OF HOW VALUABLE THAT IS</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>FIFTEEN OF THEM  RIGHT</pattern><template>Fifteen separate procedures since 1952.</template></category><category><pattern>ENFORCER  EXTORTIONIST  KILLER</pattern><template>Sparazza has been rumored to have performed in excess of 100 contract murders, including one of the Bureau's most celebrated agents, Freeman Heller.</template></category><category><pattern>FBI</pattern><template>Oh, you're FBI.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ALL THEY'RE GONNA GIVE US</pattern><template>Look at the attention we gettin', man.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WITH THESE DOWN  DOESN'T THAT POSE A MAJOR SECURITY CONCERN</pattern><template>I mean, as you said, you got to keep your eye on everything at all times.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT THE TREMOR BROTHERS</pattern><template>Three of them.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST CHILL FOR A SECOND</pattern><template>AGENT: Shots fired.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY WITH ME</pattern><template>Mecklen's gonna call any second, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>Hey, Hollis.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ELSE</pattern><template>How about the Tremor Brothers?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW ALL YOU GOT TO BE IS GRATEFUL</pattern><template>You hurting pretty bad, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  GREAT</pattern><template>If you could just tell me who has access to the floor, I think we could...</template></category><category><pattern>I AIN'T GOT NO PROBLEM WITH YOU OR YOUR BUREAU  SO I THINK YOU'RE BETTER OFF JUST MOVING ON AND LETTING US BE</pattern><template>Agent Messner is on his way in.</template></category><category><pattern>MORTAL</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE HIM TO THE SERVICE EXIT  IT'S QUICK</pattern><template>Get back here.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO SWEDISH HIT MAN ON ANYONE'S RADAR</pattern><template>Dr. Ingstrom, the Swede, is not a hired killer.</template></category><category><pattern>POSSIBLY</pattern><template>Is he gonna show you where all the bodies are buried?</template></category><category><pattern>LEAVE US BE ALONE  SHUG</pattern><template>Go on, now, shug.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>I'll see you up here someday.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU SEND US IN THERE  BUGLES BLARING  AND WHEN IT BOTTOMS OUT  WE'RE THE LAST TO KNOW</pattern><template>We need cohesion to move forward son, not...</template></category><category><pattern>GET YOUR DICK BEATERS OFF IT</pattern><template>Couple of things.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GRAVEYARD GETS OFF</pattern><template>We're gonna slip in with the daytime guys when they go on.</template></category><category><pattern>WALL TO WALL FELONY OFFENSES</pattern><template>Murder, of course. Extortion.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Ricky, this is Agent Messner.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOT ONE SINGLE CRIMINAL CHARGE LAID AGAINST HIM</pattern><template>Well, you can't kill over a hundred people without knowing how to tiptoe.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  THIS IS ONE OF THEM RARE MOMENTS WHERE YOUR ASS GET A CHANCE TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST</pattern><template>If I'm asking you what you said to Mecklen, assume the shit is rhetorical.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA GO</pattern><template>Gonna go down and get Vitoli.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ACOSTA'S PURE MERCENARY</pattern><template>He has a history of taking on tough kills, and he's certainly not alone.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU</pattern><template>Listen, I know where Israel is, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>ELEVATOR SERVICE HAS BEEN TEMPORARILY SUSPENDED AND WILL RESUME MOMENTARILY    PLEASE REMAIN CALM    ELEVATOR SERVICE HAS BEEN TEMPORARILY SUSPENDED AND WILL RESUME MOMENTARILY   WELL  LET'S GET ON IT  THEN</pattern><template>I wanna pick them down there.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SPARAZZA HAD MAJOR ELECTIVE PLASTIC SURGERY</pattern><template>It wasn't elective.</template></category><category><pattern>HIT HIM IN THE BROWN</pattern><template>I don't know. Anyway, I believe we had a retainer for services rendered.</template></category><category><pattern>REED PAID US 50 GRAND</pattern><template>What am I doing?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  THERE'S A SHIFT CHANGE AT 9:00 A M</pattern><template>The graveyard gets off.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS NOBODY HERE</pattern><template>He said he was from San Francisco.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT THE ELEVATOR DOWN</pattern><template>An emergency shutdown of our entire elevated lift system, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE USED FOR THAT SUICIDE STYLE  KAMIKAZE SHIT</pattern><template>Heard about that dinner club in Cleveland?</template></category><category><pattern>WARREN  GO AND PRACTICE YOUR NUNCHAKUS NOW</pattern><template>Leave us be alone, shug.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  WHAT</pattern><template>See? Skills. Skills.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY LOSING A WHOLE FLOOR'S WORTH OF BUSINESS  SAYING IT'S UNDER CONSTRUCTION</pattern><template>I am not shelling out this kind of bread for this shithole, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>STRAIGHT ROCKING HEAT  SLAYING NIGGAS  MAN</pattern><template>For real?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WITHHELD INFORMATION WHILE CARRUTHERS LAY DYING IN VAIN AND IN THE DARK</pattern><template>And your reasons for doing that are exactly what?</template></category><category><pattern>I'D LIKE TO SHOW YOU EXACTLY WHAT I MEANT WHEN I SAID   CHANGE MY FACE   USING THE LATEST TECHNIQUES IN COSMETIC SURGERY  I WILL HAVE MY EARS PINNED BACK</pattern><template>Removing a slight piece of bone in my chin I will alter my jaw line.</template></category><category><pattern>PADICHE: SID    SERNA: YEAH  BUZZY  I JUST GOT A CALL FROM THE MANSION</pattern><template>The Swede has arrived.   No shit.   The old man sent for him.   So get yourself on a plane and get your ass to Lake Tahoe.  Are you fucking kidding me?</template></category><category><pattern>TURN THE OVERHEADS OFF  NOW</pattern><template>Not exactly low profile, is this?</template></category><category><pattern>SO WE HAVE MAYBE A DAY BEFORE THAT LOCATION THAT I KNOW GETS GRAPEVINED AND THE WHOLE FUCKING WORLD GETS HIP TO THIS</pattern><template>He's in Lake Tahoe on the Nevada side.</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL'S MOTHER WAS 19   AT THE TIME WHEN SHE AND SPARAZZA HAD A BRIEF AFFAIR   OF WHICH ISRAEL WAS THE BYPRODUCT   THAT SAME YEAR  SHE BROUGHT A PATERNITY SUIT AGAINST HIM</pattern><template>Paternity suit?</template></category><category><pattern>I GAVE YOU SPARAZZA</pattern><template>I'm gonna give them Sparazza and the west coast syndicate gift wrapped.</template></category><category><pattern>I AIN'T CLEANING ALL THIS SHIT UP MYSELF  MAN</pattern><template>I'm tired.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA NEED A MINIBAR KEY  TOO</pattern><template>MAN ON TAPE RECORDER: Say your name. Then say,  How can I be of assistance?    VITOLI: I don't understand.   I didn't ask for your understanding.   I asked for your name, followed by the phrase,    How can I be of assistance?    My name is Vitoli.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE BRILLIANT</pattern><template>Okay, why don't you just chill for now?</template></category><category><pattern>UTTERLY USELESS</pattern><template>That's a risk we take.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ON SPEAKERPHONE</pattern><template>AGENT: Am I on the speakerphone?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID YOU SAY</pattern><template>Hugo, you're staring at me like I just asked you for the fucking square root of something.</template></category><category><pattern>SPARAZZA HAS BEEN RUMORED TO HAVE PERFORMED IN EXCESS OF 100 CONTRACT MURDERS  INCLUDING ONE OF THE BUREAU'S MOST CELEBRATED AGENTS  FREEMAN HELLER</pattern><template>I thought Heller was a double op?</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY IF YOU REALLY  TRULY MEAN IT</pattern><template>I very sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>I GAINED  LIKE  20  25 POUNDS</pattern><template>You keep eating this crap...</template></category><category><pattern>HUGO  WHAT'S HAPPENING  MAN</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>IVY: I CHANGED LIVES FOR YOU   YOU AIN'T NEVER HAD TO WASH ANOTHER MAN'S BLOOD OFF  DIG IT OUT OF YOUR FINGERNAILS</pattern><template>You had us for that.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I BE OF ASSISTANCE   VITOLI</pattern><template>Vitoli!</template></category><category><pattern>SOME MOB FOSSIL</pattern><template>A monster that the Bureau built?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  STAY AWAKE</pattern><template>Get me a medic!</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL: $50 000 FOR THIS FUCKING SUITE</pattern><template>Yo, calm down.</template></category><category><pattern>GET YOUR HANDS UP</pattern><template>Check the vitals on this guy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT AM I DOING</pattern><template>Am I standing here?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST KEEP IT FUCKING DOWN</pattern><template>CARRUTHERS: What, now?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  MAN  COME ON</pattern><template>Hoes gotta go.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THAT</pattern><template>What floor are they on?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HEAR WHAT I'M SAYING</pattern><template>I forgive you, Darwin.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WANT YOUR CAREER TO END HERE  NOW  LIKE THIS</pattern><template>Your call.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT THAT LINE</pattern><template>Can't you contact your people with that?</template></category><category><pattern>GODDAMN</pattern><template>Hey, yo, is this Madame Alex?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T LIKE THE ROLLS THAT TABLE'S BEEN GETTING</pattern><template>It's tough, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME  SIR</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>BUDDY ISRAEL</pattern><template>What else did Padiche say?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOT NOTHING</pattern><template>Get him out of here.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS APPARENTLY A FIGHT WITH SOME PROSTITUTES  BUT HE WASN'T INVOLVED</pattern><template>What, like an actual fight?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY KILLED US   THREE MINUTES</pattern><template>Prepare to move.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT GONNA HAVE ANY TROUBLE WITH THE HOTEL STAFF</pattern><template>You show them your ID with the letters  FBI  in all caps, it's instant compliance.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I FEEL BEATEN BY THEM  I FEEL BLOODIED</pattern><template>You're just gonna have to play ball.  No, I don't have to do shit, which includes cooperating with these fuckers, until I get what I want!</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHY</pattern><template>Because we don't need to bring any more shit down on our heads.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE NOW TRYING TO REHABILITATE HIM  SO WE CAN ATTEMPT A TRANSPLANT</pattern><template>You realize that you're doing this to save Sparazza?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BABY</pattern><template>They heard about that triad hit, the work y'all put in.</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN  GIRL  YOU'RE GONNA MAKE A NIGGA FALL HARD</pattern><template>Put her down. Put her down and get up against the wall right now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN AND YOU WILL</pattern><template>You are finished.</template></category><category><pattern>ASSHOLE</pattern><template>I say this from the bottom of my heart. Retire.</template></category><category><pattern>VEGAS RESIDENT</pattern><template>Used to be with the PD down there.</template></category><category><pattern>BLOOD MONEY MERCENARY</pattern><template>His countrymen have dubbed him the more dubious  EI Estrago.     The Plague.    American educated. Fluent in over a dozen languages.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DID THIS COME FROM</pattern><template>They dug it up in archives as part of the Sparazza investigation.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK IS GOING ON</pattern><template>Come on, you fucker.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE CONDUCTING A SERIES OF IMPROMPTU INSPECTIONS FOR THE NEVADA GAMING COMMISSION  AND I'D LIKE TO SPEAK WITH YOUR HEAD OF SECURITY</pattern><template>Okay, just one second.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF DEODORANT DO YOU USE</pattern><template>I don't use deodorant.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS CHRIST  THIS IS OUR TIME NOW    YOU THINK THEY'LL REALLY KICK RANSOM FOR ISRAEL    YOU AIN'T HEARD THE PUNCH LINE    BUT BEFORE I GET TO IT  ONE MORE THING  I SHOULD PROBABLY BRING IT UP    PRIMO WANTS ISRAEL'S HEART   WHAT'D HE JUST SAY</pattern><template>He's going to cut his heart out.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  IF WE CAN JUST SEE YOUR ID</pattern><template>Absolutely.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP THE ELEVATOR</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT ME  MAN</pattern><template>Look at me.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN  THESE FOOLS</pattern><template>What? What's wrong? What?  Man, fucking security's shutting down the elevators in your building.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT THE FUCKING RABBIT DOWN</pattern><template>Appreciate it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT LOOK LIKE SHE PUT A BOWL ON THAT SHIT  MAN  DAMN</pattern><template>Hey, but you need to bring your ass down here and help me out, Hugo, for real.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE BASICALLY IN CHARGE OF STANDING AROUND THE LOBBY WITH THEIR DICKS IN THEIR HANDS  YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN</pattern><template>There's a 35 person employee contingent that goes at 9:00 in the morning.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR SURVEILLANCE OF PADICHE  SERNA</pattern><template>All bogus and bad information that set off a series of unfortunate events.   He's gonna clip Israel.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS HOW THEY HATE    NOW  BIG CONCERN FOR ME  AT LEAST  WE CREW UP    LET'S NOT FUCK AROUND</pattern><template>Someone's cousin, some zip off the boat from Naples.  Zip off the boat?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  A FIGHT</pattern><template>Jesus Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL HAVE TO WAIT</pattern><template>What about that line?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS SOMETHING ABOUT SOME FAGGOT ASS FED BEING UP IN THE BUILDING</pattern><template>A fed? Like FBI?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU CAN'T KILL OVER A HUNDRED PEOPLE WITHOUT KNOWING HOW TO TIPTOE</pattern><template>Yeah, but the Bureau knows he killed Heller.</template></category><category><pattern>PRIMO WANTS ISRAEL'S HEART   HEART</pattern><template>Mention of Israel's heart?</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN'T ALLOW THAT TO HAPPEN</pattern><template>A Gulfstream is waiting at the Reagan National Airport to transport you to Lake Tahoe.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS CHRIST</pattern><template>A scuffle, a donnybrook. Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE ALL DYING</pattern><template>MESSNER: So it's a confirmed double homicide.   CARRUTHERS: Nobody from security is picking up the line.  Gunshot vics, dumped in the lake, maybe an hour cold.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE FUCKED UP  IVY</pattern><template>Hugo! You hit?</template></category><category><pattern>TOTAL CLICH</pattern><template>This guy. He's a strung out, washed up, has been, jerk, snitch, fucking drunk, seven layer loser.</template></category><category><pattern>POSSIBLE AGGRESSION INSIDE</pattern><template>Check your fire.  Clear on my mark.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GET TO THE BUSINESS AT HAND</pattern><template>This wanted felon here, Buddy Israel, little Rick Springfield, I guess.</template></category><category><pattern>PIECES OF ASS AND PUSSY</pattern><template>Something pretty in lipstick and eyeliner that can suck a fucking cock!</template></category><category><pattern>SERIOUSLY</pattern><template>Three days staring at Sparazza's house.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE</pattern><template>You know that Sparazza's had major elective plastic surgery.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  BILL  IF I'M GETTING THIS RIGHT  SO YOU CURRENTLY HAVE THE PENTHOUSE LEVEL UNDER CONSTRUCTION</pattern><template>That's correct.</template></category><category><pattern>STILL TO THIS DAY  NEVER PUNCHED IN THE FACE</pattern><template>Imagine that?</template></category><category><pattern>DO THEY EVER</pattern><template>Jesus Christ, this is our time now.   You think they'll really kick ransom for Israel?   You ain't heard the punch line.   But before I get to it, one more thing. I should probably bring it up.   Primo wants Israel's heart.  What'd he just say?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT ALL YOU'RE MISSING</pattern><template>Have you checked this stuff out yet?</template></category><category><pattern>OUTSTANDING  GET IT UP THERE</pattern><template>Come on. Come on, man.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THE WORK HE'S HAD DONE</pattern><template>It wasn't cosmetic.</template></category><category><pattern>GET IN THERE AND PIN THAT GIRL</pattern><template>Sharice?</template></category><category><pattern>GET THAT THING OUT OF MY FACE</pattern><template>You betrayed us the way you betrayed them.</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT GETS WILD AND CRAZY</pattern><template>Fate just up and fucks you for no good reason.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FUCK DO YOU MEAN  I AIN'T TRYING TO CLEAN THIS SHIT UP MYSELF  DAWG</pattern><template>Hey, don't even think I'm touching my man's coat that I know you nutted all over, you no aiming ass.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE FLOWERS HAVE WILTED</pattern><template>Call the florist.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST KEEP ZOOMING IN    SERNA: BUZZ</pattern><template>Dialogue hot. Dialogue hot.  Everybody off the walkies now.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TRIP</pattern><template>All right, then. When them tricks hit the lobby, I want you to holler at me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  WRITE THAT SHIT DOWN</pattern><template>Are you saying that just because me and baby girl here got a rep on the rise, you know, we chipped some nails on some niggas, they want us to go in and drop this mafioso motherfucker?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY</pattern><template>Yeah, a fight.</template></category><category><pattern>FORGIVE ME</pattern><template>Get your hands up!</template></category><category><pattern>DOUCHEBAG</pattern><template>Five time Vegas Showman of the Year.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO  STEP LIVELY</pattern><template>Get your ass up.</template></category><category><pattern>GIRL: FUCK YOU</pattern><template>Give me my purse!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  GODDAMN</pattern><template>Crazy motherfuckers up there, huh? Gee whiz.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU PLEASE FIND YOUR FANGS  YOU FUCKING COWARD  AND GET WITH THIS</pattern><template>What is wrong with you?</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE  BUT THAT'S VERY UNLIKELY</pattern><template>Jesus, I'll tell you, engineering this kind of play against Sparazza, going to these lengths that these two guys are going, they're playing some long odds.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST FOR FUN</pattern><template>Our surveillance of Padiche, Serna...</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE AIN'T COMING CHEAP    SO I'M THINKING WE JUMP    GET TO ISRAEL BEFORE THE SWEDE CAN  WE'RE IN A POWER POSITION    WE GRAB HIM</pattern><template>It's a double cross.   ...ransom him back, pick up that nut.   We're that much closer to doing our own thing.   Kidnapping?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT WE PUT A GUN TO YOUR HEAD</pattern><template>We've been through that already.</template></category><category><pattern>DROP THE GUN DOWN OR I'LL FUCKING DRAIN YOU</pattern><template>Put the gun down!</template></category><category><pattern>HE JUST SMASHED EVERYTHING</pattern><template>He wouldn't tell me why.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HELL  NO  THIS IS NICE</pattern><template>This is real nice! Play it up!</template></category><category><pattern>AND EVER SINCE THEN  LITTLE BOOGIE THERE HAS BEEN MAN OF THE HOUSE</pattern><template>I don't think that's been opened since my husband died.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE NOTICED A LOT OF ACTION ON THAT TABLE    COME ON  BILL</pattern><template>We just want to know what's going on.  You got some sultan.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T DO THAT  DAWG</pattern><template>What'd you say to Mecklen?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA GIVE THEM SPARAZZA AND THE WEST COAST SYNDICATE GIFT WRAPPED</pattern><template>Get it fucking done!  Listen to me, kid.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCKING KEVLAR  THE WAY I HAD TO STITCH IT  THIS SHIT IS ITCHY AS HELL</pattern><template>Let me ask you a question.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLER WAS BURIED BY THE AGENCY</pattern><template>Any time an operative failed, or was perceived to have failed, he was blackballed.</template></category><category><pattern>DEPUTY DIRECTOR LOCKE</pattern><template>Get that thing out of my face.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  WE JUST GOT TO KNOCK OFF A FEW MORE HOURS</pattern><template>These flowers have wilted.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOUR REASONS FOR DOING THAT ARE EXACTLY WHAT</pattern><template>That?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA PICK THEM DOWN THERE</pattern><template>In the elevator.</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL: NO  I TELL YOU SOMETHING  YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>Listen to me. Listen.  The deal is off in five minutes unless they give us something.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW YOU SAVED THIS BLACK MAN</pattern><template>Now all you got to be is grateful.</template></category><category><pattern>SPARAZZA'S HEALTH IS IN RAPID DECLINE AND BEFORE HE DIES  HE IS DEMANDING THE HEART OF HIS SWORN ENEMY</pattern><template>A recently opened million dollar escrow account has been traced back to Sparazza.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I ACCIDENTALLY SHOT AND KILLED MY BOY TODAY</pattern><template>If it gives you any comfort, you know, I was going in there to act a fool, baby.</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL ROLLED</pattern><template>He's giving them all up, isn't he?</template></category><category><pattern>BOTH THESE MOTHERFUCKERS IS FEDS</pattern><template>No. One of them is not.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHO ELSE HAS ACCESS TO THE FLOOR  BILL</pattern><template>I'm sorry. We're covering some very sensitive material here, and I've got to safeguard myself, so if you could just show me your ID again, get your clearance.</template></category><category><pattern>STRAPPED  WELL  SO  THEY GOT GUNS</pattern><template>What else? He drinks, you know. Self medicates.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON  MAN</pattern><template>And bones it.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  MAINTENANCE  I NEED SOMEBODY TO POWER UP THESE ELEVATORS IMMEDIATELY</pattern><template>I need to get Deputy Director Locke on a hard line as soon as possible.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT SAYS A WHOLE LOT ABOUT YOU   A HO  HO LOT</pattern><template>What up, G?</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME</pattern><template>...sell me off like a fucking field nigga...</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  FUCK THAT NIGGA  MAN</pattern><template>Anyway, we got each other.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Excuse me, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THAT  HUGO</pattern><template>You all right?</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK THE VITALS ON THIS GUY</pattern><template>Initiate all clear.</template></category><category><pattern>BULLSHIT</pattern><template>No, baby.</template></category><category><pattern>A SCUFFLE  A DONNYBROOK  YEAH</pattern><template>He had one of his men call a madam for another group of girls.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD TO SEE YOU</pattern><template>How you doing? Pete.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS DIEGO OR GARCIA</pattern><template>Yeah, run both those names through the DC database.</template></category><category><pattern>A MILLION DOLLAR HIT FEE WOULD DRAW SOME HUGE FLIES</pattern><template>And Acosta's pure mercenary.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW PROCEED TO THE FRONT IN AN ORDERLY FASHION  OR HOW THE FUCK Y'ALL WANT TO  BUT GET THE FUCK GOING</pattern><template>Let's go, step lively.</template></category><category><pattern>REMOVING A SLIGHT PIECE OF BONE IN MY CHIN I WILL ALTER MY JAW LINE</pattern><template>A procedure known as rhinoplasty will reduce the size of my nose.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE FINISHED</pattern><template>Look at my fucking face.</template></category><category><pattern>CARRUTHERS IS DEAD</pattern><template>Messner's unaccounted for.</template></category><category><pattern>MOTHER</pattern><template>Fuck!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WAIT  WAIT  WAIT  WAIT</pattern><template>The ho train has left the station.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THIS SHIT OFF</pattern><template>Move!</template></category><category><pattern>REPORTER: AS TO THE IDENTITY OF THE TWO BODIES     LOOK  IN LESS THAN AN HOUR  YOU'RE GONNA HAVE 40 TO 50 ODD FIELD AGENTS ARRIVING IN LAKE TAHOE WITHOUT THE SLIGHTEST CLUE AS TO WHY</pattern><template>We are instructed to take Israel into protective custody.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE TWO BEDS IN YOUR ROOM</pattern><template>No, no, we're not together. No.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOTTA</pattern><template>We gotta pack up.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SHE TOLD ME YOU  MORE OR LESS  HAVE A PLAN OF ATTACK</pattern><template>My associate, Mr. Serna, I can get him on the phone and if you could just speak to him and tell him your plan...</template></category><category><pattern>I AM  YES</pattern><template>Get the phone. It's probably Mecklen. Get Vitoli up here and start cleaning.</template></category><category><pattern>BUZZY  I'M UPSTAIRS</pattern><template>I can't talk very loud.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU SHOULDN'T BE FEELING ANY PAIN RIGHT NOW  OKAY</pattern><template>Hey, hey.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A DOUBLE CROSS       RANSOM HIM BACK  PICK UP THAT NUT    WE'RE THAT MUCH CLOSER TO DOING OUR OWN THING    KIDNAPPING</pattern><template>Can we bring this off?   Hey, we keep our mouth shut, play the part, nobody suspects a thing.   The old man's on the fade, Buzzy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S THAT MEDIC</pattern><template>Fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>THROW YOUR WEAPONS DOWN</pattern><template>Step out of the elevator!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S CORRECT</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>ISRAEL WANTED TO TOUCH SOMETHING REAL  SOMETHING DANGEROUS</pattern><template>But what he wound up doing was splitting the family into dual factions.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES THAT MEAN</pattern><template>It's bad for you.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO THAT DRUNK</pattern><template>Please forgive.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  GENTLEMEN  LET'S GET HIM UP ON THE ROOF</pattern><template>Get Mr. Israel up on the roof.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T SHOOT ME  PLEASE</pattern><template>He went this way! Please, don't shoot me. Don't shoot!</template></category><category><pattern>ALL BOGUS AND BAD INFORMATION THAT SET OFF A SERIES OF UNFORTUNATE EVENTS    HE'S GONNA CLIP ISRAEL</pattern><template>Buddy Israel.  Buddy Israel.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS CHRIST  BEANIE'S DEAD</pattern><template>You murdered Beanie.</template></category><category><pattern>GRANDMA WILL GET IT  GO ON</pattern><template>Little angel butt.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A NEW ONE I'M WORKING ON</pattern><template>Really getting the hairy eyeball off that guy.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU CHECKED THIS STUFF OUT YET</pattern><template>This is unbelievable.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE CLEAR</pattern><template>We're clear.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ELSE DID PADICHE SAY</pattern><template>He said the shit might get hot and might get heavy.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I WANT TO BE IN THAT PENTHOUSE A HALF A SECOND AFTER THIS DEAL IS DONE</pattern><template>We gonna get any guff from the hotel staff?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BABY</pattern><template>Don't fuck... What the...</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S ALL RIGHT  TELL HIM</pattern><template>This is good, though, what you're telling me. All right?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT THE  50 UP</pattern><template>Sure do.  What the fuck?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT HIM  WE GOT HIM</pattern><template>Here we go. Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHAT'S THE TIME FRAME</pattern><template>Fast as we can get you there.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME</pattern><template>That's good work.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  IT'S DISGUSTING</pattern><template>Thanks, God!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I BE OF ASSISTANCE   SOOT: MY NAME IS VITOLI</pattern><template>How can I be of assistance?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW</pattern><template>It's the way of the world!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S PROBABLY WHERE YOU HEARD THE SHOTS EARLIER</pattern><template>Somebody just deaded Israel's ass. It's a wrap.  I ain't come all this way just to pack it up because you thinking something up.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT FLOOR ARE THEY ON  RICKY</pattern><template>Okay, you know, that's one of our guys right over there.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  TROUBLES WITH THE LAW  DRUGS</pattern><template>Deal with the patients.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT CLEAR</pattern><template>Nobody gets in the hotel.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA GO IN  WE'RE GONNA GET THIS GUY  AND EVERYONE IS GONNA LEAVE THE THEATER GRINNING</pattern><template>No problem.</template></category><category><pattern>IN LESS THAN A MINUTE  YOU'RE GONNA ASPHYXIATE AND PASS OUT</pattern><template>But you shouldn't be feeling any pain right now, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>PEACE  BRO</pattern><template>Oh, fuck this.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SWEDE HAS ARRIVED    NO SHIT    THE OLD MAN SENT FOR HIM    SO GET YOURSELF ON A PLANE AND GET YOUR ASS TO LAKE TAHOE   ARE YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME</pattern><template>Fuck you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  SOMETHING SPECIAL</pattern><template>Nice shot.</template></category><category><pattern>GET IN THE VAN  MAN</pattern><template>Get in the van now!</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT SIX YEARS</pattern><template>Vice.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT YOUR CLOTHES ON  GIRL</pattern><template>You're acting like y'all on sundial. Y'all need to be on stopwatch.</template></category><category><pattern>COFFEE  ANYTHING</pattern><template>I don't want to order without...</template></category><category><pattern>'CAUSE OUTSIDE A GODDAMN DOG  THAT KIND OF LOYALTY  MY KIND OF SHIT  DON'T GET NO MORE DEDICATED OR DEVOUT</pattern><template>What are you trying to say?</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  RIP REED</pattern><template>Come in. Good. Good.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT YOURS</pattern><template>Put the fucking rabbit down.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OLD MAN'S IN BED    THE NURSE IS IN THERE  AND THEN SERNA IS SOMEWHERE IN THE HOUSE   WHO'S IN THE BACK</pattern><template>Who's in the back? Joe.</template></category><category><pattern>AND Y'ALL FOLLOW ME OVER TO THE HOTEL</pattern><template>Yeah, you want some of me?</template></category><category><pattern>A RECENTLY OPENED MILLION DOLLAR ESCROW ACCOUNT HAS BEEN TRACED BACK TO SPARAZZA</pattern><template>That, and the mention of this mysterious Swede makes the contract on Israel all the more real.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BET</pattern><template>So, Bill, if I'm getting this right, so you currently have the penthouse level under construction?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A JUNIOR SUITE IN VEGAS  SO  FUCK THIS AND THE FUCKING ANIMAL KINGDOM</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  MAN  STOP USING THAT FUCKING LOTION  MAN</pattern><template>You look like a damn Muppet.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DUG IT UP IN ARCHIVES AS PART OF THE SPARAZZA INVESTIGATION</pattern><template>Has anyone else seen this?</template></category><category><pattern>AND MY NAME     THAT'S HELLER</pattern><template>...will be Primo Sparazza.</template></category><category><pattern>NO MATTER HOW THEY MAKE THEIR LIVING</pattern><template>Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS REAL BRILLIANT</pattern><template>You're brilliant.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HURTING PRETTY BAD  HUH</pattern><template>I got shot twice.</template></category><category><pattern>IVY</pattern><template>So if you think I'm gonna let your little punk ass with the dirt I done...</template></category><category><pattern>SOME ASSHOLES ON THE ELEVATOR</pattern><template>Are these bitches on a permanent smoke break or what?</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU MADE ANOTHER DEAL  DIDN'T YOU</pattern><template>Israel's deal with the government was tossed out.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE FATHER AND SON</pattern><template>Israel's mother was 19   at the time when she and Sparazza had a brief affair   of which Israel was the byproduct.  That same year, she brought a paternity suit against him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU DOING  GIRL</pattern><template>Come on, man. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU SHUT THEM OFF</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT  COME ON</pattern><template>What's that in there...</template></category><category><pattern>NOSE  THREE TIMES</pattern><template>Eyes. Eyelids. Jaw.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA PACK IT UP</pattern><template>All right? Where is he?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ALL RIGHT  HUGO</pattern><template>He's fine.</template></category><category><pattern>JOE  ARE YOU GUYS SEEING ANYTHING</pattern><template>Because if you are, it's certainly not coming up here in the van and we'd certainly like to see what's going on.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOTTA PACK IT UP NOW</pattern><template>Bring him up here.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU WANT SOME OF ME</pattern><template>Yeah, just wait till we get outside!</template></category><category><pattern>JURISDICTION'S A NIGHTMARE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Anything more on Dupree's car?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS MAN IDENTIFIED HIMSELF AS A FEDERAL AGENT</pattern><template>Yeah, I mean, he had the badge and everything.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  SHITCAN THE CUE CARD RHETORIC AND TALK TO ME LIKE A MAN</pattern><template>You withheld information while Carruthers lay dying in vain and in the dark.</template></category><category><pattern>SYKES: BRING IT   GET THE FUCK DOWN</pattern><template>Get down!</template></category><category><pattern>BATTERY'S COMPLETELY DEAD</pattern><template>Forget it. You won't get a signal in here.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YO  BEANIE</pattern><template>Hey, ladies. Get up.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OTHER HAS SEVERE HYPOTHERMIA  POSSIBLE DEMENTIA  AND WILL PROBABLY BE A MULTIPLE AMPUTEE BY WEEK'S END</pattern><template>Shit, okay. You're right.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HEARD ABOUT THAT TRIAD HIT  THE WORK Y'ALL PUT IN</pattern><template>And they recognize the skills.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  BAR FIGHTERS AND BIG  SWINGING DICKS  TAKING CARE OF SHIT</pattern><template>You know, sadly, this is it.</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH WHO YOUR SUPERIOR IS  PAL</pattern><template>STEVE: Serna just picked up the house phone.   AGENT 2: He's on the phone now. He is on the phone.</template></category><category><pattern>I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE EYEBALLING ME  DAWG</pattern><template>I don't like punk bitches eyeballing me.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T HAVE TO FILL UP THE WHOLE BLACKBOARD AFTER ALL</pattern><template>Do me a favor, will you?</template></category><category><pattern>AM I STANDING HERE</pattern><template>Your attitude is fucking horrible.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH FLOOR SECURITY WAS ON</pattern><template>And then later I saw him get on the elevator with the other agent.</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN IT  I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW FUCKED UP I WAS TILL I JUST SAW YOUR ASS  GIRL</pattern><template>You went from Beyonc to Bigfoot in less than six fucking hours.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOTTA GET PACKED UP</pattern><template>We're gonna pack it up.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  DAMN</pattern><template>All right, then.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR PLANS</pattern><template>What you got in mind?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GONNA GET ANY GUFF FROM THE HOTEL STAFF</pattern><template>Israel's obviously paid them off.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE</pattern><template>My debriefing.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT YOUR FUCKING HANDS IN THE AIR</pattern><template>Throw your weapons down!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST BE OUT OF YOUR FUCKING MIND</pattern><template>If you...</template></category><category><pattern>OR IS HIS ULTIMATE WORTH BULLSHIT</pattern><template>Utterly useless?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S VERY SIMPLE  GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>We can't allow that to happen.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  'CAUSE Y'ALL MUST BE BURNING SHEETS BY THE TON</pattern><template>Well...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS YOU DOING HERE  ANYWAY</pattern><template>We was after some fool named Israel.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT FOR REAL</pattern><template>You go in and pull him out.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WAY IT'S ALWAYS GONNA BE</pattern><template>Okay, now.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I BE OF ASSISTANCE    BRAVO    (GUN FIRING)   MY NAME IS VITOLI</pattern><template>How can I be of assistance?  SOOT: My name is Vitoli.</template></category><category><pattern>COPS GET CURIOUS  THEY START CAMPING OUT AND EVERYTHING GOES SIDEWAYS  REAL FUCKING QUICK    PEOPLE GET PINCHED  SNITCHES SNITCH    THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW  BUDDY ISRAEL HAS BROUGHT THE HEAT TO BEAR  ON NONE OTHER THAN MR  PRIMO SPARAZZA HIMSELF</pattern><template>Enforcer, extortionist, killer.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DON'T RESPECT US</pattern><template>Yeah, we just meat for male consumption.</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK YOUR FIRE   CLEAR ON MY MARK</pattern><template>Shar. Shar seven,  I'm pinched.   Bring some heavy shit.  Fire from the sky. My count.</template></category><category><pattern>WANTS TO LIVE THE MOB LIFE FOR REAL   BANKROLLS A COUPLE OF B&amp;ES</pattern><template>Rich folks.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  NOW</pattern><template>Peace, bro.</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL NOW</pattern><template>Heller's op predated the second World War.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR BOY VERY WELL MIGHT HAVE BEEN ONE OF THEM</pattern><template>I probably would've busted on you, too.</template></category><category><pattern>I FUCKED UP</pattern><template>I got three coming down now.  Go! Move. Move.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU KNOW  THAT'S ONE OF OUR GUYS RIGHT OVER THERE</pattern><template>Excuse me?</template></category><category><pattern>WORD IS SOOT IS WORKING FOR ONE OF THEM</pattern><template>Now, they don't know where he's from, how long he's been in the game,   or even what he looks like.   But when Soot decides to move on somebody,   they're the last ones to see it coming.   DUPREE: So, there it is.  The bond on Buddy Israel expires in 18 hours.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HEARD FROM THAT NIGGA  KEITH</pattern><template>Or he still fucking with that little light skinned girl?  I ain't trying to break a sweat off of that motherfucker.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A TWO MAN OPERATION</pattern><template>What you're describing now is a much larger movement.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN  MAN</pattern><template>We got it, we got 'em, we got 'em.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SO  EARLIER  THERE WAS THAT GUY  CARRUTHERS</pattern><template>Yeah, Agent Carruthers.</template></category><category><pattern>BEANS</pattern><template>Bag them and get some more on deck, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE ROOM  MAKE ROOM  PLEASE</pattern><template>We'll have to go all the way around to the other side.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED  NICE AND SLOW</pattern><template>Yeah, so, earlier, there was that guy, Carruthers...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GONNA KILL ISRAEL TO SAVE SPARAZZA</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>HEARD ABOUT THAT DINNER CLUB IN CLEVELAND</pattern><template>That got squat fucked, shot to shit, slashed and burned?   What happened?   Well, the Tremor Brothers go rip shit riot on the whole fucking place.   Seven dead, 28 wounded.   Just to get this one fucking guy.   In the course of the melee, one of them gets shot in the neck. He passes out.   Another one catches blowback from a jammed piece.   He's temporarily blinded.   Third one gets a bullet lodged in his back, he can't walk.   They're speed freak, neo Nazi assholes who read and recite   Mein Kampf like it was Mother Goose.  They're meaner than shit, they're dumber than hell and these motherfuckers will go megaton at the drop of a hat.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  I'M STILL TRYING TO GET THE DOWN LOW FROM THIS CAT PADICHE</pattern><template>What we got right now is a number and a name.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO GO BACK TO WASHINGTON</pattern><template>What the hell happened here?</template></category><category><pattern>FRONTS SOME SMASH AND GRABS  PAWN SHOPS  JEWELRY STORES  THAT KIND OF THING</pattern><template>Then he gets his dick wet.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GIVING UP MY BOYS AND YOU FUCKING KNOW THAT</pattern><template>I gave you Sparazza.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T SEE YOU NOW   ARE YOU NERVOUS</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE: HE IS ON THE PHONE</pattern><template>Do you guys have any transmission?   He's on the phone.  Quiet, quiet. We got it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FUCKED UP</pattern><template>You're fucked up, Ivy!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TELL ME SOMETHING  IS HE THE ROSETTA STONE THAT'S GOING TO BLOW THE LID OFF THE LAST 60 YEARS</pattern><template>Possibly.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LOOK UP  HEY  MAN</pattern><template>That's not yours.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE HAVE TO GIVE THEM SOMEONE   GIVE THEM HUGO  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>I can take that because he needs that regimented prison shit that they'll give him.</template></category><category><pattern>SLOWLY AMASSING THE LOYALTIES OF SPARAZZA'S TOP MEN    WITH THE IDEA OF TOPPLING THE THRONE   YOU KNOW  I'VE SEEN SOME STUPID MOVES  BUT</pattern><template>Well, you spend your life pulling rabbits out of hats and sawing people in half, anything seems possible.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ALL THE LOVE WE EVER GONNA NEED    FEEL ME    YOU FEEL ME  GIRL   OH  WAIT A MINUTE</pattern><template>I think the ho train just arrived.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I'VE ALWAYS BEEN SAYING  LET'S MAKE THE FUCKING DEAL</pattern><template>You see, this is one of them rare moments where your ass get a chance to be completely honest.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE GUYS GOT SOME BALLS</pattern><template>Do they ever.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BAD FOR YOU</pattern><template>It causes Alzheimer's.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME FIGURE OUT</pattern><template>What the fuck...</template></category><category><pattern>RICH FOLKS</pattern><template>Fronts some smash and grabs, pawn shops, jewelry stores, that kind of thing.</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON  NOW  SHUG</pattern><template>Anytime, anytime, fag.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S WHAT YOU DID</pattern><template>If you thought old man Primo could twist your shit up,  wait till you see what I'm about to do here.  I don't believe this.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOING TO TELL ME WHY NO CALL WAS MADE TO INFORM US THAT THE ISRAEL SITUATION HAD BEEN ALTERED</pattern><template>Why I and my friend and partner, whose body is going into a furnace tomorrow, were never fucking contacted.</template></category><category><pattern>AM I REALLY DYING</pattern><template>Bill.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HIM</pattern><template>And my name...  That's Heller.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU READY   HERE'S THE PUNCH LINE</pattern><template>One million flat.  Holy shit.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE FORGIVE</pattern><template>Let's get to the business at hand.</template></category><category><pattern>MY GRANDMOTHER</pattern><template>I swear to God, my grandmother told me.</template></category><category><pattern>MESSNER: THEN WE LOSE OUR WITNESS   AND WE LOSE OUR CASE</pattern><template>Now, Israel's manager, a man by the name of Morris Mecklen,  has guaranteed us that Israel will enter into protective custody   once the government has approved his deal.   Now, we've been monitoring Mecklen's phone calls,  and we've learned that Israel is at the penthouse level of the Nomad Hotel and Casino in Lake Tahoe, Nevada.</template></category><category><pattern>COME IN  GOOD  GOOD</pattern><template>Great. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>ASSUME I ALREADY KNOW</pattern><template>What do you see right now?</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU LIKE  I SEND OUT</pattern><template>To what? Incinerate?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  YOU WITH ME</pattern><template>You with me, baby? Huh?</template></category><category><pattern>SKANK ASS BITCHES   BUT THAT'S THE ROLE YOU WANTED TO PLAY</pattern><template>Yeah, that says a whole lot about you.  A ho, ho lot.</template></category><category><pattern>LADIES AND GENTLEMEN  THERE'S A GUY    HE IS ONE OF THE BIGGEST STARS IN THE WORLD    AND WE ARE THRILLED TO HAVE HIM STOP BY    AND HE'S WON ALL KINDS OF AWARDS    HE HAS WON ENTERTAINER OF THE YEAR   EVERY YEAR IN LAS VEGAS FOR THE LAST FIVE YEARS    LADIES AND GENTLEMEN  WOULD YOU GIVE A BIG ROUND OF APPLAUSE    A BIG LAS VEGAS WELCOME  TO A GREAT LAS VEGAS STAR   AND HIS NAME IS MR  BUDDY ISRAEL    COME ON OUT HERE    DUPREE: BUDDY  ACES  ISRAEL   CARD SHARP  ILLUSIONIST</pattern><template>Asshole.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW YOU LEFT A MESSAGE</pattern><template>What did you say?</template></category><category><pattern>HIS LITTLE CRIMINAL FORAY SHINES A FLOODLIGHT ON THE ENTIRE CARLOTTA ORGANIZATION</pattern><template>Cops get curious, they start camping out and everything goes sideways  real fucking quick.   People get pinched, snitches snitch.   The next thing you know, Buddy Israel has brought the heat to bear  on none other than Mr. Primo Sparazza himself.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT CAN BE A CHORE</pattern><template>I'll bet.</template></category><category><pattern>EASTERN EUROPEAN JIZZ</pattern><template>That looks like some fuckhead shot his load on a $12,000 calfskin jacket!</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'LL BE FLYING TO LOS ANGELES TO FINALIZE ISRAEL'S DEAL</pattern><template>No former witness against the mob has been as crucial or as important  as Buddy  Aces  Israel.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS  WHAT FOR    HE'S BEEN SNITCHING TO THE WORLD</pattern><template>I can't even blame Primo.   You know, he's old school Sicilian.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THE DATE OF THE FIRST PROCEDURE</pattern><template>Fifteen separate procedures since 1952.</template></category><category><pattern>USED TO BE WITH THE PD DOWN THERE</pattern><template>Agent Messner, we recovered the car.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED SOMEBODY OVER AT TABLE 12</pattern><template>A little blue haired lady there who's rolled about 14 times. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WITH ME  BABY  HUH</pattern><template>We're almost home.</template></category><category><pattern>I APPRECIATE IT</pattern><template>I'm babbling.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT A TRANSPLANT  AREN'T YOU</pattern><template>You're talking about a fucking heart transplant.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOOT  I APPRECIATE THAT  MAN</pattern><template>If I needed your car and me and my brothers were wanted by the law, I would've killed you to get it, too.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN TAKE THAT BECAUSE HE NEEDS THAT REGIMENTED PRISON SHIT THAT THEY'LL GIVE HIM</pattern><template>It's bigger than that.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A MINUTE</pattern><template>What other agent?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THEN QUIT ACTING LIKE SOMEONE TOOK A SHIT IN YOUR CEREAL BOWL  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Reed paid us 50 grand.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M BABBLING</pattern><template>I do that drunk.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY ON IT  STAY ALERT</pattern><template>AGENT 1: Hey, yo, Mike, where are you, man?</template></category><category><pattern>I AIN'T TRYING TO BE UP HERE ALL DAY</pattern><template>And I tell you what.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LINE'S CLEAN    STEVE: DO YOU GUYS HAVE ANY SIGNAL OUT THERE   YEAH  WE GOT IT</pattern><template>Please stay off the walkies.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL HAVE THE ELEVATORS TAKEN OFFLINE  SIR</pattern><template>LOCKE: Pasquale Acosta.   Blood money mercenary.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  BABY</pattern><template>You know I'm playing with your pretty ass.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT WELL  JUST STAY AWAKE  GUYS</pattern><template>Stay on it. Stay alert.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  I SPOKE TO LORETTA THIS MORNING</pattern><template>And she told me you, more or less, have a plan of attack.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  I KNOW WHERE ISRAEL IS  OKAY</pattern><template>So we have maybe a day before that location that I know gets grapevined and the whole fucking world gets hip to this.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO KEEP AN EYE ON HER  THAT'S ALL</pattern><template>It's got to be frustrating.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU HEARING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>There was something about some faggot ass fed being up in the building.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GET ON A JET BACK TO DC AND MAKE NO FURTHER INQUIRY INTO THIS MATTER</pattern><template>Is that understood, Agent Messner?</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED COHESION TO MOVE FORWARD SON  NOT</pattern><template>Oh, shitcan the cue card rhetoric and talk to me like a man.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YOU TELL ME WHAT THAT IS</pattern><template>About what?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  LET'S GO</pattern><template>Has Mecklen called?</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY SHIT</pattern><template>These guys want him bad.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BIGGER THAN THAT</pattern><template>They want everybody.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU SHAKING FOR  MAN</pattern><template>But it's all good, right?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU GOT IN MIND</pattern><template>Pussy.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GIVING THEM ALL UP  ISN'T HE</pattern><template>His entire entourage.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS WE BOTH GOT BEAT OUT THEN  DIDN'T WE</pattern><template>Yeah, goddamn.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU AIN'T GONNA BELIEVE THIS SHIT</pattern><template>Both these motherfuckers is feds.</template></category><category><pattern>SON OF A BITCH</pattern><template>The Justice lawyers sign off?</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF MY FUCKING SIGHT</pattern><template>Yes, sir. Go ahead.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM NOT GIVING UP MY BOYS</pattern><template>And they are bricking us...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT YOUR CASINO FLOOR  COUNT ROOM SURVEILLANCE  THEN YOU GOT YOUR GENERAL SECURITY</pattern><template>But I guess your friend don't want to hear this.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MESSNER</pattern><template>Yeah. Who's this?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL BULLSHIT</pattern><template>You know that, Hugo.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED ABOUT TWO MINUTES</pattern><template>...which floor security was on.</template></category><category><pattern>HUGO  YOU'RE STARING AT ME LIKE I JUST ASKED YOU FOR THE FUCKING SQUARE ROOT OF SOMETHING</pattern><template>What did you say to Mecklen on the little motherfucking machine?</template></category><category><pattern>VEGAS LOUNGE ACT TURNS LEGITIMATE THUG</pattern><template>Truth is, Buddy don't know the fucking ball from the bounce.  What do you got?</template></category><category><pattern>GOODBYE</pattern><template>Good luck.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  THERE'S A PAIR OF BROADS I THINK MIGHT BE VERY GOOD FOR THIS   WHICH BROADS</pattern><template>They're reliable?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST IN TERMS OF THE MEN THAT ARE UP THERE NOW  MY TEAM  SERVING LUNCH AND DINNER AND JUST GENERALLY DOING UPKEEP</pattern><template>I'm not clear on the table.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD</pattern><template>Skank ass bitches.  But that's the role you wanted to play.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU COOK UP THIS LITTLE CONSTRUCTION THING</pattern><template>Is this a...</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  WE'LL BE AWAITING WORD   ALL RIGHT  WE GOT TIME</pattern><template>Want to go grab something to eat?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO</pattern><template>But that definitely sounds like gunshots, and I don't know where it's coming from.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY</pattern><template>Close your eyes.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOT PULL   SO HE STARTS TO MAKE PLAYS</pattern><template>Wants to live the mob life for real.  Bankrolls a couple of B&amp;Es.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS ENTIRE ENTOURAGE</pattern><template>He doesn't have a friend in the world. We got to move.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT    IT'S QUIET    SO  YOU'RE NOT SEEING ANYTHING    NO SIGNS OF TROUBLE  NOBODY LURKING  NO THREATS  NOTHING    ABSOLUTELY NO</pattern><template>We got nothing to worry about.   Israel's in the penthouse now, right?   Yeah. I guess he's been holed up there for a week or so.   How are we on time?</template></category></AIML>