<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>HE TURNED ON ME  TOTAL STREET BULLY  IN MY FACE  SCREAM</pattern><template>We wer... and I went crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MINUTE YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOU CAN POKE LIFE AND ACTUALLY SOMETHING WILL</pattern><template>You know, if you push in, something will pop out the other side, you can you can change it, you can mold it, um, that's the most important thing.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S 4</pattern><template>And maybe more, I don't know, but certainly those 4, and if you compare him with Edison, well, there was the electric power industry, the motion picture industry, and the music industry.</template></category><category><pattern>WAYNE MAY NOT BE BITTER  BUT HE WASN'T THE ONLY EARLY APPLE EMPLOYEE WHO MADE A LIFE DECISION MOST OF US WOULD REGRET</pattern><template>The funny thing is that Steve Jobs hired me, and he said... he had hair just down to his waist at the time, and as I recall he only ate fruit, and he said,  we don't have very much loot, so we'd like to pay you in stock.  I held out for the cash.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE STARTED A COMPANY CALLED NEXT TO DO A COMPUTER THAT WAS GONNA BE WHAT HE THOUGHT APPLE SHOULD HAVE BEEN</pattern><template>Uh, to aim it at the education market because they...</template></category><category><pattern>AS THE WORLD MOURNED  THE MOST FITTING TRIBUTE CAME FROM ONE OF STEVE JOBS' YOUNG FANS</pattern><template>19 year old Hong Kong based design student Jonathan Mak Long created an image on his Mac that went viral around the world.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANTED IT TO HAPPEN SO BADLY  I GAVE THIS COMPUTER AWAY</pattern><template>I gave away the listings, no copyright notices, no nothing, and then Steve Jobs came and saw the interest, and he said  why don't we start a company to make some money?  And I said,  fine.  They did want to start a business.</template></category><category><pattern>MOST POIGNANTLY HE WAS ASKED WHAT THE NEXT FEW YEARS MIGHT HOLD</pattern><template>The future is long.</template></category><category><pattern>THE RESULTING FONTS APPEARED NOT JUST ON MACS BUT ULTIMATELY PCS  TOO  DRAMATICALLY IMPROVING THE USER EXPERIENCE BUT NOT FOR ROBERT</pattern><template>I never touch computers.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALLY DON'T CARE THAT WE WERE FAMOUS AND SUCCESSFUL</pattern><template>We're not anymore, and this is where we're starting from, and this is where we're moving.  And so when you see the second coming of Steve Jobs and Apple, Apple went from being a wide open and wacky company to be a very disciplined company that understood its financials at a level that few companies do.</template></category><category><pattern>TRAGICALLY THAT  ONE MORE THING  HAS NOW BECOME  ONE LAST THING   THE NEWS THAT STEVE JOBS HAD FINALLY LOGGED OUT MADE HEADLINES EVERYWHERE</pattern><template>This man really had changed the world.</template></category><category><pattern>REED COLLEGE HAS ONE OF THE BEST CALLIGRAPHY COURSES IN THE U S</pattern><template>His teacher had a major impact on his aesthetic and the clean lines of his products.</template></category><category><pattern>HE COULD THINK QUITE INTELLIGENTLY ABOUT THE FUTURE  BUT THE WAY MICROSOFT WORKED AS A BUSINESS WAS FAR MORE INCREMENTAL THAN APPLE</pattern><template>All the while, they were working on some big leap, and Microsoft tended to do the incremental stuff almost all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IN 1985 AT THE AGE OF 30  HIS CHARMED RUN OF LUCK WAS ABOUT TO COME TO AN ABRUPT HALT</pattern><template>Seeking someone to help run his rapidly expanding business, he hired in Pepsi executive John Sculley.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAD RECENTLY RETURNED FROM INDIA</pattern><template>He's way ahead of his time.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE WHILE  THEY WERE WORKING ON SOME BIG LEAP  AND MICROSOFT TENDED TO DO THE INCREMENTAL STUFF ALMOST ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>What's Steve's done is quite phenomenal.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  STEVE JOBS WAS SO IMPRESSED WITH MY DIPLOMACY IN THAT PARTICULAR SITUATION THAT HE IMMEDIATELY CAME BACK AND SAID   OK  WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO IS FORM A COMPANY   WITH WOZ AND JOBS GETTING 45% EACH  AND I WOULD GET 10% AS A TIEBREAKER IN THE EVENT OF ANY PHILOSOPHICAL DISPUTES THAT MIGHT OCCUR IN THE FUTURE</pattern><template>10% of Apple today would be worth $37,631,420,312.42, but despite his share in the company, Ron was worried that working with Jobs and Woz might prove to be too stressful.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY KNEW THAT THEY COULDN'T DO IT ON THEIR OWN</pattern><template>They sought out older people to help, and Steve Jobs in particular was quite persuasive.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GREAT WITH ATTRACTING AND MOTIVATING THE BEST OF THE BEST PEOPLE</pattern><template>He's great at encouraging men to be creative and come up with new ideas and not just be little robots, which many big companies just want you to be a little robot and do what you're told to do, and the last thing they want to hear from you is a creative idea.</template></category><category><pattern>EVENTUALLY I SORT OF BECAME AWARE THAT THERE WERE SOME PEOPLE WHO'D COME IN TO THE ROOM  AND I LOOKED OVER MY SHOULDER  AND THERE WAS ANDY WARHOL</pattern><template>So there was this great moment that I'll never forget.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ACTUALLY CHANGED THE THAT WAY WE COMMUNICATE</pattern><template>When you grow up, you tend to get told that the world is the way it is and your life is just to live your life inside the world, try not to bash into the walls too much, try to have a nice family life, have fun, save a little money.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I USED THE BUTTER DISH  THE ROLL ON BALL AND WAS ABLE TO CREATE A PROTOTYPE</pattern><template>It's hard to believe that in a design so small as something that fits in your hand there could be much controversy around it, but it turns out there was one major controversy, which was how many buttons should there be?</template></category><category><pattern>THE LAST FEW YEARS HAVE REMINDED ME THAT LIFE IS FRAGILE UM  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Finally he withdrew from public life.</template></category><category><pattern>PRESIDENT JOHN SCULLEY ADMITS APPLE WILL BE JUST ANOTHER PERSONAL COMPUTER COMPANY UNLESS MACINTOSH BECOMES AN INDUSTRY MILESTONE IN THE N NT 100 DAYS</pattern><template>There was kind of a love affair at the beginning.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST MESSED AROUND ON MY COMPUTER  AND IT JUST HAPPENED</pattern><template>It made sense to incorporate his silhouette, his profile into the logo.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DID NOT</pattern><template>Nobody diddled me out of anything.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU GROW UP  YOU TEND TO GET TOLD THAT THE WORLD IS THE WAY IT IS  AND YOUR    YOUR LIFE IS JUST TO LIVE YOUR LIFE INSIDE THE WORLD  TRY NOT TO BASH INTO THE WALLS TOO MUCH  TRY TO HAVE A NICE FAMILY LIFE  HAVE FUN  SAVE A LITTLE MONEY</pattern><template>In this exclusive, never before seen interview, Steve Jobs gave a rare glimpse of his vision of the world.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS STEVE JOBS</pattern><template>I'd give a lot to have Steve Jobs' taste.</template></category><category><pattern>APPLE HAD HAD CONSPICUOUS SUCCESS IN EDUCATION</pattern><template>There were some people he could steal from Apple to market to that segment, and he thought starting small made sense.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TRUTH ABOUT BILL GATES IS A BRILLIANT MAN WHO YOU COULD    AND I DID TALK TO FOR LONG PERIODS ABOUT THE FUTURE</pattern><template>He could think quite intelligently about the future, but the way Microsoft worked as a business was far more incremental than Apple.</template></category><category><pattern>I ILL DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Something broke.</template></category><category><pattern>HE INVESTED $5 MILLION CAPITAL IN A CORPORATION CALLED PIXAR  AND HE TOOK 70% OF THE COMPANY  AND THE EMPLOYEES TOOK 30%</pattern><template>Steve kept investing because we would run out of money and he did not want to be embarrassed by failure after having been booted out of Apple, so he would put more money in and take more equity away from the employees.</template></category><category><pattern>APPLE LITERALLY WAS FAILING WHEN STEVE WENT BACK AND RE INFUSED THE INNOVATION AND RISK TAKING THAT HAVE BEEN PHENOMENAL</pattern><template>So the industry has benefited immensely from his work.</template></category><category><pattern>I MARCHED PAST HIM AND I WROTE ON THE WHITEBOARD  AND HE SAID   Y Y YOU CAN'T DO THAT</pattern><template>And I said,  what? Write on a whiteboard?  And he stormed out of the room, and then I was in shock for the next week or moths.</template></category><category><pattern>DROPPING OUT OF COLLEGE  JOBS WENT ON THE HIPPIE TRAIL  TRAVELING TO INDIA AND STUDYING BUDDHISM  THIS ALSO HAD AN IMPACT ON HIS WORK AT APPLE</pattern><template>I first met Steve in 1975.</template></category><category><pattern>UM  THEY BOTH HAVE THEIR MOMENTS</pattern><template>Bill Gates is a a better friend than Steve Jobs, but Steve Jobs is more fun than Bill Gates.</template></category><category><pattern>IN 1984  THEY VISITED THE HOME OF YOKO ONO FOR THE NINTH BIRTHDAY PARTY OF SEAN  HER SON WITH JOHN LENNON</pattern><template>Jobs took along a birthday gift that fascinated not only Sean but the whole star studded guest list.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH I HATE  UNSPOKEN RULES</pattern><template>That only he could sit in front of the whiteboard and only he could use it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE SCREAMING AT EACH OTHER IN FULL BULL RAGE WITH OUR FACES ABOUT THAT FAR APART  AND DURING THAT</pattern><template>So he was insulting my southwestern accent.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST THE SMOOTH LINES OF IT</pattern><template>And his achievements...</template></category><category><pattern>THE CONFERENCE ROOMS INSTEAD OF  YOU KNOW  OF NUMBER 103C WERE CALLED DA VINCI AND MICHELANGELO AND PICASSO  AND INDEED IT WAS PICASSO THAT I WAS ESCORTED TO TO SEE JOBS FOR THE FIRST TIME</pattern><template>As the two got Toto know each other, Sheff realized he had a front row seat on what was then an unimaginable technological future.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I WAS HAVING A HARD TIME  WE'D BE ON THE PHONE  HE'D DRIVE UP FROM SILICON VALLEY  TAKE ME OUT TO DINNER  HANG OUT  AND TAKE WALKS WITH ME  AND  UM  THAT'S PRETTY RARE</pattern><template>In 1984, they visited the home of Yoko Ono for the ninth birthday party of Sean, her son with John Lennon.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT JOBS' INFLUENCE ON THE MUSIC INDUSTRY WENT FAR BEYOND SIMPLE STAR MAKING</pattern><template>Way before iTunes, Steve Jobs has been a part of music because every major studio has a Mac computer in it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THERE USED TO BE A WAY TO FOOL THE ENTIRE TELEPHONE SYSTEM INTO THINKING YOU WERE A TELEPHONE COMPUTER</pattern><template>You could, you know, call from a pay phone, go to white plains, new York, take a satellite to Europe take a cable to turkey, um, come back to Los Angeles, and you'd go around the world 3 or 4 times and call the payphone next door, shout in the phone, and be about 30 seconds, it would come out the other phone.</template></category><category><pattern>IN ADDITION TO WALKING AND TALKING</pattern><template>Doing electronics projects together.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SOUGHT OUT OLDER PEOPLE TO HELP  AND STEVE JOBS IN PARTICULAR WAS QUITE PERSUASIVE</pattern><template>In Apple's earliest days, the two Steves, Jobs and Woz, took on an older and more experienced partner.</template></category><category><pattern>DESPITE THEIR RIVALRY  IN THIS JOINT APPEARANCE AFTER JOBS HAD BEEN DIAGNOSED WITH CANCER  THEY DISPLAYED A HEALTHY RESPECT AND EVEN AFFECTION FOR ONE ANOTHER</pattern><template>I think of most things in life as either a Bob Dylan or Beatles song, but there's that one line in that one Beatles song,  you and I have memories longer than the road that stretches out ahead,  and that's clearly true here.</template></category><category><pattern>A 1979 DEAL GAVE HIM ACCESS TO XEROX TECHNOLOGY  ONE THING BLEW HIM AWAY  A PROTOTYPE MOUSE</pattern><template>He gave his own team orders to make one, only better.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FACTS ARE THE STORY OF HIS LIFE  THE STORY OF HIS SUCCESSES  THE STORY OF HIS ACHIEVEMENTS  THE STORIES OF THE GREAT THINGS HE DID FOR OTHER PEOPLE CONTINUE TO GO ON BECAUSE THAT'S GOOD FOR OUR COUNTRY  IT'S GOOD FOR THE NATION  IT'S GOOD FOR THE WORLD  AND IT'S ALSO GOOD FOR THE PEOPLE</pattern><template>Of course, that's what it's all about.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS CERTAINLY A TECHNO VISIONARY  BUT THE KEY TO HIS GREATNESS IS TO SEE HOW BROAD HE THOUGHT</pattern><template>He was obsessed with design, with elegant design, and he was obsessed with the overall experience of technology and the idea of creativity generally.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HIS ACHIEVEMENTS</pattern><template>He is going to inspire a whole new generation.</template></category><category><pattern>IN ABOUT EIGHTH GRADE  HALFWAY THROUGH  THIS NEW GUY CAME INTO THE SCHOOL  WHO WAS STEVE JOBS  AND WE WERE BOTH INTROVERTED  INTELLECTUAL  KIND OF SOCIALLY INEPT  AND WE GRAVITATED TOWARDS EACH OTHER</pattern><template>The two boys shared the same hobby.</template></category><category><pattern>PC GUY IS WHAT MAKES IT ALL WORK ACTUALLY</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAS NATURAL</pattern><template>It's not a joke at all.</template></category><category><pattern>250 MILLION OR A BILLION OR HOWEVER MANY IPODS ARE OUT THERE ARE WHAT BUILT THE APPLE OF TODAY  NOT THE MAC</pattern><template>Approaching the age of 50, barely a quarter of a century after making his first million greenbacks, Jobs was worth $2.3 billion.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  STEVE REALLY TRUSTED HIM AND REALLY SAW A KINDRED SPIRIT  SOMEONE WHO WOULD HELP HIM BUILD APPLE</pattern><template>His love was Apple.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEMBER THAT WARHOL WOULD PICK UP THE MOUSE  AND INSTEAD OF GLIDING IT ALONG THE FLOOR  THE TILED FLOOR IN SEAN'S BEDROOM  HE WOULD SORT OF PICK IT UP AND WAS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO MAKE IT WORK  AND STEVE VERY PATIENTLY WOULD SORT OF LOWER HIS HAND DOWN AND SAY   NO  YOU KIND OF PUSH IT ALONG   SO ANDY SORT OF FOOLED AROUND WITH IT  AND HE WAS COMPLETELY MESMERIZED</pattern><template>I mean, when he zoned in on something, the rest of the world disappeared, and that was what it was like watching warhol in front of a macintosh for the first time.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WILL BE REGARDED AS THE PERSON WHO UNLOCKED THE CREATIVITY OF A WHOLE GENERATION</pattern><template>He's changed the way we look at computers, phones, how we share, interact.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE WAS NEVER FIRED FROM APPLE  BUT HE WAS OSTRACIZED AND DEMOTED AND PUT IN AN OFFICE IN AN EMPTY BUILDING  AND AFTER THAT HE</pattern><template>He resigned in 1985 and then immediately sold his more than 6 million shares...</template></category><category><pattern>THE NEXT DAY  HIS CLOSEST FRIEND AND COLLEAGUE STEVE WOZNIAK PAID HIS OWN TRIBUTE</pattern><template>I'm going to miss the chance to go to him and just sit down and share just person to person.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING BROKE</pattern><template>And during this face off...</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE LAST THING HE SAID TO ME WAS  YOU KNOW  WALT  YOU AND I HAVE BEEN  THROUGH LOTS OF ADVENTURES OVER THE LAST 15 YEARS  AND WE'RE GOING TO HAVE SOME MORE ADVENTURES TO COME   WE NEVER DID</pattern><template>On October 5, 2011, Steve Jobs died.</template></category><category><pattern>LATER STEVE TOLD ME IT WAS ONE OF THE FIRST TIMES HE'D WATCHED A CHILD WITH A MAC</pattern><template>Eventually I sort of became aware that there were some people who'd come in to the room, and I looked over my shoulder, and there was Andy warhol.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THERE WERE STILL PEOPLE WILLING TO BACK HIM WITH HARD CASH</pattern><template>One of them was self made texan billionaire and former presidential candidate Ross Perot.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE HIPPIES  AND THERE ARE NERDS  AND JOBS WAS DEFINITELY THE HIPPIE  AND WOZ WAS THE NERD</pattern><template>And the hippie has the grand vision, and the nerd is able to realize the vision.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD LOOK AT MY EMPLOYEES LOOKING AT STEVE  AND I REALIZED THEY'RE IN LOVE</pattern><template>They're just looking up at him with big Doe eyes just soaking in everything he's saying as if it was true, and it wasn't.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S STEVE'S DONE IS QUITE PHENOMENAL</pattern><template>His ability to always come around and figure out where that next bet should be has been phenomenal.</template></category><category><pattern>ZEN REPRESENTS THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THINGS  THINGS OF THE WORLD</pattern><template>In zen, it's expressed in the art.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS CHARACTER</pattern><template>Steve loved those creative ideas.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS ALWAYS SO EXCITED ABOUT EVERYTHING  AND WE WENT TO MOVIES TOGETHER  AND WE WENT TO THE OPERA TOGETHER  AND HE COULD TALK ABOUT EVERYTHING  AND HE WAS THIS INCREDIBLY GIVING  LOYAL FRIEND</pattern><template>When I was having a hard time, we'd be on the phone, he'd drive up from silicon valley, take me out to dinner, hang out, and take walks with me, and, um, that's pretty rare.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  TO AIM IT AT THE EDUCATION MARKET BECAUSE THEY</pattern><template>Apple had had conspicuous success in education.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS ASTONISHING</pattern><template>Steve Jobs created the most respected brand in the world and shook up a whole industry, and he did it with a lot of panache and style, and, you know, great respect for him for it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE YESTERDAY'S NEWS</pattern><template>He was conquering the world of music.</template></category><category><pattern>AS FAR AS WOZNIAK WAS CONCERNED  THE WORLD WAS A GREAT BIG SAND BOX WITH A LOT OF TOYS TO PLAY WITH</pattern><template>But Ron's opinion of Steve Jobs was not so hot.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS ALWAYS THINKING ABOUT CERTAIN TECHNOLOGY  THE EARLY PRODUCTS THAT GOT DEVELOPED  THE BUILDING PARTS  WHAT THOSE MIGHT LEAD TO IN OUR FUTURE  AND HE WAS A ALWAYS PUSHING ME AS AN ENGINEER</pattern><template>Could you possibly add this someday, could you possibly add that someday?  Yes, yes, yes, I could,  thinking,  no.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD  YOU KNOW  CALL FROM A PAY PHONE  GO TO WHITE PLAINS  NEW YORK  TAKE A SATELLITE TO EUROPE TAKE A CABLE TO TURKEY  UM  COME BACK TO LOS ANGELES  AND YOU'D GO AROUND THE WORLD 3 OR 4 TIMES AND CALL THE PAYPHONE NEXT DOOR  SHOUT IN THE PHONE  AND BE ABOUT 30 SECONDS  IT WOULD COME OUT THE OTHER PHONE</pattern><template>The pair quickly moved on from phone jacking for fun to creating computers, building the prototype of the very first Apple.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN STEVE JOBS FIRST LAUNCHED APPLE  THE COMPUTER INDUSTRY MEANT MAINFRAMES AND MINICOMPUTERS</pattern><template>Huge devices sat in air conditioned rooms, and users worked on terminals.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE KEPT INVESTING BECAUSE WE WOULD RUN OUT OF MONEY AND HE DID NOT WANT TO BE EMBARRASSED BY FAILURE AFTER HAVING BEEN BOOTED OUT OF APPLE  SO HE WOULD PUT MORE MONEY IN AND TAKE MORE EQUITY AWAY FROM THE EMPLOYEES</pattern><template>So over the course of about 4 or 5 years, he owned it all.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE JOBS' WORLD CLASS SALESMANSHIP FOUND A GLOBAL AUDIENCE IN HIS FAMOUS APPLE PRODUCT PRESENTATIONS</pattern><template>He always had  one more thing  to announce.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE BEGGING HIM TO COME BACK BECAUSE THEY KNEW HE COULD FIX IT  AND HE DID COME BACK  AND HE FIXED IT  AND THE REST IS HISTORY</pattern><template>One man who witnessed Jobs' return to Apple was friend Walt Mossberg.</template></category><category><pattern>HE CONTACTED ME  ASKED ME TO BE A PRINCIPAL INVESTOR AND TO SERVE ON THE BOARD WITH HIM  AND I AGREED TO DO IT JUST BECAUSE OF MY SUPPORT FOR HIM  AND THERE WAS NO QUESTION IN MY MIND THAT IF HE</pattern><template>If he wanted to do it, it would get done.</template></category><category><pattern>HIP HOP GROUP THE BLACK EYED PEAS WERE ASKED TO STAR IN AN ITUNES COMMERCIAL</pattern><template>They later became the most downloaded band on iTunes, but at the time, they didn't understand this new cultural phenomenon.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LOVED APHORISMS</pattern><template>You know, Picasso said,  good artists copy, great artists steal,  and he loved to say that.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID   BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THERE WON'T BE PERIODS  WHEN I WILL LEAVE AND I WILL DO OTHER THINGS AND MY LIFE WILL WEAVE IN AND OUT OF APPLE   ONCE AGAIN  JOBS' FORESIGHT WAS SPOT ON</pattern><template>Two years after Sculley arrived at Apple, the love affair turned sour as company profits faltered.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULDN'T PUT GRACIOUS IN HIS DESCRIPTION</pattern><template>He had the kind of manner, the kind of approach to people and environments that were business directed, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  WHEN HE ZONED IN ON SOMETHING  THE REST OF THE WORLD DISAPPEARED  AND THAT WAS WHAT IT WAS LIKE WATCHING WARHOL IN FRONT OF A MACINTOSH FOR THE FIRST TIME</pattern><template>And then he got this big smile on his face, and he looked up.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SURE YOU WANT TO GO FOR A WALK   WE'RE ABOUT HALFWAY TO THE NEIGHBORHOOD PARK  AND HE STOPS  YOU KN</pattern><template>He wasn't gasping for air or anything, but he was not well looking man, and I said,  Steve, why don't we go back to the house?  And he smiled or chuckled, and he said,  no. We're not going back to the house.</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE THE IMPRESSION THAT SOMEHOW OR OTHER I GOT DIDDLED OUT OF SOMETHING</pattern><template>Well, I did not.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO GET THEIR KIDS AWAY FROM THEM  AND MAYBE SOMEDAY THEY'LL EVEN BUY A SECOND ONE TO LEAVE AT HOME</pattern><template>Which made him a natural subject for  playboy.  Interviewing Jobs was a unique experience for writer David Sheff.</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY HIS CLOSEST FRIENDS SAW HOW HE WAS COPING WITH THE THREAT OF AN EARLY DEATH</pattern><template>Steve Jobs loved to take walks.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THE INDUSTRY HAS BENEFITED IMMENSELY FROM HIS WORK</pattern><template>We've both been lucky to be part of it, but I'd say he's contributed as much as anyone.</template></category><category><pattern>IT TOOK HIM ABOUT TWO SECONDS TO SHOW SEAN HOW TO DEAL WITH IT  AND SEAN PRETTY SOON WAS DRAWING PICTURES</pattern><template>Later Steve told me it was one of the first times he'd watched a child with a Mac.</template></category><category><pattern>I MARCHED PAST HIM AND WROTE ON THE WHITEBOARD</pattern><template>Now it was unspoken rule...</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THERE WAS A DECISION TO LOOK DIFFERENT</pattern><template>Remember, their motto immediately after his return was  think different,  and he didn't say that because he didn't believe it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY LATER BECAME THE MOST DOWNLOADED BAND ON ITUNES  BUT AT THE TIME  THEY DIDN'T UNDERSTAND THIS NEW CULTURAL PHENOMENON</pattern><template>They said,  hey. They want to use a black eyed peas song for an iTunes commercial,  and I said what's iTunes?  And they said,  they're not paying much, but they're going to give you guys iPods.   What's an iPod?  This is the new iPod Nano.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE STEVE STARTED WORKING ON COMPUTER TYPEFACES  THEY WERE IN VERY BAD CONDITION  AND ANY IMPROVEMENT WOULD BE A STEP FORWARD</pattern><template>The resulting fonts appeared not just on Macs but ultimately PCs, too, dramatically improving the user experience but not for Robert.</template></category><category><pattern>FOUNDERS CAN BE DIVIDED INTO TWO CAMPS</pattern><template>There are hippies, and there are nerds, and Jobs was definitely the hippie, and Woz was the nerd.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WOULD HAVE BEEN COMPUTERS  AND THERE WOULD HAVE BEEN PERSONAL COMPUTERS  BUT WE PROBABLY WOULDN'T HAVE THE KIND OF WONDERFUL EMPOWERING THINGS THAT PEOPLE FALL INTO IF WOZ AND JOBS HADN'T MET</pattern><template>This neighborhood we grew up in had a lot of lockheed engineers in it, and I would go up and down the street to the various dads on the street and get mentored in electronics, and Steve Wozniak's father was one of the people who mentored me.</template></category><category><pattern>IN APPLE'S EARLIEST DAYS  THE TWO STEVES  JOBS AND WOZ  TOOK ON AN OLDER AND MORE EXPERIENCED PARTNER</pattern><template>Ronald Wayne now lives and works near Las Vegas, a fitting location for a man who walked away with nothing from a $37 billion no lose bet.</template></category><category><pattern>BILL GATES IS A BRILLIANT MAN</pattern><template>He did a lot for the world in technology.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I WAS HAVING A HARD TIME  HE WOULD BE ON THE PHONE  HE'D DRIVE UP FROM SILICON VALLEY  TAKE ME OUT FOR DINNER  HANG OUT AND TAKE WALKS WITH ME</pattern><template>He turned on me, total street bully, in my face, screa...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE BEST WAS YET TO COME FOR JOBS</pattern><template>Apple was in trouble.</template></category><category><pattern>AND DURING THIS FACE OFF</pattern><template>Literally a face off...</template></category><category><pattern>IT HERALDS THE HOME COMPUTING REVOLUTION</pattern><template>This is the first computer where you use a keyboard and a screen to enter and read data.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S WAY  WAY OFF   BUT EVENTUALLY WE ALL DID</pattern><template>In those early days, Woz and Jobs took their creation to the home brew computer club, an early computer club, an early computer users' group in silicon valley, where it quickly attracted attention from their peers.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WASN'T THE TYPICAL TEENAGER</pattern><template>He asked questions that t re a lot more serious than the normal 20 year old.</template></category><category><pattern>FERNANDEZ ALSO KNEW ANOTHER ELECTRONICS GEEK  HIS NEIGHBORS' SON STEVE WOZNIAK  UNIVERSALLY KNOWN AS WOZ</pattern><template>So one day, Steve Jobs bicycled over to hang out with me and do electronics projects in the garage, and out in front was Wozniak washing his car.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS JUST CRAZY WHAT WAS HAPPENING THAT TIME  AND APPLE AS VERY WEAK  AND SO I CALLED BILL UP AND WE TRIED TO PATCH THINGS UP</pattern><template>I think he learned to be a better businessman.</template></category><category><pattern>THROUGH THEIR EYES  WE REVEAL WHAT MADE HIM THE MAN WHO ALWAYS GAVE US</pattern><template>Now there's one more thing.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS THE GUY WHO CAME WITH  SOMETHING WOULD BE INSANELY GREAT   WHAT DOES THAT MEAN</pattern><template>Much of what Apple did was built on the efforts of others.</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE ARE THE TELEPHONE COMPUTERS ACTUALLY SIGNING EACH OTHER  SENDING INFORMATION TO EACH OTHER TO SET UP YOUR CALL</pattern><template>And there used to be a way to fool the entire telephone system into thinking you were a telephone computer.</template></category><category><pattern>19 YEAR OLD HONG KONG BASED DESIGN STUDENT JONATHAN MAK LONG CREATED AN IMAGE ON HIS MAC THAT WENT VIRAL AROUND THE WORLD</pattern><template>There was no real research behind it.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  HE REALLY ENVISIONED THE IPAD ALMOST 30 YEARS AGO</pattern><template>Jobs and sheff quickly became close friends.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN HE GOT THIS BIG SMILE ON HIS FACE  AND HE LOOKED UP</pattern><template>He said,  I drew a circle.  And it was great.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T A PERSONAL EXPERIENCE</pattern><template>The Apple II was the first computer that looked like a consumer electronic device.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK AT FIRST IT WAS A TREMENDOUS DISAPPOINTMENT  WHICH I CAN CERTAINLY UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>Secondly, he picked himself up, dusted himself off, and started all over again with very little hesitation, and I really admired that.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE DOG WHAT HE DOES ON WALKS  WHICH IS WE WERE TALKING ABOUT DIFFERENT THINGS  AND WE GOT TO THE PARK  AND WE SAT ON A BENCH  AND WE TALKED ABOUT</pattern><template>In the park, if I remember correctly, we actually talked more about life and health and... you know, I had had a heart attack some years before, and he was lecturing me about that, and I was sort of lecturing him, as well, about work/life balance and all these things, and then we got up and walked back and talked some more.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DID A LOT OF HIS THINKING AND HIS TALKING WITH HIS CLOSE FRIENDS LIKE LARRY ELLISON AND A NUMBER OF OTHER PEOPLE THAT HE WAS FRIENDLY WITH IN SILICON VALLEY  AND HE WOULD GO ON THESE LONG WALKS SOMETIMES AROUND PALO ALTO  WHERE HE LIVED  AND SOMETIMES IN OTHER PLACES</pattern><template>It just was his preferred method of thinking and daydreaming ideas with people.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO MISS THE CHANCE TO GO TO HIM AND JUST SIT DOWN AND SHARE JUST PERSON TO PERSON</pattern><template>How much fun we had... ohh...</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE WAS VERY MUCH TAKEN WITH THAT AND ESPECIALLY CALLIGRAPHY</pattern><template>He noticed the way the lines and the spaces had a relationship.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WERE SOME PEOPLE HE COULD STEAL FROM APPLE TO MARKET TO THAT SEGMENT  AND HE THOUGHT STARTING SMALL MADE SENSE</pattern><template>But even starting small needs big money.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  THAT'S WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT</pattern><template>I think the world will miss Steve Jobs.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT ANYMORE  AND THIS IS WHERE WE'RE STARTING FROM  AND THIS IS WHERE WE'RE MOVING   AND SO WHEN YOU SEE THE SECOND COMING OF STEVE JOBS AND APPLE  APPLE WENT FROM BEING A WIDE OPEN AND WACKY COMPANY TO BE A VERY DISCIPLINED COMPANY THAT UNDERSTOOD ITS FINANCIALS AT A LEVEL THAT FEW COMPANIES DO</pattern><template>That's because Steve thought of every dollar as being his every dollar.</template></category><category><pattern>WAYNE ACTED AS REFEREE IN A MINOR DIFFERENCE OF OPINION BETWEEN THE TWO EQUAL PARTNERS</pattern><template>Well, Steve Jobs was so impressed with my diplomacy in that particular situation that he immediately came back and said,  ok. What we're going to do is form a company,  with Woz and Jobs getting 45% each, and I would get 10% as a tiebreaker in the event of any philosophical disputes that might occur in the future.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D NEVER BEEN THERE</pattern><template>I don't ever want to be there again.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OTHER STUDENTS BROUGHT HIM TO ME LIKE THEY WERE BRINGING ME SOMEONE VERY SPECIAL</pattern><template>They really had a high regard for him.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FUTURE IS LONG</pattern><template>Ha ha ha!</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE IS SO KNOW FOR HIS RESTRAINT</pattern><template>I think Gates felt that Jobs got more credit than he might have deserved as being the great technologist.</template></category><category><pattern>COMPUTERS</pattern><template>They were yesterday's news.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS MOTHER LOVES HIM</pattern><template>PC guy is what makes it all work actually.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THAT SAME FIRST APPLE I WAS AUCTIONED IN 2010  IT ATTRACTED EVEN MORE ATTENTION</pattern><template>It heralds the home computing revolution.</template></category><category><pattern>HE BECAME A BILLIONAIRE FROM IT</pattern><template>Awesome.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE BOTH BEEN LUCKY TO BE PART OF IT  BUT I'D SAY HE'S CONTRIBUTED AS MUCH AS ANYONE</pattern><template>I think he built the first software company before anybody really in our industry knew what a software company was except for these guys and that was huge.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME PEOPLE HAVE SAID TO ME THAT THE LOGO ACTUALLY MADE THEM CRY  AND I THOUGHT IT WAS A REALLY STRONG REACTION TO HAVE  BUT IT MADE SENSE BECAUSE STEVE JOBS HAD SUCH A GREAT IMPACT ON OUR WORLD</pattern><template>He wasn't just this person who made all these great gadgets.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK GATES FELT THAT JOBS GOT MORE CREDIT THAN HE MIGHT HAVE DESERVED AS BEING THE GREAT TECHNOLOGIST</pattern><template>Neither person is hugely likable.</template></category><category><pattern>SO STEVE'S GENIUS IS TO MOVE WHEN HE HAS A GOOD IDEA</pattern><template>I don't think they're necessarily his ideas, but, boy, does he know how to move and market them like crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>LIFE HAD BEEN GOOD FOR STEVE JOBS</pattern><template>He was worth a million dollars when he was 21.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MAYBE MORE  I DON'T KNOW  BUT CERTAINLY THOSE 4  AND IF YOU COMPARE HIM WITH EDISON  WELL  THERE WAS THE ELECTRIC POWER INDUSTRY  THE MOTION PICTURE INDUSTRY  AND THE MUSIC INDUSTRY</pattern><template>Edison only had 3.</template></category><category><pattern>UM  COME OVER AND MEET STEVE   SO   STEVE  MEET STEVE   AND THIS IS WHERE IT HAPPENED  BASICALLY RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Woz and Jobs became inseparable friends, but their first venture was not a computer.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE HIPPIE HAS THE GRAND VISION  AND THE NERD IS ABLE TO REALIZE THE VISION</pattern><template>The nerd knows everything about women but doesn't know any women.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYONE THINKS   WOW</pattern><template>That's... that's so much,  and,  well, we got one more thing,  and then you put your biggest thing at the end because it'll tip it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  IF YOU PUSH IN  SOMETHING WILL POP OUT THE OTHER SIDE  YOU CAN YOU CAN CHANGE IT  YOU CAN MOLD IT  UM  THAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT THING</pattern><template>There's one thing on which everyone agrees...</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU SAW THEM TOGETHER  STEVE ALWAYS DOMINATED THE CONVERSATION</pattern><template>In part that's because I think Bill was always fascinated by Steve.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TREATED HIM AS  YOU KNOW THE  DEVIL  THE ANTICHRIST  AND THEY BOOED HIM</pattern><template>But Jobs with his eye ever on the bottom line, had a different view.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN THEN HE HAD THIS ABILITY TO BRIDGE A VERY INTELLECTUAL WORLD OF HIGH TECHNOLOGY WITH SOMETHING THAT EVERYONE COULD RELATE TO</pattern><template>Here's a guy who revolutionized the computer industry, the music industry, the motion picture industry, the telephone industry...</template></category><category><pattern>HIS IS A SUCCESS STORY THAT COULD ONLY HAVE HAPPENED IN THE U S A</pattern><template>I don't mean to say that there aren't geniuses and world changing people everywhere... there are...</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE REALLY CHANGED IN A NUMBER OF WAYS  AND HE CHANGED PRIMARILY BECAUSE OF FAILURE</pattern><template>Failure affected him, and he learned from.</template></category><category><pattern>I MET BOTH STEVES  STEVE JOBS AND STEVE WOZNIAK AT A MEETING OF THE HOME BREW COMPUTER CLUB IN PALO ALTO</pattern><template>Our first meeting was really simple.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS A REAL OBSERVER  AND HE WOULD JUST LOOK AT THIS GUY AND SAY   WHAT THE HECK IS GOING ON HERE   WE'VE KEPT OUR MARRIAGE SECRET FOR OVER A DECADE NOW</pattern><template>He admired Steve for his ability to interface with people, connect with them, you know, affect them.</template></category><category><pattern>WOZ AND JOBS BECAME INSEPARABLE FRIENDS  BUT THEIR FIRST VENTURE WAS NOT A COMPUTER</pattern><template>The pair developed an electronics Kit mimicking telephone router codes to make free calls around the world.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I CAN MOVE THIS WITH JUST A TOUCH ANYWHERE I WANT</pattern><template>Steve Jobs, now at the peak of his creative genius, was leading Apple to the peak of its creative success.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE REASON I GOT AWAY FROM HIM</pattern><template>We were screaming at each other in full bull rage with our faces about that far apart, and during that...</template></category><category><pattern>JOBS CREATED A BRAND NEW PRODUCT AT APPLE  THE IMAC</pattern><template>I think there was a decision to look different.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WENT BACK AND FORTH  AND BASICALLY BY THE END OF THAT CONSTRUCTED WHAT LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE AN IPAD</pattern><template>Steve said this machine, this small device as big as a book, would allow us to keep in touch with one another, it will replace the telephone and would replace bookstores.</template></category><category><pattern>APPROACHING THE AGE OF 50  BARELY A QUARTER OF A CENTURY AFTER MAKING HIS FIRST MILLION GREENBACKS  JOBS WAS WORTH $2 3 BILLION</pattern><template>Now he picked up the pace of Apple's evolution.</template></category><category><pattern>IS STEVE CRAZY OR IS THERE SOMETHING HERE   IF STEVE WANTED SOMETHING  HIS TEAM JUST HAD TO INNOVATE  SO FOR DEAN N AT MEANT A TRIP TO THE DRUG STORE</pattern><template>As I entered Walgreens, I had in my mind most importantly was,  where do I find these spheres, these balls to be a part of the mouse?  And I had thought about the underarm deodorant as the right solution.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM THE START  GATES WAS OVERSHADOWED BY THE MORE POLISHED  CONFIDENT JOBS</pattern><template>I made... I...</template></category><category><pattern>HE CARRIED ON WORKING  BUT THE YEARS THAT FOLLOWED WERE A ROLLER COASTER OF HOPE AND DESPAIR</pattern><template>Most poignantly he was asked what the next few years might hold.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT EVEN STARTING SMALL NEEDS BIG MONEY</pattern><template>I invested $20 millions in NeXT.</template></category><category><pattern>JOBS AND WOZ WERE SOON TO START A BUSINESS TOGETHER</pattern><template>Its name was Apple.</template></category><category><pattern>HALF A MILLION SONGS ARE DOWNLOADED ON ITUNES EVERY DAY  IN MANY CASES CHANGING ARTISTS' LIVES</pattern><template>Hip hop group the black eyed peas were asked to star in an iTunes commercial.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHILE THE BANTER WAS GOOD NATURED  THE RIVALRY BETWEEN THE TWO WAS DEEP ROOTED</pattern><template>I personally can attest to having heard each of them say very nasty things about the other off the record in private over the years.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE LOVED THOSE CREATIVE IDEAS</pattern><template>His faults...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOSE IT  YOU CAN'T EVER GO BACK AND JUST HAVE THOSE CONVERSATIONS THAT MAKE US BOTH SMILE</pattern><template>As the world mourned, the most fitting tribute came from one of Steve Jobs' young fans.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS LIKE HAVING A TIGER BY THE TAIL</pattern><template>So Ron decided to hand back his share for nothing and walk away with no regrets.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS DEATH WAS NOT A SURPRISE  AND YET ITS IMPACT REVERBERATED AROUND THE WORLD</pattern><template>The news had spread, and the tributes were created on the new iDevices that his visionary genius had made.</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE PEOPLE WHO KNEW HIM BEST</pattern><template>I'd give a lot to have Steve's taste.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY JUST WENT NUTS WHEN THEY SAW  TOY STORY   AND THEY CAME BACK AND BASICALLY TOLD STEVE THAT IT WAS GOING TO BE A HUGE SUCCESS  AND THAT'S WHEN HE    THAT'S THE POINT HIS ABILITY TO SEE SOMETHING SPECTACULAR IS ABOUT TO HAPPEN</pattern><template>He just moved just in and exploited that right to the hilt, and I must say he did a great job.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DID A LOT FOR THE WORLD IN TECHNOLOGY</pattern><template>And he is now doing a lot for the world in philanthropy, and I think highly of Bill Gates, but...Of the two of them, the one that took the bigger risks and changed the game more often, it was Steve...</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS WORTH $10 MILLION WHEN HE WAS 22</pattern><template>He was worth $100 million when he was 23 years old.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THERE'S THAT DISTINCTION</pattern><template>So they really needed each other.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAIT FOR MY IPAD AND REALLY  REALLY  REALLY HAPPY NOW</pattern><template>Jobs drew on a diverse range of influences to feed his creativity, including a class he dropped into at college in Portland, Oregon, in the early seventies.</template></category><category><pattern>LIFE CAN BE MUCH BROADER ONCE YOU DISCOVER ONE SIMPLE FACT  AND THAT IS EVERYTHING AROUND YOU THAT YOU CALL LIFE WAS MADE UP BY PEOPLE THAT WERE NO SMARTER THAN YOU  AND YOU CAN CHANGE IT  YOU CAN INFLUENCE IT  YOU CAN BUILD YOUR OWN THINGS THAT OTHER PEOPLE CAN USE</pattern><template>Um, once you learn that, you'll never be the same again.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PAIR DEVELOPED AN ELECTRONICS KIT MIMICKING TELEPHONE ROUTER CODES TO MAKE FREE CALLS AROUND THE WORLD</pattern><template>You know, when you make a long distance phone call in the background you hear,  do do do do do ?</template></category><category><pattern>THE PHONE RUNG ONE DAY  AND IT WAS NOT A PR PERSON WHO CALLED  BUT IT WAS JOBS HIMSELF  AND IT REALLY WAS AN INDICATION OF THE WAY THAT HE DID BUSINESS AND REALLY CONTINUED TO DO BUSINESS</pattern><template>Apple was very different.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS CLOSEST CHILDHOOD FRIEND WAS BILL FERNANDEZ</pattern><template>In about eighth grade, halfway through, this new guy came into the school, who was Steve Jobs, and we were both introverted, intellectual, kind of socially inept, and we gravitated towards each other.</template></category><category><pattern>ON JOBS' SIDE  HE BELIEVED THAT MICROSOFT HAD STOLEN THE BASIC IDEAS IN THE MAC</pattern><template>From the point of view of Gates, I think, he found Jobs difficult to deal with.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS CONQUERING THE WORLD OF MUSIC</pattern><template>Great new products.</template></category><category><pattern>APPLE DIDN'T HAVE TO BEAT MICROSOFT</pattern><template>Apple had to remember who Apple was.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE JOBS CREATED THE MOST RESPECTED BRAND IN THE WORLD AND SHOOK UP A WHOLE INDUSTRY  AND HE DID IT WITH A LOT OF PANACHE AND STYLE  AND  YOU KNOW  GREAT RESPECT FOR HIM FOR IT</pattern><template>Life can be much broader once you discover one simple fact, and that is everything around you that you call life was made up by people that were no smarter than you.</template></category><category><pattern>IT JUST WAS HIS PREFERRED METHOD OF THINKING AND DAYDREAMING IDEAS WITH PEOPLE</pattern><template>One day I was out in silicon valley.</template></category><category><pattern>JOBS WAS HURTING HIS COMPETITORS</pattern><template>iTunes pretty well killed off the music store, and virgin mega stores, you know, have slowly been disappearing around the world.</template></category><category><pattern>HE TOOK STUFF TO A NEW PLACE  AND I DO IDENTIFY WITH THAT</pattern><template>It's exciting when you do that, so I do find the excitement of that, and he also made things that were beautiful, great to touch, great to hold, good to look at, and different colors.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TELL THE STORY</pattern><template>So Woz...</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE KNEW NOTHING BUT SUCCESS  AND WHEN YOU'RE 23 YEARS OLD  YOU'RE WORTH $100 MILLION  YOU ARE PRETTY DAMN FULL OF YOURSELF  AND THAT'S WHAT STEVE BECAME  AND SO HE HAD HUGE AMBITION</pattern><template>But in 1985 at the age of 30, his charmed run of luck was about to come to an abrupt halt.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE BUILT THE FIRST SOFTWARE COMPANY BEFORE ANYBODY REALLY IN OUR INDUSTRY KNEW WHAT A SOFTWARE COMPANY WAS EXCEPT FOR THESE GUYS AND THAT WAS HUGE</pattern><template>Bill Gates is a brilliant man.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT A JOKE AT ALL</pattern><template>I think in terms of intuitive taste both for people and products, the way he does things is just different, and I think it's magical.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S SWEET I THINK WE SHOULD END IT THERE</pattern><template>It was one of the highlights of my journalistic career to be there.</template></category><category><pattern>I SET A GOAL EVERY DAY  AND MY GOAL NOW IS TO GET TO THIS PARK   I SAID   YOU'RE SURE   AND HE SAID   YEAH   SO WE WALKED TO THE PARK  AND  YOU KNOW  HE WAS FINE</pattern><template>We talked by the way the whole way.</template></category><category><pattern>SEEKING SOMEONE TO HELP RUN HIS RAPIDLY EXPANDING BUSINESS  HE HIRED IN PEPSI EXECUTIVE JOHN SCULLEY</pattern><template>President John Sculley admits Apple will be just another personal computer company unless macintosh becomes an industry milestone in the n nt 100 days.</template></category><category><pattern>WAY BEFORE ITUNES  STEVE JOBS HAS BEEN A PART OF MUSIC BECAUSE EVERY MAJOR STUDIO HAS A MAC COMPUTER IN IT</pattern><template>I mean, the Mac computer is an artist's computer.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE JOBS  NOW AT THE PEAK OF HIS CREATIVE GENIUS  WAS LEADING APPLE TO THE PEAK OF ITS CREATIVE SUCCESS</pattern><template>The key to the success of the company was in moving beyond the computer, was in seeing how the microprocessor was getting so cheap that it could be applied to other consumer electronic devices.</template></category><category><pattern>I MADE    I</pattern><template>Let me tell the story.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY RAISED MONEY TO START A BUSINESS</pattern><template>They knew that they couldn't do it on their own.</template></category><category><pattern>JOBS AND SHEFF QUICKLY BECAME CLOSE FRIENDS</pattern><template>Through the late sixties and seventies in very similar ways, gong through some of the counter culture, you know being, influenced by some of the eastern mysticism, buddhism, the LSD culture, Timothy leary.</template></category><category><pattern>HE GAVE THEM $150 MILLION FOR WHICH HE GOT NONVOTING STOCK THAT EXPIRED AFTER A CERTAIN NUMBER OF YEARS  AND HE PROMISED TO KEEP PRODUCING MICROSOFT OFFICE  THE MACINTOSH VERSION  FOR  I THINK  5 YEARS  AND SO HE WAS ONSTAGE RESCUING APPLE  AND YET THE ACOLYTES WHO WERE FILLING THE ROOM HAD LEARNED TO HATE HIM</pattern><template>They treated him as, you know the, devil, the antichrist, and they booed him.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF THEM WAS SELF MADE TEXAN BILLIONAIRE AND FORMER PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE ROSS PEROT</pattern><template>He saw how wounded Jobs had been by Apple.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE JOBS LOVED TO TAKE WALKS</pattern><template>He did a lot of his thinking and his talking with his close friends like Larry Ellison and a number of other people that he was friendly with in silicon valley, and he would go on these long walks sometimes around Palo Alto, where he lived, and sometimes in other places.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WASN'T GASPING FOR AIR OR ANYTHING  BUT HE WAS NOT WELL LOOKING MAN  AND I SAID   STEVE  WHY DON'T WE GO BACK TO THE HOUSE   AND HE SMILED OR CHUCKLED  AND HE SAID   NO  WE'RE NOT GOING BACK TO THE HOUSE</pattern><template>I just need a minute and then we're gonna go on to the park  because that's my goal.</template></category><category><pattern>ITUNES PRETTY WELL KILLED OFF THE MUSIC STORE  AND VIRGIN MEGA STORES  YOU KNOW  HAVE SLOWLY BEEN DISAPPEARING AROUND THE WORLD</pattern><template>Half a million songs are downloaded on iTunes every day, in many cases changing artists' lives.</template></category><category><pattern>CERTAINLY STEVE JOBS IS AN ACQUIRED TASTE  AND SO IS BILL GATES FOR THAT MATTER</pattern><template>Um, they both have their moments.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'D PROBABLY LIKE TO MEET EACH OTHER   FERNANDEZ HAD NO IDEA AT THE TIME THAT THE MEETING BETWEEN HIS TWO FRIENDS WOULD CHANGE OUR WORLD</pattern><template>Jobs and Woz were soon to start a business together.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WERE TOO MANY PEOPLE AT APPLE AND IN THE APPLE ECOSYSTEM PLAYING THE GAME OF  FOR APPLE TO WIN  MICROSOFT HAS TO LOSE   AND IT WAS CLEAR THAT YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO PLAY THAT GAME BECAUSE APPLE WASN'T GOING TO BEAT MICROSOFT</pattern><template>Apple didn't have to beat Microsoft.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SECOND YOU WALKED IN THE DOOR  YOU FELT LIKE YOU WERE IN A COMPLETELY NEW ENVIRONMENT</pattern><template>The conference rooms instead of, you know, of number 103c were called Da Vinci and Michelangelo and Picasso, and indeed it was Picasso that I was escorted to to see Jobs for the first time.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S    THAT'S SO MUCH   AND   WELL  WE GOT ONE MORE THING   AND THEN YOU PUT YOUR BIGGEST THING AT THE END BECAUSE IT'LL TIP IT</pattern><template>It's good, uh... it's good showmanship really.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOING TO INSPIRE A WHOLE NEW GENERATION</pattern><template>A 5 year old 20 years from now is going to create and design and invent and define a world totally different than the way we see it now, and it's going to be because of Steve Jobs.</template></category><category><pattern>JOBS TOOK ALONG A BIRTHDAY GIFT THAT FASCINATED NOT ONLY SEAN BUT THE WHOLE STAR STUDDED GUEST LIST</pattern><template>Steve opened it up, pulled out what was one of those first Macintoshes off the assembly line, set it up on the floor.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS KIND OF A LOVE AFFAIR AT THE BEGINNING</pattern><template>I mean, Steve really trusted him and really saw a kindred spirit, someone who would help him build Apple.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST DIDN'T KNOW WHAT HAD HAPPENED</pattern><template>Everyone in Steve Jobs' life went through 3 phases...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  PICASSO SAID   GOOD ARTISTS COPY  GREAT ARTISTS STEAL   AND HE LOVED TO SAY THAT</pattern><template>He was the guy who came with  something would be insanely great.  What does that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOTTEN AROUND 200 000 RESPONSES ON MY BLOG</pattern><template>Some people have said to me that the logo actually made them cry, and I thought it was a really strong reaction to have, but it made sense because Steve Jobs had such a great impact on our world.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT JOBS WITH HIS EYE EVER ON THE BOTTOM LINE  HAD A DIFFERENT VIEW</pattern><template>There were too many people at Apple and in the Apple ecosystem playing the game of  for Apple to win, Microsoft has to lose,  and it was clear that you didn't have to play that game because Apple wasn't going to beat Microsoft.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D GIVE A LOT TO HAVE STEVE JOBS' TASTE</pattern><template>He has natural...</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE WAS INSULTING MY SOUTHWESTERN ACCENT</pattern><template>It was just street bully stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS NEIGHBORHOOD WE GREW UP IN HAD A LOT OF LOCKHEED ENGINEERS IN IT  AND I WOULD GO UP AND DOWN THE STREET TO THE VARIOUS DADS ON THE STREET AND GET MENTORED IN ELECTRONICS  AND STEVE WOZNIAK'S FATHER WAS ONE OF THE PEOPLE WHO MENTORED ME</pattern><template>As Jobs and I were walking over, I noticed Woz out washing his car, and I said,  hey, Woz.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WAIT 8 HOURS IN A LINE  AND I'M HUNGRY  I AM EVERYTHING YOU IMAGINE  BUT I'M HAPPY</pattern><template>I wait for my iPad and really, really, really happy now.</template></category><category><pattern>A STANDING OVATION FOR APPLE CEO STEVE JOBS AS HE GREETED THE PUBLIC FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MORE THAN A YEAR</pattern><template>He carried on working, but the years that followed were a roller coaster of hope and despair.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW IT WAS UNSPOKEN RULE</pattern><template>Which I hate, unspoken rules...</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HIS GENIUS WAS BEING ABLE TO TAKE THE PRINCIPLES OF ZEN AND INCORPORATE IT INTO THE PRODUCTS THAT CAME OUT OF APPLE</pattern><template>Jobs freely acknowledged how these outside influences had affected him.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAW HOW WOUNDED JOBS HAD BEEN BY APPLE</pattern><template>I think at first it was a tremendous disappointment, which I can certainly understand.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH MADE HIM A NATURAL SUBJECT FOR  PLAYBOY   INTERVIEWING JOBS WAS A UNIQUE EXPERIENCE FOR WRITER DAVID SHEFF</pattern><template>The phone rung one day, and it was not a PR person who called, but it was Jobs himself, and it really was an indication of the way that he did business and really continued to do business.</template></category><category><pattern>HE THE WORLD'S GENIUS MARKETEER  INCLUDING OF HIS OWN SELF IMAGE</pattern><template>But the best was yet to come for Jobs.</template></category><category><pattern>HE GAVE US TOOLS TO CHANGE OUR LIVES AND THE WAY WE COMMUNICATE</pattern><template>Here comes a device that comes with no manual, and everybody knows how to use it... amazing.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE WANTED TO DO IT  IT WOULD GET DONE</pattern><template>He's great with attracting and motivating the best of the best people.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE JUST LOOKING UP AT HIM WITH BIG DOE EYES JUST SOAKING IN EVERYTHING HE'S SAYING AS IF IT WAS TRUE  AND IT WASN'T</pattern><template>So you can see that it was very disruptive.</template></category><category><pattern>HUGE DEVICES SAT IN AIR CONDITIONED ROOMS  AND USERS WORKED ON TERMINALS</pattern><template>It wasn't a personal experience.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THERE'S ONE MORE THING</pattern><template>Steve Jobs Steve Jobs  One Last Thing  Mikhel for Subtitulos.es ==SPREAD THE WORD== Steven Paul Jobs died on October 5, 2011, at the age of 56, a life cut short in its creative prime by cancer.</template></category><category><pattern>I GAVE AWAY THE LISTINGS  NO COPYRIGHT NOTICES  NO NOTHING  AND THEN STEVE JOBS CAME AND SAW THE INTEREST  AND HE SAID  WHY DON'T WE START A COMPANY TO MAKE SOME MONEY   AND I SAID   FINE   THEY DID WANT TO START A BUSINESS</pattern><template>They raised money to start a business.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE EITHER BEING SEDUCED  IGNORED  OR SCOURGED  AND IT ALL DEPENDED UPON WHETHER HE NEEDED YOU OR NOT</pattern><template>If he needed you, he was your best friend, and he would seduce you, and then you would work like a dog, and if you weren't working hard enough, he would scourge you, and ultimately he would throw you away.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S BECAUSE STEVE THOUGHT OF EVERY DOLLAR AS BEING HIS EVERY DOLLAR</pattern><template>They have resolved these differences in a very, very...</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER  THEIR MOTTO IMMEDIATELY AFTER HIS RETURN WAS  THINK DIFFERENT   AND HE DIDN'T SAY THAT BECAUSE HE DIDN'T BELIEVE IT</pattern><template>He really did want to think different, and they would have to appear different to show that they were thinking different.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE STARTED DRAWING ON A PLACE MAT</pattern><template>We went back and forth, and basically by the end of that constructed what looks exactly like an iPad.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE ULTIMATELY BETRAYED EVERYONE</pattern><template>And some said the new Steve Jobs wasn't afraid of claiming l the credit, too.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DIDN'T EVEN LOOK AT THE OTHER MOVIE</pattern><template>They just went nuts when they saw  toy story,  and they came back and basically told Steve that it was going to be a huge success, and that's when he... that's the point his ability to see something spectacular is about to happen.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SOUNDS STRANGE  BUT IT WAS ACTUALLY AN EMOTIONAL THING</pattern><template>So I can move this with just a touch anywhere I want.</template></category><category><pattern>HE TURNED ON ME  TOTAL STREET BULLY  IN MY FACE  SCREA</pattern><template>We were... and I went crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS MAN REALLY HAD CHANGED THE WORLD</pattern><template>When you grow up, you tend to get told that the world is the way it is, and your... your life is just to live your life inside the world, try not to bash into the walls too much, try to have a nice family life, have fun, save a little money.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE ALWAYS THOUGHT MUCH MORE BROADLY THAN JUST TECHNOLOGY</pattern><template>He was certainly a techno visionary, but the key to his greatness is to see how broad he thought.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS INTIMATE PORTRAIT IS A REVEALING INSIGHT INTO STEVE JOBS' LIFE</pattern><template>Andy Warhol gets down on his hands and knees, Steve showing him how to use the mouse.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE DON'T WANT TO RENT THEIR MUSIC LIFE IN APPLE'S ORCHARD HAD NEVER BEEN MORE FRUITFUL</pattern><template>Then Steve Jobs learned he had cancer.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS VERY FRAIL</pattern><template>We talked about his health, and he talked about how he felt he was recovering, and in the middle of this, he said,  let's go for a walk,  and I said,  really? Really?</template></category><category><pattern>HE CAME BACK TO APPLE  AND THE COMPANY WAS ALMOST DEAD</pattern><template>Literally. It was 90 days from going bankrupt.</template></category><category><pattern>APPLE'S HISTORY INTERWEAVES WITH MICROSOFT'S</pattern><template>Their CEOs gave a unique interview to journalist Walter Mossberg.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK THEY'RE NECESSARILY HIS IDEAS  BUT  BOY  DOES HE KNOW HOW TO MOVE AND MARKET THEM LIKE CRAZY</pattern><template>He the world's genius marketeer, including of his own self image.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM THE POINT OF VIEW OF GATES  I THINK  HE FOUND JOBS DIFFICULT TO DEAL WITH</pattern><template>Steve is so know for his restraint.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THIS EXCLUSIVE  NEVER BEFORE SEEN INTERVIEW  STEVE JOBS GAVE A RARE GLIMPSE OF HIS VISION OF THE WORLD</pattern><template>That's a very limited life.</template></category><category><pattern>TURN ON  TUNE IN  ROCK OUT</pattern><template>He was always so excited about everything, and we went to movies together, and we went to the opera together, and he could talk about everything, and he was this incredibly giving, loyal friend.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID TO THE PEOPLE AT THIS VERY DEMORALIZED  ALMOST OUT OF BUSINESS COMPANY   WE'RE NOT LOOKING BACKWARD</pattern><template>I don't really care that we once had  the first successful personal computer.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYONE IN STEVE JOBS' LIFE WENT THROUGH 3 PHASES</pattern><template>They were either being seduced, ignored, or scourged, and it all depended upon whether he needed you or not.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE COMES A DEVICE THAT COMES WITH NO MANUAL  AND EVERYBODY KNOWS HOW TO USE IT    AMAZING</pattern><template>They weren't just hits in the sense that they sold well, but they actually changed the whole nature of technology and caused everyone else to follow them.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WANTED HIM BACK</pattern><template>They were begging him to come back because they knew he could fix it, and he did come back, and he fixed it, and the rest is history.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A FOND MEMORY FOR STEVE WOZNIAK</pattern><template>He was always thinking about certain technology, the early products that got developed, the building parts, what those might lead to in our future, and he was a always pushing me as an engineer...</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE JOBS STEVE JOBS  ONE LAST THING  MIKHEL FOR SUBTITULOS ES ==SPREAD THE WORD== STEVEN PAUL JOBS DIED ON OCTOBER 5  2011  AT THE AGE OF 56  A LIFE CUT SHORT IN ITS CREATIVE PRIME BY CANCER</pattern><template>His death was not a surprise, and yet its impact reverberated around the world.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S EXCITING WHEN YOU DO THAT  SO I DO FIND THE EXCITEMENT OF THAT  AND HE ALSO MADE THINGS THAT WERE BEAUTIFUL  GREAT TO TOUCH  GREAT TO HOLD  GOOD TO LOOK AT  AND DIFFERENT COLORS</pattern><template>The minute you understand that you can poke life and actually something will...</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THE ANTIPATHY PARTLY GREW OUT OF TWO THINGS</pattern><template>On Jobs' side, he believed that Microsoft had stolen the basic ideas in the Mac.</template></category><category><pattern>FINALLY HE WITHDREW FROM PUBLIC LIFE</pattern><template>Only his closest friends saw how he was coping with the threat of an early death.</template></category><category><pattern>LITERALLY A FACE OFF</pattern><template>I marched past him and wrote on the whiteboard.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW HE PICKED UP THE PACE OF APPLE'S EVOLUTION</pattern><template>Computers?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ONE OF THE HIGHLIGHTS OF MY JOURNALISTIC CAREER TO BE THERE</pattern><template>Thank you very much Thank you so much.</template></category><category><pattern>THE NERD KNOWS EVERYTHING ABOUT WOMEN BUT DOESN'T KNOW ANY WOMEN</pattern><template>You know, Steve knew women.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE NEEDED YOU  HE WAS YOUR BEST FRIEND  AND HE WOULD SEDUCE YOU  AND THEN YOU WOULD WORK LIKE A DOG  AND IF YOU WEREN'T WORKING HARD ENOUGH  HE WOULD SCOURGE YOU  AND ULTIMATELY HE WOULD THROW YOU AWAY</pattern><template>On the personal level, it was not fun, it was not the way I want to be treated by another human being.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS WORTH $100 MILLION WHEN HE WAS 23 YEARS OLD</pattern><template>So he knew nothing but success, and when you're 23 years old, you're worth $100 million, you are pretty damn full of yourself, and that's what Steve became, and so he had huge ambition.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE LEARNED A LITTLE MORE HUMILITY</pattern><template>Steve really changed in a number of ways, and he changed primarily because of failure.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS TEACHER HAD A MAJOR IMPACT ON HIS AESTHETIC AND THE CLEAN LINES OF HIS PRODUCTS</pattern><template>We had many very bright students here, d we had bright thinkers and people that wanted to change things and improve the world.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE JOBS WAS A GENIUS OF THE MODERN AGE</pattern><template>He gave us tools to change our lives and the way we communicate.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T REALLY CARE THAT WE ONCE HAD  THE FIRST SUCCESSFUL PERSONAL COMPUTER</pattern><template>I really don't care that we were famous and successful.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS EXTREMELY SERIOUS</pattern><template>Wayne acted as referee in a minor difference of opinion between the two equal partners.</template></category><category><pattern>MUSICIANS ARE STILL IMPORTANT  BUT PEOPLE LIKE STEVE JOBS ARE UBER  UBERIMPORTANT</pattern><template>They bought CDs, and they want to buy downloads.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS FAULTS</pattern><template>Steve ultimately betrayed everyone.</template></category><category><pattern>SO ONE DAY  STEVE JOBS BICYCLED OVER TO HANG OUT WITH ME AND DO ELECTRONICS PROJECTS IN THE GARAGE  AND OUT IN FRONT WAS WOZNIAK WASHING HIS CAR</pattern><template>So I thought to myself,  ok. This Steve is  an electronics buddy, he's an electronics buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>HA HA HA</pattern><template>The last few years have reminded me that life is fragile um, you know...</template></category><category><pattern>WE TALKED BY THE WAY THE WHOLE WAY</pattern><template>We were dog what he does on walks, which is we were talking about different things, and we got to the park, and we sat on a bench, and we talked about...</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER TOUCH COMPUTERS</pattern><template>I write everything by hand.</template></category><category><pattern>RONALD WAYNE NOW LIVES AND WORKS NEAR LAS VEGAS  A FITTING LOCATION FOR A MAN WHO WALKED AWAY WITH NOTHING FROM A $37 BILLION NO LOSE BET</pattern><template>Wayne was invited to discuss a business proposal with Jobs and Woz.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS ENTHUSING ABOUT A MACHINE HE HAD CREATED IN HIS GARAGE AND SEEKING ADVICE ON A FONT</pattern><template>He was interested in telling me what he was doing and how he was using what he had learned in class, but he wanted some help with Greek letters because he wanted a Greek font, and he couldn't find satisfactory models to go from.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT NEW PRODUCTS</pattern><template>Jobs was hurting his competitors.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN STEVE JOBS LEARNED HE HAD CANCER</pattern><template>A standing ovation for Apple ceo Steve Jobs as he greeted the public for the first time in more than a year.</template></category><category><pattern>HE KNEW HOW TO BEAT IT OUT OF WOZ  AND HE WOULD DO THAT  AND HIS CONTRIBUTIONS AT THAT TIME WERE SAYING   GOSH  WE COULD SELL THESE THINGS   I MEAN  WHICH DOESN'T SOUND LIKE MUCH  BUT IT'S HUGE WHEN YOU'RE DEALING WITH A GUY IN WOZ WHO NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT SELLING ANYTHING</pattern><template>I wanted it to happen so badly, I gave this computer away.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE ABSOLUTE WHIRLWINDS</pattern><template>It was like having a tiger by the tail.</template></category><category><pattern>HE FELT SO BETRAYED  SO ANGRY  SO DISILLUSIONED THAT SCULLEY WAS  IN HIS MIND  AT LEAST PART OF IF NOT THE RINGLEADER IN WHAT HE VIEWED AS A COUP TO REMOVE HIM  AND STEVE WAS PISSED OFF  AND HE WAS REALLY PISSED OFF ABOUT SCULLEY BECAUSE HE BROUGHT SCULLEY IN AND TRUSTED HIM AND THEN FELT BETRAYED BY HIM</pattern><template>So he sold his stock and he went off, took his tens of millions of dollars but not hundreds of millions of dollars and started a new life.</template></category><category><pattern>HE JUST MOVED JUST IN AND EXPLOITED THAT RIGHT TO THE HILT  AND I MUST SAY HE DID A GREAT JOB</pattern><template>He became a billionaire from it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS WORTH A MILLION DOLLARS WHEN HE WAS 21</pattern><template>He was worth $10 million when he was 22.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS LOOKING TO UNDERSTAND THE TRUE NATURE OF THINGS  AND I THINK HE CAME TO THE ZEN CENTER TOTO CONTINUE HIS SEARCH</pattern><template>Steve was very much taken with Zen, Zen Buddhism.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S ONE THING ON WHICH EVERYONE AGREES</pattern><template>Steve Jobs left a legacy that has changed the world.</template></category><category><pattern>HE REALLY DID WANT TO THINK DIFFERENT  AND THEY WOULD HAVE TO APPEAR DIFFERENT TO SHOW THAT THEY WERE THINKING DIFFERENT</pattern><template>The pair joked about the relationship between  Mac Man  Jobs and  PC Man  Bill Gates.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S UPENDED INDUSTRY AFTER INDUSTRY  IT'S FORCED EVERYONE ELSE TO FOLLOW IN HIS PATH  AND IT HAS TOUCHED BILLIONS OF PEOPLE</pattern><template>He will be regarded as the person who unlocked the creativity of a whole generation.</template></category><category><pattern>ITS NAME WAS APPLE</pattern><template>If Woz and Jobs had never met, there never would have been an Apple computer.</template></category><category><pattern>THE VERY FIRST APPLE II COMPUTERS HAD MICROSOFT SOFTWARE IN THEM</pattern><template>But while the banter was good natured, the rivalry between the two was deep rooted.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT ONLY THAT  BUT THEN  ONCE I HAD THE BALLS  I SAID  THAT'S A QUICK WAY TO HAVE A STRUCTURE TO PUT AROUND THE BALL SO THAT I CAN START INTERACTING WITH IT   I REMEMBER GOING TO THE HOUSE WARES AREA  AND I FOUND A BUTTER DISH WHICH WAS ABOUT THIS BIG  AND THAT BECAME THE BEGINNING PART FOR THE MOUSE  AS I FELT IT</pattern><template>So I used the butter dish, the roll on ball and was able to create a prototype.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE NEEDED YOU  HE WAS YOUR BEST FRIEND  AND HE WOULD SEDUCE YOU</pattern><template>When I was having a hard time, he would be on the phone, he'd drive up from silicon valley, take me out for dinner, hang out and take walks with me.</template></category><category><pattern>LIFE CAN BE MUCH BROADER ONCE YOU DISCOVER ONE SIMPLE FACT  AND THAT IS EVERYTHING AROUND YOU THAT YOU CALL LIFE WAS MADE UP BY PEOPLE THAT WERE NO SMARTER THAN YOU</pattern><template>The facts are the story of his life, the story of his successes, the story of his achievements, the stories of the great things he did for other people continue to go on because that's good for our country, it's good for the nation, it's good for the world, and it's also good for the people.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE IT IN FLOWER ARRANGING  IKEBANA  YOU SEE IT CALLIGRAPHY  YOU SEE IT IN IN ARTWORKS</pattern><template>Steve was very much taken with that and especially calligraphy.</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE MID 1980S  HE WAS ONE OF THE RICHEST SELF MADE MEN IN AMERICA</pattern><template>He was just 29.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I EMERGED WITH SOME ROLL ON DEODORANT AND A BUTTER DISH</pattern><template>And as you can see here, there are of course different sized balls, depending upon how it is applied.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ACTUALLY DESIGNED  AND THEY THOUGHT ABOUT THE USER EXPERIENCE AND THAT IT WAS INTENDED REALLY TO BE USED BY A SINGLE PERSON IN SOME INTERACTIVE WAY THAT WAS ENJOYABLE TO THE USER  DIFFERENT</pattern><template>Steve always thought much more broadly than just technology.</template></category><category><pattern>JOBS FREELY ACKNOWLEDGED HOW THESE OUTSIDE INFLUENCES HAD AFFECTED HIM</pattern><template>He was always trying to look for external references and external influences, and he'd talk about, you know, his Mercedes was beautifully designed because those German guys were thinking beautiful thoughts, I guess.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAD THE KIND OF MANNER  THE KIND OF APPROACH TO PEOPLE AND ENVIRONMENTS THAT WERE BUSINESS DIRECTED  OK</pattern><template>He was extremely serious.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE JOBS LEFT A LEGACY THAT HAS CHANGED THE WORLD</pattern><template>He had the ability to think up new ways of doing things, not just improve what we have, do a better version of something, but do it in a totally different way that the world would swing towards.</template></category><category><pattern>SELLING FOR 110 000</pattern><template>From the hippie days of 1970s California, a handful of teenage geeks emerged to change how we work, play, and communicate with each other.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY REALLY HAD A HIGH REGARD FOR HIM</pattern><template>I guess they could see the dynamics already forming in his thinking.</template></category><category><pattern>I INVESTED $20 MILLIONS IN NEXT</pattern><template>He contacted me, asked me to be a principal investor and to serve on the board with him, and I agreed to do it just because of my support for him, and there was no question in my mind that if he...</template></category><category><pattern>THE APPLE II WAS THE FIRST COMPUTER THAT LOOKED LIKE A CONSUMER ELECTRONIC DEVICE</pattern><template>It was actually designed, and they thought about the user experience and that it was intended really to be used by a single person in some interactive way that was enjoyable to the user, different.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE LOVED THOSE CREATIVE IDEAS  AND THAT WAS A MAGIC PART OF THE SUCCESS OF NEXT</pattern><template>A new Steve Jobs was rising out of the ashes of the boardroom battle at Apple, and this time he was ruthless.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE WAS VERY MUCH TAKEN WITH ZEN  ZEN BUDDHISM</pattern><template>Zen represents the relationship between things, things of the world.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ASKED QUESTIONS THAT T RE A LOT MORE SERIOUS THAN THE NORMAL 20 YEAR OLD</pattern><template>He was looking to understand the true nature of things, and I think he came to the zen center Toto continue his search.</template></category><category><pattern>MUCH OF WHAT APPLE DID WAS BUILT ON THE EFFORTS OF OTHERS</pattern><template>A 1979 deal gave him access to Xerox technology, one thing blew him away, a prototype mouse.</template></category><category><pattern>AS I ENTERED WALGREENS  I HAD IN MY MIND MOST IMPORTANTLY WAS   WHERE DO I FIND THESE SPHERES  THESE BALLS TO BE A PART OF THE MOUSE   AND I HAD THOUGHT ABOUT THE UNDERARM DEODORANT AS THE RIGHT SOLUTION</pattern><template>And I emerged with some roll on deodorant and a butter dish.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE DAY I WAS OUT IN SILICON VALLEY</pattern><template>He found out about it, and he conveyed to me that he would like me to come over to his house, and this was just after his liver transplant, which as we all know is a very serious kind of thing that takes a lot of recovery, and he wanted me to come over and just talk about industry gossip in a way or events that had gone on since he'd been kind of out of action.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE LEARNED TO BE A BETTER BUSINESSMAN</pattern><template>I think he learned a little more humility.</template></category><category><pattern>APPLE HAD TO REMEMBER WHO APPLE WAS</pattern><template>It was just crazy what was happening that time, and Apple as very weak, and so I called Bill up and we tried to patch things up.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SHOOK UP A WHOLE INDUSTRY</pattern><template>His character...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  STEVE KNEW WOMEN</pattern><template>So there's that distinction.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU VERY MUCH THANK YOU SO MUCH</pattern><template>In fact, we were quite taken aback by the standing ovation and seeing some of the people from where we were sitting onstage actually shedding tears.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FUNNY THING IS THAT STEVE JOBS HIRED ME  AND HE SAID    HE HAD HAIR JUST DOWN TO HIS WAIST AT THE TIME  AND AS I RECALL HE ONLY ATE FRUIT  AND HE SAID   WE DON'T HAVE VERY MUCH LOOT  SO WE'D LIKE TO PAY YOU IN STOCK   I HELD OUT FOR THE CASH</pattern><template>When Steve Jobs first launched Apple, the computer industry meant mainframes and minicomputers.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE PARK  IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY  WE ACTUALLY TALKED MORE ABOUT LIFE AND HEALTH AND    YOU KNOW  I HAD HAD A HEART ATTACK SOME YEARS BEFORE  AND HE WAS LECTURING ME ABOUT THAT  AND I WAS SORT OF LECTURING HIM  AS WELL  ABOUT WORK/LIFE BALANCE AND ALL THESE THINGS  AND THEN WE GOT UP AND WALKED BACK AND TALKED SOME MORE</pattern><template>And the last thing he said to me was  you know, Walt, you and I have been  through lots of adventures over the last 15 years, and we're going to have some more adventures to come.  We never did.</template></category><category><pattern>WAYNE WAS INVITED TO DISCUSS A BUSINESS PROPOSAL WITH JOBS AND WOZ</pattern><template>That was the first time I had met Steve Wozniak, a fascinating guy a fun guy to be with, very... not only a fun guy to be with, the most gracious man I've ever met in my life.</template></category><category><pattern>INNOVATIVE NEW PRODUCTS POURED IN A SEEMINGLY ENDLESS STREAM FROM APPLE'S DEVELOPMENT LABORATORIES  POURING A STREAM OF CASH INTO APPLE'S COFFERS</pattern><template>250 million or a billion or however many iPods are out there are what built the Apple of today, not the Mac.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE FIRST COMPUTER WHERE YOU USE A KEYBOARD AND A SCREEN TO ENTER AND READ DATA</pattern><template>Selling for 110,000.</template></category><category><pattern>APPLE WAS VERY DIFFERENT</pattern><template>The second you walked in the door, you felt like you were in a completely new environment.</template></category><category><pattern>ALVY QUICKLY FELT HE WAS LOSING CONTROL TO THE NEW MASTER</pattern><template>I would look at my employees looking at Steve, and I realized they're in love.</template></category><category><pattern>IN PART THAT'S BECAUSE I THINK BILL WAS ALWAYS FASCINATED BY STEVE</pattern><template>He was a real observer, and he would just look at this guy and say,  what the heck is going on here?  We've kept our marriage secret for over a decade now.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS CAREER</pattern><template>He shook up a whole industry.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE IS NOW DOING A LOT FOR THE WORLD IN PHILANTHROPY  AND I THINK HIGHLY OF BILL GATES  BUT   OF THE TWO OF THEM  THE ONE THAT TOOK THE BIGGER RISKS AND CHANGED THE GAME MORE OFTEN  IT WAS STEVE</pattern><template>It was Steve Jobs.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I THOUGHT TO MYSELF   OK  THIS STEVE IS  AN ELECTRONICS BUDDY  HE'S AN ELECTRONICS BUDDY</pattern><template>They'd probably like to meet each other.  Fernandez had no idea at the time that the meeting between his two friends would change our world.</template></category><category><pattern>BILL GATES WAS ACTUALLY ONSTAGE RESCUING APPLE  RESCUING APPLE</pattern><template>He did two things.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM THE HIPPIE DAYS OF 1970S CALIFORNIA  A HANDFUL OF TEENAGE GEEKS EMERGED TO CHANGE HOW WE WORK  PLAY  AND COMMUNICATE WITH EACH OTHER</pattern><template>Founders can be divided into two camps.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST NEED A MINUTE AND THEN WE'RE GONNA GO ON TO THE PARK  BECAUSE THAT'S MY GOAL</pattern><template>I set a goal every day, and my goal now is to get to this park.  I said,  you're sure?  And he said,  yeah.  So we walked to the park, and, you know, he was fine.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I SAID   WHAT  WRITE ON A WHITEBOARD   AND HE STORMED OUT OF THE ROOM  AND THEN I WAS IN SHOCK FOR THE NEXT WEEK OR MOTHS</pattern><template>I just didn't know what had happened.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WASN'T JUST THIS PERSON WHO MADE ALL THESE GREAT GADGETS</pattern><template>He actually changed the that way we communicate.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ORIGINAL XEROX PARC HAD 3 BUTTONS  AND THERE WAS A GREAT DEBATE ABOUT HOW MANY BUTTONS WERE RIGHT  AND STEVE ALWAYS HAD THE NOTION OF SIMPLICITY</pattern><template>The magic of Apple products is simple.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MAGIC OF APPLE PRODUCTS IS SIMPLE</pattern><template>There was one button, and it's magic.</template></category><category><pattern>STANDING UP TO JOBS COULD BE A PAINFUL EXPERIENCE  AS ALVY FOUND OUT IN ONE MEMORABLE BOARDROOM MEETING</pattern><template>He turned on me, total street bully, in my face, scream...</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S WAY AHEAD OF HIS TIME</pattern><template>He wasn't the typical teenager.</template></category><category><pattern>A NEW STEVE JOBS WAS RISING OUT OF THE ASHES OF THE BOARDROOM BATTLE AT APPLE  AND THIS TIME HE WAS RUTHLESS</pattern><template>He invested $5 million capital in a corporation called Pixar, and he took 70% of the company, and the employees took 30%.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS THEY COULD SEE THE DYNAMICS ALREADY FORMING IN HIS THINKING</pattern><template>Jobs completed the course in 1974 but returned to palladino just two years later.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE LOS ALTOS SUBURB OF SAN FRANCISCO  CALIFORNIA  JUST ABOUT EVERYBODY WAS AN ENGINEER OR WORKED IN ELECTRONICS A CHILDHOOD SPENT HERE IN THE FUTURE SILICON VALLEY WAS THE FIRST KEY LUCKY BREAK IN STEVE JOBS' YOUNG LIFE</pattern><template>His closest childhood friend was Bill Fernandez.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TWO BOYS SHARED THE SAME HOBBY</pattern><template>We started taking long walks and talking about the meaning of life and what is this all about, and after a while we started doing...</template></category><category><pattern>THEIR INTERVIEW GAVE WALT UNPARALLELED INSIGHTS INTO THE DYNAMICS OF THEIR RELATIONSHIP</pattern><template>But then there was a floating...</template></category><category><pattern>HE GAVE HIS OWN TEAM ORDERS TO MAKE ONE  ONLY BETTER</pattern><template>You got to build it for less than 15 bucks,  it's got to last two years,  I want it to work on the desktop,  a normal formica desktop, and I also want to be able to use it on my jeans.  As I left the meeting headed out to my car, I was thinking,  does this really make sense?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOOD  UH    IT'S GOOD SHOWMANSHIP REALLY</pattern><template>Tragically that  one more thing  has now become  one last thing.  The news that Steve Jobs had finally logged out made headlines everywhere.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WOZ</pattern><template>I'm not fake Steve Jobs.</template></category><category><pattern>BILL GATES IS A A BETTER FRIEND THAN STEVE JOBS  BUT STEVE JOBS IS MORE FUN THAN BILL GATES</pattern><template>Jobs had glamour and dynamism.</template></category><category><pattern>10% OF APPLE TODAY WOULD BE WORTH $37 631 420 312 42  BUT DESPITE HIS SHARE IN THE COMPANY  RON WAS WORRIED THAT WORKING WITH JOBS AND WOZ MIGHT PROVE TO BE TOO STRESSFUL</pattern><template>At 40, I thought I was getting a little old for that.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS ARTISTRY</pattern><template>Just the smooth lines of it.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD YOU POSSIBLY ADD THIS SOMEDAY  COULD YOU POSSIBLY ADD THAT SOMEDAY   YES  YES  YES  I COULD   THINKING   NO</pattern><template>It's way, way off,  but eventually we all did.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SOME SAID THE NEW STEVE JOBS WASN'T AFRAID OF CLAIMING L THE CREDIT  TOO</pattern><template>Disney took  toy story  and another one of their movies to new York for the critics to see, and the critics just...</template></category><category><pattern>I FIRST MET STEVE IN 1975</pattern><template>He had recently returned from India.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THOSE EARLY DAYS  WOZ AND JOBS TOOK THEIR CREATION TO THE HOME BREW COMPUTER CLUB  AN EARLY COMPUTER CLUB  AN EARLY COMPUTER USERS' GROUP IN SILICON VALLEY  WHERE IT QUICKLY ATTRACTED ATTENTION FROM THEIR PEERS</pattern><template>I met both Steves, Steve Jobs and Steve Wozniak at a meeting of the home brew computer club in Palo Alto.</template></category><category><pattern>AWESOME</pattern><template>So Steve's genius is to move when he has a good idea.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME I HAD MET STEVE WOZNIAK  A FASCINATING GUY A FUN GUY TO BE WITH  VERY    NOT ONLY A FUN GUY TO BE WITH  THE MOST GRACIOUS MAN I'VE EVER MET IN MY LIFE</pattern><template>As far as Wozniak was concerned, the world was a great big sand box with a lot of toys to play with.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MUCH FUN WE HAD IN THOSE DAYS DOING THINGS TOGETHER  YOU KNOW  BUT YOU LOSE IT  YOU CAN'T EVER GO BACK  AND JUST TO HAVE THOSE CONVERSATIONS THAT MAKE US BOTH SMILE</pattern><template>Through their eyes, we reveal what made him the man who always gave us...</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAID   HEY  THEY WANT TO USE A BLACK EYED PEAS SONG FOR AN ITUNES COMMERCIAL   AND I SAID WHAT'S ITUNES   AND THEY SAID   THEY'RE NOT PAYING MUCH  BUT THEY'RE GOING TO GIVE YOU GUYS IPODS    WHAT'S AN IPOD   THIS IS THE NEW IPOD NANO</pattern><template>But Jobs' influence on the music industry went far beyond simple star making.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS INTERESTED IN TELLING ME WHAT HE WAS DOING AND HOW HE WAS USING WHAT HE HAD LEARNED IN CLASS  BUT HE WANTED SOME HELP WITH GREEK LETTERS BECAUSE HE WANTED A GREEK FONT  AND HE COULDN'T FIND SATISFACTORY MODELS TO GO FROM</pattern><template>Before Steve started working on computer typefaces, they were in very bad condition, and any improvement would be a step forward.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DID TWO THINGS</pattern><template>He gave them $150 million for which he got nonvoting stock that expired after a certain number of years, and he promised to keep producing Microsoft office, the macintosh version, for, I think, 5 years, and so he was onstage rescuing Apple, and yet the acolytes who were filling the room had learned to hate him.</template></category><category><pattern>AT 40  I THOUGHT I WAS GETTING A LITTLE OLD FOR THAT</pattern><template>They were absolute whirlwinds.</template></category><category><pattern>JOBS COMPLETED THE COURSE IN 1974 BUT RETURNED TO PALLADINO JUST TWO YEARS LATER</pattern><template>He was enthusing about a machine he had created in his garage and seeking advice on a font.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE SOLD HIS STOCK AND HE WENT OFF  TOOK HIS TENS OF MILLIONS OF DOLLARS BUT NOT HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS OF DOLLARS AND STARTED A NEW LIFE</pattern><template>But there were still people willing to back him with hard cash.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS OBSESSED WITH DESIGN  WITH ELEGANT DESIGN  AND HE WAS OBSESSED WITH THE OVERALL EXPERIENCE OF TECHNOLOGY AND THE IDEA OF CREATIVITY GENERALLY</pattern><template>So somehow he was able to bring these things together and create technology that made peoples' eyes light up.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU GROW UP  YOU TEND TO GET TOLD THAT THE WORLD IS THE WAY IT IS AND YOUR LIFE IS JUST TO LIVE YOUR LIFE INSIDE THE WORLD  TRY NOT TO BASH INTO THE WALLS TOO MUCH  TRY TO HAVE A NICE FAMILY LIFE  HAVE FUN  SAVE A LITTLE MONEY</pattern><template>How amazing is it that we live in an era where his legacy will transform people's lives and experiences of technology for the foreseeable future?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY BOUGHT CDS  AND THEY WANT TO BUY DOWNLOADS</pattern><template>People don't want to rent their music Life in Apple's orchard had never been more fruitful.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  OTHERWISE YOU COULD SIT AROUND IN A DARK ROOM AND SULK ABOUT IT  BUT THAT'S NOT STEVE</pattern><template>Steve started a company called NeXT to do a computer that was gonna be what he thought Apple should have been.</template></category><category><pattern>SECONDLY  HE PICKED HIMSELF UP  DUSTED HIMSELF OFF  AND STARTED ALL OVER AGAIN WITH VERY LITTLE HESITATION  AND I REALLY ADMIRED THAT</pattern><template>You know, otherwise you could sit around in a dark room and sulk about it, but that's not Steve.</template></category><category><pattern>THEIR CEOS GAVE A UNIQUE INTERVIEW TO JOURNALIST WALTER MOSSBERG</pattern><template>It was to my knowledge the only time they ever got onstage together to submit themselves to an extended interview with journalists.</template></category><category><pattern>A 5 YEAR OLD 20 YEARS FROM NOW IS GOING TO CREATE AND DESIGN AND INVENT AND DEFINE A WORLD TOTALLY DIFFERENT THAN THE WAY WE SEE IT NOW  AND IT'S GOING TO BE BECAUSE OF STEVE JOBS</pattern><template>Even then he had this ability to bridge a very intellectual world of high technology with something that everyone could relate to.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BRING THEM HOME OVER THE WEEKEND TO WORK ON SOMETHING SUNDAY MORNING</pattern><template>They're not going to be able to get their kids away from them, and maybe someday they'll even buy a second one to leave at home.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE OPENED IT UP  PULLED OUT WHAT WAS ONE OF THOSE FIRST MACINTOSHES OFF THE ASSEMBLY LINE  SET IT UP ON THE FLOOR</pattern><template>Sean was down on the floor with him, Steve turned it on, put macpaint in there.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS NO REAL RESEARCH BEHIND IT</pattern><template>I just messed around on my computer, and it just happened.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS JUST 29</pattern><template>People are going to bring them home over the weekend to work on something Sunday morning.</template></category><category><pattern>DOING ELECTRONICS PROJECTS TOGETHER</pattern><template>Fernandez also knew another electronics geek, his neighbors' son Steve Wozniak, universally known as Woz.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW AMAZING IS IT THAT WE LIVE IN AN ERA WHERE HIS LEGACY WILL TRANSFORM PEOPLE'S LIVES AND EXPERIENCES OF TECHNOLOGY FOR THE FORESEEABLE FUTURE</pattern><template>This single individual gave us the original Apple, the macintosh, and Pixar and the iPod and the iPhone, iPad.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MUCH FUN WE HAD    OHH</pattern><template>How much fun we had in those days doing things together.</template></category><category><pattern>SO RON DECIDED TO HAND BACK HIS SHARE FOR NOTHING AND WALK AWAY WITH NO REGRETS</pattern><template>A lot of people have the impression that somehow or other I got diddled out of something.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR FIRST MEETING WAS REALLY SIMPLE</pattern><template>It was in the parking lot, and I helped them unload Woz's FIAT and carried in what I guess was the first Apple I to show it off to the assembled multitudes.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAD THE ABILITY TO THINK UP NEW WAYS OF DOING THINGS  NOT JUST IMPROVE WHAT WE HAVE  DO A BETTER VERSION OF SOMETHING  BUT DO IT IN A TOTALLY DIFFERENT WAY THAT THE WORLD WOULD SWING TOWARDS</pattern><template>And so we fall in love with Steve because he gave us these toys that were not only fun but really useful. Wow!</template></category><category><pattern>APPLE WAS IN TROUBLE</pattern><template>They wanted him back.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THERE WAS THIS GREAT MOMENT THAT I'LL NEVER FORGET</pattern><template>Andy warhol gets down on his hands and knees with Sean on one side and Steve on the other side.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO YEARS AFTER SCULLEY ARRIVED AT APPLE  THE LOVE AFFAIR TURNED SOUR AS COMPANY PROFITS FALTERED</pattern><template>Steve was never fired from Apple, but he was ostracized and demoted and put in an office in an empty building, and after that he...</template></category><category><pattern>AS JOBS AND I WERE WALKING OVER  I NOTICED WOZ OUT WASHING HIS CAR  AND I SAID   HEY  WOZ</pattern><template>Um, come over and meet Steve.  So,  Steve, meet Steve.  And this is where it happened, basically right here.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT ONLY HE COULD SIT IN FRONT OF THE WHITEBOARD AND ONLY HE COULD USE IT</pattern><template>Nobody had ever tested it, but at this point, I tested it.</template></category><category><pattern>FAILURE AFFECTED HIM  AND HE LEARNED FROM</pattern><template>Jobs created a brand new product at Apple, the iMac.</template></category><category><pattern>I PERSONALLY CAN ATTEST TO HAVING HEARD EACH OF THEM SAY VERY NASTY THINGS ABOUT THE OTHER OFF THE RECORD IN PRIVATE OVER THE YEARS</pattern><template>I think the antipathy partly grew out of two things.</template></category><category><pattern>AS THE TWO GOT TOTO KNOW EACH OTHER  SHEFF REALIZED HE HAD A FRONT ROW SEAT ON WHAT WAS THEN AN UNIMAGINABLE TECHNOLOGICAL FUTURE</pattern><template>Steve started drawing on a place mat.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MADE SENSE TO INCORPORATE HIS SILHOUETTE  HIS PROFILE INTO THE LOGO</pattern><template>It's gotten around 200,000 responses on my blog.</template></category><category><pattern>IN ZEN  IT'S EXPRESSED IN THE ART</pattern><template>You see it in flower arranging, Ikebana, you see it calligraphy, you see it in in artworks.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS JUST STREET BULLY STUFF</pattern><template>I ill don't know what happened.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WER    AND I WENT CRAZY</pattern><template>I'd never been there.</template></category><category><pattern>THE NEWS HAD SPREAD  AND THE TRIBUTES WERE CREATED ON THE NEW IDEVICES THAT HIS VISIONARY GENIUS HAD MADE</pattern><template>His is a success story that could only have happened in the U.S.A.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>It's worth thinking about.</template></category><category><pattern>SO SOMEHOW HE WAS ABLE TO BRING THESE THINGS TOGETHER AND CREATE TECHNOLOGY THAT MADE PEOPLES' EYES LIGHT UP</pattern><template>And I wait 8 hours in a line, and I'm hungry, I am everything you imagine, but I'm happy.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT RON'S OPINION OF STEVE JOBS WAS NOT SO HOT</pattern><template>I wouldn't put gracious in his description.</template></category><category><pattern>SEAN WAS DOWN ON THE FLOOR WITH HIM  STEVE TURNED IT ON  PUT MACPAINT IN THERE</pattern><template>It took him about two seconds to show Sean how to deal with it, and Sean pretty soon was drawing pictures.</template></category><category><pattern>LITERALLY  IT WAS 90 DAYS FROM GOING BANKRUPT</pattern><template>He said to the people at this very demoralized, almost out of business company,  we're not looking backward.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAVE RESOLVED THESE DIFFERENCES IN A VERY  VERY</pattern><template>It was an investment from Bill Gates that ultimately helped to save Apple, but when Gates made a a live appearance with Jobs to explain the deal, it didn't go down well with the loyal Apple audience.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS ALWAYS TRYING TO LOOK FOR EXTERNAL REFERENCES AND EXTERNAL INFLUENCES  AND HE'D TALK ABOUT  YOU KNOW  HIS MERCEDES WAS BEAUTIFULLY DESIGNED BECAUSE THOSE GERMAN GUYS WERE THINKING BEAUTIFUL THOUGHTS  I GUESS</pattern><template>He loved aphorisms.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE'S A GUY WHO REVOLUTIONIZED THE COMPUTER INDUSTRY  THE MUSIC INDUSTRY  THE MOTION PICTURE INDUSTRY  THE TELEPHONE INDUSTRY</pattern><template>There's 4...</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS GOING TO INSPIRE A WHOLE NEW GENERATION</pattern><template>By the people who knew him best.</template></category><category><pattern>ANDY WARHOL GETS DOWN ON HIS HANDS AND KNEES WITH SEAN ON ONE SIDE AND STEVE ON THE OTHER SIDE</pattern><template>I member that warhol would pick up the mouse, and instead of gliding it along the floor, the tiled floor in Sean's bedroom, he would sort of pick it up and was trying to figure out how to make it work, and Steve very patiently would sort of lower his hand down and say,  no. You kind of push it along.  So Andy sort of fooled around with it, and he was completely mesmerized.</template></category><category><pattern>NOBODY HAD EVER TESTED IT  BUT AT THIS POINT  I TESTED IT</pattern><template>I marched past him and I wrote on the whiteboard, and he said,  y y you can't do that.</template></category><category><pattern>WE TALKED ABOUT HIS HEALTH  AND HE TALKED ABOUT HOW HE FELT HE WAS RECOVERING  AND IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS  HE SAID   LET'S GO FOR A WALK   AND I SAID   REALLY  REALLY</pattern><template>You're sure you want to go for a walk?  We're about halfway to the neighborhood park, and he stops, you kn..</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS IN THE PARKING LOT  AND I HELPED THEM UNLOAD WOZ'S FIAT AND CARRIED IN WHAT I GUESS WAS THE FIRST APPLE I TO SHOW IT OFF TO THE ASSEMBLED MULTITUDES</pattern><template>When that same first Apple I was auctioned in 2010, it attracted even more attention.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR MANAGEMENT STYLE WAS TO BE TWO HOURS AWAY FROM HIM  TRY NOT TO HAVE HIM COME INTO THE BUILDING</pattern><template>Standing up to Jobs could be a painful experience, as Alvy found out in one memorable boardroom meeting.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU CAN SEE THAT IT WAS VERY DISRUPTIVE</pattern><template>Our management style was to be two hours away from him, try not to have him come into the building.</template></category><category><pattern>PC GUY IS GREAT BUT NOT A BIG HEART</pattern><template>His mother loves him.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS SINGLE INDIVIDUAL GAVE US THE ORIGINAL APPLE  THE MACINTOSH  AND PIXAR AND THE IPOD AND THE IPHONE  IPAD</pattern><template>That is astonishing.</template></category><category><pattern>I WRITE EVERYTHING BY HAND</pattern><template>Getting letters in the mail is getting to be very rare.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS AN INVESTMENT FROM BILL GATES THAT ULTIMATELY HELPED TO SAVE APPLE  BUT WHEN GATES MADE A A LIVE APPEARANCE WITH JOBS TO EXPLAIN THE DEAL  IT DIDN'T GO DOWN WELL WITH THE LOYAL APPLE AUDIENCE</pattern><template>Bill Gates was actually onstage rescuing Apple, rescuing Apple.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THEY REALLY NEEDED EACH OTHER</pattern><template>He knew how to beat it out of Woz, and he would do that, and his contributions at that time were saying,  gosh. We could sell these things.  I mean, which doesn't sound like much, but it's huge when you're dealing with a guy in Woz who never thought about selling anything.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SO WE FALL IN LOVE WITH STEVE BECAUSE HE GAVE US THESE TOYS THAT WERE NOT ONLY FUN BUT REALLY USEFUL  WOW</pattern><template>It's upended industry after industry, it's forced everyone else to follow in his path, and it has touched billions of people.</template></category><category><pattern>SO OVER THE COURSE OF ABOUT 4 OR 5 YEARS  HE OWNED IT ALL</pattern><template>Alvy quickly felt he was losing control to the new master.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE    AND I WENT CRAZY</pattern><template>I'd never been there.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ALWAYS HAD  ONE MORE THING  TO ANNOUNCE</pattern><template>Everyone thinks,  wow.</template></category><category><pattern>EDISON ONLY HAD 3</pattern><template>That's impact.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I THINK IN JOBS' CASE  THE PARTICULAR PATH OF HIS CAREER  THIS COULD ONLY HAVE HAPPENED IN AMERICA</pattern><template>Steve Jobs' world class salesmanship found a global audience in his famous Apple product presentations.</template></category><category><pattern>HE RESIGNED IN 1985 AND THEN IMMEDIATELY SOLD HIS MORE THAN 6 MILLION SHARES</pattern><template>He was the largest single shareholder of Apple at the time, and sold his stock at a bad price and didn't get as much money as he should have or could have had he done it smartly, but he was angry.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WOZ AND JOBS HAD NEVER MET  THERE NEVER WOULD HAVE BEEN AN APPLE COMPUTER</pattern><template>There would have been computers, and there would have been personal computers, but we probably wouldn't have the kind of wonderful empowering things that people fall into if Woz and Jobs hadn't met.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK OF MOST THINGS IN LIFE AS EITHER A BOB DYLAN OR BEATLES SONG  BUT THERE'S THAT ONE LINE IN THAT ONE BEATLES SONG   YOU AND I HAVE MEMORIES LONGER THAN THE ROAD THAT STRETCHES OUT AHEAD   AND THAT'S CLEARLY TRUE HERE</pattern><template>That's sweet I think we should end it there.</template></category><category><pattern>NOBODY DIDDLED ME OUT OF ANYTHING</pattern><template>Wayne may not be bitter, but he wasn't the only early Apple employee who made a life decision most of us would regret.</template></category><category><pattern>UM  ONCE YOU LEARN THAT  YOU'LL NEVER BE THE SAME AGAIN</pattern><template>In the Los altos suburb of San Francisco, California, just about everybody was an engineer or worked in electronics a childhood spent here in the future silicon valley was the first key lucky break in Steve Jobs' young life.</template></category><category><pattern>ANDY WARHOL GETS DOWN ON HIS HANDS AND KNEES  STEVE SHOWING HIM HOW TO USE THE MOUSE</pattern><template>His career...</template></category><category><pattern>HE NOTICED THE WAY THE LINES AND THE SPACES HAD A RELATIONSHIP</pattern><template>I think his genius was being able to take the principles of zen and incorporate it into the products that came out of Apple.</template></category><category><pattern>ON THE PERSONAL LEVEL  IT WAS NOT FUN  IT WAS NOT THE WAY I WANT TO BE TREATED BY ANOTHER HUMAN BEING</pattern><template>Steve ultimately betrayed everyone.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS TO MY KNOWLEDGE THE ONLY TIME THEY EVER GOT ONSTAGE TOGETHER TO SUBMIT THEMSELVES TO AN EXTENDED INTERVIEW WITH JOURNALISTS</pattern><template>Their interview gave Walt unparalleled insights into the dynamics of their relationship.</template></category><category><pattern>JOBS HAD GLAMOUR AND DYNAMISM</pattern><template>By the mid 1980s, he was one of the richest self made men in America.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT PALLADINO WITNESSED FIRST HAND THE IMPACT JOBS HAD ON HIS PEERS</pattern><template>The other students brought him to me like they were bringing me someone very special.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ADMIRED STEVE FOR HIS ABILITY TO INTERFACE WITH PEOPLE  CONNECT WITH THEM  YOU KNOW  AFFECT THEM</pattern><template>They were partners, you know, for a long time.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S WORTH THINKING ABOUT</pattern><template>The truth about Bill Gates is a brilliant man who you could... and I did talk to for long periods about the future.</template></category><category><pattern>ON OCTOBER 5  2011  STEVE JOBS DIED</pattern><template>The next day, his closest friend and colleague Steve Wozniak paid his own tribute.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THE WORLD WILL MISS STEVE JOBS</pattern><template>He took stuff to a new place, and I do identify with that.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT IN A DESIGN SO SMALL AS SOMETHING THAT FITS IN YOUR HAND THERE COULD BE MUCH CONTROVERSY AROUND IT  BUT IT TURNS OUT THERE WAS ONE MAJOR CONTROVERSY  WHICH WAS HOW MANY BUTTONS SHOULD THERE BE</pattern><template>The original Xerox PARC had 3 buttons, and there was a great debate about how many buttons were right, and Steve always had the notion of simplicity.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A VERY LIMITED LIFE</pattern><template>Life can be much broader once you discover one simple fact, and that is everything around you that you call life was made up by people that were no smarter than you, and you can change it, you can influence it, you can build your own things that other people can use.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  THE MAC COMPUTER IS AN ARTIST'S COMPUTER</pattern><template>Musicians are still important, but people like Steve Jobs are uber, uberimportant.</template></category><category><pattern>WE STARTED TAKING LONG WALKS AND TALKING ABOUT THE MEANING OF LIFE AND WHAT IS THIS ALL ABOUT  AND AFTER A WHILE WE STARTED DOING</pattern><template>In addition to walking and talking...</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T MEAN TO SAY THAT THERE AREN'T GENIUSES AND WORLD CHANGING PEOPLE EVERYWHERE    THERE ARE</pattern><template>But I think in Jobs' case, the particular path of his career, this could only have happened in America.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PAIR QUICKLY MOVED ON FROM PHONE JACKING FOR FUN TO CREATING COMPUTERS  BUILDING THE PROTOTYPE OF THE VERY FIRST APPLE</pattern><template>It's a fond memory for Steve Wozniak.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WEREN'T JUST HITS IN THE SENSE THAT THEY SOLD WELL  BUT THEY ACTUALLY CHANGED THE WHOLE NATURE OF TECHNOLOGY AND CAUSED EVERYONE ELSE TO FOLLOW THEM</pattern><template>This intimate portrait is a revealing insight into Steve Jobs' life...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MUCH FUN WE HAD IN THOSE DAYS DOING THINGS TOGETHER</pattern><template>You lose it, you can't ever go back and just have those conversations that make us both smile.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT FAKE STEVE JOBS</pattern><template>If you saw them together, Steve always dominated the conversation.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAW IT AS A READER ON THIS VERY SMALL DEVICE AND READ IT WITH EDITING CAPACITY  NOTE TAKING CAPACITY</pattern><template>I mean, he really envisioned the iPad almost 30 years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS ONE BUTTON  AND IT'S MAGIC</pattern><template>From the early days, one man influenced Steve Jobs more than any other, his friend and rival Bill Gates.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT TO BUILD IT FOR LESS THAN 15 BUCKS   IT'S GOT TO LAST TWO YEARS   I WANT IT TO WORK ON THE DESKTOP   A NORMAL FORMICA DESKTOP  AND I ALSO WANT TO BE ABLE TO USE IT ON MY JEANS   AS I LEFT THE MEETING HEADED OUT TO MY CAR  I WAS THINKING   DOES THIS REALLY MAKE SENSE</pattern><template>Is Steve crazy or is there something here?  If Steve wanted something, his team just had to innovate, so for dean n at meant a trip to the drug store.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GREAT AT ENCOURAGING MEN TO BE CREATIVE AND COME UP WITH NEW IDEAS AND NOT JUST BE LITTLE ROBOTS  WHICH MANY BIG COMPANIES JUST WANT YOU TO BE A LITTLE ROBOT AND DO WHAT YOU'RE TOLD TO DO  AND THE LAST THING THEY WANT TO HEAR FROM YOU IS A CREATIVE IDEA</pattern><template>Steve loved those creative ideas, and that was a magic part of the success of NeXT.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS THE LARGEST SINGLE SHAREHOLDER OF APPLE AT THE TIME  AND SOLD HIS STOCK AT A BAD PRICE AND DIDN'T GET AS MUCH MONEY AS HE SHOULD HAVE OR COULD HAVE HAD HE DONE IT SMARTLY  BUT HE WAS ANGRY</pattern><template>He felt so betrayed, so angry, so disillusioned that Sculley was, in his mind, at least part of if not the ringleader in what he viewed as a coup to remove him, and Steve was pissed off, and he was really pissed off about Sculley because he brought Sculley in and trusted him and then felt betrayed by him.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE PARTNERS  YOU KNOW  FOR A LONG TIME</pattern><template>The very first Apple II computers had Microsoft software in them.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS LOVE WAS APPLE</pattern><template>He envisioned being with Apple for his life.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS ABILITY TO ALWAYS COME AROUND AND FIGURE OUT WHERE THAT NEXT BET SHOULD BE HAS BEEN PHENOMENAL</pattern><template>Apple literally was failing when Steve went back and re infused the innovation and risk taking that have been phenomenal.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM THE EARLY DAYS  ONE MAN INFLUENCED STEVE JOBS MORE THAN ANY OTHER  HIS FRIEND AND RIVAL BILL GATES</pattern><template>Apple's history interweaves with Microsoft's.</template></category><category><pattern>JOBS DREW ON A DIVERSE RANGE OF INFLUENCES TO FEED HIS CREATIVITY  INCLUDING A CLASS HE DROPPED INTO AT COLLEGE IN PORTLAND  OREGON  IN THE EARLY SEVENTIES</pattern><template>Reed college has one of the best calligraphy courses in the U.S.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MAN WHO WITNESSED JOBS' RETURN TO APPLE WAS FRIEND WALT MOSSBERG</pattern><template>He came back to Apple, and the company was almost dead.</template></category><category><pattern>DISNEY TOOK  TOY STORY  AND ANOTHER ONE OF THEIR MOVIES TO NEW YORK FOR THE CRITICS TO SEE  AND THE CRITICS JUST</pattern><template>They didn't even look at the other movie.</template></category><category><pattern>IN FACT  WE WERE QUITE TAKEN ABACK BY THE STANDING OVATION AND SEEING SOME OF THE PEOPLE FROM WHERE WE WERE SITTING ONSTAGE ACTUALLY SHEDDING TEARS</pattern><template>It sounds strange, but it was actually an emotional thing.</template></category><category><pattern>STEVE SAID THIS MACHINE  THIS SMALL DEVICE AS BIG AS A BOOK  WOULD ALLOW US TO KEEP IN TOUCH WITH ONE ANOTHER  IT WILL REPLACE THE TELEPHONE AND WOULD REPLACE BOOKSTORES</pattern><template>He saw it as a reader on this very small device and read it with editing capacity, note taking capacity.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AS YOU CAN SEE HERE  THERE ARE OF COURSE DIFFERENT SIZED BALLS  DEPENDING UPON HOW IT IS APPLIED</pattern><template>Not only that, but then, once I had the balls, I said, that's a quick way to have a structure to put around the ball so that I can start interacting with it?  I remember going to the house wares area, and I found a butter dish which was about this big, and that became the beginning part for the mouse, as I felt it.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PAIR JOKED ABOUT THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN  MAC MAN  JOBS AND  PC MAN  BILL GATES</pattern><template>PC guy is great but not a big heart.</template></category><category><pattern>HE FOUND OUT ABOUT IT  AND HE CONVEYED TO ME THAT HE WOULD LIKE ME TO COME OVER TO HIS HOUSE  AND THIS WAS JUST AFTER HIS LIVER TRANSPLANT  WHICH AS WE ALL KNOW IS A VERY SERIOUS KIND OF THING THAT TAKES A LOT OF RECOVERY  AND HE WANTED ME TO COME OVER AND JUST TALK ABOUT INDUSTRY GOSSIP IN A WAY OR EVENTS THAT HAD GONE ON SINCE HE'D BEEN KIND OF OUT OF ACTION</pattern><template>He was very frail.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID   I DREW A CIRCLE   AND IT WAS GREAT</pattern><template>Life had been good for Steve Jobs.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T EVER WANT TO BE THERE AGAIN</pattern><template>That's the reason I got away from him.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KEY TO THE SUCCESS OF THE COMPANY WAS IN MOVING BEYOND THE COMPUTER  WAS IN SEEING HOW THE MICROPROCESSOR WAS GETTING SO CHEAP THAT IT COULD BE APPLIED TO OTHER CONSUMER ELECTRONIC DEVICES</pattern><template>Innovative new products poured in a seemingly endless stream from Apple's development laboratories, pouring a stream of cash into Apple's coffers.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IN TERMS OF INTUITIVE TASTE BOTH FOR PEOPLE AND PRODUCTS  THE WAY HE DOES THINGS IS JUST DIFFERENT  AND I THINK IT'S MAGICAL</pattern><template>Despite their rivalry, in this joint appearance after Jobs had been diagnosed with cancer, they displayed a healthy respect and even affection for one another.</template></category><category><pattern>NEITHER PERSON IS HUGELY LIKABLE</pattern><template>Certainly Steve Jobs is an acquired taste, and so is Bill Gates for that matter.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ENVISIONED BEING WITH APPLE FOR HIS LIFE</pattern><template>He said,  but that doesn't mean there won't be periods  when I will leave and I will do other things and my life will weave in and out of Apple.  Once again, Jobs' foresight was spot on.</template></category><category><pattern>THROUGH THE LATE SIXTIES AND SEVENTIES IN VERY SIMILAR WAYS  GONG THROUGH SOME OF THE COUNTER CULTURE  YOU KNOW BEING  INFLUENCED BY SOME OF THE EASTERN MYSTICISM  BUDDHISM  THE LSD CULTURE  TIMOTHY LEARY</pattern><template>Turn on, tune in, rock out.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S CHANGED THE WAY WE LOOK AT COMPUTERS  PHONES  HOW WE SHARE  INTERACT</pattern><template>He's going to inspire a whole new generation.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  WHEN YOU MAKE A LONG DISTANCE PHONE CALL IN THE BACKGROUND YOU HEAR   DO DO DO DO DO</pattern><template>Those are the telephone computers actually signing each other, sending information to each other to set up your call.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEN THERE WAS A FLOATING</pattern><template>From the start, Gates was overshadowed by the more polished, confident Jobs.</template></category><category><pattern>GETTING LETTERS IN THE MAIL IS GETTING TO BE VERY RARE</pattern><template>Dropping out of college, Jobs went on the hippie trail, traveling to India and studying Buddhism, this also had an impact on his work at Apple.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAD MANY VERY BRIGHT STUDENTS HERE  D WE HAD BRIGHT THINKERS AND PEOPLE THAT WANTED TO CHANGE THINGS AND IMPROVE THE WORLD</pattern><template>But Palladino witnessed first hand the impact Jobs had on his peers.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D GIVE A LOT TO HAVE STEVE'S TASTE</pattern><template>If he needed You, he was your best friend, and he would seduce you.</template></category></AIML>