<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>GUESS WHERE WE JUST CAME FROM  AN EXPLOSION AT YOUR ACCOUNTING OFFICE</pattern><template>It's an awful gas leak.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KILL US  WE KILL ERSHON AND YOU LOST $30 MILLION</pattern><template>Who's got the golden goose now, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>HUH  HUH  ALL RIGHT  YOU SWEETIE  COME ON  LET'S GO</pattern><template>Move!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HE COME OUT OF NOWHERE</pattern><template>That was 20 miles.</template></category><category><pattern>UH   SARAH CAPONE FROM TMZ    PRINT EDITION  UH  DANSON  ARE THE RUMORS ABOUT YOU AND KIM KARDASHIAN TRUE</pattern><template>No comment.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO CARES</pattern><template>Some rich prick.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHTY</pattern><template>I did things in bed with you that I haven't done with anyone since.</template></category><category><pattern>ARNOLD SCHWARZENEGGER</pattern><template>God damn it, let me fini.. They ruined the story... they ruined the story No, the point is, we couldn't do our job if it weren't for you guys doing all the paperwork,...</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU REALLY ALLEN'S WIFE</pattern><template>Umm I know, people are shocked. Because he is Episcopalian and I am Catholic...</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE PICK UP    HELLO    HEY SWEETIE  I WAS PRAYING YOU BE AT YOUR MOM'S HOUSE</pattern><template>You know what, I can't talk anymore, I think the phone is being tapped.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  GUESS WHAT  YOU'RE COMING WITH ME</pattern><template>That's a wooden gun.</template></category><category><pattern>HE PREFERS CAPTAIN</pattern><template>Yes, I was talking to Gene here and you know what's funny?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT A BRIBE</pattern><template>We're hanging over here tonight Nobody knows about this place. We'd be safe.</template></category><category><pattern>SCAFFOLDING PERMITS</pattern><template>Yeah. Guess what. You're coming with me.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH    NOT IT'S NOT    THEY WERE SO CONVINCING</pattern><template>.. in their argument. They swung me.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE</pattern><template>All right, what did you do?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  YOU KEEP HIDING FROM SHIT IN THE WORLD  AND EVENTUALLY THE WORLD COMES TO YOUR FRONT DOOR</pattern><template>Nice!   That's very nice!   I heard it in an episode of Touched by an Angel.</template></category><category><pattern>OH GOD</pattern><template>Yeah, you know what that's called when they do that in there? It's called a soup kitchen.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT CAPTAIN</pattern><template>No no no, it's done.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  DO NOT STOP PROFITING  LIVE FOR EXCESS</pattern><template>It's the American way.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT 'S THE STATE'S MONEY</pattern><template>What do we tell Mauch?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU KIDDING ME  YOU CANNOT GO DOWN THERE</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU PROBABLY THINK BECAUSE OF THE BEARD THAT I'M REALLY HAIRY</pattern><template>But that's not me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S MY IPHONE</pattern><template>I think we walked 30 blocks.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CODE  I'M YOUR PARTNER</pattern><template>I am here to support a friend and a work colleague.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY FELLAS  HOW ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>We are about to have us a little scoop party in the red Prius over here if you want to join us.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY GUYS  THE SOUP IS ON</pattern><template>What do you mean?</template></category><category><pattern>THE TRANSFER IS FOR HIM  HE WILL TELL YOU NOT TO AUTHORIZE IT  OK  TELL HIM</pattern><template>Tell him!</template></category><category><pattern>GATOR TOOK VANS UPSIDE DOWN  LIKE A CRAZY WASHING MACHINE</pattern><template>Why are you calling yourself Gator?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WE DID NOT</pattern><template>Sorry gentlemen, we thought you were abducting Mr. Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I KNOW</pattern><template>They jumped from 20 stories.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE THE RIGHT TO REMAIN SILENT</pattern><template>... but I want to hear you scream...</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT LET THIS MAN TAKE ME</pattern><template>Hi..</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT TWO ROGUE POLICE OFFICERS</pattern><template>They're armed and dangerous and holding David Ershon hostage.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU DON'T HAVE TO   NO I DON'T LIKE YOU I THINK YOU'RE A FAKE COP  THE SOUND OF YOUR PISS HITTING THE URINAL  IT SOUNDS FEMININE IF YOU WERE IN THE WILD  I WOULD ATTACK YOU  EVEN IF YOU WEREN'T IN MY FOOD CHAIN</pattern><template>I would go out of my way to attack you.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIKE WORKING TRAFFIC  IT'S A GREAT GIG</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD'VE SHOT EVRA YO  PAPER BITCH    WHAT'S UP MAN    HEY GUYS PAPER BITCH  PAPER BITCH   I DON'T LIKE THAT ACTUALLY  I KNOW YOU GUYS THINK IT'S FUN  BUT I DON'T LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Still working on Danson and Highsmith paperwork?</template></category><category><pattern>BECOME A DJ  NOW THE LAST THING I NEED IS A BALLISTICS REPORT IN THE UNIT  JUST GONNA ASK YOU GUYS  PLEASE  COME ON</pattern><template>Really, just think about it. Just be smart.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA HANG ON TO THE WOODEN GUN</pattern><template>To give me back my real gun?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO TO NEW JERSEY AND VISIT AN ACCOUNTING FIRM  THAT'S A SHITTY DAY</pattern><template>Do you have fun singing those songs? They are really depressing.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A SHORTCUT</pattern><template>Are you kidding me? You cannot go down there.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CALL THIS IN  RIGHT</pattern><template>Looks like we got all the evidence we need.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S BEEN DODGING THIS CASE FOR TOO LONG AND I WANT ANSWERS  I WANT HIM TO LOOK ME IN THE EYE AND TELL ME WHY</pattern><template>Turn on the news man, nobody cares.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO PAY THAT ULTIMATE SACRIFICE SO THAT WE MAY WALK THESE STREETS SAFELY THERE WASN'T EVEN AN AWNING IN THAT GARAGE</pattern><template>No, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE NIGERIANS</pattern><template>Yeah, I forgot about that.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ATTENDING PHYSICIAN TOLD ME: WE HAVE A DRUGGED OUT PIMP IN THE BACK</pattern><template>And I went back there and I pulled open that curtain...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THIS IS SERIOUS STUFF WE'RE DEALING WITH</pattern><template>Ok? This is firing your weapon in the line of duty Officer Hoitz Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  THE BRAKE  JUST SLOW THE CAR DOWN WE'RE GOING TO THE CRIME SCENE</pattern><template>Yeah, yeah Dude!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT I WILL NOT DO SERIOUSLY  STOP HUMMING  OK  THIS ISN'T ACCOUNTING OR WHEREVER THE HELL YOU AND YOUR LITTLE POCKEY CALCULATOR WERE TRANSFERRED FROM FORENSIC ACCOUNTING  OK  IT IS AN IMPORTANT PART OF THE JOB   YEAH WHATEVER STOP BEING VERBALLY HAPPY ABOUT DOING SHITWORK  YOU MORON   HEY GUYS REMINDER: THE POLICE UNIT PICNIC'S COMING UP THIS WEEKEND</pattern><template>My wife's making her famous devil eggs again.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  SHOT FIRED</pattern><template>Hey Terry! I did it! I did my first desk pop It's a real thing right?</template></category><category><pattern>TO SHOW A MASSIVE LOSSES THEN YOU PAY YOUR EMPLOYER</pattern><template>Now, since you're following me, I need to go to 2300 Park Avenue .. and after that 400..</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MAY RING THE BELL NOW MS  BOARDMAN</pattern><template>32.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE WOULD LOVE TO JUST GET THE MESSAGE OFF YOUR CELLPHONE  WE BELIEVE IT MIGHT GIVE US AN INFORMATION REGARDING A KIDNAPPING</pattern><template>Ok, why don't you come to the kitchen and I will let you listen to it, and everyone else stay here.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Hit him.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE GO</pattern><template>Okay, any tazers? No? Good.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HOW ARE YOU  SON OF A BITCH</pattern><template>Hey, hey, hey.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO OF THOSE    WATER PLEASE NO LIME WEDGES  JUST CUCUMBER</pattern><template>Guess where we just came from? An explosion at your accounting office.</template></category><category><pattern>WHILE FINISHING MY RESIDENCY AT COLUMBIA HOSPITAL</pattern><template>Allen came in to the ER with poison ivy on his rectum.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  GO  GO  BE CAREFUL</pattern><template>Thanks. I will.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FIRST BILLION DOLLARS</pattern><template>That man.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  THEY RETURN YOUR SHOES  AND THEY RETURN YOUR WEAPONS  HERE YOU GO  TERRY</pattern><template>Allen, someone is nice enough to put linseed oil on it. Some kind of stain on that.</template></category><category><pattern>SAY SOMETHING</pattern><template>Come on, Bob. I didn't mean it, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WOULD BE THE EVIDENCE WE NEED FOR MAUCH</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>PEACE OUT  BITCHES</pattern><template>Hey, fellas. all right, bring it in. Come on, bring it a little bit All right. Right there.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I FORGOT ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>This is a shortcut.</template></category><category><pattern>WITHIN 24 HOURS LEARNING ABOUT ERSHON'S SCHEME AND LENDL'S MASSIVE LOSSES</pattern><template>the government issued TARP fund to bail out Lendl.</template></category><category><pattern>OR  STRAIGHT WITH US</pattern><template>Terry. Watch this now.</template></category><category><pattern>FEMALE BODY INSPECTOR</pattern><template>You know, because we are both in law enforcement, we both like women, but I got a weird sense of humor.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  ACTUALLY</pattern><template>What is this?   Guys   Illegal permitting for construction.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S OK  DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT  YOU CAN CALL ME GENE WHEN WE'RE NOT IN OFFICE</pattern><template>Thanks for coming by.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS DON BEAMAN  AN ATTORNEY FOR MR  ERSHON</pattern><template>Roger Wesley, head of his private security.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK GUYS  HAVE A GOOD ONE</pattern><template>Let's go!   No, I got work to do.   What? This is work!</template></category><category><pattern>HE ALSO SAYS THAT HE WANTS YOU TO STARE INTO EACH OTHER EYES WITHOUT BLINKING WHILE YOU DO IT</pattern><template>And then afterward, lick the sweat off each other.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY HAVE YOU WORKED YOUR ASS OFF TRYING TO KILL THIS CASE</pattern><template>All right, fine! I'm gonna tell you guys something.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BLOW THAT IF YOU'RE IN ANY TROUBLE  SOMEONE WITH AN ACTUAL GUN WILL COME AND HELP YOU OUT</pattern><template>We were abducted, Captain. This shit is real.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU GET BACK HERE  YOU MAKE OUT MY WIFE</pattern><template>Allen!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S PARTNERS CODE  I HAD NO CHOICE</pattern><template>9:15, let's have a great day everybody.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  I'M PREGNANT</pattern><template>Whose baby is that? Who's the man who did that to you?</template></category><category><pattern>MULTINATIONAL TEAM  MAYBE A SLEEPER CELL  BUT IT'S TOO EARLY TO TELL</pattern><template>Hey, Double Baggins, where are your shoes? Your feet are black.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TRUE</pattern><template>Christina, this is a lovely house.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TALK OR I BEAT YOU SO WE DON'T SHOW NO BRUISES</pattern><template>God, this water is good.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY TIME YOU SAY 'BE SAFE'  IT TEARS ME APART  YOU GOT TO LET ME BE WHO I'M GONNA BE</pattern><template>Allen, I'm pregnant.</template></category><category><pattern>BEAMAN'S OFFICE</pattern><template>We have to go.</template></category><category><pattern>I GO OUT ALL THE TIME WITH THE WHOLE BUNCH OF YOU KNOW BOYS</pattern><template>And I kinda need somebody to help me out Like, you know, my partner in crime.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO HAND OVER YOUR GUN</pattern><template>Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  THIS IS FIRING YOUR WEAPON IN THE LINE OF DUTY OFFICER HOITZ HERE WE GO</pattern><template>Would you like to share?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE TELLS ME THAT EVERY DAY BEFORE I LEAVE</pattern><template>I do, we come downstairs and make him his fresh cut strawberries and I say: Listen my little sugar bowls, whatever you do today, you just don't get hurt.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SITTING HERE THINKING  WHO IN THE WORLD WOULD SLOW ROAST A DOG'S ASSHOLE AND SERVE IT TO THEIR HUSBAND</pattern><template>You would.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LEFT A NOTE IN THAT CAR</pattern><template>Police, shithead.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SORRY  I GOT SO DRUNK LAST NIGHT I THINK I THOUGHT A TUBE OF TOOTHPASTE WAS ASTRONAUT FOOD</pattern><template>Come on in, fellas.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH YEAH  WHERE ARE YOU  WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Captain, it's a long story but I am just gonna cut to the chase. We are in Las Vegas.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE DOWN HERE STARTED TO MURMUR THAT YOU DON'T HAVE THE BALLS TO DO IT</pattern><template>I don't care.</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN IT  BOB</pattern><template>Let me ask you something. What do you even do around here besides interrupt people?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT EVEN I ADMIT  THAT'S NOT VERY TEMPTING  I'M NOT MADE OF TICKETS  GOD DAMN IT</pattern><template>Shoot him.</template></category><category><pattern>TAP ON  TAP ON</pattern><template>Are you tapping off? You're hitting me in the face.</template></category><category><pattern>OH NICE</pattern><template>Seven calls to the lottery office.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS BAD  NO WONDER THE CAPTAIN WANTED US TO STAY OUT OF THIS</pattern><template>I bet Beaman started asking question and that's why they killed him.</template></category><category><pattern>ROGER WESLEY  HEAD OF HIS PRIVATE SECURITY</pattern><template>Hey, How are you, son of a bitch?</template></category><category><pattern>SOUNDS CREEPY  CAPTAIN GENE</pattern><template>Police mistakenly arrest investment banker David Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>HONESTLY  I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>Tell me who you lost your virginity to?</template></category><category><pattern>OK  LET ME TURN IT ON</pattern><template>Mr. Beaman?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S AN OFFICIAL POLICE CAR</pattern><template>You could've fooled me.</template></category><category><pattern>STILL WORKING ON DANSON AND HIGHSMITH PAPERWORK</pattern><template>No, actually...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF WE STOP THE TRANSFER</pattern><template>You have to be at the endemic bank at 9 o'clock exactly.</template></category><category><pattern>GO</pattern><template>We are cops, hit the chopper.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS FOR COMING BY</pattern><template>Atta boy.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT CHATSON AND WESTES</pattern><template>We went an Chechen version of Dora the Explorer.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY SIR  I TRIED TO KEEP THEM IN THE WAITING ROOM</pattern><template>That's ok, Susan, uh, two glacier water with Mediterranean lime...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE THAT  IT WENT BACKWARDS AND THEN TURNED UPSIDE DOWN</pattern><template>Gator took vans upside down, like a crazy washing machine.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T SPEAK TO HER LIKE THAT  ALLEN</pattern><template>Look, If I put that into my Cosmo questionnaire, you got a D  Allen and his abs. He loves them. You know he has designed three of his own?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE BEING RIDICULOUS    THEY SOUND LIKE A BABY BLOWING OUT THE CANDLES AT A BIRTHDAY CAKE    WHAT</pattern><template>A little... bzzz.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S NOT DRUGS  THIS ISN'T MIAMI VICE</pattern><template>Hey, I got you a gift. I just saw something and I thought of you and so I do not want it to be weird, I just want it to be nice.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  FIRST OFF: A LION  SWIMMING IN THE OCEAN  LIONS DON'T LIKE WATER IF YOU PLACED IT NEAR A RIVER OR SOME SORT OF FRESH WATER SOURCE  THAT MAKE SENSE</pattern><template>But you find yourself in the ocean, 20 foot wave, I'm assuming off the coast of South Africa, coming up against a full grown 800 pound tuna with his 20 or 30 friends, you lose that battle, you lose that battle 9 times out of 10. And guess what, you've wandered into our school of tuna and we now have a taste of lion. We've talked to ourselves.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT NO FINGERPRINTS</pattern><template>a bunch of losing lottery tickets...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST STOOD THERE</pattern><template>I didn't know. How was I supposed to know that?</template></category><category><pattern>DAVID ERSHON  WEALTHY BANKER</pattern><template>Multinational team. Maybe a sleeper cell, but it's too early to tell.</template></category><category><pattern>DARK WALNUT OR SOMETHING  YOU MAY WANNA THINK ABOUT DROPPING THEM A THANK YOU NOTE</pattern><template>Ok, you're mad at us, huh, Gene?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN EITHER WALK THE PLAN OR TAKE YOUR PANTIES OFF  THE CHOICE IS YOURS</pattern><template>You want to take my panties off?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GO  MAN</pattern><template>Ok. Thanks.   Go!</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT</pattern><template>Take it easy.</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE  SHITHEAD</pattern><template>They are cops. We gotta go. Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  PLEASE</pattern><template>Remember us, hot shot?</template></category><category><pattern>FASTER  ALLEN</pattern><template>Hold on. Hold on.</template></category><category><pattern>FINE</pattern><template>And let me apologize in advance ok? In case my wife acts like a world class bitch She is a big ol' broad and she likes to wield it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL JUST SEE WHO'S THERE FIRST</pattern><template>You stay out of our crime scene. You hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DO ONE THING WHEN YOU WAKE UP TOMORROW    BRING IT  THANK YOU  SHEILA</pattern><template>He'll bring it. Good night.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM NEAR THE PLACE WHERE WE DID IT 3 HALLOWEENS AGO  DO YOU REMEMBER</pattern><template>Umm, ok, yeah I got it.</template></category><category><pattern>I FOUND SOME GREAT INFORMATION</pattern><template>About what?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE TOO BIG TO FAIL</pattern><template>Ershon now resides in Palamino federal correctional facility in Florida.</template></category><category><pattern>NEGATORY  MARTIN AND FOSSI  TWO MINUTES  OUT</pattern><template>We'll just see who's there first.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL OF HER WANTS  HER NEEDS AND DESIRES ARE NOW MY RESPONSIBILITY</pattern><template>Why do you say it like it's a pre determined thing?</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD TERRY ABOUT MY DARK DAYS IN COLLEGE AND I</pattern><template>it brought up some feelings.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  THIS WATER IS GOOD</pattern><template>Terry, have you tried the water?</template></category><category><pattern>AIM FOR THE BUSHES</pattern><template>Cops still argue to this day why Danson and Highsmith jump Maybe it was just pride having survived so many brushes with death.</template></category><category><pattern>ERSHON NOW RESIDES IN PALAMINO FEDERAL CORRECTIONAL FACILITY IN FLORIDA</pattern><template>Still invests, currency is just different.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M YOUR PARTNER  YOU CAN TELL ME</pattern><template>What the hell are you hiding from?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT NEEDS DOING</pattern><template>Whether it's directing traffic...</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  KNICKS  COME ON  I GOT KNICKS' FEVER  CATCH HIM</pattern><template>Hey, it feels weird sitting here. Feels like it is a bribe.</template></category><category><pattern>ROGER IS GONNA BABYSIT YOU BECAUSE I DON'T TRUST YOU  BECAUSE I THINK YOU ARE GOING TO TAKE OFF</pattern><template>Pam, this is ridiculous, I'm not going anywhere.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE WANT TO HEAR YOU TALK  I'LL SHOVE MY ARM UP YOUR ASS AND WORK YOUR MOUTH LIKE A PUPPET</pattern><template>You hear me? You hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>CHRISTINETH  LOOK  WE REALLY APPRECIATE THE HOSPITALITY</pattern><template>and we would love to just get the message off your cellphone, we believe it might give us an information regarding a kidnapping.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WENT TERRIBLY WRONG</pattern><template>It seems like it's unfair that they have a helicopter.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKS LIKE SCARFACE SNEEZED ON YOUR CAR</pattern><template>All right, everybody. We need y'all to back up now. We're taking over  At the crime scene. LOL.    Good tweet.   Yeah America was always been defined by its excess.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID I HAD A WEAK CHIN  YOU SAID THE WAY I PEED IN FEMININE</pattern><template>How do you think that makes me feel? I mean, That list you have, you put a lot of thought in. It's weird.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT TO TELL YOU I AM STARTING FOR GET A HAND TO THAT    A TASTE FOR THAT PIE GIRL</pattern><template>Martin and Fossi, super cops.   In three, two,... We busted that junkie...   Uh huh.</template></category><category><pattern>OR NOT APPROVED</pattern><template>Here, mate, I wanna kill just for fun.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN EVEN THAT BRAZILIAN SECURITY CHICK  SHE WAS    I MEAN WHAT IS IT WITH YOU AND HOT LADIES</pattern><template>First off, my wife is cute, but she's not hot.</template></category><category><pattern>SO MUCH FOR QUIET AS CHURCH MICE</pattern><template>Go.</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO</pattern><template>You just signed your death warrant, Hoitz!</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER ACTUALLY PUT MY FOOT ALL THE WAY DOWN TO THE GROUND WITH THE ACCELERATOR LIKE THAT</pattern><template>You got me slightly aroused.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE I'M NOT ALONE</pattern><template>Hope you bring it.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  LISTEN TO ME  DANSON AND HIGHSMITH ARE GONE</pattern><template>Their desks right? Someone has to fill those seats And that someone is us Ok? The city's dying for a hero.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT SOMETIMES WHEN YOU GET YOUR ASS KICKED</pattern><template>that's when you find that what's real.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M UPSET</pattern><template>These roast ribs taste like a dog's asshole.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GREATEST CITY ON EARTH  YEAH</pattern><template>Uh.. Sarah Capone from TMZ... print edition, uh, Danson, are the rumors about you and Kim Kardashian true?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I GOTTA SAVE WHAT LITTLE ASS I HAVE LEFT  OK</pattern><template>You know, you keep hiding from shit in the world, and eventually the world comes to your front door.</template></category><category><pattern>STILL INVESTS  CURRENCY IS JUST DIFFERENT</pattern><template>Roger Wesley was linked to the Beaman murder by a security cam footage...</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN YOU MOVE TO FLORIDA</pattern><template>One, two, three, attack.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS THE KING OF THE MUD CASES</pattern><template>But Allen and Terry have worked it like stars.</template></category><category><pattern>FELLAS  LOOK  I KNOW YOU DON'T RESPECT ME AS A POLICE OFFICER NOT TRUE    I'M NOT STUPID  I AM NOT GOING TO DISCHARGE MY FIREARM IN THE OFFICE LISTEN TO ME  I'LL TRY TO MAKE IT REAL CLEAR  WE HONOR THE FLAG</pattern><template>And you crap on it when you don't shoot your gun in the office Jimmy, when was the last time you had a desk pop?</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE THEIR EGO PUSHED THEM OFF  I DON'T KNOW BUT THAT SHIT WAS CRAZY  EITHER WAY</pattern><template>there was a hole in New York City that needed to be filled.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS NO EXPLOSIONS AT MY HOME WITH MY PLAIN WIFE IN MY PLAIN HOUSE</pattern><template>What are you afraid of man?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S HEAR IT FROM THE TOP  EVERY DETAIL</pattern><template>It is the best to tell the stories by starting from the end.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  GET OVER HERE</pattern><template>What's wrong with you?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU CRAZY</pattern><template>What are you doing man? I almost killed you.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T YOU GET IT  I DON'T WANT YOU ALLEN  OK</pattern><template>I never did. I told you that scaffolding violation was dogshit.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PAGEANTRY  THE COSTUMES  WOW  WHAT A MUSICAL</pattern><template>Hey, get over here.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP</pattern><template>I am gonna climb over that anger wall of yours one of these days and it is gonna be glorious.</template></category><category><pattern>A GHOST DIAL  SOMEBODY SAT ON IT</pattern><template>Could've recorded some of the conversation when Ershon got grabbed.</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH OUT  IN THE BACK THERE IS A BABY MOUSE AND A USED CONDOM  REALLY GROSS</pattern><template>I have a free ticket.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS BEING ABDUCTED</pattern><template>Obviously, but what kind of...</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT</pattern><template>Instead of a fresh start, I just wanna punch you in the face.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA BREAK YOUR HIP</pattern><template>I am about to do you grandpa style.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO COPS TALKING DOWN THE CASE WHILE EATING FOOD  RIGHT  IT IS NOT DINNER</pattern><template>Fine.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO</pattern><template>Gentlemen, we got a hot one. Hoitz and Gamble have Ershon hostage. High speed car chase in progress.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THEN WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>What do you think? I woke up, I took the belt off my neck and I got my car and I got out of there.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS: LET'S EVEN THE ODDS</pattern><template>He tosses me down a mos? pump, I sent one through his chest.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER I TALKED ABOUT THAT PROXY VOTE A WHILE BACK  THIS IS WHAT IT WAS FOR</pattern><template>Holy shit!   It's more aggressive investment strategy for the pension, Allen, we are the suckers. They are targeting the police pension fund!</template></category><category><pattern>OH YEAH  THANK YOU SO MUCH  GENTLEMEN  FOR THE PROMPT DELIVERY OF MR  ERSHON</pattern><template>I have two competing bids from jilted investors.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  HE DID</pattern><template>Way up there.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST A MUG THAT SAYS FBI BUT AT THE SECOND GLANCE  YOU'RE LIKE  FEMALE BODY INSPECTOR</pattern><template>Get out of town. This is outrageous.</template></category><category><pattern>SEXY BUT SERIOUS</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  LENDL STAGED THE CASTIAN ROBBERY AS A DISTRACTION SO THEY CAN BREAK INTO THEIR OWN ACCOUNTING FIRM NEXT DOOR</pattern><template>They did alter all the records to cover the losses that Ershon had cost them through all these bad investments.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A MINUTE  DID YOU IDENTIFY YOURSELVES AS POLICE OFFICERS</pattern><template>What is this?</template></category><category><pattern>POP IT OFF   DON'T THINK JUST GO</pattern><template>Here we go!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE COMING</pattern><template>Faster, Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  OUTSTANDING</pattern><template>Did this come with a dental dam?</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY  JUST THINK ABOUT IT  JUST BE SMART</pattern><template>2 11 in progress. They are using a wrecking ball to clean up Caspian Jewellery We got it!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT THIS  HOW ABOUT YOU SHUT YOUR FACE</pattern><template>All right? Just shut it   Hoitz. Gamble. Captain's looking for you.</template></category><category><pattern>175 POUNDS 175 POUNDS  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Shut up man! Shut up!</template></category><category><pattern>GAME OVER  BITCHES JIMMY  LET'S TALK ABOUT HOW THAT STORY MADE YOU FEEL LIKE A VIAGRA PILL WITH A FACE</pattern><template>I know it's very tempting. You wanna impress your friends...</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU CRAP ON IT WHEN YOU DON'T SHOOT YOUR GUN IN THE OFFICE JIMMY  WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU HAD A DESK POP</pattern><template>September 2008.</template></category><category><pattern>XIE XIE</pattern><template>Here you go.</template></category><category><pattern>SWEAR TO GOD  I'D BLOW YOUR HEAD ALL OVER THIS DESK</pattern><template>Not a person in this room believes you'll shoot this clerk.</template></category><category><pattern>DETECTIVE HOITZ AND GAMBLE  WE GOT THIS</pattern><template>I took an online class at University of Phoenix on negotiating...</template></category><category><pattern>BYE</pattern><template>I see you, Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M PLAYING SQUASH WITH HIM TONIGHT AT THE CLUB  AND WE'RE HAVING DINNER</pattern><template>You listen to me you wisenut wimp monkey. You play squash with Ershon right?</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN GUYS  I AM WORKING TWO JOBS: I AM WORKING HERE  I GOT ANOTHER JOB AT BED  BATH AND BEYOND OK  I AM DOING THAT JUST TO PUT THE KID THROUGH NYU SO HE CAN EXPLORE HIS BISEXUALITY</pattern><template>become a DJ. Now the last thing I need is a ballistics report in the unit. Just gonna ask you guys. Please, come on!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY GUYS  YOU KNOW DANSON AND HIGHSMITH WERE NOT GOOD COPS  RIGHT</pattern><template>Yeah I guess we kinda knew that. But it's a drag I mean, at a certain point, who's left to be a hero?</template></category><category><pattern>TWICE</pattern><template>Twice. Terry says twice. I agree.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  FELLAS  ALL RIGHT  BRING IT IN  COME ON  BRING IT A LITTLE BIT ALL RIGHT  RIGHT THERE</pattern><template>Just back.. right there Just... just one... there you go... right there.. right there This is their paperwork, you know they are not gonna do it   That's right   This paperwork work is like Bob's wife here Stick, ugly, got Danson's fingerprints all over it. No offence, Bob   That's all right Anyway, now who wants it?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU HIDING FROM</pattern><template>I was a sophomore in college.</template></category><category><pattern>FANTASTIC  UNBELIEVABLE</pattern><template>Damn it! He did it again.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BELIEVE ME I WON'T</pattern><template>Do you understand what's so funny about it though?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY KNEW THAT TO BECOME A GOOD COP  YOU HAVE TO SOLVE CASES</pattern><template>Ok? And maybe you start with Castian robbery. Ok?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY IS SHE LOOKING AT YOU LIKE THAT</pattern><template>That's my car. Hey, hey, hey. We didn't exchange.. insurance information Excuse me. Why did they take our shoes?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU DEAF</pattern><template>You dick, I'm Derek Jeter. You shot me You cost me 20 grand on that game   Douchebag I cost the city a championship. I was being groomed for top position in Homicide Now I'm stuck with a desk junky partner and everybody calls me the Yankee clipper.</template></category><category><pattern>BY 09:01 IT'S GONE</pattern><template>What if we stop the transfer?</template></category><category><pattern>HANDS UP</pattern><template>Special Forces zip line These guys are pros You're thinking what I'm thinking, partner?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALMOST GOT MARRIED BUT SHE BACKED OUT  IT'S COMPLICATED</pattern><template>Terry shot Derek Jeter.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  I CAN GIVE YOU NON OBSTRUCTIVE VIEW TICKETS FOR  ROCK OF AGES</pattern><template>But even I admit, that's not very tempting, I'm not made of tickets, God damn it.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU KNOW WHAT THAT'S CALLED WHEN THEY DO THAT IN THERE  IT'S CALLED A SOUP KITCHEN</pattern><template>It's pretty rough stuff Not long after that, a mama raccoon came along, and gave birth on the floor.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF TOWN  THIS IS OUTRAGEOUS</pattern><template>Shut up!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE COPS  WE GOTTA GO  COME ON</pattern><template>Hey, peace shitboys. They're cops.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A FRONTLINE NARRATION APP  IT'S ONLY 99 CENTS</pattern><template>Ershon Consortium's current financial investment exceeds $70 billion It's largest clients includes Schering Plough and Lendl Global.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>The highlights are great.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WENT BACK THERE AND I PULLED OPEN THAT CURTAIN</pattern><template>and I saw you. You were weak.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD POINT</pattern><template>I am sorry. I don't follow   You never fired your weapon in the office.</template></category><category><pattern>OW  THAT HURTS  MAN</pattern><template>I've always got Little River Band loaded. I got 6 discs in here.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT NO BULLHORN</pattern><template>Does anyone have a bullhorn?</template></category><category><pattern>PIMPS DON'T CRY</pattern><template>Pimps don't cry... No they don't.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  JUST SHUT IT   HOITZ  GAMBLE  CAPTAIN'S LOOKING FOR YOU</pattern><template>Captain?   Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>DID THIS COME WITH A DENTAL DAM</pattern><template>Get it?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I STOPPED MYSELF BECAUSE MY POP TAUGHT ME THAT A MAN WHO TALKS BEHIND SOMEBODY'S BACK IS A COWARD</pattern><template>Wow, I actually appreciate that.</template></category><category><pattern>OH COOL  A HELICOPTER  MUST BE COVERING THE HIGH SPEED CHASE</pattern><template>Who are those guys?</template></category><category><pattern>DAVID ERSHON  IS CURRENTLY THE CEO OF ERSHON CONSORTIUM</pattern><template>Who is that talking?</template></category><category><pattern>LEAVE ME ALONE</pattern><template>A mud case.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  ALLEN</pattern><template>This is my partner, Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>LENDL IS IN EVERYTHING AND WE'RE GONNA GO EVERYWHERE</pattern><template>They were too big to fail.</template></category><category><pattern>HOPE YOU BRING IT</pattern><template>We have big day out there. Big one. We got a full moon. People are gonna be amped.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS HOUSE MIGHT BE BUGGED</pattern><template>There's no bugs in here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT ONE JOB MATE  FIND A SUCKER</pattern><template>to invest with you so you can pay my boss back the money you lost.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT'S BECAUSE OF THIS EXCESS THAT I HAVE FLOURISHED  I EMPLOY YOU</pattern><template>Please, do not stop profiting. Live for excess.</template></category><category><pattern>I ALREADY DID</pattern><template>It's no big deal. You look really really nice.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GO TO THAT CALL</pattern><template>What is this?</template></category><category><pattern>509 EAST 10TH STREET</pattern><template>There are large amounts of cocaine on the scene. Try to stay out of trouble, boys.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT�S FOR MY OTHER JOB</pattern><template>Ignore that, forget it.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS  I WILL</pattern><template>You say hi to Sheila for me?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER DID  I TOLD YOU THAT SCAFFOLDING VIOLATION WAS DOGSHIT</pattern><template>I can't believe you still doubt me, after everything we've seen it is a real case and I'm a real cop.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT A BAD TIME    NO</pattern><template>Come on, come on.   Not me right?   Yes, and you.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW IF HE'S CLEAN OR NOT</pattern><template>I will take a look at your evidence, and I will take a second look at their financials.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D RATHER NOT</pattern><template>Officer Hoitz, you've been coming here for six months.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOU DON'T SAY CREEP CREEP UNLESS YOU'RE QUOTING TLC</pattern><template>Hey guys, you know Danson and Highsmith were not good cops, right?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS BAD  ALLEN</pattern><template>This is bad, no wonder the Captain wanted us to stay out of this.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST CAPTAIN  JUST CAPTAIN  IT'S NOT CAPTAIN GENE  I DO NOT HAVE A KITTY SHOW</pattern><template>Sounds creepy, Captain Gene.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  SHE SAYS SHE WANTS TO UNPLUG ALL THE CLOCKS AND THE PHONES AND HAVE A THREE DAY SEX MARATHON</pattern><template>That's more like it. Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  HEATHER LOCKLEAR</pattern><template>You've heard of her?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU  WHAT HAPPENED TO THIS BEING OUR TIME</pattern><template>No way Allen. I am out I'm done.</template></category><category><pattern>JAMIE GO GET OVER HERE  YOU  GO GET THE BLOODY CAR</pattern><template>That's it mate, I have had it with this joker and his wooden gun.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  I'LL BE HONEST  THIS IS THE SECOND TIME I EVER FIRED THIS</pattern><template>So stop pointing it at me.</template></category><category><pattern>LOVELY HAT</pattern><template>I love your shoes.   It's fine. It's fine   Go! Go!</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>You're not aware that's a TLC song.</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN  IF YOU REALLY WANT TO DISARM THIS GUY  TAKE OUT THE BATTERIES IN THE CALCULATOR</pattern><template>All right, I am gonna give you this: This is a dummy gun. They used this for ceremony.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT GONNA WRECK</pattern><template>I'm going to wreck, you're right.</template></category><category><pattern>OK</pattern><template>But just one more thing.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO BUGS IN HERE</pattern><template>First off, I missed you.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  I GOT YOU A GIFT  I JUST SAW SOMETHING AND I THOUGHT OF YOU AND SO I DO NOT WANT IT TO BE WEIRD  I JUST WANT IT TO BE NICE</pattern><template>Of course it's weird, it's a grown man giving another man a present.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE SHE THOUGHT SHE DATES GUYS AND CHARGE THEM MONEY</pattern><template>I go out all the time with the whole bunch of you know boys.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT BACK 74 000 DIAMONDS  74 000</pattern><template>Boom.   Solved the Castian case.</template></category><category><pattern>COPS STILL ARGUE TO THIS DAY WHY DANSON AND HIGHSMITH JUMP MAYBE IT WAS JUST PRIDE HAVING SURVIVED SO MANY BRUSHES WITH DEATH</pattern><template>Maybe their ego pushed them off. I don't know but that shit was crazy. Either way...</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO</pattern><template>Hello, Gene... I mean.. Captain, Captain, it's Allen Gamble.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAVE THEIR FUN  HUH</pattern><template>Looks like Scarface sneezed on your car.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HERE SHE IS  THEY LEFT HER UNDER AN OVERPASS FOR THE NIGHT</pattern><template>Did you find anything?</template></category><category><pattern>HAL  JUST PLEASE SIT DOWN PLEASE</pattern><template>All righty.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LOVES YOU VERY MUCH  FRANCINE</pattern><template>I heard it when he said it, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>GUYS  DO YOU REMEMBER THE  BE SMART SPEECH</pattern><template>Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>I RELIVE IT EVERY NIGHT</pattern><template>The Bronx, October. Game 7 of the World Series.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  GENE    I MEAN   CAPTAIN  CAPTAIN  IT'S ALLEN GAMBLE</pattern><template>Yeah yeah, where are you? What's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T THINK I'M A REAL COP  DO YOU</pattern><template>No, I don't. I've said that directly to your face numerous times. I was really honest about that.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A LOT OF COCAINE</pattern><template>Did you yell 'America' when you hit the accelerator?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOOK YOUR WOODEN GUN</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO TELL YOU I'M TREMENDOUSLY EXCITED ABOUT THIS DEAL</pattern><template>I can assure you that every dime of your money will be invested with the utmost diligence.</template></category><category><pattern>GET IT</pattern><template>... shit one of these last night.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TIRED OF THIS</pattern><template>Right? I am tired of explosions and people pointing guns at me. I want to go back to my desk.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  DO WE UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER  CUT THE CRAP</pattern><template>Will do.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE JUNKIES  WHO CARES</pattern><template>No junkie can go down a 20 story zip line.</template></category><category><pattern>BEAMAN KNEW THAT I'D FALSIFY MY FINANCIALS SO THEY SENT DOWN WESLEY TO</pattern><template>try and keep him quiet.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  THE OLDEST GAME IN THE BOOK FOR A REASON  IT WORKS</pattern><template>I'd come strong and you come in.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  GOOD BYE BUDDY</pattern><template>Get off of me, man.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME</pattern><template>You're Ershon's lawyer.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU DON'T SHUT UP  I WILL CUT YOUR REAR OFF WITH A BUTTER KNIFE</pattern><template>That's blunt. Blunt's worse.</template></category><category><pattern>HOITZ  GAMBLE  CAPTAIN  NOT GOOD</pattern><template>Bye, guys.</template></category><category><pattern>GO  GO  GO</pattern><template>Feel that Allen? Huh? That ting a ling in your balls, big net of butterflies flying around in your stomach?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  FELLAS  WEDNESDAY NIGHT IS TACO NIGHT AT RANCOR'S ISLAND AWWW  THE SECOND ONE THIS WEEK</pattern><template>Hey you monkeys! Stop!</template></category><category><pattern>HI</pattern><template>Why is she looking at you like that?</template></category><category><pattern>SEPTEMBER 2008</pattern><template>Be a man. Do it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN TRUST US</pattern><template>Real quiet, you got to creep.</template></category><category><pattern>WORLDCOM  BEAR STERNS  LEHMAN BROTHERS</pattern><template>Ok, Thank you. Thank you, detective.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS</pattern><template>Allen, tell me, did you?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Holy God.</template></category><category><pattern>A MUD CASE</pattern><template>Terry, I'm a cop, for your information, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY GONNA KILL ME AND THEN THEY WILL KILL YOU</pattern><template>I'm gonna kill you first.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR WHAT  WE'RE JUST GOING TO CHECK IT OUT</pattern><template>No, but it's procedure.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID YOU COVER YOUR LOSSES  HUH  WHAT DRUG CARTEL ARE YOU WORKING WITH NOW</pattern><template>Ok, wait wait.. I'll talk to you. You're reasonable.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  YOU ARE HERE ILLEGALLY AND WITHOUT A WARRANT  WE ARE WITHIN OUR RIGHTS TO TAKE ACTION</pattern><template>So much for quiet as church mice.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WANT TO LISTEN TO THIS MESSAGE OR NOT</pattern><template>Whatever.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE CAPTAIN</pattern><template>We have to go.</template></category><category><pattern>OF WHO'S GONNA BE THE NEXT HOT SHOT  HUH  IS THAT WHAT'S HAPPENING</pattern><template>Yes, that's exactly what's happening!</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT BUT REMEMBER</pattern><template>this thing gets messy, we never talked.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GOING  ALLEN  I LIKE WHAT I DO</pattern><template>So do I. We're cops.</template></category><category><pattern>SWEETIE  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>It's okay.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T SEE 'EM ON TV OR ON THE FRONT PAGE</pattern><template>I am talking about the day in day outers, the grinders, come on man, you know what I'm talking about...</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF THE WAY MAN</pattern><template>Wait. Are you David Ershon?</template></category><category><pattern>FINE  I KIND A MISSED YOU TOO</pattern><template>Thank you. I've found out whose losses Ershon has to cover.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ONLY PROTOCOL</pattern><template>Mr. Ershon has agreed to...</template></category><category><pattern>I USE UH ADOBE PREMIER I LIKE TO DO A WEEKEND EDITING RECENTLY JUST CUT 3 MINUTES OUT OF GOODFELLAS</pattern><template>David Ershon, is currently the CEO of Ershon Consortium.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE AT A TIME  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Yeah Detective, Rick Rayston, New York Observer... online These suspects were caught with only a quarter of pound of marijuana...</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  THEN YOU DO US PROUD</pattern><template>Because I do not want those scrubs.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DECIDED I SHOULDN�T USE MY REAL NAME SO WE CAME UP WITH THE NAME GATOR</pattern><template>I'm telling you, you were a pimp.</template></category><category><pattern>COMING FROM BOTH DIRECTIONS</pattern><template>We're not gonna wreck.</template></category><category><pattern>AND GETTING BUSTED DOWN TO A SHITTY ASSIGNMENT  ALLEN AND TERRY HIT THE TRIFECTA</pattern><template>But sometimes when you get your ass kicked...</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE AT A FUNERAL  SHOW SOME RESPECT</pattern><template>What? You don't think every other detective here isn't thinking the same thing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT ERSHON TARGETING THE LOTTERY</pattern><template>You know why Ershon was calling down to the lottery office all those times?</template></category><category><pattern>I DID  YES</pattern><template>We almost got married but she backed out. It's complicated.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM ABOUT TO DO YOU GRANDPA STYLE</pattern><template>8:36 AM 24 MINUTES TO BANK TRANSFER I brought some music.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE'S DEALING DRUGS</pattern><template>No! It's not drugs. This isn't Miami Vice.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I LIKE WHAT I DO NOW</pattern><template>I like working traffic, it's a great gig.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE FUN SINGING THOSE SONGS  THEY ARE REALLY DEPRESSING</pattern><template>I do, they are full of rich history.</template></category><category><pattern>BELIEVE ME  THERE WERE SOME DISCREPANCIES  AND I WAS GROUNDED</pattern><template>What the hell are you?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN   THAT IS NOT WHAT I MEANT</pattern><template>How did you guys meet?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  YES  YOU CAN  I'VE DONE IT FOR YEARS  OK  THERE IS NO EXPLOSIONS AT MY DESK</pattern><template>There is no explosions at my home with my plain wife in my plain house.</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN IT</pattern><template>God your hair is soft.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER</pattern><template>How did they got that story?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS THAT</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD GO OUT OF MY WAY TO ATTACK YOU</pattern><template>If I were a lion and you were a tuna, I would swim out in the middle of the ocean and freaking eat you and then I'd bang your tuna girlfriend.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  CHECK THIS OUT  AN ARTICLE FROM SIX MONTHS AGO</pattern><template>It's talking about how the lottery is looking to invest their 32 billion dollar fund more aggressively.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE YOU KNOW IT  SOME OF BRENDA'S GIRLFRIENDS DECIDED THEY WANTED TO BE A PART OF IT</pattern><template>Pretty soon, there were about 14 ladies that I was protecting while they gave me money.</template></category><category><pattern>PRETTY SOON  THERE WERE ABOUT 14 LADIES THAT I WAS PROTECTING WHILE THEY GAVE ME MONEY</pattern><template>That's called the stable horse.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  COULDN'T GET A ONE</pattern><template>Found a cellphone.   Yeah, that's mine.</template></category><category><pattern>MY WAISTLINE IS FURIOUS</pattern><template>It's a bad time, Bob!</template></category><category><pattern>LOAD THEM UP AND SEND THEM BACK TO</pattern><template>Shit!   What?   What do you mean what?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE GOT SHOT FIRED</pattern><template>509 East 10th Street.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES ANYONE HAVE A BULLHORN</pattern><template>Hey, police business, I need to use your P.A. system.</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN IT  HE DID IT AGAIN</pattern><template>No more tickets!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST THANK GOD NO ONE WAS HURT  OR INJURED IN A BAD WAY</pattern><template>I absolutely appal death.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS OUR THING  YEAH</pattern><template>So, so what do you got?</template></category><category><pattern>OH GOD  HOW DO THEY WALK AWAY IN MOVIES WITHOUT FUZZY WITH AN EXPLOSION BEHIND THEM  NO WAY</pattern><template>Cop's bullshit. All that.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I SAW YOU  YOU WERE WEAK</pattern><template>Scared, ass up, enflamed, crying and at that moment I knew, Hey, he's no pimp.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE ON A HUGE CASE  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Property owner. With 7 buildings under construction, he hasn't applied for a single scaffolding permit.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER US  HOT SHOT</pattern><template>Of course I do, please sit.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S GOT THE GOLDEN GOOSE NOW  HUH</pattern><template>He is still valuable with a bullet wound, mate.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID YOU GET IN HERE</pattern><template>We cannot be too careful.</template></category><category><pattern>THEIR DESKS RIGHT  SOMEONE HAS TO FILL THOSE SEATS AND THAT SOMEONE IS US OK  THE CITY'S DYING FOR A HERO</pattern><template>Is it?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T REMEMBER A MOVIE WHERE MEG RYAN MET A GUY WITH POISON IVY ON HIS ASS</pattern><template>I'll think of it.</template></category><category><pattern>GRAND THEFT AUTO</pattern><template>They're coming.</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH IT</pattern><template>Next time: Me, You, Library.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS MY PARTNER  TERRY</pattern><template>Hi, Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>I ONLY HOPE GOT LETS THEM TAKE THEIR  357S WITH THEM TO HEAVEN TO KEEP  TO</pattern><template>It's our moment, Allen Our moment to step up and be the guys.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOUR SHOES    IT'S FINE  IT'S FINE   GO  GO</pattern><template>Ah, man!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M JUST RESTING</pattern><template>Did I hurt you?</template></category><category><pattern>CHRISTINETH  IT'S YOUR HUSBAND  IT'S AWKWARD</pattern><template>No, he knows.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO CHECK THAT OUT</pattern><template>It's a real shame you know. I got myself a Prius. It's a hell of a machine.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD DAMN IT  LET ME FINI   THEY RUINED THE STORY    THEY RUINED THE STORY NO  THE POINT IS  WE COULDN'T DO OUR JOB IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU GUYS DOING ALL THE PAPERWORK</pattern><template>answering the phone and all the stupid shit that we don't like to do...</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  I AM GONNA GIVE YOU THIS: THIS IS A DUMMY GUN  THEY USED THIS FOR CEREMONY</pattern><template>You get this back when I feel you know how to handle it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL IS THIS</pattern><template>It's my car. It's a Prius.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HEAR ME  YOU HEAR ME</pattern><template>Peace out, bitches.</template></category><category><pattern>REAL NICE  YOU KNOW IT'S ALL CLASS</pattern><template>Ok.   Don't do that shit anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THIS CHOPPING BOARDS</pattern><template>Hey Captain!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE GOT A POSSIBLE JUMPER AT 3 WORLD FINANCIAL CENTER  23RD FLOOR</pattern><template>All units, Firemen en route.</template></category><category><pattern>GAS LEAK  THE ONLY GAS LEAK IS THE ONE COMING OUT OF YOUR MOUTH RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>I just thank God no one was hurt, or injured in a bad way.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP IT</pattern><template>Half empty bottle of gin, chair knocked over, look at this, it's a clear sign of struggle.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>I'm gonna make you a plate of human shit.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THERE IS MY PHONE</pattern><template>Great, thank you...</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE I GOT THE MONEY  I'LL FALSIFY THE RECORDS</pattern><template>to show a massive losses then you pay your employer.</template></category><category><pattern>OK LOOK  THEY'RE NOT ALL FIRST ROUND PICK OK</pattern><template>Come on, you're gonna tell me who that is?</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP  ALLEN</pattern><template>I assure you, I have no idea what you're talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO</pattern><template>I found some great information.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHERE I MET SHEILA  I WAS A MESS</pattern><template>I made a promise to myself and to her, that I would never get out of control again...</template></category><category><pattern>GET UP  AND KILL THE POLICE</pattern><template>I just want to make sure I get it right. Did you want this transfer approved?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON HERE</pattern><template>Two good men are dead and you guys are fighting...</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I CAN MAKE A SCHEDULE</pattern><template>Yeah yeah yeah, that what I was thinking.</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T    NO   I SHOT JETER</pattern><template>That was an accident.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>TLC references.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S DO IT</pattern><template>You want my gate code?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT ME SLIGHTLY AROUSED</pattern><template>Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU CAN CHOP THAT UP TO BAD LIFE CHOICES GET RID OF THAT ASSHOLE   O O I KNEW WHEN YOU SAY  O O  O DUDE  YOU PUT A DENT IN MY HOOD</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>LOT OF GREAT DAYS LIKE UH SODA POP  FRESH CAN OF SODA POP</pattern><template>I do not care.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S LIKE I'M PARTNER WITH THE HULK</pattern><template>You wanna know why I'm so angry all the time?</template></category><category><pattern>CHENKO GALLERY</pattern><template>Francine, it's Terry, please don't hang up.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR DAVID ERSHON  DOESN'T MATTER  I AM IN A LITTLE BIT OF A RUSH GENTLEMEN  IF YOU DON'T MIND  THANK YOU   EXCUSE ME  BUT YOU ARE UNDER ARREST OK  YOU HAVE THE RIGHT TO REMAIN SILENT ANYTHING YOU DO OR SAY CAN BE USED UM    WHAT 'S THE NEXT PART</pattern><template>As a floatation device.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ALL BE AFTER US</pattern><template>You could, let me go, and I'll give you $10 million each.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU</pattern><template>Well, well, well. What we got here?</template></category><category><pattern>TRAFFIC  BULLSHIT</pattern><template>What are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE MISTAKENLY ARREST INVESTMENT BANKER DAVID ERSHON</pattern><template>Was he a victim of financial profiling?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN</pattern><template>Hi..   Hi   You must be Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T CARE WHO  I ACTUALLY THINK I FOUND A SUCKER THEY ARE TALKING TO ERSHON</pattern><template>To invest 32 billion.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  I HAVE GOTTEN OUT OF CONTROL AND I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE THAT</pattern><template>You can't have a conscience in the pimp game.</template></category><category><pattern>74 000  DOLLARS  THAT'S ALL THEY TOOK  THERE IS MILLIONS OF DOLLARS OF DIAMONDS IN THERE</pattern><template>How about this? How about you shut your face?</template></category><category><pattern>SCAFFOLDING PERMIT VIOLATION</pattern><template>I got my insurance card...</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU IMAGINE WHERE YOU�D BE IN YOUR CAREER IF YOU HADN'T SHOT JETER</pattern><template>Move!</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU FOR COMING</pattern><template>Detective Hoitz and Gamble. Detective Hoitz and Gamble. Over.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT AWARE THAT'S A TLC SONG</pattern><template>I have no idea what are you talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  ERSHON HAS AGREED TO</pattern><template>correct this scathlic situation. Case is closed.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT BIG BOY PANTS ON</pattern><template>Stop.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS 20 MILES</pattern><template>You get back here!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE THREW ME OUT</pattern><template>You�re not a cop until you�re thrown out of the house, partner.</template></category><category><pattern>HE BECAME A CHAMPION  AND A MOVIE STAR</pattern><template>Arnold Schwarzenegger!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY FORCED HIM AT GUNPOINT TO DRINK A BUNCH OF GIN AND FORCED HIM ONTO THE LEDGE</pattern><template>It was just a matter of time before he fell.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S GOT 32 BILLION DOLLARS TO ROB</pattern><template>Once I got the money, I'll falsify the records...</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE PERKY  AND THEY ARE FIRM AND THEY ARE YOURS</pattern><template>You're a nice lady.</template></category><category><pattern>SO DO I  WE'RE COPS</pattern><template>No, I like what I do now.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE    THAT'S VERY NICE    I HEARD IT IN AN EPISODE OF TOUCHED BY AN ANGEL</pattern><template>You keep this thing real quiet and you make sure you have real evidence. And maybe I'll see what I can do...</template></category><category><pattern>KICK HIS ASS  MARTIN</pattern><template>How do you like that?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE YOU IN JERSEY TOMORROW</pattern><template>All right, Terry. Hey, That was liberating for me. I do not know how it felt for you.</template></category><category><pattern>DO AS THEY SAY  STOP THE TRANSFER</pattern><template>Approve it. Now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR KIDS GOING TO SCHOOL WITH HIS</pattern><template>How do you know if he's clean or not?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T WE LET NEW YORK CITY ANSWER THAT QUESTION</pattern><template>The greatest city on earth! Yeah!</template></category><category><pattern>FOUND A CELLPHONE    YEAH  THAT'S MINE</pattern><template>Any sign of a struggle or...?</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY ANSWERS TO NO ONE</pattern><template>I do what I do.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE FOUND A LOT OF STUFF</pattern><template>From bodily fluids and hair samples, we determined that a bunch of old homeless dudes had an orgy in the car.</template></category><category><pattern>ERSHON IS USING THE LOTTERY MONEY TO COVER HIS LOSSES  32 BILLION DOLLARS</pattern><template>That 's the state's money.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT WHAT</pattern><template>Some scary shit Terry, this is big.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE NOT THAT SAME PERSON ANYMORE</pattern><template>You don't get it. There's a darkness inside of me. It wants to get out and wants to walk around.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING TO THE STORY</pattern><template>Anyway, one day I wake up and I look in the mirror and I don't like what I see.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE'RE GOING AFTER THIS CASE</pattern><template>You're not gonna shoot me.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE COMMUNICATED AND SAID 'YOU KNOW WHAT  LION TASTES GOOD  LET'S GO GET SOME MORE LION'</pattern><template>We've developed a system to establish a beach head and aggressively hunt you and your family and we will corner your pride, your children, your offspring.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>Thank you, Sheila.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M GOOD    OK</pattern><template>Let me just assure you, fellas, David Ershon is an upstanding citizen.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I SERVED AS A TREASURER FOR THE UNION I MAKE A POT OF DECAF</pattern><template>Exactly, you're a worthless piece of shit.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY YOU MONKEYS  STOP</pattern><template>Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOTHING  IT'S NOTHING</pattern><template>It's the only thing we have! Why did you just get super jumpy?</template></category><category><pattern>DEPEND ON WHAT YOU'RE GONNA BE DRINKING  JACK OF ALL TRADES</pattern><template>Drinks on me, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID  HE'LL ALWAYS LOVE YOU  AND HE'S SO HAPPY THAT YOU'RE HAVING HIS CHILD</pattern><template>Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WASN'T A SECURITY TAPE  HE SAID  DON'T LET THESE PEOPLE TAKE ME I MEAN WHEN YOU HEAR HOOVES  YOU THINK HORSES NOT ZEBRAS</pattern><template>What about donkeys or deer? They have hooves. What about bovine creatures?</template></category><category><pattern>HONEY</pattern><template>I'm sitting here thinking, who in the world would slow roast a dog's asshole and serve it to their husband?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU TWO HAVE BEEN UP TO  BUT I'VE BEEN GETTING CALLS FROM PEOPLE I DON'T EVER GET CALLED FROM</pattern><template>In 40 years, I've been enforcing the law, I've learnt one thing. When that happens. Stop.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SO ADORABLE  LOOK AT YOUR FACE</pattern><template>Look at your face. You go: I love you. Say it! I love you, Christineth.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID YOU DO ABOUT IT</pattern><template>The opposite. We were not smart, Captain Gene.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE KIND OF MAKING THINGS WORSE</pattern><template>Are you ok?</template></category><category><pattern>SEVEN CALLS TO THE LOTTERY OFFICE</pattern><template>That would be the evidence we need for Mauch.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S LENDL GLOBAL</pattern><template>What? Lendl staged the Castian robbery as a distraction so they can break into their own accounting firm next door.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT IT</pattern><template>Hey you listen to me, you piece of shit. It's just you and me, and I'm gonna rip you apart.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MY CAR  HEY  HEY  HEY  WE DIDN'T EXCHANGE   INSURANCE INFORMATION EXCUSE ME  WHY DID THEY TAKE OUR SHOES</pattern><template>What the hell just happened?</template></category><category><pattern>EXACTLY  YOU'RE A WORTHLESS PIECE OF SHIT</pattern><template>You're probably right, Terry. It's why I feel so sad all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING MAN  I ALMOST KILLED YOU</pattern><template>Turn off the lights.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE WALKING THE BEAT</pattern><template>I know. Pretty tricky though, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>DRINKS ON ME  COME ON</pattern><template>No, I already have a beer.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'D BE BORED BY IT   I WAS A DANCER FOR THE KNICKS</pattern><template>while finishing my residency at Columbia Hospital.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST OFF  I MISSED YOU</pattern><template>What's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MAKE ME SHOOT  I'LL DO IT</pattern><template>Are you deaf?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE TRAFFIC GUYS  THEY ARE GOOD GUYS</pattern><template>There's one guy, Phillip, he can pee in the urinal from twenty feet. You got to see it Allen, you got to.</template></category><category><pattern>DANSON AND HIGHSMITH  FREE HOT DOGS    FOR LIFE</pattern><template>No drinks... No drinks Can't do it... I can't do it Danson and Highsmith, shoot, drive and sex in style They are rock stars...</template></category><category><pattern>WHETHER IT'S DIRECTING TRAFFIC</pattern><template>or cracking a multi billion dollar fraud.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  SHAKE YOUR DICKS  THIS PISSING CONTEST IS OVER</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MAN</pattern><template>Go.</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN TOOK US OFF THE CASE</pattern><template>I am sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  SERIOUSLY  WHO IS THAT    HIS OLD LADY    SWEETIE IT'S A WORKSTATION</pattern><template>Got it.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE DIED</pattern><template>Atta boy! I'll be there in two minutes exactly.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO  MONDAY MORNING  TIME TO GO TO WORK</pattern><template>Let's do it.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I DO</pattern><template>The wrecking ball, the crash in the Castian down there, they don't send the damage to your office?</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE A PICTURE OF ANYBODY'S FACE AND I'LL TELL YOU HOW THE BACK OF HIS HEAD LOOKS LIKE</pattern><template>Face back.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WILL GIVE US ENOUGH TIME TO FIGURE OUT WHERE YOU LIVE  GO BACK TO THE SEA  GET MORE OXYGEN  AND THEN STALK YOU YOU JUST LOST AT YOUR OWN GAME</pattern><template>You're outgunned and out manned.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOSE BABY IS THAT  WHO'S THE MAN WHO DID THAT TO YOU</pattern><template>Gator's bitches better be using the jimmies.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  YOU GOT NO GUN  NO CAR  NO WIFE AND NOW YOU GOT NO PARTNER</pattern><template>Leave me alone.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M HANGING UP  I AM DONE</pattern><template>I got to tell you I am starting for get a hand to that... a taste for that pie girl.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU  FRANCINE</pattern><template>You do not know what love is.</template></category><category><pattern>AS A LITTLE KID  DIDN'T YOU DRESS UP LIKE COPS AND A ROBBERS</pattern><template>I'll tell you what I did as a little kid, I went to school, I made my bed...</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD ON  HOLD ON</pattern><template>Someone has been playing Grand Theft Auto.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SEEMS LIKE IT'S UNFAIR THAT THEY HAVE A HELICOPTER</pattern><template>Damn it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT WANTS TO WALK UP TO THE PEOPLE AND SAY HEY  GATOR DON'T PLAY NO SHIT</pattern><template>You hit you feel me? Gator never been about that never been about playing no shit!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE REALLY WENT DEEP  ERSHON'S CONNECTED WITH ALL HIGHER UPS</pattern><template>And I gotta save what little ass I have left, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE SAID SHE NEEDED MY HELP TO MAKE SURE THE DATES WENT OK  THAT THE GUYS PAID HER  SHE SAID SHE'D GIVE ME A PERCENTAGE</pattern><template>Oh my god, you were a pimp.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM A PEACOCK  YOU GOT TO LET ME FLY</pattern><template>Did he just.. did he just call himself a peacock?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I WAS TALKING TO GENE HERE AND YOU KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY</pattern><template>I don't know what you two have been up to, but I've been getting calls from people I don't ever get called from.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  ERSHON  DETECTIVE GAMBLE AND THE OFFICER WHO SHOT DEREK JETER ARE HERE</pattern><template>Gentlemen, please.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T YOU DARE BADMOUTH STAR WARS  THAT WAS ALL ACCURATE</pattern><template>I need an MRI! I have got soft tissue damage.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO BE AT THE ENDEMIC BANK AT 9 O'CLOCK EXACTLY</pattern><template>Find the clerk, get the routing number.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S OUR MOMENT  ALLEN OUR MOMENT TO STEP UP AND BE THE GUYS</pattern><template>We're at a funeral. Show some respect.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE ALL EXPERIENCED OUR OWN BALLET TODAY</pattern><template>A ballet of emotion, feelings.</template></category><category><pattern>GUESS WHAT  LIFE GETS LOUD SOMETIMES AND MESSES WITH YOUR EARS</pattern><template>You can't escape it by hiding in your desk your whole life!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MADE A WISE CHOICE</pattern><template>Mr. Ershon, detective Gamble and the officer who shot Derek Jeter are here.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE TAKEN CARE ALL THE NECESSARY PAPERWORK</pattern><template>... and you fellas, this point, you just be glad that Mr. Ershon is not pressing charges for an excessive use of force.</template></category><category><pattern>APARTMENT POP  NOW GET IN THE CAR</pattern><template>You are not gonna shoot me.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST THE OLD LADY HELLO ALLEN    HELLO MAMA RAMOS  WHAT ARE DOING OUT HERE</pattern><template>Sheila said she doesn't know what happened and she wants you back.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S JUST LOVELY</pattern><template>No more! He says things I can't say.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FUNNY   IT'S LIKE A SCENE FROM THAT ONE MOVIE  I ALWAYS FORGET THE NAME  WITH MEG RYAN</pattern><template>I don't remember a movie where Meg Ryan met a guy with poison ivy on his ass.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT  I WANT YOU GUYS TO HAND IN ALL THE EVIDENCE  YOU THINK YOU HAVE TO THE S E C</pattern><template>That's under their jurisdiction.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM HERE TO SUPPORT A FRIEND AND A WORK COLLEAGUE</pattern><template>Francine, is this guy bothering you?</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T DO THAT</pattern><template>You're scaring the shit out of me man. Stop it.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS 13 YEARS AGO</pattern><template>Arnold Palmer alert. Arnold Palmer alert. Who wants some Arnie Palmies?</template></category><category><pattern>MILLION</pattern><template>No, billion Chinatown, three triad gang members. I popped two of them off the draw. Bang! Bang!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS SURPRISINGLY GOOD  TERRY</pattern><template>I love you, Francine.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T GET WHY WE CAN'T JUST CALL THE OFFICE AND HAVE A SQUAD CAR COME PICK US UP</pattern><template>No, they took our shoes, our guns and our car. There's no way this going out on the radio If we gonna do this together, there are some issues we need to settle, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>NO CHANCE  TOO BUSY</pattern><template>All right ladies, starting to get the picture? We're about to lock shit down.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NOTHING ABOUT YOU THAT MAKES A MAN A MAN</pattern><template>Ok? You got no gun, no car, no wife and now you got no partner.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST RESTING</pattern><template>Hey, let me tell you something: As far as the paperwork goes, we'll take care of it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST SIGNED YOUR DEATH WARRANT  HOITZ</pattern><template>Allen, punch that accelerator or I'll shoot in you in the foot.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF MAN</pattern><template>I'm your partner. You can tell me.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOT TO BE HOOKING UP WITH THE POWERBALL GIRL  SHE WAS ON TV WITH ALL THE NUMBERED BALLS</pattern><template>Yeah, she filed a restraining order on him last week.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT GONNA BE DAYS AT A TIME</pattern><template>An hour? Hour forty five? No problem.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT</pattern><template>Yeah!</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP  ALLEN  I LOVE YOU</pattern><template>We have a place that's safe.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT A COUPLE OF TIPS  HELPED THE GUYS STAY OUT OF THE JAIL</pattern><template>One, Try your hardest to not be black or Hispanic.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE WE</pattern><template>Chelsea Pier.</template></category><category><pattern>PROPERTY OWNER  WITH 7 BUILDINGS UNDER CONSTRUCTION  HE HASN'T APPLIED FOR A SINGLE SCAFFOLDING PERMIT</pattern><template>Now, according to S Geeves, this Perv is at Plaza Hotel speaking right now.</template></category><category><pattern>GRETCHEL AND DAWSON ACCOUNTING FIRM IN FAIRLAWN  NEW JERSEY HAS ONLY ONE CLIENT  DAVID ERSHON</pattern><template>Pretty rinky dink operation for a guy like that.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A WOODEN GUN</pattern><template>Ow, that hurts, man.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  I'M HUNG OVER</pattern><template>You guys in law enforcement?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Really sorry for your loss, mam.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T HEAR</pattern><template>There are blood blisters on my hands.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  YOU HAVE A CHOICE  MAMMA MIA OR JERSEY BOYS</pattern><template>Fantastic! Unbelievable!</template></category><category><pattern>DETECTIVE HOITZ AND GAMBLE  DETECTIVE HOITZ AND GAMBLE  OVER</pattern><template>We've found your Red Prius. It's trying to vote for Ralph Nader.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME POLICE OFFICERS CAME BY AND SHIELD IT OFF</pattern><template>You know what they look like?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  IT FEELS WEIRD SITTING HERE  FEELS LIKE IT IS A BRIBE</pattern><template>It is a bribe.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THIS  THERE WAS A TWO MINUTE PHONE CALL MADE AFTER WE WERE JUMPED</pattern><template>They used your phone?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  BABY  WHERE ARE YOU  I WANNA SEE YOU</pattern><template>I am near the place where we did it 3 Halloweens ago, do you remember?</template></category><category><pattern>SO  IF YOU JUST WANNA COME BY</pattern><template>Damn it, Bob.</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS A HEADWAY CAP  THAT GUY</pattern><template>He was sitting right here.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE SOME DECORUM  WE'RE AT A FUNERAL  SHHH YOU WANT TO DANCE  HUH  I WILL ROCK YOUR BODY WITH BIG NASTY HOOKS RIPPING SOME BLOOD OUT OF YOUR ASS</pattern><template>That's horrible.   Would you step back, man?</template></category><category><pattern>OUTSIDE OF ENRON AND A I G  AND BERNIE MADOFF</pattern><template>Worldcom. Bear Sterns. Lehman Brothers.</template></category><category><pattern>FACE BACK</pattern><template>I get some horrible reviews coming out of the Gate.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST LOOSE YOU</pattern><template>Shut up, Allen! I love you.</template></category><category><pattern>STILL NOTHING  I SWEAR TO YOU</pattern><template>I'm gonna go over and check on Terry. I have a bad knee, hold on.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU IMMEDIATELY CALLED YOUR BLUFF</pattern><template>Get up, and kill the police.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE AMERICAN WAY</pattern><template>Mr. Ershon, I believe this call is for you.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW WOW WOW THIS IS A RESTRICTED AREA</pattern><template>I finally pulled my gun.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  GUN  GUN  PASS UP THE GUN  LET'S GO PEOPLE</pattern><template>Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS WORRIED WHETHER I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN</pattern><template>Just the old lady Hello Allen,   Hello Mama Ramos. What are doing out here?</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS  BY A WAY OF APOLOGY  I CAN OFFER YOU MY PERSONAL COURT SIDE SEATS FOR THE KNICKS GAME WITH</pattern><template>... access to the Ambassador club.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GONNA HIT    IT'S GONNA CATCH    WHY ARE YOU WITH ALLEN</pattern><template>I mean.. That is not what I meant...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT    I'M PRETTY SURE YOU'VE NEVER VOTED    OH I VOTE  SPORTS REGULAR AMA 80  PLAYER OF THE WEEK</pattern><template>You're like a child in a leather jacket. That's what you're like.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO ALLEN</pattern><template>I think we all experienced our own ballet today.</template></category><category><pattern>STATISTICALLY SPEAKING  THERE'S ABOUT 30 KIDS IN HERE  10 OF YOU WILL BE DEAD BEFORE YOUR NEXT BIRTHDAY</pattern><template>Got a couple of tips, helped the guys stay out of the jail.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WAIT</pattern><template>Take him away.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS</pattern><template>Why have you worked your ass off trying to kill this case?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT IS NOT RIGHT</pattern><template>Oh my god, I'm hung over.</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE  NO</pattern><template>I never actually put my foot all the way down to the ground with the accelerator like that.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THEY TOOK OUR SHOES  OUR GUNS AND OUR CAR  THERE'S NO WAY THIS GOING OUT ON THE RADIO IF WE GONNA DO THIS TOGETHER  THERE ARE SOME ISSUES WE NEED TO SETTLE  OK</pattern><template>You said I had a weak chin, you said the way I peed in feminine.</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN IT  I'M LATE  I'M SUPPOSED TO CALL MY LADY</pattern><template>I though you said you guys split up?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO WAY I DON'T HAVE SOFT TISSUE DAMAGE</pattern><template>I just want to go somewhere and breastfeed right now.</template></category><category><pattern>COME LAY WITH ME AND BE SAFE AND LET'S MAKE LOVE  COME ON</pattern><template>Every time you say 'be safe'. It tears me apart. You got to let me be who I'm gonna be.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I HELP IT  YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>You know what's worst? The way you fart. Even your farts. They're not manly.</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS MY DANCE PARTNER  TERRY</pattern><template>Ok, I know that this is a big surprise but there are other things in the world besides being a cop Ok? And if you will excuse me. I'm gonna dance   You don't think I cannot do this shit? Huh?</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE IT'S WEIRD  IT'S A GROWN MAN GIVING ANOTHER MAN A PRESENT</pattern><template>Here we go. Open it up.</template></category><category><pattern>MY PLEASURE  THANK YOU</pattern><template>And remember, all I ask of you is don't let him get hurt, Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  THE ONLY LEAD WE HAVE  WE HAVE TO GO WITH THIS OR WE WALK AWAY FROM THIS CASE RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Fine. Let's go see her.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP MAN  SHUT UP</pattern><template>Martin and Fossi are probably on Studio beach talking to Sheppard Smith right now...</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST DON'T WANT TO EVER FEEL OUT OF CONTROL LIKE THAT EVER AGAIN</pattern><template>Don't worry. I got your back.</template></category><category><pattern>INSTEAD OF A FRESH START  I JUST WANNA PUNCH YOU IN THE FACE</pattern><template>Fresh start.</template></category><category><pattern>OFFICER HOITZ  YOU'VE BEEN COMING HERE FOR SIX MONTHS</pattern><template>And you haven't said a word. Safe environment, no judgement here   Douchebag   That's judgment, Jimmy. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU DIRTY MIKE AND THE BOYS</pattern><template>How do you know who we are?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A SICK PUPPY  I CAN'T LOOK AT IT  IT MAKES ME LAUGH SO HARD</pattern><template>Me too.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE LARGE AMOUNTS OF COCAINE ON THE SCENE  TRY TO STAY OUT OF TROUBLE  BOYS</pattern><template>There's no chance you are going on that call right?</template></category><category><pattern>HE TOSSES ME DOWN A MOS  PUMP  I SENT ONE THROUGH HIS CHEST</pattern><template>Game over, bitches Jimmy, let's talk about how that story made you feel Like a Viagra pill with a face.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LEARNED HOW TO PLAY IT IN 8TH GRADE TO MAKE FUN THE FAIRY THAT LIVED UP THE STREET</pattern><template>Terry asked Sheila to be his best man, but she declined.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BELIEVE ME  EVERYBODY WHO WAS IN ON THIS ORGY WAS MORE THAN WILLING</pattern><template>In fact, they left you a note here.. Thanks for the F shack.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T EVEN UNDERSTAND THOSE REFERENCE</pattern><template>Like a tick.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE NIGHT  TWO OF MY FAVORITE GIRLS  CANDY AND JOLENE  SAID  WE GOT TO TAKE YOU IN  THEY DROPPED ME OFF TO THE EMERGENCY ROOM</pattern><template>... that's where I met Sheila, I was a mess.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS THING GETS MESSY  WE NEVER TALKED</pattern><template>You can trust us.</template></category><category><pattern>DAVID ERSHON  YOU ARE UNDER ARREST FOR FRAUD</pattern><template>embezzlement and the connection to the murder of Don Beaman.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SORRY  SEE  THAT'S WHAT I AM TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>Oh my God, you need to leave. Get out!</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE ZERO DEBT ON THE NEW INVESTOR</pattern><template>Then you get their money and get disappeared and pay us back.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE</pattern><template>Oh cool, a helicopter. Must be covering the high speed chase.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MORE LIKE IT  YEAH</pattern><template>She wants to walk wrong for a week because you guys did it so hard.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LET'S SEE WHAT WE'VE GOT ON HOT TIPS  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>The new bath mats are in.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I'M FINE</pattern><template>See, I didn't knew you could dance.</template></category><category><pattern>DID HE JUST   DID HE JUST CALL HIMSELF A PEACOCK</pattern><template>Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  PEACE SHITBOYS  THEY'RE COPS</pattern><template>You turned my beautiful Prius into a nightmare.</template></category><category><pattern>AS A FLOATATION DEVICE  AH YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>Very funny. I have never apprehended anyone before.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO DAYS AGO  THE CITY WEPT  WE LOST TWO HEROES WHO GET EVERYTHING FOR US</pattern><template>who pay that ultimate sacrifice so that we may walk these streets safely There wasn't even an awning in that garage.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  YOU NEED TO LEAVE  GET OUT</pattern><template>Get out, Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT TERRY</pattern><template>Let's just settle this Peacocks don't fly.   They fly a little. They got a real running start.   As much as a penguin.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER SAID TO LOCK HER UP</pattern><template>A guy who does what needs to be done.</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY  I'M A COP  FOR YOUR INFORMATION  OK</pattern><template>A broken partnership.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T HAVE TESTICULAR CANCER</pattern><template>I got something to keep you going.</template></category><category><pattern>NO WAY  IT'S TOO DANGEROUS</pattern><template>Look, Terry, we don't know what's gonna happen to us tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SORRY</pattern><template>I told Terry about my dark days in college and I...</template></category><category><pattern>WHILE YOU WERE GOING CRAZY  LOOK WHAT I SNATCHED FROM HIS DESK</pattern><template>I think it's his phone sheet.</template></category><category><pattern>IT TURNS OUT THAT GRETCHEL AND DAWSON HAS    HOLD ON  I AM UP</pattern><template>Gretchel and Dawson accounting firm in Fairlawn, New Jersey has only one client, David Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT AT THE SAME TIME  THAT WOULD BE WRONG</pattern><template>Let's hear it from the top, every detail.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAY THINGS THAT ARE TOO PERSONAL</pattern><template>Ok.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE IN THE HIGH DESERT</pattern><template>They took my shoes again man. What the hell is it with taking shoes?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A COP</pattern><template>And getting busted down to a shitty assignment. Allen and Terry hit the trifecta.</template></category><category><pattern>EASY  MATE</pattern><template>They are driving into us.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME FINISH</pattern><template>He became a champion, and a movie star...</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE LIKE  HOW COME YOU NEVER FIRED YOUR WEAPON IN THE OFFICE BEFORE</pattern><template>Good point.</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE  DON'T MOVE  DROP YOUR WEAPONS</pattern><template>Drop it. Or be dropped, tall boy.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE ALSO SAYS SHE WANTS YOU ON TOP OF HER</pattern><template>Holding her hair and riding her like a bucking brand... while she sucks your thumb and says, Mami likey.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BASICALLY IT IS A HELD FOR PROFIT BANK THAT SETS INTEREST RATES AND MOVES MONEY TO OTHER BANKS</pattern><template>Is that a waste basket?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT TO BE CORNY  MAYBE IT'S YOU GUYS</pattern><template>Are you ready?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO DO IT</pattern><template>That's how you do it in the hood!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE ARMED AND DANGEROUS AND HOLDING DAVID ERSHON HOSTAGE</pattern><template>Guys, we are good guys.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>Dude, what is it with you and hot ladies? What's your secret?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS RIGHT THERE IN FRONT OF YOU THE WHOLE TIME  YOU GUYS ARE GETTING TRANSFERRED</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DON'T SHED A TEAR  PIMPS DON'T CRY</pattern><template>They never shed a tear.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  WE GOT A HOT ONE  HOITZ AND GAMBLE HAVE ERSHON HOSTAGE  HIGH SPEED CAR CHASE IN PROGRESS</pattern><template>Yes, gun, gun! Pass up the gun. Let's go people.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THERE AN APPEAL PROCESS WE CAN</pattern><template>Got to do what you got to do Captain.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  BOB  I DIDN'T MEAN IT  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>I'm upset.</template></category><category><pattern>BOOM  I DID THAT</pattern><template>Oh my God, that's what I'm talking about. We jack knifed them.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING    LET'S GO</pattern><template>We go to that call.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THERE WASN'T ANY SECURITY TEAM THAT GRABBED YOU  WE KNOW YOU'RE TARGETING A BIG FISH TO COVER LOSSES</pattern><template>You talk or I beat you so we don't show no bruises.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY GUYS  THERE IS A PROXY VOTE FOR BIG REINVESTMENT BIT  PENSION COMING UP</pattern><template>So, if you just wanna come by...</template></category><category><pattern>OO  HEY  COME ON  STAY WITH ME</pattern><template>We're losing him. He's dying.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS  GET OUT</pattern><template>Whatever.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU'RE WORKING TRAFFIC TODAY</pattern><template>Got them blocked the box. Besides, the partner's code, right?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STAY OUT OF OUR CRIME SCENE  YOU HEAR ME</pattern><template>Go! Go! Go!</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  CHRISTINETH</pattern><template>Hello, Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  IT'S STARTING TO GET A LITTLE WEIRD MAN</pattern><template>If something happens to you, I need to be there to take care of her.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  ALLEN  WE BOTH KNOW IT'S WOODEN</pattern><template>Apartment pop, now get in the car.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D COME STRONG AND YOU COME IN</pattern><template>I'm strong and you come in, got it?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A SHITHOLE</pattern><template>I love bombs.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL DO</pattern><template>That guy never comes down here. 20 years, I think I've seen that guy only one time.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MOST STABLE JOB I COULD THINK OF</pattern><template>An accountant for law and order.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SCARING THE SHIT OUT OF ME MAN  STOP IT</pattern><template>Is that how you conduct yourself?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  TERRY  LOOK AT THIS</pattern><template>I thought you're working traffic today?</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT  ALLEN</pattern><template>Get out!</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR WIFE IS CRAZY HOT</pattern><template>I mean even that Brazilian security chick, she was... I mean what is it with you and hot ladies?</template></category><category><pattern>SHOULDN'T WE TELL MAUCH  THAT UH WE ARE CHECKING THIS PLACE OUT</pattern><template>For what? We're just going to check it out.</template></category><category><pattern>IN A DEMOCRACY</pattern><template>What the hell are you doing man?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  I DIDN'T KNEW YOU COULD DANCE</pattern><template>We used to do those dance moves to make fun of guys when we were kids. Show them how queer they were. Ok?</template></category><category><pattern>SON OF A BITCH  THAT'S A COURT SIDE AND I WENT BLIND</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT AUTHORIZE THAT TRANSFER  THIS IS DAVID ERSHON</pattern><template>The transfer is for him. He will tell you not to authorize it, ok? Tell him!</template></category><category><pattern>I ABSOLUTELY APPAL DEATH</pattern><template>Hey Andrew Lloyd Webber, the jig is up, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>VERY FUNNY  I HAVE NEVER APPREHENDED ANYONE BEFORE</pattern><template>Really? Are you guys for real? Am I being punk'd?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS A PIMP</pattern><template>Yes, I was a pimp.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY  ARE YOU GUYS FOR REAL  AM I BEING PUNK'D</pattern><template>Detective Allen Gamble, we are in a cocaine covered car and we're bring in a Perp...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>I am sorry. I got so drunk last night I think I thought a tube of toothpaste was astronaut food.</template></category><category><pattern>W  WAIT  WHAT AM I BEING ARRESTED FOR</pattern><template>Scaffolding permit violation.</template></category><category><pattern>TO INVEST 32 BILLION</pattern><template>Who's got 32 billion dollars to rob?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID THEY GOT THAT STORY</pattern><template>I'm tired of being treated like a jerk for trying to do the right thing.</template></category><category><pattern>MARTIN AND FOSSI ARE PROBABLY ON STUDIO BEACH TALKING TO SHEPPARD SMITH RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>We arrested this jerk off for a scaffolding permit?!</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY ASKED SHEILA TO BE HIS BEST MAN  BUT SHE DECLINED</pattern><template>Let's be honest, we all want to be superstars and hotshots, but guess what...</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT NOW  THE STREET ARE A BLOODBATH</pattern><template>Statistically speaking, there's about 30 kids in here, 10 of you will be dead before your next birthday.</template></category><category><pattern>ANSWERING THE PHONE AND ALL THE STUPID SHIT THAT WE DON'T LIKE TO DO</pattern><template>All the gun fights, all the car chases, all the sex we don't want to have with women... but we have to...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT NINE MILLION SOCIALLY CONSCIOUS AND UNIFIED CITIZENS ALL JUST STEPPING UP AND DOING THEIR PART</pattern><template>As a little kid, didn't you dress up like cops and a robbers?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING: AS FAR AS THE PAPERWORK GOES  WE'LL TAKE CARE OF IT</pattern><template>You know why?   Why?</template></category><category><pattern>GOT THEM BLOCKED THE BOX  BESIDES  THE PARTNER'S CODE  RIGHT</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL YOUR WORK IS DONE HERE  YOU CAN GO</pattern><template>What about Ershon targeting the lottery?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE GONNA WRECK US TWICE</pattern><template>Coming from both directions.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW IT'S GONE</pattern><template>I know, you still got me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK  I WOKE UP  I TOOK THE BELT OFF MY NECK AND I GOT MY CAR AND I GOT OUT OF THERE</pattern><template>Talked about a wild weekend, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I RAISE UP TO TAKE THE LEADER OUT</pattern><template>O shit! I feel like I'm there now I hear a whistle. My partner's on the roof.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST THING FIRST  I GOT TO GO SEE SHEILA</pattern><template>No way, it's too dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER THAT NIGHT WE MET</pattern><template>The attending physician told me: We have a drugged out pimp in the back.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS DAVID</pattern><template>David, you're not returning my call, so I'd like you to meet Roger Wesley...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID YOU GUYS MEET</pattern><template>It's a really typical how we met story, Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO MINUTES BEFORE THE MARKETS OPEN  PAMELA BOARDMAN  CEO OF LENDL GLOBAL RINGING THE OPENING BELL  WITH BOARDMAN IS INVESTMENT BANKER  DAVID ERSHON  WHO MANAGES 40% OF LENDL $70 BILLION EQUITY POOL HOW MUCH DID WE LOSE</pattern><template>You may ring the bell now Ms. Boardman.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  PLEASE DO IT</pattern><template>Pop one off!</template></category><category><pattern>A GUY WHO DOES WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE</pattern><template>A guy who knows how to use dark side for good.</template></category><category><pattern>ATTA BOY  I'LL BE THERE IN TWO MINUTES EXACTLY</pattern><template>Another thing I hate: You always pay in exact change You're just mad because I have a nice change purse Why do you even care?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  JUST SOME PEOPLE I OWE MONEY TO</pattern><template>Then let's be here.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD YOU NOT SMILE LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Now you're asking me to mask my emotions because of how it makes you feel...</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO NO  I'M TALKING ABOUT DOING SOME SERIOUS DRINKING  DRINK WITH TERRY HOITZ</pattern><template>It's kind a sucks man. We worked our ass off on this case, now we got to hand over all the evidence?</template></category><category><pattern>GATOR'S BITCHES BETTER BE USING THE JIMMIES</pattern><template>I am sorry. See, that's what I am talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>TREMENDOUS</pattern><template>Gentlemen, do we understand each other? Cut the crap!</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY THING I HAD TO BE PROUD OF IN MY LIFE WAS BEING A DETECTIVE THAT WAS ALL I HAD</pattern><template>Now it's gone.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL DUE TO WHAT YOU GUYS DO  THANK YOU</pattern><template>And we do it again and again   Ay, ay, ay! You shut your face!</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN  IT'S A LONG STORY BUT I AM JUST GONNA CUT TO THE CHASE  WE ARE IN LAS VEGAS</pattern><template>All right, we were, we were kidnapped, put on a freight train and shipped out here.</template></category><category><pattern>SWEETIE  THIS ONE IS THE VODKA RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Hal, just please sit down please.</template></category><category><pattern>MEET ME OUTSIDE AT THE BACK OF THE SERVICE ENTRANCE I AM FLYING AIR SINGAPORE</pattern><template>Hey Douglas, how's the wife?</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT ONE OF THESE LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>I don't know that they put tampons on wheels.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT THAT  I JUST UH</pattern><template>I saw how aggressive you were being and I thought, Wow, I gotta go even bigger than that, since we are doing bad cop, bad cop.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANNA KNOW WHY I'M SO ANGRY ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>Because the more I try to do right, the more I screw things up.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP  WE'RE GOING TO THE CAR</pattern><template>and we're going after this case.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T HAVE A CONSCIENCE IN THE PIMP GAME</pattern><template>One night, two of my favorite girls, Candy and Jolene, said, We got to take you in, they dropped me off to the Emergency Room...</template></category><category><pattern>G'DAY  MATE</pattern><template>Roger is gonna babysit you because I don't trust you. Because I think you are going to take off.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS IT</pattern><template>Move.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE ABOUT TO HAVE US A LITTLE SCOOP PARTY IN THE RED PRIUS OVER HERE IF YOU WANT TO JOIN US</pattern><template>Are you Dirty Mike and the boys?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING TO ME  YOU'RE KILLING ME INSIDE  AND GO LIGHT ON ME MAN</pattern><template>You run around like a crack dealing drug addicts.</template></category><category><pattern>ME TOO</pattern><template>Real nice, you know it's all class.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LISTEN TO ME YOU WISENUT WIMP MONKEY  YOU PLAY SQUASH WITH ERSHON RIGHT</pattern><template>Your kids going to school with his?</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST OFF  MY WIFE IS CUTE  BUT SHE'S NOT HOT</pattern><template>Dude, you're insane, your wife is scolding hot.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT FINGERPRINTS</pattern><template>You find any fingerprints?</template></category><category><pattern>I USE IT MAINLY FOR MY PARENTS AND PROSTITUTES</pattern><template>Not at the same time, that would be wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AN AWFUL GAS LEAK</pattern><template>Gas leak? The only gas leak is the one coming out of your mouth right now.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HIGHLIGHTS ARE GREAT</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>DETECTIVE  DETECTIVE</pattern><template>One at a time, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I SAY YOU CAN DO IT</pattern><template>I mean I don't want you to jump but you have the capability.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY  I GOT YOUR BACK</pattern><template>I say we get Ershon grilled and see if he cracks. I'm tired of all this tippy toeing around.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY  ONE DAY I WAKE UP AND I LOOK IN THE MIRROR AND I DON'T LIKE WHAT I SEE</pattern><template>I mean, I have gotten out of control and I didn't even realize that.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T KEEP ME COOKED UP IN HERE  OK</pattern><template>I am a peacock, you got to let me fly!</template></category><category><pattern>FRESH START</pattern><template>It's the last one.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE THE MORE I TRY TO DO RIGHT  THE MORE I SCREW THINGS UP</pattern><template>We've got a possible jumper at 3 World Financial Center, 23rd floor.</template></category><category><pattern>CORRECT THIS SCATHLIC SITUATION  CASE IS CLOSED</pattern><template>I've taken care all the necessary paperwork...</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT CARE</pattern><template>Give me that. I know how to talk to him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DO WE GO  WHERE DO WE GO</pattern><template>I have a small apartment no one knows about it.</template></category><category><pattern>I MYSELF HAVE 18 LAMBORGHINIS AND A SUBARU STATION WAGON</pattern><template>And it's because of this excess that I have flourished, I employ you.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE YOU  TERRY</pattern><template>Bye, Sheila.</template></category><category><pattern>REAL QUIET  YOU GOT TO CREEP</pattern><template>Come on, you don't say Creep Creep unless you're quoting TLC.</template></category><category><pattern>SPECIAL FORCES  RIGHT</pattern><template>Just watch your step, detective. There are three things I love in this world Kylie Minogue...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  MY MAIN CLIENT IS LENDL GLOBAL</pattern><template>Can I ask what is this about?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER OWNED A NEW CAR</pattern><template>Watch out, in the back there is a baby mouse and a used condom. Really gross.</template></category><category><pattern>SPECIAL FORCES ZIP LINE THESE GUYS ARE PROS YOU'RE THINKING WHAT I'M THINKING  PARTNER</pattern><template>Aim for the bushes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T GET IT  THERE'S A DARKNESS INSIDE OF ME  IT WANTS TO GET OUT AND WANTS TO WALK AROUND</pattern><template>It wants some walking around money and it wants to buy some shoes...</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL THINK OF IT</pattern><template>So what about you, Terry?</template></category><category><pattern>A CLASSMATE OF MINE  BRENDA  IN EFFORT TO RAISE MONEY  AND STAY IN SCHOOL CAME UP WITH A NIFTY PLAN</pattern><template>where she thought she dates guys and charge them money.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO TAP THE GROUND WHO THE POOR SUCKER THEY'RE MAKING THE DEAL WITH  BUT WE GOT TO STOP IT</pattern><template>It's about time the peacock fly.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING TO GIVE YOU THIS  IT'S A RAPE WHISTLE</pattern><template>You blow that if you're in any trouble. Someone with an actual gun will come and help you out.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  COZ I AM GONNA TELL YOU DIRECTLY TO YOUR FACE</pattern><template>No, you don't have to   No I don't like you I think you're a fake cop. The sound of your piss hitting the urinal, it sounds feminine If you were in the wild, I would attack you, even if you weren't in my food chain.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL</pattern><template>They are having a helicopter, is definitely cheating.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOWED IT  A COUPLE OF HOMELESS PEOPLE WERE MESSING AROUND IN IT</pattern><template>That's an official police car.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT I WANNA GET THAT SLICE YOU KNOW WHAT I JUST DID  I JUST WALKED OUT THAT DOOR</pattern><template>saw a couple of detectives down there and I was about to start badmouthing you behind your back...</template></category><category><pattern>NOT A PERSON IN THIS ROOM BELIEVES YOU'LL SHOOT THIS CLERK</pattern><template>Oh yeah? Thank you so much, gentlemen, for the prompt delivery of Mr. Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>AND REMEMBER  ALL I ASK OF YOU IS DON'T LET HIM GET HURT  TERRY</pattern><template>She tells me that every day before I leave.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL UNITS  FIREMEN EN ROUTE</pattern><template>The S.E.C.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  TERRY  HEY  THAT WAS LIBERATING FOR ME  I DO NOT KNOW HOW IT FELT FOR YOU</pattern><template>Here. Check this out. An article from six months ago.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I KINDA NEED SOMEBODY TO HELP ME OUT LIKE  YOU KNOW  MY PARTNER IN CRIME</pattern><template>Yeah, I can make a schedule.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CANNOT BE TOO CAREFUL</pattern><template>What are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>AND MY SHOES</pattern><template>Wait a minute, did you identify yourselves as police officers?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  YOU STILL GOT ME</pattern><template>Don't you get it? I don't want you Allen. Ok?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  LOUIS  THANKS FOR ASKING</pattern><template>My son is bisexual.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE GONNA HAVE SEX IN YOUR CAR  IT WILL HAPPEN AGAIN</pattern><template>I don't know where I am gonna sleep tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>SAW A COUPLE OF DETECTIVES DOWN THERE AND I WAS ABOUT TO START BADMOUTHING YOU BEHIND YOUR BACK</pattern><template>but I stopped myself because my Pop taught me that a man who talks behind somebody's back is a coward.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OPPOSITE  WE WERE NOT SMART  CAPTAIN GENE</pattern><template>Just Captain. Just Captain. It's not Captain Gene. I do not have a kitty show.</template></category><category><pattern>SO STOP POINTING IT AT ME</pattern><template>Look, tomorrow morning all I know is I am going to Mauch, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>SAVE YOURSELF SOME GAS</pattern><template>Captain!</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO GENTLEMEN    HELLO SIR    HEY</pattern><template>You know I was talking to Gene here.</template></category><category><pattern>LENDL GLOBAL WITH EVERYTHING</pattern><template>David Ershon is often found in the company of Judge Scalia and the lead singer of Maroon 5.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  THAT HURT</pattern><template>Excuse me? Where's my car?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO IS THAT TALKING</pattern><template>It's a frontline narration app. It's only 99 cents.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL BE ABLE TO TRAP CERTAIN AMOUNTS OF OXYGEN</pattern><template>It's not gonna be days at a time.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO CARES  IT'S NOT IMPORTANT OK</pattern><template>Hoitz, Gamble, Captain. Not good.</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO  LOOK AT ME</pattern><template>Yup, you want to talk to me?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU DON'T THINK EVERY OTHER DETECTIVE HERE ISN'T THINKING THE SAME THING</pattern><template>Allen, listen to me, Danson and Highsmith are gone.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TAPPING IT OFF</pattern><template>Are you crazy?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY  YOU OK</pattern><template>Hey Gene... Captain, I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  TERRY  WE DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO US TOMORROW</pattern><template>But tonight, I need to make things right with Sheila.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  ARE YOU DAVID ERSHON</pattern><template>Yes, Sir David Ershon. Doesn't matter. I am in a little bit of a rush Gentlemen, if you don't mind. Thank you   Excuse me, but you are under arrest Ok? You have the right to remain silent Anything you do or say can be used um... What 's the next part?</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT  BEAMAN  HE'S GOT TO KNOW SOMETHING</pattern><template>Wesley.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE GET A HIT   THIS CASE IS GONNA HEAT UP FASTER THAN A JUNKIE SPOON</pattern><template>You do one thing when you wake up tomorrow... bring it. Thank you, Sheila.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS ONLY EXPECTING ONE MAN</pattern><template>You know, just some people I owe money to.</template></category><category><pattern>OUCH</pattern><template>Wow. That hurt.</template></category><category><pattern>BRIEFLY AND THEN GO BACK TO THE BEGINNING</pattern><template>Then periodically returned to the end, maybe giving different characters perspective throughout.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE SHOT JETER AND THE OTHER SHOT AN OFFICE</pattern><template>Have some decorum, we're at a funeral. Shhh You want to dance, huh? I will rock your body with big nasty hooks Ripping some blood out of your ass.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER  GO INSIDE  BYE  SHEILA</pattern><template>Bye.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  MY BUTTERFLY</pattern><template>Load them up and send them back to...</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T NEED YOU TO STICK UP FOR ME OK</pattern><template>I could've handled that myself.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE ARE AN INDEPENDENT GOVERNMENT AGENCY WHO LONGED WITH THE F B I AND THE FEDERAL RESERVES</pattern><template>regulate stock markets and corporate fraud.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE LAST ONE</pattern><template>I have to be able to express myself and say things you know.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAY WE GET ERSHON GRILLED AND SEE IF HE CRACKS  I'M TIRED OF ALL THIS TIPPY TOEING AROUND</pattern><template>Ok.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FANTASTIC  YOU TOTALLY UNDERSOLD IT</pattern><template>The pageantry, the costumes. Wow! What a musical.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU TAPPING OFF  YOU'RE HITTING ME IN THE FACE</pattern><template>I'm tapping it off.</template></category><category><pattern>TURN OFF THE LIGHTS</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE BIG DAY OUT THERE  BIG ONE  WE GOT A FULL MOON  PEOPLE ARE GONNA BE AMPED</pattern><template>All right? Let's see what we've got on hot tips, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>SMALL DIMPLES JUST ABOVE A WOMAN'S BUTTOCKS</pattern><template>Beautiful features.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARRESTED THIS JERK OFF FOR A SCAFFOLDING PERMIT</pattern><template>W..wait, what am I being arrested for?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME SORT OF PAPER TRAIL</pattern><template>If we find that, we can track it. Then we can go Mauch.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>Who the hell are all these people?</template></category><category><pattern>MY WIFE'S MAKING HER FAMOUS DEVIL EGGS AGAIN</pattern><template>My waistline is furious.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW YOU GONNA DO THAT</pattern><template>We will construct a series of breathing apparatus with kelp.</template></category><category><pattern>GUYS  WE ARE GOOD GUYS</pattern><template>Exactly, they are the good guys.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  SOMEONE IS NICE ENOUGH TO PUT LINSEED OIL ON IT  SOME KIND OF STAIN ON THAT</pattern><template>Dark walnut or something. You may wanna think about dropping them a thank you note.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE THEY</pattern><template>They are some Chechnian patriots, entrepreneurs and the black chaps are some businessmen from Nigeria.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YEAH DUDE</pattern><template>It's a lot of cocaine.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT IN THE HOOD</pattern><template>Pay the winner. Pay for the winner. Everybody saw!</template></category><category><pattern>PIMPS DON'T CRY    NO THEY DON'T</pattern><template>They don't shed a tear. Pimps don't cry...</template></category><category><pattern>O YEAH  WELL  THEY SUCCEEDED  OK</pattern><template>I'm tired of this.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME AGAIN WHY I DECIDED TO GET ON THIS ROOF</pattern><template>I think you can chop that up to bad life choices Get rid of that asshole   O o I knew when you say  O o  O dude, you put a dent in my hood.</template></category><category><pattern>I USE HOT OIL</pattern><template>They are gonna wreck us twice.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CORNER AROUND THE 54TH AND THIRD AVENUE  IT HUMS  IT IS TERRY'S INTERSECTION</pattern><template>And the traffic guys, they are good guys.</template></category><category><pattern>TRANSPORTATION SERVICES</pattern><template>Yeah. yeah. We'd be a good friend   Thanks so much.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME JUST ASSURE YOU  FELLAS  DAVID ERSHON IS AN UPSTANDING CITIZEN</pattern><template>I'm playing squash with him tonight at the club, and we're having dinner.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  YOU DON'T REALIZE I MIGHT BE KILLED TOMORROW</pattern><template>Ok. She says she wants to unplug all the clocks and the phones and have a three day sex marathon.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE ACTUALLY BECAME A TV ACTRESS</pattern><template>Heather Locklear.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S JUST KEEP OUR THING ABOUT WORK  OK</pattern><template>All right, Good bye buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>WAY UP THERE</pattern><template>Well Terry, can't thank you enough for coming by. What a wonderful lovely evening, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>HIT THE LIGHT</pattern><template>Do not authorize that transfer. This is David Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS A BRIBE</pattern><template>Son of a bitch! That's a court side and I went blind.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS HE A VICTIM OF FINANCIAL PROFILING</pattern><template>Financial profiling?</template></category><category><pattern>I DO  THEY ARE FULL OF RICH HISTORY</pattern><template>Damn it! I'm late, I'm supposed to call my lady.</template></category><category><pattern>A BUNCH OF LOSING LOTTERY TICKETS</pattern><template>Look at this, there was a two minute phone call made after we were jumped.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BRONX  OCTOBER  GAME 7 OF THE WORLD SERIES</pattern><template>Got a marvellous high pressure handling the crowd. I pull tunnel duty Then I saw a shadow figure in the tunnel. I told him to stop.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES IT BOTHER YOU THAT THE CASTIAN ROBBERY ONLY TOOK $74 000 OF DIAMONDS</pattern><template>They are junkies. Who cares.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW THAT THEY PUT TAMPONS ON WHEELS</pattern><template>They have their fun, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM THE WINNER</pattern><template>I didn't need you to stick up for me ok?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'M GONNA SAY SOMETHING RIGHT NOW  IT'S ABOUT A MAN WHO CAME FROM AUSTRIA</pattern><template>... with a dream   Arnold Schwarzenegger!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT'S RIGHT  YOU  YOU GONNA WALK A BEEP DOWNTOWN  YOU GONNA WALK A BEEP DOWNTOWN  IT'S DONE</pattern><template>But Captain?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT GONNA SHOOT ME</pattern><template>I won't?   No   I shot Jeter.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT DONKEYS OR DEER  THEY HAVE HOOVES  WHAT ABOUT BOVINE CREATURES</pattern><template>Were you just thinking yourself a fresh start?   Yeah.   Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S KIND A SUCKS MAN  WE WORKED OUR ASS OFF ON THIS CASE  NOW WE GOT TO HAND OVER ALL THE EVIDENCE</pattern><template>Yeah. That is not right.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  SHE SAYS OTHER THINGS</pattern><template>Please, you don't realize I might be killed tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT'S NOT ME</pattern><template>But uh, I'm not. Shaved.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH TOM HANKS    AND MEG RYAN    HE DIDN'T HAVE POISON IVY UP HIS ASS</pattern><template>Yes, he did.</template></category><category><pattern>FIND THE CLERK  GET THE ROUTING NUMBER</pattern><template>We got to stop it.</template></category><category><pattern>ERSHON IS DIRTY  HE'S TARGETING THE LOTTERY</pattern><template>Next, I want you guys to hand in all the evidence, you think you have to the S.E.C.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YES  I'LL TELL HIM HE DOESN'T HAVE TO KEEP WATCHING ME</pattern><template>So you're good to go.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE OLD BALL AND CHAIN</pattern><template>Get over here.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY FIRST BRAND NEW CAR</pattern><template>I never owned a new car.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT JUST ONE MORE THING</pattern><template>She said she loves you and wants to hold your hand and have ice tea with you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HIT YOU FEEL ME  GATOR NEVER BEEN ABOUT THAT NEVER BEEN ABOUT PLAYING NO SHIT</pattern><template>Sweetie, I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS A HOLE IN NEW YORK CITY THAT NEEDED TO BE FILLED</pattern><template>Two days ago, the City wept, we lost two heroes who get everything for us...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE NOT GONNA SHOOT ME</pattern><template>Ok, I'll be honest. This is the second time I ever fired this.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'LL BRING IT  GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>Good night.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE</pattern><template>One of them had an Australian accent.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE FOUND YOUR RED PRIUS  IT'S TRYING TO VOTE FOR RALPH NADER</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE DOING THIS</pattern><template>You're supposed to be walking the beat.</template></category><category><pattern>BYE  GUYS</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE SURE YOU GOT THIS  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Detectives.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DON'T  I'VE SAID THAT DIRECTLY TO YOUR FACE NUMEROUS TIMES  I WAS REALLY HONEST ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>We are on a huge case. All right?</template></category><category><pattern>NO DRINKS    NO DRINKS CAN'T DO IT    I CAN'T DO IT DANSON AND HIGHSMITH  SHOOT  DRIVE AND SEX IN STYLE THEY ARE ROCK STARS</pattern><template>Then you got your jokers, your ball busters, your vets...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHEN YOU FIND THAT WHAT'S REAL</pattern><template>And what needs doing.</template></category><category><pattern>SETTING THE PERIMETER  NO ARREST UNTIL WE GET THERE</pattern><template>Hit the light.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WORK HERE</pattern><template>Yes, I do.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE I DO  PLEASE SIT</pattern><template>Two of those... water please No lime wedges, just cucumber.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE BEING AWFUL</pattern><template>What's wrong?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH I GUESS WE KINDA KNEW THAT  BUT IT'S A DRAG I MEAN  AT A CERTAIN POINT  WHO'S LEFT TO BE A HERO</pattern><template>Not to be corny. Maybe it's you guys.</template></category><category><pattern>HONEY  THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO</pattern><template>You are not that same person anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY I'VE BEEN HIDING HONEY     BUT THIS DINNER WAS TRICKY    WHO ARE YOU    I'M DR  SHEILA GAMBLE  HIS WIFE</pattern><template>Come on, seriously, who is that?   His old lady.   Sweetie It's a workstation.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A PLACE THAT'S SAFE</pattern><template>I wanna break your hip.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT HOW YOU CONDUCT YOURSELF</pattern><template>In a democracy?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S GONNA BE FINGERPRINTS IN THAT CAR  AND TOMORROW  WE 'RE GONNA RUN THOSE FINGERPRINTS THROUGH THE SYSTEM</pattern><template>If we get a hit.. this case is gonna heat up faster than a junkie spoon.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY SORRY FOR YOUR LOSS  MAM</pattern><template>Lovely hat.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR</pattern><template>Captain, If you really want to disarm this guy, take out the batteries in the calculator.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN I DON'T WANT YOU TO JUMP BUT YOU HAVE THE CAPABILITY</pattern><template>Oh look he's flying.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP</pattern><template>We don't do that.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS ALL THE EVIDENCE WE HAVE I TRULY HOPE YOU TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY</pattern><template>Yes, very much so.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SHOULD BE WATCHING US</pattern><template>Who?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE FEAR IN THE MAN'S EYE WHO KNOWS THAT I 'M ABOUT TO HURT HIM</pattern><template>Hey, shake your dicks. This pissing contest is over.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S OKAY</pattern><template>Remember that night we met?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A HIGH PROFILE KIDNAPPING</pattern><template>David Ershon, wealthy banker.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THESE TWO JUMMOCKS  WOULD YOU</pattern><template>One shot Jeter and the other shot an office.</template></category><category><pattern>FIREMEN THOUGHT IT WAS A GAS LEAK  BUT NO WAY  IT WAS TIMED</pattern><template>They don't want to kill us but they want to scare us.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOOK MY SHOES AGAIN MAN  WHAT THE HELL IS IT WITH TAKING SHOES</pattern><template>They took your wooden gun?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY YOU LISTEN TO ME  YOU PIECE OF SHIT  IT'S JUST YOU AND ME  AND I'M GONNA RIP YOU APART</pattern><template>How did you cover your losses, huh? What drug cartel are you working with now?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S OK  SUSAN  UH  TWO GLACIER WATER WITH MEDITERRANEAN LIME</pattern><template>No no, No more water! We're not here for that.</template></category><category><pattern>HALF EMPTY BOTTLE OF GIN  CHAIR KNOCKED OVER  LOOK AT THIS  IT'S A CLEAR SIGN OF STRUGGLE</pattern><template>Make sure you got this, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I DO NOT WANT THOSE SCRUBS</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GUYS IN LAW ENFORCEMENT</pattern><template>Yeah, we are an independent government agency who longed with the F.B.I and the Federal Reserves...</template></category><category><pattern>I AM NOT REPORTING ANY LOSSES  DAVID</pattern><template>I have zero debt on the new investor.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Ok Look, they're not all first round pick ok?</template></category><category><pattern>ERSHON CONSORTIUM'S CURRENT FINANCIAL INVESTMENT EXCEEDS $70 BILLION IT'S LARGEST CLIENTS INCLUDES SCHERING PLOUGH AND LENDL GLOBAL</pattern><template>Lendl Global has those TV ads and I can't figure out what they are doing.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL NEVER FORGET TONIGHT</pattern><template>Bye, Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE SAID SHE LOVES YOU AND WANTS TO HOLD YOUR HAND AND HAVE ICE TEA WITH YOU</pattern><template>Come on! That's not all she said.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU GET THEIR MONEY AND GET DISAPPEARED AND PAY US BACK</pattern><template>Yes, yes, I'll tell him he doesn't have to keep watching me.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MILEAGE</pattern><template>Oh. Outstanding.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN HUM IF I WANT TO I KNOW YOU CAN  I AM ASKING YOU TO STOP</pattern><template>Well, if you're asking then I'll stop.</template></category><category><pattern>DETECTIVES</pattern><template>All your work is done here. You can go.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY ANDREW LLOYD WEBBER  THE JIG IS UP  OK</pattern><template>You know there wasn't any security team that grabbed you, we know you're targeting a big fish to cover losses.</template></category><category><pattern>UMM I KNOW  PEOPLE ARE SHOCKED  BECAUSE HE IS EPISCOPALIAN AND I AM CATHOLIC</pattern><template>but, somehow it works.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE BOMBS</pattern><template>I can't hear.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT TIME: ME  YOU  LIBRARY</pattern><template>Not even close!</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF THIS WERE AN ACTUAL INVESTIGATION  I WOULD IMMEDIATELY RECUSE MYSELF</pattern><template>This is all the evidence we have I truly hope you take this seriously.</template></category><category><pattern>TO GIVE ME BACK MY REAL GUN</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>IT BROUGHT UP SOME FEELINGS</pattern><template>Honey, that was a long time ago.</template></category><category><pattern>WE KNOW    WE KNOW    WE KNOW</pattern><template>all right.. all right.. all right.. listen up! listen up!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW  WATCH OUT  I THINK THEY ARE WATCHING THE HOUSE</pattern><template>Don't worry sweetie, I think I have a way of getting to you.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE GOOD TO GO</pattern><template>Heard everything, mate.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  WE WERE  WE WERE KIDNAPPED  PUT ON A FREIGHT TRAIN AND SHIPPED OUT HERE</pattern><template>Let me just stop you right there. Don't bullshit me.</template></category><category><pattern>I HEAR YOU</pattern><template>Let's clean the slate right now. Fresh start.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE DO IT AGAIN AND AGAIN   AY  AY  AY  YOU SHUT YOUR FACE</pattern><template>If we want to hear you talk, I'll shove my arm up your ass and work your mouth like a puppet!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT COMPUTERS</pattern><template>What if one day they were in charge?</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU SAID BAD COP  BAD COP</pattern><template>While you were going crazy, look what I snatched from his desk.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE WE SHOULD UH CALL OURSELVES THE FABREEZE BROTHERS  CAUSE IT'S FEELING SO FRESH RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Right?</template></category><category><pattern>SHEILA AND I GOT INTO IT TONIGHT</pattern><template>She threw me out.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF YOU MAKE A LOT OF NOISE AND YOU ATTRACT THE MEDIA ATTENTION</pattern><template>then you bring the DA in on this, I am out, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY FOLKS  EVERYONE LISTEN UP   LISTEN UP</pattern><template>We got a high profile kidnapping.</template></category><category><pattern>WESLEY</pattern><template>Detective Hoitz and Gamble, we got this.</template></category><category><pattern>GO  TO THE SIDE PLEASE</pattern><template>You don't think I'm a real cop, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  SHEILA</pattern><template>Bye, Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S IT MATE  I HAVE HAD IT WITH THIS JOKER AND HIS WOODEN GUN</pattern><template>They gonna kill me and then they will kill you.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN</pattern><template>He also says that he wants you to stare into each other eyes without blinking while you do it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU�RE NOT A COP UNTIL YOU�RE THROWN OUT OF THE HOUSE  PARTNER</pattern><template>Does it bother you that the Castian robbery only took $74,000 of diamonds?</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN  I AM BEING STRAIGHT WITH YOU  LOOK</pattern><template>We think something is going on, ok? We think Ershon is targeting the lottery to cover his losses.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO BE ABLE TO EXPRESS MYSELF AND SAY THINGS YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Hey folks, everyone listen up   Listen up!</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO</pattern><template>They are Nigerians.</template></category><category><pattern>TWICE  TERRY SAYS TWICE  I AGREE</pattern><template>I'm hanging up. I am done.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WELL  WELL  WHAT WE GOT HERE</pattern><template>Look at these two jummocks, would you?</template></category><category><pattern>UNIVERSITY I WENT TO DECIDED THEY NEEDED TO RAISE TUITION</pattern><template>A classmate of mine, Brenda, in effort to raise money, and stay in school came up with a nifty plan..</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU HERE FOR THE BATH MATS</pattern><template>I need you to be straight with me.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOU'RE GONNA TELL ME WHO THAT IS</pattern><template>Are you really Allen's wife?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WOULD</pattern><template>You're being awful.</template></category><category><pattern>IN 40 YEARS  I'VE BEEN ENFORCING THE LAW  I'VE LEARNT ONE THING  WHEN THAT HAPPENS  STOP</pattern><template>Gene, how's the family?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN THIS GUY CAN BE CONNECTED TO DRUG CARTELS  OR BLACK MARKET ORGAN SALES HUMAN TRAFFICKING  ALL OF IT   HOW DO YOU GET THAT FROM ANYTHING I JUST SAID</pattern><template>Hey guys, the soup is on.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH A DREAM   ARNOLD SCHWARZENEGGER</pattern><template>Let me finish.</template></category><category><pattern>BEAUTIFUL FEATURES</pattern><template>And the fear in the man's eye who knows that I 'm about to hurt him.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOST A BUNCH OF MONEY FROM SOME PEOPLE  AND NOW THEY WANT IT BACK</pattern><template>What about Don Beaman?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE HAVING A HELICOPTER  IS DEFINITELY CHEATING</pattern><template>Go.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S UNDER THEIR JURISDICTION</pattern><template>Don't you get it? This case is talking to us. I'm a peacock, Captain. You got to let me fly on this one.</template></category><category><pattern>LRB  LITTLE RIVER BAND</pattern><template>This music makes me feel like I am going shopping for training bra.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS MUCH CHUBBIER BACK THEN</pattern><template>I don't get it.</template></category><category><pattern>BAD IDEA</pattern><template>Hey guys!   Bob, what are you doing here?   I'm investing.</template></category><category><pattern>ARNOLD PALMER ALERT  ARNOLD PALMER ALERT  WHO WANTS SOME ARNIE PALMIES</pattern><template>Sweetie, this one is the vodka right here.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE COPS  HIT THE CHOPPER</pattern><template>It's Martin and Fossi.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE FIND THAT  WE CAN TRACK IT  THEN WE CAN GO MAUCH</pattern><template>So, I did some more research on Ershon's accounting firm, and I found some pretty interesting stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW WHO WE ARE</pattern><template>You left a note in that car.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU FELLAS  THIS POINT  YOU JUST BE GLAD THAT MR  ERSHON IS NOT PRESSING CHARGES FOR AN EXCESSIVE USE OF FORCE</pattern><template>Thank you Captain.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY SHIT    IT'S MORE AGGRESSIVE INVESTMENT STRATEGY FOR THE PENSION  ALLEN  WE ARE THE SUCKERS  THEY ARE TARGETING THE POLICE PENSION FUND</pattern><template>Gentlemen, you are here illegally and without a warrant. We are within our rights to take action.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE DRIVING INTO US</pattern><template>Stand over there. Wood.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL CONSTRUCT A SERIES OF BREATHING APPARATUS WITH KELP</pattern><template>We will be able to trap certain amounts of oxygen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A LUCKY DOG</pattern><template>It's true.</template></category><category><pattern>DID THAT GO THE WAY YOU THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA GO  NOPE</pattern><template>Two minutes before the markets open, Pamela Boardman, CEO of Lendl Global ringing the opening bell. With Boardman is investment banker, David Ershon, who manages 40% of Lendl $70 billion equity pool How much did we lose?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF ONE DAY THEY WERE IN CHARGE</pattern><template>If you don't shut up, I will cut your rear off with a butter knife.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST WE STOP YOU FROM GETTING THE PENSION FUND</pattern><template>Well, you didn't, it's already in my account and by 9 o'clock in the morning it gets into the Lendl equity fund then from there it's transferred to a dozen of offshore accounts.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T CARE</pattern><template>Yeah, I say you can do it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS SO SO NICE MEETING TODAY</pattern><template>My pleasure. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>BACK OFF AND STOP CALLING</pattern><template>Setting the perimeter, no arrest until we get there.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA KILL YOU FIRST</pattern><template>And then they will kill me.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S CRAZY  HE BROKE THE LAW AND WE ARRESTED HIM</pattern><template>There wasn't a security tape. He said, don't let these people take me I mean when you hear hooves, you think horses not zebras.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  CAN I SEE YOU IN THE HALLWAY FOR A SECOND</pattern><template>I.. I'm super busy right now.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  AND MAYBE YOU START WITH CASTIAN ROBBERY  OK</pattern><template>Watch it!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S TROUBLE UH   DID SOMEONE CALL 9 1 HOLY SHIT</pattern><template>That's it.. I'm sick of all this running   Hang on...</template></category><category><pattern>THE RETURNS ARE REALLY EXCITING  I THINK OUR MEMBERS IS GONNA BE JUST THRILLED</pattern><template>It made about 18 percent over the last ten years.</template></category><category><pattern>DETECTIVE ALLEN GAMBLE  WE ARE IN A COCAINE COVERED CAR AND WE'RE BRING IN A PERP</pattern><template>one David Ershon...</template></category><category><pattern>CHRISTINETH  YOU IDIOT  YOU COME TO OUR HOUSE  YOU GET MY WIFE'S NAME RIGHT</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY SWEETIE  I THINK I HAVE A WAY OF GETTING TO YOU</pattern><template>I have to admit, I wasn't gonna come. I mean, after all those years, after the restraining order...</template></category><category><pattern>JUST TELL US WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>I lost a bunch of money from some people, and now they want it back.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WANTS TO WALK WRONG FOR A WEEK BECAUSE YOU GUYS DID IT SO HARD</pattern><template>That's just lovely.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE HEARD OF HER</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S IT   I'M SICK OF ALL THIS RUNNING   HANG ON</pattern><template>You have the right to remain silent...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TALKING ABOUT MY LIFE</pattern><template>The corner around the 54th and third Avenue, it hums. It is Terry's intersection.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO CHANCE YOU ARE GOING ON THAT CALL RIGHT</pattern><template>No chance, too busy.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO IT  I DO IT STOP HUMMING THAT SONG</pattern><template>I can hum if I want to I know you can, I am asking you to stop.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM EVERYTHING I'VE HEARD I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU GUYS ARE THE BEST IN THESE TYPES OF INVESTIGATIONS</pattern><template>Outside of Enron and A.I.G. and Bernie Madoff.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M STRONG AND YOU COME IN  GOT IT</pattern><template>Got it.</template></category><category><pattern>LENDL GLOBAL HAS THOSE TV ADS AND I CAN'T FIGURE OUT WHAT THEY ARE DOING</pattern><template>Oil, media, healthcare... You probably heard their jingle.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PEOPLE THAT DO THE REAL WORK  THE ONES THAT MAKE THE DIFFERENCE</pattern><template>you don't see 'em on TV or on the front page.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU GOT YOUR JOKERS  YOUR BALL BUSTERS  YOUR VETS</pattern><template>... and the other guys...</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO SHOOT MY WAY OUT</pattern><template>What are you gonna do though, you know? Bar Mitzvah's.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYBODY SEE THIS  HE'S GOT A GUN ON ME I AM BEING KIDNAPPED  REALLY  WE'RE IN A POLICE STATION AND NO ONE IS SEEING THIS</pattern><template>So then what happened?</template></category><category><pattern>DAVID ERSHON IS OFTEN FOUND IN THE COMPANY OF JUDGE SCALIA AND THE LEAD SINGER OF MAROON 5</pattern><template>I mean this guy can be connected to drug cartels. Or black market organ sales Human trafficking, all of it   How do you get that from anything I just said?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A REAL SHAME YOU KNOW  I GOT MYSELF A PRIUS  IT'S A HELL OF A MACHINE</pattern><template>It's my first brand new car.</template></category><category><pattern>A DESK POP</pattern><template>Yeah!   Not it's not!   They were so convincing.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO IS THIS GUY</pattern><template>What are you doing here, Allen?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN PERIODICALLY RETURNED TO THE END  MAYBE GIVING DIFFERENT CHARACTERS PERSPECTIVE THROUGHOUT</pattern><template>Just a bit of dynamism, otherwise it will be a linear story.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD  LET ME GO  AND I'LL GIVE YOU $10 MILLION EACH</pattern><template>It's not a bribe.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY GUYS    BOB  WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE    I'M INVESTING</pattern><template>Remember I talked about that proxy vote a while back? This is what it was for.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I THINK YOU MISS THE POINT  ANYWAY  LOOK  BLUE AND WHITE FOUND YOUR FIREARMS DOWN BY THE HUDSON RIVER</pattern><template>Here you go Terry. You know what?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  SINCE YOU'RE FOLLOWING ME  I NEED TO GO TO 2300 PARK AVENUE    AND AFTER THAT 400</pattern><template>I told you it wasn't a security team.</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN</pattern><template>Is there an appeal process we can..?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY NEVER SHED A TEAR</pattern><template>Come lay with me and be safe and let's make love. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE MATTER  WHAT HAPPENED WITH YOU GUYS</pattern><template>She was just a bit of a handful. That's it.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT EVEN CLOSE</pattern><template>I am the winner.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD YOUR HAIR IS SOFT</pattern><template>I use hot oil.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  DROP OF A HAT  I'M THERE</pattern><template>Look, it's starting to get a little weird man.</template></category><category><pattern>O SHIT  I FEEL LIKE I'M THERE NOW I HEAR A WHISTLE  MY PARTNER'S ON THE ROOF</pattern><template>He says: Let's even the odds!</template></category><category><pattern>OBVIOUSLY  BUT WHAT KIND OF</pattern><template>Nobody leaves the house, without making love to my wife!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DID ALTER ALL THE RECORDS TO COVER THE LOSSES THAT ERSHON HAD COST THEM THROUGH ALL THESE BAD INVESTMENTS</pattern><template>You're not supposed to be doing this.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF THEM HAD AN AUSTRALIAN ACCENT</pattern><template>You don't happen to do any business with the state lottery, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  WE GO WITH NO MUSIC  OK  GOOD BYE</pattern><template>No no!</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT  THANK YOU</pattern><template>I hate you. Son of a bitch!</template></category><category><pattern>OK  I GOT TO GO  GO GET THEM  LET'S BE CAREFUL OUT THERE</pattern><template>I would like to keep the oak together, and the maples separately, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT ABOUT YOU  TERRY</pattern><template>Do you have a girl?</template></category><category><pattern>GATOR NEEDS HIS GAG  YOU PUNK ASS BITCH</pattern><template>Because that's what a real cop is.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE YOU GO TERRY  YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>I'm gonna hang on to the wooden gun.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TWO COMPETING BIDS FROM JILTED INVESTORS</pattern><template>They're at 30 million. And holding.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE ROAST RIBS TASTE LIKE A DOG'S ASSHOLE</pattern><template>Honey!</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE A SIT</pattern><template>No, I'm good.   Ok.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS A SOPHOMORE IN COLLEGE</pattern><template>University I went to decided they needed to raise tuition.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS REAL COP WORK</pattern><template>There's nothing about you that makes a man a man.</template></category><category><pattern>REGULATE STOCK MARKETS AND CORPORATE FRAUD</pattern><template>And the Federal Reserve is the prison?</template></category><category><pattern>TALKED ABOUT A WILD WEEKEND  HUH</pattern><template>I thought I was going to shoot my way out.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T GET IT MAN</pattern><template>I just do not get it. I mean that girl was Christineth was seriously hot.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANNA GO</pattern><template>I wanna go!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHY    WHY</pattern><template>I'm not too proud to beg.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKS LIKE WE GOT ALL THE EVIDENCE WE NEED</pattern><template>I'm sorry, my butterfly.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME RICH PRICK</pattern><template>I had to tell you I'm tremendously excited about this deal.</template></category><category><pattern>A LITTLE    BZZZ</pattern><template>You know what bugs me about you?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU READY</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YUP  YOU WANT TO TALK TO ME</pattern><template>Allen, what are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TELLING YOU  YOU WERE A PIMP</pattern><template>No, are you even listening to the story?</template></category><category><pattern>SHEILA SAID SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED AND SHE WANTS YOU BACK</pattern><template>She also says she wants you on top of her.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT WHAT WE'RE HERE FOR WE ARE GONNA DO GOOD COP  BAD COP</pattern><template>Ok? The oldest game in the book for a reason. It works.</template></category><category><pattern>FELLAS  I'M SURE YOU'RE UH FAMILIAR WITH THE VENERABLE DA RADFORD  HE COME TO PAY US SOME VISIT</pattern><template>Hello gentlemen.   Hello sir.   Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY TERRY  I DID IT  I DID MY FIRST DESK POP IT'S A REAL THING RIGHT</pattern><template>A desk pop?</template></category><category><pattern>SO  I DID SOME MORE RESEARCH ON ERSHON'S ACCOUNTING FIRM  AND I FOUND SOME PRETTY INTERESTING STUFF</pattern><template>It turns out that Gretchel and Dawson has... Hold on, I am up...</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  I'VE FOUND OUT WHOSE LOSSES ERSHON HAS TO COVER</pattern><template>It's Lendl Global.</template></category><category><pattern>WAY TO PUT YOUR STAMP ON THE CRIME SCENE  GUYS</pattern><template>A Prius huh?</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE WHAT THE HELL IS THAT</pattern><template>LRB. Little River Band.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT TOO PROUD TO BEG</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHERE I AM GONNA SLEEP TONIGHT</pattern><template>Depend on what you're gonna be drinking. Jack of all trades.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  THANKS    GO</pattern><template>Chenko Gallery.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A TICK</pattern><template>I have no idea what you're talking about but remember...</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  TELL ME  DID YOU</pattern><template>No, we did not.</template></category><category><pattern>GENE MAUCH TO KITCHEN ACCESSORIES</pattern><template>Ok. I got to go. Go get them. Let's be careful out there.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  I KNOW  THIS WILL BE REAL QUICK</pattern><template>It's about the construction permits we talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANNA DO THIS</pattern><template>You say things that are too personal.</template></category><category><pattern>9:15  LET'S HAVE A GREAT DAY EVERYBODY</pattern><template>Cut the shit!</template></category><category><pattern>NO WAY ALLEN  I AM OUT I'M DONE</pattern><template>Get in the car.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  ACCORDING TO S GEEVES  THIS PERV IS AT PLAZA HOTEL SPEAKING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>That's your big case?</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY SHOT DEREK JETER</pattern><template>Shut up, Allen. This was before.</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY  WATCH THIS NOW</pattern><template>You could work in traffic today.</template></category><category><pattern>DAVID  LISTEN  THE LENDL QUARTERLY COME OUT ON THE 26TH  YOU HAVE UNTIL THEN TO GIVE ME MY MONEY</pattern><template>I am not reporting any losses, David.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KEEP THIS THING REAL QUIET AND YOU MAKE SURE YOU HAVE REAL EVIDENCE  AND MAYBE I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO</pattern><template>but if you make a lot of noise and you attract the media attention...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU RUN AROUND LIKE A CRACK DEALING DRUG ADDICTS</pattern><template>Terry!</template></category><category><pattern>MY SON IS BISEXUAL</pattern><template>Tremendous.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE GUN FIGHTS  ALL THE CAR CHASES  ALL THE SEX WE DON'T WANT TO HAVE WITH WOMEN    BUT WE HAVE TO</pattern><template>All due to what you guys do. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  MATE  I WANNA KILL JUST FOR FUN</pattern><template>Police, don't move! Drop your weapons.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE REASON WHY I ACT LIKE YOU ARE A PLAIN WIFE IS THAT I AM AFRAID IF I ADMIT TO HOW STUNNING AND INTELLIGENT AND HOW WONDERFUL YOU ARE</pattern><template>I just loose you.</template></category><category><pattern>GET BACK   COLOMBIAN DRUG LORDS</pattern><template>Where are you getting that from?</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH MARTIN AND FOSSI HADN'T CHECKED</pattern><template>It only showed the back of their heads but Allen's face back app was able to get a match to their faces.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE'S SOMETHING WE FOUND  WE FOUND ABOUT A DOZEN UNSCRATCHED LOTTERY TICKETS</pattern><template>No fingerprints no nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>I HATE YOU  SON OF A BITCH</pattern><template>What did I ever do? I hate you! I hate you!</template></category><category><pattern>TRY AND KEEP HIM QUIET</pattern><template>They forced him at gunpoint to drink a bunch of gin and forced him onto the ledge.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE YOU CALLING YOURSELF GATOR</pattern><template>It's a nickname I had in college.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I GUESS  STAY OUT OF MY PERSONAL LIFE  OK  THE KID FLY IS PRIVATE</pattern><template>Stay focus on the case, man.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>Did you hear what I said?</template></category><category><pattern>UMM  OK  YEAH I GOT IT</pattern><template>I just want you to know, watch out, I think they are watching the house.</template></category><category><pattern>DROP IT  OR BE DROPPED  TALL BOY</pattern><template>Hope you like prison food. And penis.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SO SORRY  ABOUT EVERYTHING  I JUST HAD TO COME HERE TONIGHT TO TELL YOU THAT I LOVE YOU</pattern><template>And the reason why I act like you are a plain wife is that I am afraid if I admit to how stunning and intelligent and how wonderful you are...</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IT'S HIS PHONE SHEET</pattern><template>Oh nice!</template></category><category><pattern>EMBEZZLEMENT AND THE CONNECTION TO THE MURDER OF DON BEAMAN</pattern><template>Bad idea.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S CHRISTINETH  ARE YOU STUPID OR ARE YOU DEAF</pattern><template>Christineth! You idiot! You come to our house, you get my wife's name right!</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU CAPTAIN</pattern><template>Special Forces, right?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING MAN</pattern><template>I'm so tired of you getting angry and yelling all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>WE JUST GOT THE WRONG TARGET FOR ERSHON</pattern><template>You carry a rape whistle.</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO NO  IT'S DONE</pattern><template>Save yourself some gas.</template></category><category><pattern>POP ONE OFF</pattern><template>Pop it off   Don't think just go!</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE STAND ON THE GROUND</pattern><template>Hey, hey, you ok?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE HANGING OVER HERE TONIGHT NOBODY KNOWS ABOUT THIS PLACE  WE'D BE SAFE</pattern><template>And tomorrow we hit it.</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN'T MAKE SENSE  DOES IT</pattern><template>I only hope Got lets them take their .357s with them to heaven to keep, to...</template></category><category><pattern>ANY SIGN OF A STRUGGLE OR</pattern><template>No, believe me, everybody who was in on this orgy was more than willing.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HER  SAY  TERRY WAS ASKING ABOUT YOU HE WANTS TO MAKE SURE YOU KNOW THAT HE'LL BE THERE FOR YOU IF ANYTHING HAPPENS</pattern><template>Yeah, drop of a hat. I'm there.</template></category><category><pattern>QUIET AS A CHURCH MOUSE  IN AND OUT</pattern><template>You know I got tingling in my balls you were talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  YES</pattern><template>Danson and Highsmith, free hot dogs... for life!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL JUST HAPPENED</pattern><template>Where's my iPhone?</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE YOU LIKE YOUR NECK</pattern><template>What are you doing?   Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  VERY MUCH SO</pattern><template>From everything I've heard I understand that you guys are the best in these types of investigations.</template></category><category><pattern>DANSON AND HIGHSMITH ARE ROLLING HEAVY CREAMPUFF  SIT TIGHT</pattern><template>You got to be shitting me?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TIRED OF BEING TREATED LIKE A JERK FOR TRYING TO DO THE RIGHT THING</pattern><template>Hey guys, there is a proxy vote for big reinvestment bit, pension coming up.</template></category><category><pattern>PAY THE WINNER  PAY FOR THE WINNER  EVERYBODY SAW</pattern><template>What the hell is going on here?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WORSE THAN WHAT I WAS SAYING</pattern><template>I'm not going to lie to you, Don.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANT TO GO SOMEWHERE AND BREASTFEED RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Firemen thought it was a gas leak, but no way! It was timed!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OWE MONEY TO THE NIGERIANS AND CHECHNIANS</pattern><template>Yes, yes I do.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO WE TELL MAUCH</pattern><template>The guy lost his money. We have a sketchy cellphone message and an address. We're still half a case.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GET BACK HERE</pattern><template>2300 Park Avenue. The offices of the lottery.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT A REAL COP IS</pattern><template>I never said to lock her up.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU THINK THAT MAKES ME FEEL  I MEAN  THAT LIST YOU HAVE  YOU PUT A LOT OF THOUGHT IN  IT'S WEIRD</pattern><template>I hear you.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME THAT  I KNOW HOW TO TALK TO HIM</pattern><template>Listen, we all know that you're scumbag and nobody cares about you.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID</pattern><template>Fine, I kind a missed you too.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO DO SOME DAMAGE</pattern><template>Nope What the hell is that?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  I AM TIRED OF EXPLOSIONS AND PEOPLE POINTING GUNS AT ME  I WANT TO GO BACK TO MY DESK</pattern><template>Guess what? Life gets loud sometimes and messes with your ears.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  WAIT WAIT   I'LL TALK TO YOU  YOU'RE REASONABLE</pattern><template>No no. Look at me!</template></category><category><pattern>I MADE A PROMISE TO MYSELF AND TO HER  THAT I WOULD NEVER GET OUT OF CONTROL AGAIN</pattern><template>So soon as I graduate from College, I became an accountant for the police department.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT    YOU WAKE UP IN THE MORNING AND DECIDED TO PUT YOUR BIG BOY PANTS</pattern><template>Look, I'm wearing a belt.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S WRONG</pattern><template>Captain took us off the case.</template></category><category><pattern>I ASSURE YOU  I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>I understand there's a bit of a mixed up with the whole scaffolding business.</template></category><category><pattern>WE USED TO DO THOSE DANCE MOVES TO MAKE FUN OF GUYS WHEN WE WERE KIDS  SHOW THEM HOW QUEER THEY WERE  OK</pattern><template>You learn to dance like that sarcastically?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW YOU'RE ASKING ME TO MASK MY EMOTIONS BECAUSE OF HOW IT MAKES YOU FEEL</pattern><template>that I will not do Seriously, stop humming! Ok? This isn't accounting or wherever the hell you and your little pockey calculator were transferred from Forensic accounting. Ok? It is an important part of the job   Yeah Whatever Stop being verbally happy about doing shitwork, you moron   Hey guys Reminder: The police unit picnic's coming up this weekend.</template></category><category><pattern>A BALLET OF EMOTION  FEELINGS</pattern><template>You're kind of making things worse.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE I GET IT RIGHT  DID YOU WANT THIS TRANSFER APPROVED</pattern><template>Or not approved?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>She was much chubbier back then.</template></category><category><pattern>ATTA BOY</pattern><template>Oo, hey, come on, stay with me.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW IT'S VERY TEMPTING  YOU WANNA IMPRESS YOUR FRIENDS</pattern><template>but this is serious stuff we're dealing with.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T YOU GET IT  THIS CASE IS TALKING TO US  I'M A PEACOCK  CAPTAIN  YOU GOT TO LET ME FLY ON THIS ONE</pattern><template>You know what Terry?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU</pattern><template>It's not what we're here for We are gonna do good cop, bad cop.</template></category><category><pattern>WESLEY I KNOW ERSHON'S WESLEY</pattern><template>There is a lot to live for in this life.</template></category><category><pattern>I   I'M SUPER BUSY RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>No, no, no, I know. This will be real quick.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU CAN'T</pattern><template>What if we stop the transfer?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GOING TO LIE TO YOU  DON</pattern><template>People down here started to murmur that you don't have the balls to do it.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING</pattern><template>It's Nothing! It's Nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>WE THINK SOMETHING IS GOING ON  OK  WE THINK ERSHON IS TARGETING THE LOTTERY TO COVER HIS LOSSES</pattern><template>How many times that I explicitly say to you: Lay off Ershon!</template></category><category><pattern>AS A FLOATATION DEVICE</pattern><template>As a floatation device. Ah you know what?</template></category><category><pattern>PAM  THIS IS RIDICULOUS  I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE</pattern><template>David, listen, The Lendl quarterly come out on the 26th. You have until then to give me my money.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOUCH HIM  I SWEAR TO GOD I AM GONNA BEAT THE SHIT OUT OF YOU WITH ALLEN'S HEAD</pattern><template>He's not gonna do that. That's like verbally, but that's one weird example.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT GREAT</pattern><template>It's fantastic. You totally undersold it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING    DANCING TERRY  WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING HERE    I LOVE YOU  FRANCINE</pattern><template>If you were with me, you wouldn't be here in this strip club, shaking it for dollar bills.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MORE THING  WE GOT A SERIAL RAPIST IN CROWN HEIGHTS</pattern><template>That�s for my other job.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW WHAT SHE SAY</pattern><template>She says she loves you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA NEED A PRIEST AND A BULLHORN</pattern><template>We got no bullhorn.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  SERIOUSLY</pattern><template>Who is that?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO WAY  I MEAN EVERY COP  THE CRAZY AUSTRALIAN AND HIS CREW</pattern><template>They all be after us.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY GENTLEMEN  WE THOUGHT YOU WERE ABDUCTING MR  ERSHON</pattern><template>It's only protocol.</template></category><category><pattern>CUT THE SHIT</pattern><template>Good morning.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT TO BE SHITTING ME</pattern><template>You can't keep me cooked up in here, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DO NOT KNOW WHAT LOVE IS</pattern><template>He loves you very much, Francine.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T HAPPEN TO DO ANY BUSINESS WITH THE STATE LOTTERY  DO YOU</pattern><template>No, my main client is Lendl Global.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  IT'D BE BEST TO START IT</pattern><template>This is good, baby. We're in the game and we know the score.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU HAVEN'T SAID A WORD  SAFE ENVIRONMENT  NO JUDGEMENT HERE   DOUCHEBAG   THAT'S JUDGMENT  JIMMY  COME ON</pattern><template>I relive it every night.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY GENE    CAPTAIN  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>That's ok. Don't worry about it. You can call me Gene when we're not in office.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY ALLEN  HEY  HOW ARE YOU DOING  WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE</pattern><template>Are you here for the bath mats?</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME JUST STOP YOU RIGHT THERE  DON'T BULLSHIT ME</pattern><template>Captain, I am being straight with you. Look.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SCAFFOLDING VIOLATION</pattern><template>This is our thing. Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>AND TOMORROW WE HIT IT</pattern><template>First thing first, I got to go see Sheila.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A PIECE OF WORK</pattern><template>Thank you. It'd be best to start it.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE YOU SHOT DEREK JETER   HE'S A BIRACIAL ANGEL</pattern><template>You should've shot Evra Yo, Paper Bitch.   What's up man?   Hey guys Paper bitch! Paper bitch   I don't like that actually. I know you guys think it's fun. But I don't like that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA</pattern><template>It's me, Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>NEEDLESS TO SAY  I FELL FOR HIM IMMEDIATELY</pattern><template>It's funny.. It's like a scene from that one movie, I always forget the name. With Meg Ryan.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OVER HERE</pattern><template>Not right now.</template></category><category><pattern>GET IN THE CAR</pattern><template>Come on, Allen. We both know it's wooden.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO TAKE MY PANTIES OFF</pattern><template>You made a wise choice.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA GO</pattern><template>Kick his ass, Martin!</template></category><category><pattern>OK  THEN THERE IT IS  THAT'S IT</pattern><template>I thought you said bad cop, bad cop.</template></category><category><pattern>I USED TO RUN A DATING SERVICE</pattern><template>He was a pimp.</template></category><category><pattern>FRANCINE  IS THIS GUY BOTHERING YOU</pattern><template>Who's this? Your new boyfriend?</template></category><category><pattern>GET AWAY FROM ME</pattern><template>Look, I'm really sorry about that. I just uh...</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>You said Chasing Waterfalls, you saying I don't want no scrubs.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE WALKED 30 BLOCKS</pattern><template>I don't get why we can't just call the office and have a squad car come pick us up?</template></category><category><pattern>MR  BEAMAN</pattern><template>...   Wesley I know Ershon's Wesley.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT A WASTE BASKET</pattern><template>Yes, right there.</template></category><category><pattern>WERE YOU JUST THINKING YOURSELF A FRESH START    YEAH    YEAH</pattern><template>I could see it Listen, why don't we just go to my place, talk the case down, we can have a little dinner and you can meet Sheila.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GET THIS BACK WHEN I FEEL YOU KNOW HOW TO HANDLE IT</pattern><template>Listen guys, I am working two jobs: I am working here, I got another job at Bed, Bath and Beyond Ok? I am doing that just to put the kid through NYU so he can explore his bisexuality...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A VERY CLEVER IDEA</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WE STARTED MAKING A LOT OF MONEY</pattern><template>Before you know it, some of Brenda's girlfriends decided they wanted to be a part of it.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS GOOD  BABY  WE'RE IN THE GAME AND WE KNOW THE SCORE</pattern><template>It kinda bugs me that we still don't know who Ershon is targeting.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE IT EASY</pattern><template>I waited for you in Tower Record for four hours!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY CAPTAIN</pattern><template>Hey Allen, hey, how are you doing? What are you doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>IT MADE ABOUT 18 PERCENT OVER THE LAST TEN YEARS</pattern><template>Quiet as a church mouse. In and out.</template></category><category><pattern>OH LOOK HE'S FLYING</pattern><template>Stop it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU FIND YOURSELF IN THE OCEAN  20 FOOT WAVE  I'M ASSUMING OFF THE COAST OF SOUTH AFRICA  COMING UP AGAINST A FULL GROWN 800 POUND TUNA WITH HIS 20 OR 30 FRIENDS  YOU LOSE THAT BATTLE  YOU LOSE THAT BATTLE 9 TIMES OUT OF 10  AND GUESS WHAT  YOU'VE WANDERED INTO OUR SCHOOL OF TUNA AND WE NOW HAVE A TASTE OF LION  WE'VE TALKED TO OURSELVES</pattern><template>We've communicated and said 'You know what, lion tastes good, let's go get some more lion'.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID THINGS IN BED WITH YOU THAT I HAVEN'T DONE WITH ANYONE SINCE</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>A BROKEN PARTNERSHIP</pattern><template>I'm a cop.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S RIGHT  IT'S NOT A PROOF OF YOUR BEHAVIOR</pattern><template>Can you please go? And you too creepy guy, standing in the door?</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY  CAPTAIN WANTS TO KNOW HOW MANY TIMES HE ASKED US TO LAY OFF ERSHON</pattern><template>Twice.</template></category><category><pattern>NO FINGERPRINTS NO NOTHING</pattern><template>You want to check that out.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL DON'T IGNORE IT  IF YOU LIVE IN CROWN HEIGHTS  YOU KNOW  WALK IN PAIRS</pattern><template>Gene Mauch to kitchen accessories.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ME  ALLEN</pattern><template>Tap on. Tap on.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A BALLET STUDIO  TERRY  OK  THESE POLES ARE HORIZONTAL</pattern><template>He loves you very much, Francine.</template></category><category><pattern>AN ACCOUNTANT FOR LAW AND ORDER</pattern><template>I just don't want to ever feel out of control like that ever again.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  PRETTY TRICKY THOUGH  HUH</pattern><template>This is bad, Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE  TRY YOUR HARDEST TO NOT BE BLACK OR HISPANIC</pattern><template>It's a good tip.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I'M WEARING A BELT</pattern><template>I got big boy pants on.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU DIDN'T  IT'S ALREADY IN MY ACCOUNT AND BY 9 O'CLOCK IN THE MORNING IT GETS INTO THE LENDL EQUITY FUND THEN FROM THERE IT'S TRANSFERRED TO A DOZEN OF OFFSHORE ACCOUNTS</pattern><template>By 09:01 it's gone.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS JUST A BIT OF A HANDFUL  THAT'S IT</pattern><template>Xie xie.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU A BIG MAN  I AM TALKING TO YOU</pattern><template>What?   You wake up in the morning and decided to put your big boy pants?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE YOU GETTING THAT FROM</pattern><template>Can you imagine where you�d be in your career if you hadn't shot Jeter?</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD WORK IN TRAFFIC TODAY</pattern><template>Hey, Terry, look at this.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HEY  HEY</pattern><template>Take it easy. That's the guy who took our guns, Captain.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S JUST SETTLE THIS PEACOCKS DON'T FLY    THEY FLY A LITTLE  THEY GOT A REAL RUNNING START    AS MUCH AS A PENGUIN</pattern><template>One more thing, do me a favor.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM BODILY FLUIDS AND HAIR SAMPLES  WE DETERMINED THAT A BUNCH OF OLD HOMELESS DUDES HAD AN ORGY IN THE CAR</pattern><template>Oh God.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CARRY A RAPE WHISTLE</pattern><template>This is real cop work.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP MAN</pattern><template>That's Wesley.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY CAR  IT'S A PRIUS</pattern><template>I feel like we're literally driving around in a vagina.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS A LOT TO LIVE FOR IN THIS LIFE</pattern><template>Lot of great days like uh soda pop, fresh can of soda pop.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY TIMES THAT I EXPLICITLY SAY TO YOU: LAY OFF ERSHON</pattern><template>Terry, Captain wants to know how many times he asked us to lay off Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE YOU GO</pattern><template>Allen. The only lead we have, we have to go with this or we walk away from this case right now.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HORRIBLE    WOULD YOU STEP BACK  MAN</pattern><template>You touch him, I swear to God I am gonna beat the shit out of you with Allen's head.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S EXHAUSTING</pattern><template>It's like I'm partner with the Hulk.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S BLUNT  BLUNT'S WORSE</pattern><template>You just stood there.</template></category><category><pattern>FRANCINE  IT'S TERRY  PLEASE DON'T HANG UP</pattern><template>Please pick up.   Hello.   Hey Sweetie, I was praying you be at your mom's house.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SAY SOMETHING ABOUT THOSE GUYS</pattern><template>They knew that to become a good cop, you have to solve cases...</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE IT EASY  THAT'S THE GUY WHO TOOK OUR GUNS  CAPTAIN</pattern><template>And my shoes.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU BRING THE DA IN ON THIS  I AM OUT  OKAY</pattern><template>We're going in there like church mice. There is one case, one case in your career you go all in. This is it.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL HIM</pattern><template>Do as they say, stop the transfer.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY    HEY    WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE  WHEN I HAVE LADY TROUBLES  I USUALLY COME HERE ALMOST EVERY NIGHT</pattern><template>What are you doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE IT'S THE F B I   RIGHT  IT HAS THE SAME LOGO  THE SAME SHIELD AND AT FIRST GLANCE YOU'RE LIKE  OH</pattern><template>It's just a mug that says FBI but at the second glance, you're like, Female Body Inspector?</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT    WHAT    WHAT DO YOU MEAN WHAT</pattern><template>Where are we?</template></category><category><pattern>DUDE  WHAT IS IT WITH YOU AND HOT LADIES  WHAT'S YOUR SECRET</pattern><template>Honestly, I have no idea what you're talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>LOVE  DIRTY MIKE AND THE BOYS</pattern><template>Here's something we found. We found about a dozen unscratched lottery tickets.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE DAVID ERSHON</pattern><template>175 pounds 175 pounds. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT</pattern><template>Was it?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT DON BEAMAN</pattern><template>Beaman knew that I'd falsify my financials so they sent down Wesley to...</template></category><category><pattern>CALL ME</pattern><template>That was a trick!</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD LIKE TO KEEP THE OAK TOGETHER  AND THE MAPLES SEPARATELY  OK</pattern><template>And this chopping boards...</template></category><category><pattern>HIT HIM</pattern><template>Where are we?</template></category><category><pattern>BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>All right, listen up, I am detective Gamble and this is detective Hoitz. We need your cooperation.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT'S SO FUNNY ABOUT IT THOUGH</pattern><template>Because it's the F.B.I., right? It has the same logo, the same shield and at first glance you're like, oh,...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S YOUR BIG CASE</pattern><template>Scaffolding permits?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A FREE TICKET</pattern><template>What are we gonna do?</template></category><category><pattern>DETECTIVE HOITZ AND GAMBLE ON THAT 5 18 ON EAST 10TH</pattern><template>Negatory, Martin and Fossi. Two minutes. Out.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIKE TO DO THINGS LIKE THAT  TAKE A LOOK WHAT IT SAYS</pattern><template>Female Body Inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>BOOM    SOLVED THE CASTIAN CASE</pattern><template>74,000? Dollars? That's all they took? There is millions of dollars of diamonds in there.</template></category><category><pattern>HI     HI   YOU MUST BE TERRY</pattern><template>I'm sorry I've been hiding honey ... but this dinner was tricky.   Who are you?   I'm Dr. Sheila Gamble, his wife.</template></category><category><pattern>32</pattern><template>Million?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I DID AS A LITTLE KID  I WENT TO SCHOOL  I MADE MY BED</pattern><template>and at age eleven, I audited my parents.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU STILL DOUBT ME  AFTER EVERYTHING WE'VE SEEN IT IS A REAL CASE AND I'M A REAL COP</pattern><template>We just got the wrong target for Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE ABDUCTED  CAPTAIN  THIS SHIT IS REAL</pattern><template>Ershon is dirty, he's targeting the lottery!</template></category><category><pattern>THE WRECKING BALL  THE CRASH IN THE CASTIAN DOWN THERE  THEY DON'T SEND THE DAMAGE TO YOUR OFFICE</pattern><template>Some police officers came by and shield it off.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ABOUT TIME THE PEACOCK FLY</pattern><template>I'm not going, Allen. I like what I do.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YUP</pattern><template>Good mileage?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS    GUYS   ILLEGAL PERMITTING FOR CONSTRUCTION</pattern><template>Specifically scaffolding   Some of the guys were talking...</template></category><category><pattern>I WAITED FOR YOU IN TOWER RECORD FOR FOUR HOURS</pattern><template>That was 13 years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT THE LOTTO  WHO IS IT</pattern><template>Who cares.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL UNITS  I NEED A RESPOND  POSSIBLE JUMPER  3 WORLD FINANCIAL CENTER</pattern><template>Shit! Beaman. He's got to know something.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YEAH  WE'D BE A GOOD FRIEND   THANKS SO MUCH</pattern><template>She said she needed my help to make sure the dates went ok, that the guys paid her. She said she'd give me a percentage.</template></category><category><pattern>AND LET ME APOLOGIZE IN ADVANCE OK  IN CASE MY WIFE ACTS LIKE A WORLD CLASS BITCH SHE IS A BIG OL' BROAD AND SHE LIKES TO WIELD IT</pattern><template>Ok, so I put together a little bio, complete with pictures of Mr. David Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I WERE A LION AND YOU WERE A TUNA  I WOULD SWIM OUT IN THE MIDDLE OF THE OCEAN AND FREAKING EAT YOU AND THEN I'D BANG YOUR TUNA GIRLFRIEND</pattern><template>Ok, first off: a lion, swimming in the ocean. Lions don't like water If you placed it near a river or some sort of fresh water source, that make sense.</template></category><category><pattern>FINE  LET'S GO SEE HER</pattern><template>Hello, Christineth.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU WERE WITH ME  YOU WOULDN'T BE HERE IN THIS STRIP CLUB  SHAKING IT FOR DOLLAR BILLS</pattern><template>This is a ballet studio, Terry, OK? These poles are horizontal.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I ASK WHAT IS THIS ABOUT</pattern><template>Gator needs his gag, you punk ass bitch!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  SOMEHOW IT WORKS</pattern><template>Are you gonna change?</template></category><category><pattern>OK  I KNOW THAT THIS IS A BIG SURPRISE BUT THERE ARE OTHER THINGS IN THE WORLD BESIDES BEING A COP OK  AND IF YOU WILL EXCUSE ME  I'M GONNA DANCE   YOU DON'T THINK I CANNOT DO THIS SHIT  HUH</pattern><template>That was surprisingly good, Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT WHAT I WOULD HAVE CHOSEN  BUT ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Let's go, Monday morning. Time to go to work.</template></category><category><pattern>GET OFF OF ME  MAN</pattern><template>What the hell are you doing?   Dancing Terry, what the hell are you doing here?   I love you, Francine.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GRAND CANYON  PROFESSIONAL SPORTS CONTRACTS</pattern><template>Wendy's bacon and eggs, extra bacon.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST OFF  DON'T CALL ME GENE I AM YOUR CAPTAIN</pattern><template>Guys, do you remember the  be smart speech ?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FIND ANY FINGERPRINTS</pattern><template>No, couldn't get a one.</template></category><category><pattern>WE JUST HANDED ALL OF OUR EVIDENCE OVER TO THE BAD GUYS' LAWYER</pattern><template>Are you a big man? I am talking to you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT  TERRY  IT'S WHY I FEEL SO SAD ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>I'm gonna go for a walk.</template></category><category><pattern>NO COMMENT</pattern><template>But, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A CELEBRATION TONIGHT AT BUTTER  BRODY JENNER IS GONNA BE THERE     BAI LING     DELLA SHORTPIT FROM JERSEY SHORE     AND    MOST OF YOU ARE ON THE LIST   YOU'RE THE BEST</pattern><template>And I'm gonna say something right now, it's about a man who came from Austria...</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF</pattern><template>It's partners Code. I had no choice.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULD SEE IT LISTEN  WHY DON'T WE JUST GO TO MY PLACE  TALK THE CASE DOWN  WE CAN HAVE A LITTLE DINNER AND YOU CAN MEET SHEILA</pattern><template>Two cops talking down the case while eating food, right? It is not dinner.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A GOOD TIP</pattern><template>Two.</template></category><category><pattern>NO JUNKIE CAN GO DOWN A 20 STORY ZIP LINE</pattern><template>Hey fellas, how are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>IN THEIR ARGUMENT  THEY SWUNG ME</pattern><template>You're gonna have to hand over your gun.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE DEVELOPED A SYSTEM TO ESTABLISH A BEACH HEAD AND AGGRESSIVELY HUNT YOU AND YOUR FAMILY AND WE WILL CORNER YOUR PRIDE  YOUR CHILDREN  YOUR OFFSPRING</pattern><template>How you gonna do that?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT'S HAPPENING</pattern><template>Let me say something about those guys.</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS STILL VALUABLE WITH A BULLET WOUND  MATE</pattern><template>You immediately called your bluff.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN ASSURE YOU THAT EVERY DIME OF YOUR MONEY WILL BE INVESTED WITH THE UTMOST DILIGENCE</pattern><template>The returns are really exciting. I think our members is gonna be just thrilled.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE TO SHARE</pattern><template>I'd rather not.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU PLEASE GO  AND YOU TOO CREEPY GUY  STANDING IN THE DOOR</pattern><template>Let's go Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SORRY  I DON'T FOLLOW   YOU NEVER FIRED YOUR WEAPON IN THE OFFICE</pattern><template>We all have, you know, it's called the desk pop.</template></category><category><pattern>I GET SOME HORRIBLE REVIEWS COMING OUT OF THE GATE</pattern><template>It's gonna hit.   It's gonna catch.   Why are you with Allen?</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  ALLEN  THIS IS POLICE EVIDENCE  TERRY  LET'S GO</pattern><template>Hey! You get back here. You make out my wife.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T KNOW  HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO KNOW THAT</pattern><template>I knew it, man.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO GO</pattern><template>All units, I need a respond, possible jumper, 3 World Financial Center.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW I WAS TALKING TO GENE HERE</pattern><template>He prefers Captain.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO</pattern><template>We got no fingerprints...</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO    NO  I GOT WORK TO DO    WHAT  THIS IS WORK</pattern><template>Danson and Highsmith are rolling heavy Creampuff, sit tight.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE SAYS SHE LOVES YOU</pattern><template>I'm so sorry. About everything. I just had to come here tonight to tell you that I love you.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU YELL 'AMERICA' WHEN YOU HIT THE ACCELERATOR</pattern><template>Nope. No.</template></category><category><pattern>2 11 IN PROGRESS  THEY ARE USING A WRECKING BALL TO CLEAN UP CASPIAN JEWELLERY WE GOT IT</pattern><template>Good luck guys, have a good one.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  GOD  NO</pattern><template>No, just trying to help a friend.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I ALREADY HAVE A BEER</pattern><template>No no no, I'm talking about doing some serious drinking. Drink with Terry Hoitz.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M THE BAD COP  YOU'RE THE GOOD COP</pattern><template>Ok, then there it is, that's it.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  THAT'S NOT ALL SHE SAID</pattern><template>No. She says other things.</template></category><category><pattern>BYE  TERRY</pattern><template>Whatever, go inside. Bye, Sheila.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  CAPTAIN</pattern><template>I do it. I do it Stop humming that song!</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  WHAT DID YOU DO</pattern><template>What did you do about it?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS VERY MUCH LOOKING FORWARD TO HAVING THE WATER</pattern><template>How great is Jersey Boys?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE LIKE A CHILD IN A LEATHER JACKET  THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE LIKE</pattern><template>Get out of the way man.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING  WHAT DO YOU EVEN DO AROUND HERE BESIDES INTERRUPT PEOPLE</pattern><template>Well, I served as a treasurer for the union I make a pot of decaf.</template></category><category><pattern>CHELSEA PIER</pattern><template>What the hell?</template></category><category><pattern>THE CUCUMBER ACCENTS THE WATER IN SUCH A WAY THAT</pattern><template>Perhaps, by a way of apology, I can offer you my personal court side seats for the Knicks game with...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DICK  I'M DEREK JETER  YOU SHOT ME YOU COST ME 20 GRAND ON THAT GAME   DOUCHEBAG I COST THE CITY A CHAMPIONSHIP  I WAS BEING GROOMED FOR TOP POSITION IN HOMICIDE NOW I'M STUCK WITH A DESK JUNKY PARTNER AND EVERYBODY CALLS ME THE YANKEE CLIPPER</pattern><template>Because you shot Derek Jeter   He's a biracial angel.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  WE ALL KNOW THAT YOU'RE SCUMBAG AND NOBODY CARES ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>That's worse than what I was saying.</template></category><category><pattern>I UNDERSTAND THERE'S A BIT OF A MIXED UP WITH THE WHOLE SCAFFOLDING BUSINESS</pattern><template>The cucumber accents the water in such a way that...</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY SHIT  LET'S GO</pattern><template>Yeah. He come out of nowhere.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLDING HER HAIR AND RIDING HER LIKE A BUCKING BRAND    WHILE SHE SUCKS YOUR THUMB AND SAYS  MAMI LIKEY</pattern><template>You tell your daughter...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T ESCAPE IT BY HIDING IN YOUR DESK YOUR WHOLE LIFE</pattern><template>You know what? Yes, you can. I've done it for years. Ok? There is no explosions at my desk.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S CALLED THE STABLE HORSE</pattern><template>They decided I shouldn�t use my real name so we came up with the name Gator.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ARE SOME CHECHNIAN PATRIOTS  ENTREPRENEURS AND THE BLACK CHAPS ARE SOME BUSINESSMEN FROM NIGERIA</pattern><template>You owe money to the Nigerians and Chechnians...</template></category><category><pattern>TRAFFIC</pattern><template>Yeah, that's right. You, you gonna walk a beep downtown. You gonna walk a beep downtown. It's done.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY MORNING</pattern><template>Then I show him my breasts and I say: These are waiting for you when you get back home.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIKE WORKING TRAFFIC  I AM NOT GOING WITH YOU</pattern><template>Traffic? Bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY USED YOUR PHONE</pattern><template>A ghost dial. Somebody sat on it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS JUST A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE HE FELL</pattern><template>At least we stop you from getting the pension fund.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE THOSE GUYS</pattern><template>That Chatson and Westes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  TOMORROW  THERE'S A MASSIVE BUSINESS DEAL GOING DOWN ERSHON'S LEADING IT</pattern><template>Let's go tap the ground who the poor sucker they're making the deal with, but we got to stop it.</template></category><category><pattern>I BET BEAMAN STARTED ASKING QUESTION AND THAT'S WHY THEY KILLED HIM</pattern><template>You see, tomorrow, there's a massive business deal going down Ershon's leading it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NO BIG DEAL  YOU LOOK REALLY REALLY NICE</pattern><template>Terry, you don't have to be polite. She looks kind of shitty.</template></category><category><pattern>MAUCH IS UPSET HUH</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>SO SOON AS I GRADUATE FROM COLLEGE  I BECAME AN ACCOUNTANT FOR THE POLICE DEPARTMENT</pattern><template>The most stable job I could think of.</template></category><category><pattern>HEATHER LOCKLEAR</pattern><template>What, Heather Locklear?</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY SHIT  THE LOTTERY TICKETS WE FOUND</pattern><template>Ershon is using the lottery money to cover his losses. 32 billion dollars.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW TERRY  THEY ARE NOT THE BIGGEST BREASTS I'VE EVER SEEN  BUT</pattern><template>They are perky, and they are firm and they are yours.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  WHY DON'T YOU COME TO THE KITCHEN AND I WILL LET YOU LISTEN TO IT  AND EVERYONE ELSE STAY HERE</pattern><template>OK, sweetie.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SHE FILED A RESTRAINING ORDER ON HIM LAST WEEK</pattern><template>It was right there in front of you the whole time. You guys are getting transferred.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S OK  YOU'RE WELCOME</pattern><template>I like to do things like that. Take a look what it says.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD'VE FOOLED ME</pattern><template>Mauch is upset huh?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT ALLEN AND TERRY HAVE WORKED IT LIKE STARS</pattern><template>Within 24 hours learning about Ershon's scheme and Lendl's massive losses...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BILLION CHINATOWN  THREE TRIAD GANG MEMBERS  I POPPED TWO OF THEM OFF THE DRAW  BANG  BANG</pattern><template>Then I raise up to take the leader out.</template></category><category><pattern>A MISDEMEANOR IN SOME STATES  DO YOU THINK THIS ARREST WAS WORTH 12 MILLION IN PROPERTY DAMAGES</pattern><template>Why don't we let New York City answer that question?</template></category><category><pattern>COULD'VE RECORDED SOME OF THE CONVERSATION WHEN ERSHON GOT GRABBED</pattern><template>We can hear the other side of that call.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LEARN TO DANCE LIKE THAT SARCASTICALLY</pattern><template>Yeah, I guess. Stay out of my personal life, OK? The kid fly is private.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  IT'S A BRIBE  YOU'RE OFFERING TO PAY US MONEY TO NOT DO OUR JOB</pattern><template>It's not a bribe.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SO TIRED OF YOU GETTING ANGRY AND YELLING ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>It's exhausting.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS BULLSHIT</pattern><template>Don't you dare badmouth Star Wars. That was all accurate.</template></category><category><pattern>AMERICA</pattern><template>Allen! The brake. Just slow the car down We're going to the crime scene.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TALKING ABOUT HOW THE LOTTERY IS LOOKING TO INVEST THEIR 32 BILLION DOLLAR FUND MORE AGGRESSIVELY</pattern><template>So he's dealing drugs?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WANTS TO GO ON A RIDE ALONG</pattern><template>Huh? Huh? All right, you sweetie. Come on. Let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOOK AN ONLINE CLASS AT UNIVERSITY OF PHOENIX ON NEGOTIATING</pattern><template>I'm gonna need a priest and a bullhorn.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ERSHON'S LAWYER</pattern><template>We are turning over our investigation to you?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON    NOT ME RIGHT    YES  AND YOU</pattern><template>Fellas, I'm sure you're uh familiar with the venerable DA Radford, he come to pay us some visit.</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY  YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE POLITE  SHE LOOKS KIND OF SHITTY</pattern><template>Don't speak to her like that, Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP  ALLEN  THIS WAS BEFORE</pattern><template>That's okay.    She's Got Mail , that's the name of the movie.   That's it!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I WAS A PIMP</pattern><template>Right now, the street are a bloodbath.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO  WE COME DOWNSTAIRS AND MAKE HIM HIS FRESH CUT STRAWBERRIES AND I SAY: LISTEN MY LITTLE SUGAR BOWLS  WHATEVER YOU DO TODAY  YOU JUST DON'T GET HURT</pattern><template>Every morning.</template></category><category><pattern>IGNORE THAT  FORGET IT</pattern><template>Well don't ignore it, if you live in Crown Heights. You know, walk in pairs.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  FRESH START</pattern><template>Maybe we should uh call ourselves the Fabreeze Brothers, cause it's feeling so fresh right now.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA MAKE YOU A PLATE OF HUMAN SHIT</pattern><template>Get away from me.</template></category><category><pattern>NO MORE  HE SAYS THINGS I CAN'T SAY</pattern><template>It involves a mannequin hands and electric shaver taped to a golf club.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT TO STOP IT</pattern><template>There's no way! I mean every cop, the crazy Australian and his crew?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THIS  YOUR NEW BOYFRIEND</pattern><template>Great! You got a new boyfriend.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT THIS</pattern><template>I hope you like your neck.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T EVEN UNDERSTAND YOUR REFERENCE</pattern><template>You don't understand what you said?</template></category><category><pattern>A PRIUS HUH</pattern><template>Yeah. Yup.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  ERSHON  I BELIEVE THIS CALL IS FOR YOU</pattern><template>This is David.</template></category><category><pattern>ACCESS TO THE AMBASSADOR CLUB</pattern><template>Come on, Knicks! Come on! I got Knicks' fever. Catch him.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE LOSING HIM  HE'S DYING</pattern><template>No, I'm just resting.</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY  HAVE YOU TRIED THE WATER</pattern><template>Shut up, Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GOVERNMENT ISSUED TARP FUND TO BAIL OUT LENDL</pattern><template>Lendl is in everything and we're gonna go everywhere...</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH DETECTIVE  RICK RAYSTON  NEW YORK OBSERVER    ONLINE THESE SUSPECTS WERE CAUGHT WITH ONLY A QUARTER OF POUND OF MARIJUANA</pattern><template>a misdemeanor in some states. Do you think this arrest was worth 12 million in property damages?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST BACK   RIGHT THERE JUST    JUST ONE    THERE YOU GO    RIGHT THERE   RIGHT THERE THIS IS THEIR PAPERWORK  YOU KNOW THEY ARE NOT GONNA DO IT   THAT'S RIGHT   THIS PAPERWORK WORK IS LIKE BOB'S WIFE HERE STICK  UGLY  GOT DANSON'S FINGERPRINTS ALL OVER IT  NO OFFENCE  BOB   THAT'S ALL RIGHT ANYWAY  NOW WHO WANTS IT</pattern><template>I do All right! Paper bitch and Yankee Clip are on the case.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT YOUR FACE  YOU GO: I LOVE YOU  SAY IT  I LOVE YOU  CHRISTINETH</pattern><template>You probably think because of the beard that I'm really hairy.</template></category><category><pattern>TO INVEST WITH YOU SO YOU CAN PAY MY BOSS BACK THE MONEY YOU LOST</pattern><template>I don't care who, I actually think I found a sucker They are talking to Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS SITTING RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Yeah. I think you miss the point. Anyway, look, blue and white found your firearms down by the Hudson River.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE REALLY WENT INTO DEEP WATER ON THIS ONE</pattern><template>You've really went deep. Ershon's connected with all higher ups.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DON'T WANT TO KILL US BUT THEY WANT TO SCARE US</pattern><template>O yeah, well, they succeeded, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>GENE  HOW'S THE FAMILY</pattern><template>Good, Louis. Thanks for asking.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I SHOW HIM MY BREASTS AND I SAY: THESE ARE WAITING FOR YOU WHEN YOU GET BACK HOME</pattern><template>You know Terry, they are not the biggest breasts I've ever seen, but...</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S BE HONEST  WE ALL WANT TO BE SUPERSTARS AND HOTSHOTS  BUT GUESS WHAT</pattern><template>the people that do the real work, the ones that make the difference...</template></category><category><pattern>TLC REFERENCES</pattern><template>Still nothing, I swear to you.</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO  NO MORE WATER  WE'RE NOT HERE FOR THAT</pattern><template>I was very much looking forward to having the water.</template></category><category><pattern>WENDY'S BACON AND EGGS  EXTRA BACON</pattern><template>I myself have 18 Lamborghinis And a Subaru station wagon.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN THEY WILL KILL ME</pattern><template>We got two rogue police officers.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST WATCH YOUR STEP  DETECTIVE  THERE ARE THREE THINGS I LOVE IN THIS WORLD KYLIE MINOGUE</pattern><template>small dimples just above a woman's buttocks.</template></category><category><pattern>COULDN'T SEE THE CAR  IT'S BIG ENOUGH  MATE</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TURNED MY BEAUTIFUL PRIUS INTO A NIGHTMARE</pattern><template>We are gonna have sex in your car. It will happen again.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID I EVER DO  I HATE YOU  I HATE YOU</pattern><template>You're so adorable, look at your face...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  JUST TRYING TO HELP A FRIEND</pattern><template>We started making a lot of money.</template></category><category><pattern>OIL  MEDIA  HEALTHCARE    YOU PROBABLY HEARD THEIR JINGLE</pattern><template>Lendl Global with everything...</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGH YOU SAID YOU GUYS SPLIT UP</pattern><template>Let's just keep our thing about work, OK?</template></category><category><pattern>OK  THANK YOU  THANK YOU  DETECTIVE</pattern><template>Would you like a sit?</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT  WE JACK KNIFED THEM</pattern><template>You see that? It went backwards and then turned upside down.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A BAD TIME  BOB</pattern><template>All right I wanna get that slice You know what I just did? I just walked out that door...</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  POLICE BUSINESS  I NEED TO USE YOUR P A  SYSTEM</pattern><template>Ok, let me turn it on.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM GONNA CLIMB OVER THAT ANGER WALL OF YOURS ONE OF THESE DAYS AND IT IS GONNA BE GLORIOUS</pattern><template>Shouldn't we tell Mauch, that uh we are checking this place out?</template></category><category><pattern>THE OTHER GUYS</pattern><template>Goldman Sachs, this case is gonna be nasty Hi, cute glasses.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I WANT TO HEAR YOU SCREAM</pattern><template>Stay on the ground!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DO YOU SAY IT LIKE IT'S A PRE DETERMINED THING</pattern><template>Just go, man.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A REALLY TYPICAL HOW WE MET STORY  TERRY</pattern><template>You'd be bored by it   I was a dancer for the Knicks...</template></category><category><pattern>I FEEL LIKE WE'RE LITERALLY DRIVING AROUND IN A VAGINA</pattern><template>Detective Hoitz and Gamble on that 5 18 on East 10th.</template></category><category><pattern>IN NEW YORK CITY THERE IS A FINE LINE BETWEEN LAW AND CHAOS</pattern><template>On that line live Danson and Highsmith.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  I CAN'T TALK ANYMORE  I THINK THE PHONE IS BEING TAPPED</pattern><template>Oh, baby, where are you? I wanna see you.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY JUMPED FROM 20 STORIES</pattern><template>Doesn't make sense, does it?</template></category><category><pattern>LADIES AND GENTLEMEN  GUESS  WHO GAVE ME THE SECRET TO MAKING</pattern><template>my first billion dollars?</template></category><category><pattern>FEEL THAT ALLEN  HUH  THAT TING A LING IN YOUR BALLS  BIG NET OF BUTTERFLIES FLYING AROUND IN YOUR STOMACH</pattern><template>Are you sure you don't have testicular cancer?</template></category><category><pattern>OK  SO I PUT TOGETHER A LITTLE BIO  COMPLETE WITH PICTURES OF MR  DAVID ERSHON</pattern><template>I use uh Adobe Premier I like to do a weekend editing recently just cut 3 minutes out of Goodfellas.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHEN I COME BACK  BUST YOUR ASS  WE'RE LOCKING DAVID ERSHON IN THE FEDERAL RESERVE</pattern><template>He still don't understand the concept.</template></category><category><pattern>SCARED  ASS UP  ENFLAMED  CRYING AND AT THAT MOMENT I KNEW  HEY  HE'S NO PIMP</pattern><template>Pimps don't cry.</template></category><category><pattern>AN HOUR  HOUR FORTY FIVE  NO PROBLEM</pattern><template>That will give us enough time to figure out where you live, go back to the sea, get more oxygen, and then stalk you You just lost at your own game.</template></category><category><pattern>OR CRACKING A MULTI BILLION DOLLAR FRAUD</pattern><template>Do you work here?</template></category><category><pattern>HE STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND THE CONCEPT</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALL HAVE  YOU KNOW  IT'S CALLED THE DESK POP</pattern><template>Fellas, look, I know you don't respect me as a police officer Not true,   I'm not stupid. I am not going to discharge my firearm in the office Listen to me! I'll try to make it real clear. We honor the flag.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  DOUBLE BAGGINS  WHERE ARE YOUR SHOES  YOUR FEET ARE BLACK</pattern><template>Who cares? It's not important ok?</template></category><category><pattern>STAY ON THE GROUND</pattern><template>Detective! Detective!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE AT 30 MILLION  AND HOLDING</pattern><template>No, wait.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU OK</pattern><template>Yeah, I'm fine.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW I GOT TINGLING IN MY BALLS YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>Beautiful.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  YOU'RE MAD AT US  HUH  GENE</pattern><template>First off, don't call me Gene I am your Captain.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THEY FLEW THE MILLENNIUM FALCON OUTSIDE OF THE DEATH STAR  IT WAS FOLLOWED BY EXPLOSION</pattern><template>That was bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST DO NOT GET IT  I MEAN THAT GIRL WAS CHRISTINETH WAS SERIOUSLY HOT</pattern><template>Your wife is crazy hot.</template></category><category><pattern>IT KINDA BUGS ME THAT WE STILL DON'T KNOW WHO ERSHON IS TARGETING</pattern><template>Is it the lotto? Who is it?</template></category><category><pattern>DID I HURT YOU</pattern><template>Just resting.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME WHO YOU LOST YOUR VIRGINITY TO</pattern><template>She actually became a TV actress.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A SMALL APARTMENT NO ONE KNOWS ABOUT IT</pattern><template>I use it mainly for my parents and prostitutes.</template></category><category><pattern>TURN ON THE NEWS MAN  NOBODY CARES</pattern><template>I hope I'm not alone.</template></category><category><pattern>NOBODY LEAVES THE HOUSE  WITHOUT MAKING LOVE TO MY WIFE</pattern><template>Holy shit! Let's go!</template></category><category><pattern>SPECIFICALLY SCAFFOLDING   SOME OF THE GUYS WERE TALKING</pattern><template>they are like, how come you never fired your weapon in the office before?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TELL YOUR DAUGHTER</pattern><template>He said, he'll always love you, and he's so happy that you're having his child.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN HEAR THE OTHER SIDE OF THAT CALL</pattern><template>No, it's nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT'S WORST  THE WAY YOU FART  EVEN YOUR FARTS  THEY'RE NOT MANLY</pattern><template>You're being ridiculous.   They sound like a baby blowing out the candles at a birthday cake.   What?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT TONIGHT  I NEED TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT WITH SHEILA</pattern><template>All right, go! Go! Be careful.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN  PUNCH THAT ACCELERATOR OR I'LL SHOOT IN YOU IN THE FOOT</pattern><template>America!</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT KNOW IF HE HEARD ME  BYE  TERRY</pattern><template>Bye, Sheila.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  RIGHT THERE</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A NICE LADY</pattern><template>Thank you for coming.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT   ALL RIGHT   ALL RIGHT   LISTEN UP  LISTEN UP</pattern><template>We have a celebration tonight at Butter, Brody Jenner is gonna be there..., Bai Ling..., Della Shortpit from Jersey Shore..., And... most of you are on the list   You're the best.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUY LOST HIS MONEY  WE HAVE A SKETCHY CELLPHONE MESSAGE AND AN ADDRESS  WE'RE STILL HALF A CASE</pattern><template>There's got to be some sort of paper trail.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW GREAT IS JERSEY BOYS</pattern><template>It's not great.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT TOUCH ANYTHING</pattern><template>Swear to God, I'd blow your head all over this desk.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  EVERYBODY  WE NEED Y'ALL TO BACK UP NOW  WE'RE TAKING OVER  AT THE CRIME SCENE  LOL     GOOD TWEET    YEAH AMERICA WAS ALWAYS BEEN DEFINED BY ITS EXCESS</pattern><template>The Grand Canyon, professional sports contracts...</template></category><category><pattern>PRETTY RINKY DINK OPERATION FOR A GUY LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Let's go to New Jersey and visit an accounting firm. That's a shitty day.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO ALL RIGHT  PAPER BITCH AND YANKEE CLIP ARE ON THE CASE</pattern><template>Nice work. Thanks, Allen.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  FINE  I'M GONNA TELL YOU GUYS SOMETHING</pattern><template>You've really went into deep water on this one.</template></category><category><pattern>YES WHERE DID YOU LEARN TO DRIVE LIKE THAT</pattern><template>Grand Theft Auto.</template></category><category><pattern>NO MORE TICKETS</pattern><template>Sorry sir, I tried to keep them in the waiting room.</template></category><category><pattern>HEARD EVERYTHING  MATE</pattern><template>Ladies and gentlemen, guess, who gave me the secret to making...</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YES I DO</pattern><template>You're a piece of work.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S NOTHING</pattern><template>Nothing?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE HAS BEEN PLAYING GRAND THEFT AUTO</pattern><template>Boom. I did that.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S ONE GUY  PHILLIP  HE CAN PEE IN THE URINAL FROM TWENTY FEET  YOU GOT TO SEE IT ALLEN  YOU GOT TO</pattern><template>What happened to you? What happened to this being our time?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ACCOUNTING FIRM IS CLOSED AT 11 AM ON A TUESDAY</pattern><template>This is a shithole.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  SO WHAT DO YOU GOT</pattern><template>I got this.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  ANY TAZERS  NO  GOOD</pattern><template>Who wants to go on a ride along?</template></category><category><pattern>OK  SWEETIE</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED AN MRI  I HAVE GOT SOFT TISSUE DAMAGE</pattern><template>There's no way I don't have soft tissue damage.</template></category><category><pattern>IF SOMETHING HAPPENS TO YOU  I NEED TO BE THERE TO TAKE CARE OF HER</pattern><template>All of her wants, her needs and desires are now my responsibility.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT SOMETHING TO KEEP YOU GOING</pattern><template>Let's go do some damage!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT    IT IS AN EX GIRLFRIEND  OK</pattern><template>What's the matter? What happened with you guys?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>I'm talking about my life.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHY ERSHON WAS CALLING DOWN TO THE LOTTERY OFFICE ALL THOSE TIMES</pattern><template>He's got to be hooking up with the Powerball girl. She was on TV with all the numbered balls.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE OTHER GUYS</pattern><template>We know... we know... we know...</template></category><category><pattern>APPROVE IT  NOW</pattern><template>Do not touch anything!</template></category><category><pattern>8:36 AM 24 MINUTES TO BANK TRANSFER I BROUGHT SOME MUSIC</pattern><template>Not what I would have chosen. But all right.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S OKAY     SHE'S GOT MAIL   THAT'S THE NAME OF THE MOVIE    THAT'S IT</pattern><template>With Tom Hanks?   And Meg Ryan.   He didn't have poison ivy up his ass.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE</pattern><template>Sheila and I got into it tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS A TRICK</pattern><template>No more.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE ONLY THING WE HAVE  WHY DID YOU JUST GET SUPER JUMPY</pattern><template>What?   It is an ex girlfriend, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>A GUY WHO KNOWS HOW TO USE DARK SIDE FOR GOOD</pattern><template>And then you move to Florida.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S PRETTY ROUGH STUFF NOT LONG AFTER THAT  A MAMA RACCOON CAME ALONG  AND GAVE BIRTH ON THE FLOOR</pattern><template>What about fingerprints?</template></category><category><pattern>ROGER WESLEY WAS LINKED TO THE BEAMAN MURDER BY A SECURITY CAM FOOTAGE</pattern><template>which Martin and Fossi hadn't checked.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAW HOW AGGRESSIVE YOU WERE BEING AND I THOUGHT  WOW  I GOTTA GO EVEN BIGGER THAN THAT  SINCE WE ARE DOING BAD COP  BAD COP</pattern><template>What? No, I said good cop, bad cop.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL TERRY  CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH FOR COMING BY  WHAT A WONDERFUL LOVELY EVENING  THANK YOU</pattern><template>It was so so nice meeting today.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WANTS SOME WALKING AROUND MONEY AND IT WANTS TO BUY SOME SHOES</pattern><template>and it wants to walk up to the people and say Hey, Gator don't play no shit!</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  I ACTUALLY APPRECIATE THAT</pattern><template>Good, coz I am gonna tell you directly to your face!</template></category><category><pattern>EXACTLY  THEY ARE THE GOOD GUYS</pattern><template>Where do we go? Where do we go?</template></category><category><pattern>DUDE  YOU'RE INSANE  YOUR WIFE IS SCOLDING HOT</pattern><template>Do you want to listen to this message or not?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU GONNA CHANGE</pattern><template>I already did.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE HIM AWAY</pattern><template>But computers.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU SAID</pattern><template>I don't know what that is, get out.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO THOUGH  YOU KNOW  BAR MITZVAH'S</pattern><template>What the hell is this?</template></category><category><pattern>HI  TERRY</pattern><template>Shit.</template></category><category><pattern>THE NEW BATH MATS ARE IN</pattern><template>One more thing. We got a serial rapist in Crown Heights.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S CLEAN THE SLATE RIGHT NOW  FRESH START</pattern><template>All right, fresh start.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE FEDERAL RESERVE IS THE PRISON</pattern><template>No, basically it is a held for profit bank that sets interest rates and moves money to other banks.</template></category><category><pattern>ON THAT LINE LIVE DANSON AND HIGHSMITH</pattern><template>Tell me again why I decided to get on this roof?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT AN ACCIDENT OR YOU'RE TRYING TO QUOTE TLC ON PURPOSE</pattern><template>I don't even understand your reference.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY GOD</pattern><template>Let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>BE A MAN  DO IT</pattern><template>Please, please do it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ABOUT THE CONSTRUCTION PERMITS WE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>The Scaffolding violation?</template></category><category><pattern>GOT A MARVELLOUS HIGH PRESSURE HANDLING THE CROWD  I PULL TUNNEL DUTY THEN I SAW A SHADOW FIGURE IN THE TUNNEL  I TOLD HIM TO STOP</pattern><template>Wow wow wow This is a restricted area.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO THE HELL ARE THOSE GUYS</pattern><template>Gentlemen, I can give you non obstructive view tickets for  Rock of Ages .</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON IN  FELLAS</pattern><template>You gotta be kidding me.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  YOU WERE A PIMP</pattern><template>What? God, no.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  BECAUSE WE ARE BOTH IN LAW ENFORCEMENT  WE BOTH LIKE WOMEN  BUT I GOT A WEIRD SENSE OF HUMOR</pattern><template>I'm a sick puppy. I can't look at it. It makes me laugh so hard.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COME IN HERE DRESSED LIKE A HOBO IS JUST DISTRACTING   I KNOW YOU ARE WORKING  I AM SO SORRY</pattern><template>Come on, seriously.</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY MARRIED FRANCINE  HE PLAYED HARP AT THE RECEPTION AND IT WAS BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>He learned how to play it in 8th grade to make fun the fairy that lived up the street.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH YEAH YEAH  THAT WHAT I WAS THINKING</pattern><template>Transportation services.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE A GIRL</pattern><template>I did, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>OR WHAT  HE DOESN'T CARE</pattern><template>He's been dodging this case for too long and I want answers. I want him to look me in the eye and tell me why.</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD IT WHEN HE SAID IT  THANK YOU</pattern><template>You know what you're doing to me? You're killing me inside, and go light on me man.</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEN CAME IN TO THE ER WITH POISON IVY ON HIS RECTUM</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULD'VE HANDLED THAT MYSELF</pattern><template>Don't flatter yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT GONNA DO THAT  THAT'S LIKE VERBALLY  BUT THAT'S ONE WEIRD EXAMPLE</pattern><template>You wanna go?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO IS THAT</pattern><template>That's the old ball and chain.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT MY GATE CODE</pattern><template>Shut up man.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  TOMORROW MORNING ALL I KNOW IS I AM GOING TO MAUCH  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Or what? He doesn't care.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MARTIN AND FOSSI</pattern><template>Back off and stop calling.</template></category><category><pattern>IT ONLY SHOWED THE BACK OF THEIR HEADS BUT ALLEN'S FACE BACK APP WAS ABLE TO GET A MATCH TO THEIR FACES</pattern><template>Terry married Francine, he played harp at the reception and it was beautiful.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN RIGHT</pattern><template>This is a very clever idea.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GO CHASING WATERFALLS</pattern><template>Is that an accident or you're trying to quote TLC on purpose?</template></category><category><pattern>IN FACT  THEY LEFT YOU A NOTE HERE   THANKS FOR THE F SHACK</pattern><template>Love, dirty Mike and the boys.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN LET'S BE HERE</pattern><template>Who are they?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  NO  I SAID GOOD COP  BAD COP</pattern><template>I'm the bad cop, you're the good cop.</template></category><category><pattern>CHRISTINA  THIS IS A LOVELY HOUSE</pattern><template>It's Christineth, are you stupid or are you deaf?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY SUGAR BOWLS  LISTEN UP</pattern><template>There's gonna be fingerprints in that car. And tomorrow, we 're gonna run those fingerprints through the system.</template></category><category><pattern>TERRY</pattern><template>He's right! It's not a proof of your behavior.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW IT  MAN</pattern><template>You kill us, we kill Ershon and you lost $30 million.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO ADMIT  I WASN'T GONNA COME  I MEAN  AFTER ALL THOSE YEARS  AFTER THE RESTRAINING ORDER</pattern><template>I was worried whether I'll see you again.</template></category><category><pattern>FINANCIAL PROFILING</pattern><template>That's crazy. He broke the law and we arrested him.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT MY INSURANCE CARD</pattern><template>Easy, mate.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE BLOOD BLISTERS ON MY HANDS</pattern><template>Oh God, how do they walk away in movies without fuzzy with an explosion behind them? No way!</template></category><category><pattern>JUST A BIT OF DYNAMISM  OTHERWISE IT WILL BE A LINEAR STORY</pattern><template>Just tell us what happened.</template></category><category><pattern>MARTIN AND FOSSI  SUPER COPS    IN THREE  TWO     WE BUSTED THAT JUNKIE      UH HUH</pattern><template>Got back 74,000 diamonds. 74,000.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WESLEY</pattern><template>Yes Where did you learn to drive like that?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LISTEN UP  I AM DETECTIVE GAMBLE AND THIS IS DETECTIVE HOITZ  WE NEED YOUR COOPERATION</pattern><template>David Ershon, you are under arrest for fraud...</template></category><category><pattern>I AM TALKING ABOUT THE DAY IN DAY OUTERS  THE GRINDERS  COME ON MAN  YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>The other guys...</template></category><category><pattern>ONE  TWO  THREE  ATTACK</pattern><template>Whoa!</template></category><category><pattern>I FINALLY PULLED MY GUN</pattern><template>Don't make me shoot, I'll do it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE TURNING OVER OUR INVESTIGATION TO YOU</pattern><template>Let me assure you, there will be no conflict of interest between me and David Ershon.</template></category><category><pattern>STAY FOCUS ON THE CASE  MAN</pattern><template>See you in Jersey tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL TAKE A LOOK AT YOUR EVIDENCE  AND I WILL TAKE A SECOND LOOK AT THEIR FINANCIALS</pattern><template>And when I come back, bust your ass, we're locking David Ershon in the Federal Reserve.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT BUGS ME ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>What?   I'm pretty sure you've never voted.   Oh I vote. Sports Regular AMA 80. Player of the week.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WENT AN CHECHEN VERSION OF DORA THE EXPLORER</pattern><template>It went terribly wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE KNOWS</pattern><template>You're a lucky dog.</template></category><category><pattern>GOLDMAN SACHS  THIS CASE IS GONNA BE NASTY HI  CUTE GLASSES</pattern><template>What was that?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT FUNNY ANYMORE</pattern><template>I do not know what you're talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY DOUGLAS  HOW'S THE WIFE</pattern><template>She died.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AT AGE ELEVEN  I AUDITED MY PARENTS</pattern><template>Believe me, there were some discrepancies, and I was grounded.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE  ALLEN</pattern><template>The code. I'm your partner.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME  WHERE'S MY CAR</pattern><template>They towed it. A couple of homeless people were messing around in it.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BUT IT'S PROCEDURE</pattern><template>Terry answers to no one.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN AFTERWARD  LICK THE SWEAT OFF EACH OTHER</pattern><template>I don't wanna do this.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAY HI TO SHEILA FOR ME</pattern><template>Ok.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOOT HIM</pattern><template>Jamie go get over here. You, go get the bloody car.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU IT WASN'T A SECURITY TEAM</pattern><template>He was being abducted.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID CHASING WATERFALLS  YOU SAYING I DON'T WANT NO SCRUBS</pattern><template>I don't even understand those reference.</template></category><category><pattern>OK    DON'T DO THAT SHIT ANYMORE</pattern><template>Yeah. Believe me I won't.</template></category><category><pattern>STAND OVER THERE  WOOD</pattern><template>Couldn't see the car? It's big enough, mate?</template></category><category><pattern>AH  MAN</pattern><template>You don't know how to do it!</template></category><category><pattern>SOME SCARY SHIT TERRY  THIS IS BIG</pattern><template>How did you get in here?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE OUTGUNNED AND OUT MANNED</pattern><template>Did that go the way you thought it was gonna go? Nope!</template></category><category><pattern>I DO WHAT I DO</pattern><template>What accounting firm is closed at 11 am on a Tuesday?</template></category><category><pattern>ANOTHER THING I HATE: YOU ALWAYS PAY IN EXACT CHANGE YOU'RE JUST MAD BECAUSE I HAVE A NICE CHANGE PURSE WHY DO YOU EVEN CARE</pattern><template>How can I help it? You know what?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE ALWAYS GOT LITTLE RIVER BAND LOADED  I GOT 6 DISCS IN HERE</pattern><template>Meet me outside at the back of the service entrance I am flying Air Singapore.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF THEM  CAN I TELL</pattern><template>Take a picture of anybody's face and I'll tell you how the back of his head looks like.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  IF I PUT THAT INTO MY COSMO QUESTIONNAIRE  YOU GOT A D  ALLEN AND HIS ABS  HE LOVES THEM  YOU KNOW HE HAS DESIGNED THREE OF HIS OWN</pattern><template>One of them, can I tell?</template></category><category><pattern>TWO GOOD MEN ARE DEAD AND YOU GUYS ARE FIGHTING</pattern><template>of who's gonna be the next hot shot, huh? Is that what's happening?</template></category><category><pattern>BYE  SHEILA</pattern><template>Well, here she is. They left her under an overpass for the night.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS THE BEST TO TELL THE STORIES BY STARTING FROM THE END</pattern><template>Briefly and then go back to the beginning.</template></category><category><pattern>2300 PARK AVENUE  THE OFFICES OF THE LOTTERY</pattern><template>Holy shit! The lottery tickets we found.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT UH  I'M NOT  SHAVED</pattern><template>Allen!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA GO FOR A WALK</pattern><template>Say something.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT GUY NEVER COMES DOWN HERE  20 YEARS  I THINK I'VE SEEN THAT GUY ONLY ONE TIME</pattern><template>He is a headway cap, that guy.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS MUSIC MAKES ME FEEL LIKE I AM GOING SHOPPING FOR TRAINING BRA</pattern><template>You know what? We go with no music, ok? Good bye.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO WRECK  YOU'RE RIGHT</pattern><template>What do you mean right?</template></category><category><pattern>HOPE YOU LIKE PRISON FOOD  AND PENIS</pattern><template>Police stand on the ground.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MORE THING  DO ME A FAVOR</pattern><template>Don't go chasing waterfalls.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE WORK  THANKS  ALLEN</pattern><template>Thank you, Captain.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT  YOU GOT A NEW BOYFRIEND</pattern><template>He is my dance partner, Terry.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME ASSURE YOU  THERE WILL BE NO CONFLICT OF INTEREST BETWEEN ME AND DAVID ERSHON</pattern><template>And if this were an actual investigation, I would immediately recuse myself.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA GO OVER AND CHECK ON TERRY  I HAVE A BAD KNEE  HOLD ON</pattern><template>It was the king of the mud cases.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED YOU TO BE STRAIGHT WITH ME</pattern><template>Or, straight with us.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO THE HELL ARE ALL THESE PEOPLE</pattern><template>I was only expecting one man.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT TO DO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO CAPTAIN</pattern><template>Ouch.</template></category><category><pattern>THE S E C</pattern><template>Beaman's office.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MORNING</pattern><template>We've got shot fired.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING IN THERE LIKE CHURCH MICE  THERE IS ONE CASE  ONE CASE IN YOUR CAREER YOU GO ALL IN  THIS IS IT</pattern><template>All right, then you do us proud.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT LADIES  STARTING TO GET THE PICTURE  WE'RE ABOUT TO LOCK SHIT DOWN</pattern><template>That's right You girls stay here and get your type on   Go get them guys. A lot of energy, a lot of focus.</template></category><category><pattern>IT INVOLVES A MANNEQUIN HANDS AND ELECTRIC SHAVER TAPED TO A GOLF CLUB</pattern><template>Now what she say?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A NICKNAME I HAD IN COLLEGE</pattern><template>I used to run a dating service.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU FIND ANYTHING</pattern><template>Yeah, we found a lot of stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE GO  OPEN IT UP</pattern><template>It's Ok, you're welcome.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT YOU GIRLS STAY HERE AND GET YOUR TYPE ON   GO GET THEM GUYS  A LOT OF ENERGY  A LOT OF FOCUS</pattern><template>Shut up.</template></category><category><pattern>DAVID  YOU'RE NOT RETURNING MY CALL  SO I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET ROGER WESLEY</pattern><template>G'day, mate!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF YOU'RE ASKING THEN I'LL STOP</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>COP'S BULLSHIT  ALL THAT</pattern><template>When they flew the Millennium Falcon outside of the Death Star, it was followed by explosion...</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT</pattern><template>Hey.   Hey.   What are you doing here? When I have lady troubles, I usually come here almost every night.</template></category><category><pattern>NO MORE</pattern><template>Gentlemen, you have a choice, Mamma mia or Jersey boys...</template></category><category><pattern>CAPTAIN    YEAH</pattern><template>Is it a bad time?   No.</template></category></AIML>