<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>I'M SELLING BONDS NOW  WITH WALTER CHASE'S OUTFIT</pattern><template>Let's say, after diner, you and I we go into town.</template></category><category><pattern>— UH  NO  THANK YOU</pattern><template>— No?</template></category><category><pattern>MY GOD  HE HAS</pattern><template>— He's got nothing to do with— — with your odd little racket.</template></category><category><pattern>— THEY'RE SCREAMING  THEY'RE SHOUTING   DAISY BUCHANAN  WE CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT YOU   I'M PARALYZED WITH HAPPINESS</pattern><template>Jordan Baker, a very famous golfer.</template></category><category><pattern>A FELLA NAMED GATSBY</pattern><template>Jay Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>JORDAN BAKER  A VERY FAMOUS GOLFER</pattern><template>She was the most frightening person I'd ever seen.  Well I— I've seen your face on the cover of Sporting Life. Nick Carraway.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A MINUTE  IT'S THE OPPOSITE</pattern><template>The sun is getting colder every year.</template></category><category><pattern>— HELLO  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>— Jay.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SEEING  WE COULDN'T BUT… BOTH OF US LOVED EACH OTHER ALL THAT TIME  DIDN'T WE</pattern><template>Oh, that's all?</template></category><category><pattern>OH GOD</pattern><template>All right, folks. Make some room, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON</pattern><template>— I wanna hear all about it.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS HE A FRIEND OF YOURS</pattern><template>He was… the single most hopeful person I've ever met, and I'm ever likely to meet again.</template></category><category><pattern>— LOVELY THOUGH  A LOVELY CLOCK</pattern><template>— Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY RESPECTABLE THING ABOUT YOU  OLD SPORT  IS YOUR MONEY</pattern><template>Your money, that's it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW OXFORD</pattern><template>— Yes, I've heard of it.</template></category><category><pattern>— THIS GENTLEMAN WILL BE JOINING— — EXCUSE ME  ONE MOMENT</pattern><template>— Nick, please, just sit down.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR DAUGHTER  I SUPPOSE SHE TALKS AND EATS AND EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Pammy?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL HAVE TEA NEXT WEEK</pattern><template>I'm in the phone book.</template></category><category><pattern>HE MUST KNOW WHAT A SMALL TOWN IT IS</pattern><template>Listen to me! Listen to me!</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE'S MET HIM</pattern><template>They say he's third cousin to the Kaiser, and second cousin to the devil.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER THIS IS THE FRIEND I TOLD YOU ABOUT</pattern><template>Oh my, I beg your pardon.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH NICKY  HOW FUNNY</pattern><template>Look, it's my house.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE JUST HEARD THE MOST SHOCKING THING</pattern><template>Where have you been?</template></category><category><pattern>— CAN'T REPEAT THE PAST</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S LIKE AN AMUSEMENT PARK</pattern><template>How do you live here all alone?</template></category><category><pattern>TOWN</pattern><template>Oh! Women get these notions!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT  MY DEAR FELLOW  IS THE QUESTION</pattern><template>Are you ready?</template></category><category><pattern>I DID LOVE HIM ONCE— BUT I LOVED YOU TOO</pattern><template>You— you loved— you loved me  too ?</template></category><category><pattern>— THANK YOU</pattern><template>— One of your old Oxford pals?</template></category><category><pattern>I'D REALLY RATHER NOT BE THE POLO PLAYER</pattern><template>All these things excite me so.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>— Just sitting here.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE  MR  CARRAWAY</pattern><template>Disgusted with everyone, and everything.</template></category><category><pattern>WRITE IT DOWN</pattern><template>A place… The Valley of Ashes was a grotesque place.</template></category><category><pattern>ABSOLUTELY  OLD SPORT  ABSOLUTELY</pattern><template>Ladner, open the gates.</template></category><category><pattern>—  HOW TO DRESS  ACT AND SPEAK…  — GATSBY</pattern><template>—  …like a gentleman  — Jay Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK</pattern><template>Daisy, don't create a scene.</template></category><category><pattern>ANOTHER SWELL PARTY  JAY</pattern><template>Be careful for the snake charmer, Mr. McLennahan.</template></category><category><pattern>— OKAY</pattern><template>— Nick Carraway.</template></category><category><pattern>I RANG  I WROTE  I IMPLORED    BUT NOT A SINGLE ONE OF THE SPARKLING HUNDREDS THAT ENJOYED HIS HOSPITALITY    ATTENDED THE FUNERAL</pattern><template>And from Daisy…   not even a flower.   I was all he had.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT  DAISY</pattern><template>Come look.</template></category><category><pattern>ABSOLUTELY</pattern><template>We don't go around very much. I don't think I recognize a single person.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER THE HONEYMOON  I SAW THEM IN SANTA BARBARA</pattern><template>Well it was touching, really, I'd never seen a girl so in love with her husband.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  EVERY NIGHT I CAN SEE THAT LIGHT AT THE END OF YOUR DOCK BLINKING</pattern><template>What light?</template></category><category><pattern>APPARENTLY FOR LUNCH AT THE YALE CLUB    BUT THE DAY TOOK AN UNEXPECTED TURN   COME ON</pattern><template>— Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU THINK I SHOULD</pattern><template>I mean, does Daisy want to see Gatsby?</template></category><category><pattern>HENRY  HAVE THE CAR BROUGHT AROUND NOW</pattern><template>Just like that? Can't anyone at least have a cigarette first?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL HAVE THE LOBSTER  IT'S DECORATED WITH TRUFFLES AND FINE HERBS</pattern><template>How's the bond business, Mr. Carraway?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE THE ADVERTISEMENT OF THE MAN IN TIMES SQUARE</pattern><template>The man in the cool beautiful shirts.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  THESE TOWNS ARE VERY CLOSE TOGETHER  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>If it gets in the papers, you understand?</template></category><category><pattern>COUPÉ</pattern><template>We just got here from New York.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  LET'S HAVE FUN</pattern><template>It's too hot to fuss.</template></category><category><pattern>— SHAKESPEARE</pattern><template>— Tom!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GONNA DEFEND HIM NOW</pattern><template>I'll telephone for a taxi, Nick.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>Well. This, huh, this Mr. Gatsby you spoke of. He's my neighbor.</template></category><category><pattern>— LEMON OR SUGAR</pattern><template>— Neither.</template></category><category><pattern>— MY INVITATION</pattern><template>Hello.</template></category><category><pattern>— LOOK AT YOU</pattern><template>Mr. Carraway, this is my good friend, Mr. Meyer Wolfsheim.</template></category><category><pattern>— I DON'T BELIEVE YOU</pattern><template>— They're screaming, they're shouting,  Daisy Buchanan, we can't live without you!  I'm paralyzed with happiness!</template></category><category><pattern>JUST IN TO THE RIGHT  GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>To the right, in the living room.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT TODAY</pattern><template>Not today. It's so beautiful.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THIS SOMETHING I ALWAYS CARRY WITH ME  A SOUVENIR OF OXFORD DAYS</pattern><template>That was taken in Trinity Quad, the man on my left is now the Earl of Doncaster.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I… YOU SEE  AFTER WE LEFT NEW YORK  SHE WAS… SHE WAS VERY NERVOUS  SHE THOUGHT… THAT DRIVING WOULD STEADY HER</pattern><template>But… this woman, she rushed out at us.</template></category><category><pattern>NICK  DAISY IS FURIOUS</pattern><template>You haven't called her.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAS MY FIRST PHOTO OF YOU</pattern><template>You remember this letter, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S THE MAN WHO FIXED THE 1919 WORLD'S SERIES</pattern><template>— Fixed it?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'LL BE DAMNED IF I KNOW HOW YOU GOT WITHIN A MILE OF HER  UNLESS YOU BROUGHT THE GROCERIES TO THE BACK DOOR  BUT ALL THE REST OF THAT IS A GODDAMN LIE</pattern><template>Daisy loved me when she married me, and she loves me now.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS ALWAYS GLAD I SAID THAT    IT WAS THE ONLY COMPLIMENT I EVER PAID HIM    THAT MORNING  WALL STREET BOOMED ITS USUAL GOLDEN ROAR    BUT I WASN'T WORTH A DECENT STROKE OF WORK    AND I WAITED FOR GATSBY TO CALL WITH NEWS…   WHILE HE WAITED FOR DAISY   GATSBY'S</pattern><template>I know Mr. Gatsby will be very happy that you've called.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIVE RIGHT NEXT DOOR TO HIM</pattern><template>He's a cousin of Kaiser Wilhem's.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS SOMETHING ABOUT HIM  A SENSITIVITY  HE WAS LIKE… HE WAS LIKE ONE OF THOSE MACHINES THAT REGISTER EARTHQUAKES 10 000 MILES AWAY</pattern><template>Where did you meet him?</template></category><category><pattern>STOP  STOP</pattern><template>— Myrtle! Baby!</template></category><category><pattern>﻿1 THE GREAT GATSBY TRANSCRIPT AND SYNC: JCDR V3 — 10 10 2013  IN MY YOUNGER AND MORE VULNERABLE YEARS    MY FATHER GAVE ME SOME ADVICE     ALWAYS TRY TO SEE THE BEST IN PEOPLE   HE WOULD SAY    AS A CONSEQUENCE  I'M INCLINED TO RESERVE ALL JUDGMENTS    BUT EVEN I HAVE A LIMIT    BACK THEN  ALL OF US DRANK TOO MUCH    THE MORE IN TUNE WITH THE TIMES WE WERE    THE MORE WE DRANK    AND NONE OF US CONTRIBUTED ANYTHING NEW   WHEN I CAME BACK FROM NEW YORK  I WAS DISGUSTED</pattern><template>I see, Mr. Carraway.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT'S ONLY HALF PAST NINE</pattern><template>— No, I've had enough! Of everyone.</template></category><category><pattern>— STOP</pattern><template>Please!</template></category><category><pattern>I AM THE SON OF VERY WEALTHY PEOPLE FROM THE MIDDLE WEST</pattern><template>Sadly, all of them are dead now.</template></category><category><pattern>— HOW HAVE YOU BEEN</pattern><template>— Yeah! Good.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A GREAT EXPRESSION OF YOURS  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>What is?</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YOU JOIN US  MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>Two bottles of whiskey, wrap them in a towel.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>You saved my letters.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY ABOUT THE CLOCK</pattern><template>That's an old clock.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE HAD A VERY BAD TIME  NICKY</pattern><template>I'm pretty cynical about everything.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SENDS OVER A SELECTION AT THE BEGINNING OF EACH SEASON</pattern><template>These are silk.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  I GREW UP TERRIBLY  TERRIBLY POOR  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>My folks were…  — He revealed his humble beginnings,   his transformative voyage with Dan Cody.   The war, Oxford, and how he joined Wolfsheim in the business.   That was also that night that I became aware of Gatsby's extraordinary gift for hope.  I can't describe how surprised I was to find out that I loved her, old sport, and that she loved me too.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE THESE FISTS</pattern><template>He's the next heavyweight champion.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  I THOUGH YOU OUGHT TO KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT MY LIFE  I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO THINK I WAS… WELL  I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO THINK I WAS JUST SOME NOBODY</pattern><template>— No!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS TAKEN IN TRINITY QUAD  THE MAN ON MY LEFT IS NOW THE EARL OF DONCASTER</pattern><template>What could I say?   The photograph was undoubtedly authentic.   Could it all be true?  But of course, you don't need to take my word for it, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>— WOULDN'T ASK TOO MUCH</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>♪ AT LEAST I MISS  ♪ TRIPS AROUND THE WORLD  ♪ DON'T MEAN A THING  ♪ IF I AIN'T YOUR GIRL  ♪ I AIN'T GOT TIME  ♪ FOR YOU BABY  ♪ EITHER YOU'RE MINE OR YOU'RE NOT  MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>Sweet baby, come on!</template></category><category><pattern>IS EVERYTHING ALRIGHT</pattern><template>Oh, the grass looks fine, if that's what you mean.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S UPSET</pattern><template>Everybody out!</template></category><category><pattern>— SLOW DOWN</pattern><template>Slow down.</template></category><category><pattern>GO AWAY  NO  I CAN'T LEAVE NOW</pattern><template>Not tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>— IS THAT SO</pattern><template>We're gonna live here.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE MIGHT HAVE THE DECENCY NOT TO TELEPHONE AT DINER TIME  DON'T YOU THINK</pattern><template>Is that too much to ask?</template></category><category><pattern>TOM  I'M— I'M JUST LEAVING NOW</pattern><template>Nick! Wait!</template></category><category><pattern>— WELL… — UH… LOOK HERE OLD SPORT  YOU— YOU DON'T MAKE MUCH MONEY  DO YOU</pattern><template>— Not really.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT THAT DAY I CARRIED YOU DOWN FROM THE PUNCH BOWL TO KEEP YOUR SHOES DRY</pattern><template>Never?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE A ROTTEN CROWD</pattern><template>You're worth the whole damn bunch put together.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FOLKS WERE…  — HE REVEALED HIS HUMBLE BEGINNINGS    HIS TRANSFORMATIVE VOYAGE WITH DAN CODY    THE WAR  OXFORD  AND HOW HE JOINED WOLFSHEIM IN THE BUSINESS    THAT WAS ALSO THAT NIGHT THAT I BECAME AWARE OF GATSBY'S EXTRAORDINARY GIFT FOR HOPE   I CAN'T DESCRIBE HOW SURPRISED I WAS TO FIND OUT THAT I LOVED HER  OLD SPORT  AND THAT SHE LOVED ME TOO</pattern><template>A gift that I have never found in any other person…  I never realized how extraordinary a nice girl could be.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY  SIR  IT'S MR  SLAGLE</pattern><template>He's quite emotional.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DAMN THING CAME OUT OF NOWHERE</pattern><template>Yeah. Yeah, big yellow Duesy.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NO COINCIDENCE  HE BOUGHT THAT HOUSE TO BE NEAR HER</pattern><template>He threw all those parties, hoping she would wander in one night.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I ARRIVED HOME  I NOTICED THAT A FIGURE HAD EMERGED ON MY NEIGHBOR'S DOCK    AND SOMETHING TOLD ME IT WAS…   MR  GATSBY    HE SEEMED TO BE REACHING TOWARDS SOMETHING OUT THERE IN THE DARK    THE GREEN LIGHT   I DON'T WANNA TALK ABOUT THIS  DOCTOR</pattern><template>Then write about it.</template></category><category><pattern>— MY WIFE AND I  WE WANNA GO WEST</pattern><template>Oh, your wife does?</template></category><category><pattern>— MR  BUCHANAN  CANDY</pattern><template>— Uh. No! Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING'S BEEN SO… SO CONFUSED SINCE THAT NIGHT</pattern><template>He talked a lot about the past.   As if he wanted to recover something.  If I c— if I could just get back to the start.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A COUSIN OF KAISER WILHEM'S</pattern><template>You know, the evil German king?</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY  YOU TABLE IS READY</pattern><template>Gatsby!</template></category><category><pattern>LINEN</pattern><template>— Nicky, he's a mad man!</template></category><category><pattern>TRYING TO FORGET SOMETHING SAD</pattern><template>Just when I thought it couldn't be any more fantastical…  Then came the war, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>AND FROM DAISY…   NOT EVEN A FLOWER    I WAS ALL HE HAD</pattern><template>The only one who cared.   After Gatsby's death, New York was haunted for me.   That city…   my once golden shimmering mirage…   now made me sick.   On my last night in New York,   I returned to that huge incoherent house once more.   Wolfsheim Associates had cleaned it out.  He threw all those parties, hoping she would wander in one night.</template></category><category><pattern>NICK  WAIT</pattern><template>I'm just… I'm just going, I've gotta get out of here.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS HOUSE… AND EVERYTHING IN IT ARE ALL PART OF AN ELABORATE DISGUISE</pattern><template>But Mr. Gatsby doesn't exist.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO CLUE HOW I GOT HOME</pattern><template>But I do know that I awoke with a distinctly uneasy feeling   that Gatsby was watching me.  Watching you?</template></category><category><pattern>THE REASON WHY AFTER THE WAR  I… I HADN'T BEEN ABLE TO RETURN</pattern><template>I asked her to wait until I made something of myself. But she was… See, I felt married to her.</template></category><category><pattern>— HE'S GOT NOTHING TO DO WITH— — WITH YOUR ODD LITTLE RACKET</pattern><template>Daisy?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHY WE LEFT CHICAGO</pattern><template>I'm surprised they didn't treat you to the story of that little spree.</template></category><category><pattern>NERVE PILLS  I GET THEM FROM A DOCTOR IN QUEENS</pattern><template>Do you want one?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS GATSBY</pattern><template>And the way he looked at her, is the way all girls want to be looked at.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YEAH  BIG YELLOW DUESY</pattern><template>Custom job.</template></category><category><pattern>PARIS  VENICE  ROME  VIENNA  ZURICH  HELSINKI  MOSCOW  ISTANBUL  COLLECTING JEWELS —CHIEFLY RUBIES— HUNTING BIG GAME  PAINTING A LITTLE— THINGS FOR MYSELF ONLY</pattern><template>Trying to forget something sad.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WILL BE</pattern><template>I remembered how we had all come to Gatsby's and guessed at his corruption,   while he stood before us, concealing an incorruptible dream.  It's perfect. From your perfect irresistible imagination.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU HAVE HALF OF WALL STREET OUT THERE SWILLING YOUR FREE BOOZE  AT THAT FUN PARK EVERY WEEKEND</pattern><template>I'm surprised he hasn't tried to drag you in.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT IS THIS ENORMOUS REQUEST  JORDAN— — HE WANTS YOU TO INVITE DAISY TO TEA</pattern><template>Daisy?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA WAIT HERE ALL NIGHT  IF NECESSARY</pattern><template>No, no, no. That's not a good idea.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ALL FOR HER  THE HOUSE  THE PARTIES  EVERYTHING   GOD SEES EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Mr. Gatsby, sir, excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD BEEN DRUNK JUST TWICE IN MY LIFE    AND THE SECOND TIME WAS THAT AFTERNOON    THAT NIGHT IN THE HIDDEN FLAT THAT TOM KEPT FOR MYRTLE    WE WERE BUOYED BY A SORT OF CHEMICAL MADNESS    A WILLINGNESS OF THE HEART THAT BURST THUNDEROUSLY UPON US ALL    AND SUDDENLY  I BEGAN TO LIKE NEW YORK   THIS IS BETTER THAN THE YALE CLUB</pattern><template>High over the city,   our yellow windows must have contributed their share of human secrets   to the casual watcher in the street.   And I was him too,   looking up and wondering, I was within… and without…  …enchanted and repelled… by the inexhaustible variety of life.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THIS DRUGSTORE BUSINESS IS JUST SMALL CHANGE COMPARED TO THIS BONDS STUNT THAT YOU AND WOLFSHEIM HAVE GOT GOING</pattern><template>Your friend Walter Chase isn't too proud to come in on it.</template></category><category><pattern>JORDAN  WHAT'S SHE GOT TO DO WITH IT</pattern><template>Well I assure you it's nothing underhand.</template></category><category><pattern>LADNER  OPEN THE GATES</pattern><template>— Open the gates!</template></category><category><pattern>I… HELLO</pattern><template>They were careless people, Tom and Daisy.</template></category><category><pattern>ENOUGH  HEY  WILSON</pattern><template>I was bringing you the coupé.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST LIKE THAT  CAN'T ANYONE AT LEAST HAVE A CIGARETTE FIRST</pattern><template>We smoked all through lunch.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MARLENE MOON</pattern><template>I adore her pictures.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT MR  GATSBY DOESN'T EXIST</pattern><template>Phooey! I've met him.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT LATER</pattern><template>— Highballs, Mr. Gatsby?</template></category><category><pattern>HE THREW ALL THOSE PARTIES  HOPING SHE WOULD WANDER IN ONE NIGHT</pattern><template>He constantly asked about Daisy.</template></category><category><pattern>FINE  THANK YOU</pattern><template>I understand you're looking for a business connection.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONE THAT BURNS ALL NIGHT AT THE END OF YOUR DOCK</pattern><template>Possibly it had occurred to Gatsby that the colossal significance of that light   had vanished forever.   Now it was once again just a green light on a dock,   and his count of enchanted object had diminished by one.  Who is this? Your father?</template></category><category><pattern>— HIGHBALLS  MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>— Highballs it is.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WEARS A PINK SUIT  FOR CHRIST SAKE</pattern><template>Tom, we're almost out of gas.</template></category><category><pattern>I CANNOT FIND ANYONE WHO KNOWS ANYTHING REAL ABOUT MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>Well, I don't care!</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  AH</pattern><template>Call your sister, she will like him.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RUDE</pattern><template>I'm Catherine.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT COLOR IS YOUR CAR</pattern><template>It's blue.</template></category><category><pattern>OH I WOULD LIKE TO BE OUT ON THAT BAY TODAY</pattern><template>I'm right across from you.</template></category><category><pattern>LOVELY TO SEE YOU AGAIN  MISS BAKER</pattern><template>If there is anything that you want… just ask for it, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>♪ RIGHT HERE  RIGHT NOW  BUT YOU ARE MISTAKEN</pattern><template>For I am the mysterious Mr. Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN LYING ON THAT SOFA FOR AS LONG AS I CAN REMEMBER</pattern><template>This summer, I'll fling you two together, I'll push you into linen closets, and out to sea in boats!</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER YOU WANT</pattern><template>Hey, Mr. Buchanan, you want a— you want a soda?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THEY JUST STOPPED</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT EXACTLY  NO</pattern><template>Oh yes, I understand that you went to Oxford.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BE CAREFUL WITH THOSE TABLES NOW  SENATOR</pattern><template>I'll put a bet on for you, Jay!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU LIVE HERE ALL ALONE</pattern><template>She makes it look so— so splendid, don't you think, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY  IT WAS YOUR GREAT IDEA</pattern><template>Why don't we? Let's all go to town?</template></category><category><pattern>— WHY NOT</pattern><template>— I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE… I'M GATSBY</pattern><template>You're…  His smile was one of those rare smiles   that you may come across four or five times in life.   It seemed to understand you and believe in you,   just as you would like to be understood and believed in.  Sorry old sport, I though you knew.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY TO KEEP HER FROM YOU  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Don't forget, we're going up in that hydroplane tomorrow morning.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEEM TO… HAVE LOST MY TEMPER</pattern><template>That's right, Mr. Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  IT'S MY HOUSE</pattern><template>Just there, across the bay.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL A CUSTOM JOB</pattern><template>Supercharged engine.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS THERE  I SAW IT</pattern><template>I understand! I understand you.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVEN'T SEEN IT ALL AFTERNOON</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>THE MAN IN THE COOL BEAUTIFUL SHIRTS</pattern><template>She had told Gatsby that she loved him.   And Tom had seen it.  Let's go to town!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT LIGHT</pattern><template>You see, Mr. Buchanan, I wanted to be close… Daisy and I have— — It's so hot!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T WE  LET'S ALL GO TO TOWN</pattern><template>I changed my mind, you brute.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT…  AFTER TOM AND DAISY'S VISIT  GATSBY'S LIGHTS WENT OUT ONE BY ONE    THERE WERE NO MORE PARTIES    DAISY VISITED DISCREETLY    FOR THE VERY SAME FAME THAT HAD ALL SUMMER BEEN A SOURCE OF SATISFACTION TO JAY GATSBY    HAD BECOME A THREAT   I DON'T WANNA GO HOME</pattern><template>I— I heard you fired all your servants.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LIVE AROUND HERE  NICK</pattern><template>— Just next door.</template></category><category><pattern>KLIPSPRINGER</pattern><template>He must be awake.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE… WE'VE UH… WE'VE MET BEFORE</pattern><template>I'll have someone to come repair this immediately.</template></category><category><pattern>IN NEW YORK</pattern><template>In the summer 1922,   the tempo of the city approached… hysteria.   Stocks reached record peaks,   and Wall Street boomed in a steady golden roar.   The parties were bigger.   The shows were broader.   The buildings were higher.   The models were looser, and the ban on alcohol had backfired,   making the liquor cheaper.   Wall Street was luring the young and ambitious,   and I was one of them.   I rented a house twenty miles from the city on Long Island.   I lived in West Egg, in a forgotten groundskeeper's cottage,   squeezed among the mansions of the newly rich.   To get started, I bought a dozen volumes on credit banking and investment,   all new to me.   The stock market hit another high.  The market's moving up, up, up!</template></category><category><pattern>— NICK  I'VE… GOT TO SPEAK TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING</pattern><template>— Yes, I— I'll be right back!</template></category><category><pattern>NICK  COME AND SEE ME</pattern><template>We'll have tea next week!</template></category><category><pattern>UH YES  I WENT THERE</pattern><template>Sure. The man in the pink suit went to Oxford.</template></category><category><pattern>I KEEP IT ALWAYS FULL OF INTERESTING CELEBRATED PEOPLE</pattern><template>Come with me.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF I RUN OUT  I'LL STOP AT A DRUGSTORE</pattern><template>I hear you can buy anything at a drugstore nowadays.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THERE YOU ARE</pattern><template>Daisy just left.</template></category><category><pattern>A PLACE… THE VALLEY OF ASHES WAS A GROTESQUE PLACE</pattern><template>New York's dumping ground half way between West Egg and the city,   where the burnt out coal that powered the booming golden city was discarded by men,   who moved dimly and already crumbling through the powdery air.   This Fantastic Farm was ever watched by Dr. T.J. Eckleburg.   A forgotten oculist whose eyes brooded over it all.   Like the eyes of God.   Tom had invited me to town.</template></category><category><pattern>SLOW DOWN</pattern><template>— It's beautiful!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S MINE</pattern><template>Your face is familiar. Weren't you in the third Division during the war?</template></category><category><pattern>I'D NEVER BEEN IN SUCH A BEAUTIFUL HOUSE BEFORE</pattern><template>May I save the next dance?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE LOOKS WELL  DON'T SHE</pattern><template>Gatsby hoped to inherit Cody's fortune.  — Old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY  DON'T CREATE A SCENE</pattern><template>I love seeing you at my table, Nicky.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY  TALK TO ME  DARLING</pattern><template>I just lost my temper, that's all.</template></category><category><pattern>THOUGH ONCE IN A WHILE  I— I GO OFF ON A SPREE  I ALWAYS COME BACK</pattern><template>— A spree!</template></category><category><pattern>DO I HAVE TO DO IT MYSELF</pattern><template>Do you think I come here to admire the view?</template></category><category><pattern>SWEET BABY  COME ON</pattern><template>♪ Right here, right now  But you are mistaken!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE AS LONG AS THEY CAN COOK AND MAKE BEDS  RIGHT</pattern><template>Nick, Daisy's ready.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEVER TOLD ME YOU HAD A POMPADOUR OR A YACHT</pattern><template>I wanna show you something.</template></category><category><pattern>— SO  AFTER DINER… — WELL  I'M NOT EVEN FAINTLY LIKE A ROSE</pattern><template>— Nick wanted to go into town.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL IT WAS TOUCHING  REALLY  I'D NEVER SEEN A GIRL SO IN LOVE WITH HER HUSBAND</pattern><template>A week later, Tom crashed his car.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING  SIR</pattern><template>Sir, I'm asking you to— — Get off me!</template></category><category><pattern>A GERMAN SPY</pattern><template>No no, no no. He's the Kaizer's assassin.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA ASK MR  GATSBY ONE MORE QUESTION</pattern><template>Oh, please! Please go on, Mr. Buchanan, go on.</template></category><category><pattern>HE GIVES LARGE PARTIES  AND I LIKE LARGE PARTIES  THEY'RE SO INTIMATE</pattern><template>Small parties, there isn't any privacy.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DOES A REPUTABLE BANKER LIKE WALTER CHASE  FIND HIMSELF UP TO HIS EYEBALLS IN DEBT— — I'LL TELL YOU HOW</pattern><template>— to a little kike like Wolfsheim?</template></category><category><pattern>TOM  WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF GAS</pattern><template>Wilson? What are you waiting for?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU CAN  IF YOU WANT</pattern><template>Neither of them can stand the person they're married to.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT WE COULD… THIS REMARKABLE LITTLE CAMERA'S THE LATEST DESIGN</pattern><template>Let me show you, I'll show you how it's done.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS NO POINT IN STOP— NO POINT   NO POINT</pattern><template>What about that woman?</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>Well. Goodbye.</template></category><category><pattern>— HIGHBALLS IT IS</pattern><template>— Alright!</template></category><category><pattern>CONGRATULATIONS  MR  BUCHANAN</pattern><template>After the honeymoon, I saw them in Santa Barbara.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  I'M… I ALL RUN DOWN</pattern><template>I need money real bad.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD THE WRONG MAN</pattern><template>Now if you'll excuse me, I have to make that call.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  UH NICK</pattern><template>McKee is in the artistic game.</template></category><category><pattern>NICKY  I HEARD A RUMOR THAT YOU WERE GETTING MARRIED TO A GIRL OUT WEST</pattern><template>It's a libel. I'm too poor.</template></category><category><pattern>LEAVE ME ALONE</pattern><template>Jordan, no one must know about this.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY  DAISY</pattern><template>Do you want any of this?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKEWISE</pattern><template>Senator, I'll catch you up later, perhaps at the crap table.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THE WHOLE THING'S INCREDIBLE</pattern><template>I live just next door.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME  LISTEN TO ME</pattern><template>I said a small town.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I'VE STILL GOT MY MAN WORKING ON IT</pattern><template>Yeah well he works pretty slow, don't he?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'RE YOU KIDS GOING</pattern><template>— Long Island, please.</template></category><category><pattern>AND GATSBY</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>THE CAR'S WAITING</pattern><template>— Come on, we're leaving.</template></category><category><pattern>— TRUST ME</pattern><template>— What are we doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T TALK NOW  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>He must know what a small town it is.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  SHE DIDN'T LIKE IT  SHE… SHE DID NOT HAVE A GOOD TIME  I… FEEL SO FAR AWAY FROM HER NOW</pattern><template>So hard to make her understand.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T BELIEVE IT</pattern><template>You? Did you ransack a greenhouse?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MR  CARRAWAY  HER COUSIN</pattern><template>Madame is not available, Monsieur Carraway.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY WAS SHOWING US THE GROUNDS</pattern><template>He certainly must have strained himself to get this menagerie together.</template></category><category><pattern>— I HEARD HE KILLED A MAN ONCE</pattern><template>— It's true!</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YOU COME  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>We need you.</template></category><category><pattern>— TOM</pattern><template>— Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE DIFFERENT</pattern><template>I am, they are, she is.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU DON'T HAVE A LEGITIMATE REASON TO BE IN THE BUILDING  I WANT YOU OUTSIDE</pattern><template>If you saw anything tonight you'd like to talk to me about, well, then you can talk to me outside.</template></category><category><pattern>TEDDY BARTON  NICK CARRAWAY</pattern><template>A German spy?</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE ALL SUMMER  NOW YOU WANNA SIT ON THE SIDELINE AND WATCH  OR D'YOU WANNA PLAY BALL</pattern><template>— Play ball!</template></category><category><pattern>WHO OWNS THE YELLOW CAR</pattern><template>A fella named Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO INTRODUCE YOU</pattern><template>I'd really rather not be the Polo player.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>Daisy, darling, that… that wouldn't be respectable.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE DON'T</pattern><template>Daisy.</template></category><category><pattern>— THERE'S SO MUCH TO TALK ABOUT</pattern><template>It's just for a drink or two.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  BUT IT IS THOUGH</pattern><template>You see, I though you ought to know something about my life, I didn't want you to think I was… Well, I didn't want you to think I was just some nobody.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST TEAM  ALL AMERICAN</pattern><template>See? Made me who I am today.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU COME INSIDE AND HAVE SOME SUPPER WHILE YOU WAIT</pattern><template>No thanks. I'll wait outside.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HOUSE LOOKS WELL  DOESN'T IT</pattern><template>See the way the whole front catches the light like that?!</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT ABOUT</pattern><template>— About things.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY IN MOURNING</pattern><template>They're crying. Yes, they're wailing.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WISH TO CONTACT HER… I HAVE NO FURTHER INFORMATION  MONSIEUR</pattern><template>— Please!</template></category><category><pattern>— THE PARTY</pattern><template>I couldn't care less about the parties.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY IS MY COUSIN</pattern><template>Listen, I know you like to watch.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO</pattern><template>Hello, Nicky. We're having a row.</template></category><category><pattern>AND CERTAINLY NOT FOR A COMMON SWINDLER LIKE YOU</pattern><template>Mr. Gatsby, exactly who are you, anyhow?</template></category><category><pattern>HE BEGAN TALKING EXCITEDLY    BUT WITH EVERY WORD  DAISY WAS DRAWING FURTHER AND FURTHER INTO HERSELF   …TO GO TO YOUR PARENTS' HOUSE IN LOUISVILLE</pattern><template>Please, Tom, I can't stand it anymore!</template></category><category><pattern>— NOW</pattern><template>— Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>GATSBY</pattern><template>Something ought to be done about a fella like that.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH YEAH</pattern><template>— Yeah. I… — Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>— I CAN'T</pattern><template>— Catch up with the ol'wolf pack.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST NEED TO SPEAK TO DAISY ALONE  YOU SEE  YOU— YOU'VE GOT HER ALL EXCITED NOW  DON'T YOU OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Daisy, hey— Even alone I can't say I never loved Tom, it wouldn't be true.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I THINK I'LL MAKE A POINT OF FINDING OUT</pattern><template>— I'm not sure. Ask them in the kitchen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST KNOW THE FACES OF MANY PEOPLE YOU'VE HEARD OF</pattern><template>Absolutely.</template></category><category><pattern>A CARAVANSARY OF BILLIONAIRE PLAYBOY PUBLISHERS AND THEIR BLOND NURSES…   HEIRESSES COMPARING INHERITANCES ON GATSBY'S BEACH    MY BOSS  WALTER CHASE  LOSING MONEY AT THE ROULETTE TABLES    GOSSIP COLUMNISTS ALONGSIDE GANGSTERS AND GOVERNORS EXCHANGING TELEPHONE NUMBERS    FILM STARS  BROADWAY DIRECTORS    MORALITY PROTECTORS  HIGH SCHOOL DEFECTORS    AND EWING KLIPSPRINGER  DUBIOUS DESCENDANT OF BEETHOVEN   DO YOU KNOW WHERE I MIGHT FIND THE HOST  MR  GATSBY  I LIVE JUST NEXT DOOR</pattern><template>Gatsby? I've never seen Mr. Gatsby, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>AND LET ALL THIS GLORIOUS LOVE END IN NOTHING</pattern><template>Come home.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS THE NIGHT HE FINALLY TOLD ME THE TRUTH    ALL OF IT   YOU KNOW  I THOUGHT FOR A WHILE I HAD A LOT OF THINGS  BUT… THE TRUTH IS I'M… I'M EMPTY</pattern><template>I suppose that's why I make things up about myself, but I wanted to tell you the whole story for a very long time.</template></category><category><pattern>MEYER  NO NO NO</pattern><template>He's a gambler.</template></category><category><pattern>— SHE'S LEAVING YOU</pattern><template>— Nonsense!</template></category><category><pattern>TURN ON THE CAMERA</pattern><template>— Where did you go?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  JORDAN</pattern><template>Will you join us, Mr. Gatsby?</template></category><category><pattern>I BELIEVE WE'VE MET BEFORE  MR  BUCHANAN</pattern><template>About a month ago.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS JUST THE FIRST PERSON THAT KNEW HER</pattern><template>All that for a girl he hasn't seen in five years.</template></category><category><pattern>— DAISY</pattern><template>— He won't annoy you.</template></category><category><pattern>LAUGHTER</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURPRISED HE HASN'T TRIED TO DRAG YOU IN</pattern><template>My God, he has.</template></category><category><pattern>— SIT DOWN  DAISY</pattern><template>Please. Please take a seat.</template></category><category><pattern>— NICK  PLEASE  JUST SIT DOWN</pattern><template>— Well, it's all rather strange, he picks me up in his fancy yellow car, and he's going on and on about his life, — Please keep your voice down, — and the war and… — Everybody can hear you.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE MAKES IT LOOK SO— SO SPLENDID  DON'T YOU THINK  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Music! And then we can dance all night.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DID YOU GET THIS FROM</pattern><template>You might fool me, but you don't fool God!</template></category><category><pattern>NOT TODAY  IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>You know, old sport… I haven't used that pool once all summer.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  I KNOW YOUR WIFE</pattern><template>— Is that so?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Good night, old sport. Good night.</template></category><category><pattern>— NONSENSE  WE'RE GOING</pattern><template>First team, all American.</template></category><category><pattern>— REALLY</pattern><template>Shall we?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF THAT'S THE IDEA  YOU CAN COUNT ME OUT</pattern><template>See, nowadays people begin by sneering at family life and family institutions, and the next you'll know, we'll throw everything overboard, and we'll have intermarriage between black and white!</template></category><category><pattern>♪ HUNDRED  HUNDRED  HUNDRED DOLLAR BILLS  YEAH</pattern><template>— …hands off! Get your hands off me!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A SISSY</pattern><template>Live is something you dominate, Nick!</template></category><category><pattern>HERZOG  WE'RE TALKING  THANK YOU</pattern><template>She just needs time to think— — No, Jay… Daisy— She just needs time to think, she's going to call in the morning.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU</pattern><template>You're nothing but a goddamn coward!</template></category><category><pattern>— BUT HOW DO YOU LIVE HERE ALL ALONE</pattern><template>— Well I don't.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>— Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  OF COURSE YOU CAN</pattern><template>Of course you can.</template></category><category><pattern>HENRY  WHERE ARE YOU</pattern><template>Oui, Monsieur.</template></category><category><pattern>— IF YOU FORGIVE ME</pattern><template>You see… I happen to run a little— a little business on the side, a sort of side line. I mean, you understand what I'm saying, right?</template></category><category><pattern>— TOM  FUNNY SEEING YOU</pattern><template>— How have you been?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL MY LIFE… I WISH IT COULD ALWAYS BE LIKE THIS</pattern><template>It will be.</template></category><category><pattern>IN CASE YOU NEED TO TAKE DOWN ANY ADDRESSES</pattern><template>Please move aside. Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>— WELL I DON'T</pattern><template>I keep it always full of interesting celebrated people.</template></category><category><pattern>— DELIGHTED</pattern><template>Oh and Mr. Buchanan, the polo player.</template></category><category><pattern>GATSBY DISAPPEARED TO DEAL WITH A DISPUTE OF SOME SORT    DAISY WAITED    BUT GATSBY WAS UNABLE TO RETURN   WITH THESE HOT HEADED TYPES IN HERE  I RELY ON YOU</pattern><template>But you were not available.</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH I HAD DONE EVERYTHING ON EARTH WITH YOU</pattern><template>All my life… I wish it could always be like this.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL CALL YOU UP</pattern><template>Well, we rode in the hydroplane, and I attended two more of his parties.   Even made use of his beach.   But you know, doctor,   I realized that I knew absolutely nothing about Gatsby at all.   Until…  It's pretty, isn't it, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>— WELL  GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>— Good night.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY… HELLO   HELLO</pattern><template>Hello, is everything all right?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOT TO KEEP GOING UP</pattern><template>She has to go to Tom… and tell him that she never loved him.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE NEED EVER READ IT</pattern><template>You could always burn it.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YES</pattern><template>Listen, Nick. When she was born, Tom was… God knows where.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE</pattern><template>Slow down! Slow down!</template></category><category><pattern>A BIG REQUEST</pattern><template>Yes. Ms. Baker will explain everything when you take her to tea this afternoon.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M PERFECTLY WILLING</pattern><template>It's a marvelous idea.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM  THEY ARE  SHE IS</pattern><template>We're all different from you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  WE WERE BORN DIFFERENT</pattern><template>It's in our blood.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO DO ANY BUSINESS WITH WOLFSHEIM  I ASSURE YOU</pattern><template>It's a favor, Jay, just a favor.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU MUST BE CRAZY</pattern><template>— No, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHERE ARE WE GOING</pattern><template>— We're going on a holiday.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU DO…  SOMETHING HAPPENING</pattern><template>Why, I thought everybody knew.</template></category><category><pattern>EWING ​​IS A FUNNY GENIUS  HE CAN PLAY ANYTHING</pattern><template>Then I demand a Charleston.</template></category><category><pattern>THROWING YOUR LOT IN WITH THOSE SOCIAL CLIMBING PRIMITIVE NEW MONEY TYPES</pattern><template>My little shack's just a cardboard box at $80 a month.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW COULD YOU DO THAT</pattern><template>— Keep your voice down!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON BOYS  IT'S TOO LATE</pattern><template>Good night, gentlemen!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL CHAT LATER  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>— COME ON  YEAH</pattern><template>He's gonna sit on the side and watch? Uh?</template></category><category><pattern>CALL YOUR SISTER  SHE WILL LIKE HIM</pattern><template>No no no. Uh. That's alright, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT DAY WOULD SUIT YOU</pattern><template>I don't want to put you to any trouble.</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON  GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>I rang, I wrote, I implored.   But not a single one of the sparkling hundreds that enjoyed his hospitality,   attended the funeral.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE</pattern><template>Gatsby disappeared to deal with a dispute of some sort.   Daisy waited.   But Gatsby was unable to return.  With these hot headed types in here, I rely on you.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  HE SENT ME AN ACTUAL INVITATION</pattern><template>Seems I'm the only one.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SURE YOU WANT ME TO COME</pattern><template>Absolutely, old sport. Absolutely.</template></category><category><pattern>— A SPREE</pattern><template>— And in my heart I love— — I love her all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST TELL ME</pattern><template>Oh Nick, I'm sorry, I swore.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF THEM WAS IN THE CAR WITH HER</pattern><template>It was Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT… THIS WOMAN  SHE RUSHED OUT AT US</pattern><template>It all happened so quickly.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR MONEY  THAT'S IT</pattern><template>I have just as much as you, that means we're equal.</template></category><category><pattern>I IMAGINE HE'LL BE AT LUNCH TOO</pattern><template>Βy the time we reached the bridge, Ι was impossibly confused.   I didn't know what to think.   But the city seen from the Queensboro Bridge   is always the city seen for the first time…   In its first wild promise of all the mystery and the beauty in the world.   Anything can happen!   Now that we've slid over this bridge, I though…   Anything at all, even Gatsby, could happen.   Yes, absolutely.</template></category><category><pattern>TOM WAS FEELING THE HOT WHIPS OF PANIC    HIS MISTRESS AND WIFE  AN HOUR AGO SO SECURE    WERE BOTH SLIPPING FROM HIS CONTROL   I WISED UP TO SOMETHING FUNNY THESE LAST TWO DAYS</pattern><template>There she is. She's going West, whether she wants it or not.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT'S ME</pattern><template>…other affairs.  — I thought I told you not to call me here.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GLAD IT'S A GIRL</pattern><template>And I hope she'll be a fool.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S SPLENDID</pattern><template>Come on, you two.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>Why, what's the matter?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE HAD BEEN MUSIC FROM MY NEIGHBOR'S ALL SUMMER    IN HIS BLUE GARDENS  MEN AND GIRLS CAME AND WENT LIKE MOTHS    AMONG THE WHISPERINGS AND THE LAUGHTER AND THE STARS   — BREAKFAST</pattern><template>— Yes. Thank you, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>TOM  I'M NOT COMFORTABLE HERE</pattern><template>Daisy is my cousin.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAITED FOR A MOMENT LONGER</pattern><template>He knew his mind would never again be free to romp like…   the mind of God.   That falling in love would change his destiny…   for ever.  Αnd then I just let myself go.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BE CAREFUL NOW  YOU'RE TURNING INTO A REAL JAZZ HOUND  COMMISSIONER</pattern><template>That's the commissioner back there.</template></category><category><pattern>WILSON</pattern><template>Who owns the yellow car?</template></category><category><pattern>— I DON'T KNOW  SHE WOULDN'T TELL ME</pattern><template>But it was too late.</template></category><category><pattern>HE MUST KNOW WHAT A SMALL TOWN IS</pattern><template>Listen to me. He is of no use to us if Detroit is his idea of ​​a small town, you understand?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  WHAT'S THE MATTER</pattern><template>I don't know, I'm… I all run down.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D LIKE TO KNOW WHO HE IS</pattern><template>What he does.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T HER FAULT  D'YOU SEE</pattern><template>No one must know that Daisy was driving.</template></category><category><pattern>— NICKY  STAY</pattern><template>— I have to work early.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M FINE</pattern><template>You knew her, eh?</template></category><category><pattern>— NICK WANTED TO GO INTO TOWN</pattern><template>Right, Nick? To the Yale club.</template></category><category><pattern>BE CAREFUL FOR THE SNAKE CHARMER  MR  MCLENNAHAN</pattern><template>Is all this made entirely from your own imagination?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DON'T</pattern><template>Tom's got some woman in New York.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY SIR  PHILADELPHIA ON THE PHONE</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>A YEAR LATER  TOM BUCHANAN OF CHICAGO SWEPT IN AND STOLE HER AWAY</pattern><template>He gave her a string of pearls worth 350,000 dollars.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MAYBE</pattern><template>A guy like that, who knows?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE BRIGHT  PRECIOUS THINGS FADE SO FAST</pattern><template>And they don't come back.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT</pattern><template>Klipspringer.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ABOUT THE BUTLER'S NOSE</pattern><template>Things went from bad to worse.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>No, you see… she never loved you.</template></category><category><pattern>D'YOU KNOW HIM</pattern><template>I live right next door to him.</template></category><category><pattern>MISS BAKER'S A HONEST SPORTSWOMAN  SHE WOULDN'T DO ANYTHING THAT WASN'T ALRIGHT</pattern><template>Pull over! Pull over to the curb!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WOMEN GET THESE NOTIONS</pattern><template>Daisy?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THAT'S VERY KIND OF YOU</pattern><template>Lovely to see you again, Miss Baker.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WE'LL MAKE PLANS  TO GO AWAY TOGETHER</pattern><template>Uh, Daisy, she— She just needs time to think things through.</template></category><category><pattern>— OUT  OUT YOU GO</pattern><template>Tell Walter Chase. He keeps his mouth shut or he doesn't get a penny.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS THE DAY I GOT MY NEW ENGLISH GOLF SHOES</pattern><template>Daisy was by far the most popular girl with the officers from Camp Taylor.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Well, I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>COME BACK IN AN HOUR  FERDIE</pattern><template>His name is Ferdie.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU SPEAK TO HER  TELL HER THE FUNERAL'S TOMORROW</pattern><template>I'm sorry, Monsieur.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL BE MARRIED THERE</pattern><template>See… See, Daisy and I are gonna start over just as if it were 5 years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHY WE CAN'T JUST HAVE FUN LIKE THAT AGAIN</pattern><template>Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE SOME ROOM BACK THERE</pattern><template>If you have no business, clear out!</template></category><category><pattern>— I HAVE TO WORK EARLY</pattern><template>— Nonsense.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M IN THE PHONE BOOK</pattern><template>I'll call you up.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE CARE OF YOU</pattern><template>I'll make some calls.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  SLAGLE IS HERE</pattern><template>No, not now!</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE GOTTEN ALL THESE THINGS FOR HER  I'VE GOTTEN ALL THESE THINGS FOR HER  NOW SHE JUST… SHE JUST WANTS TO RUN AWAY</pattern><template>She even wants to leave that.</template></category><category><pattern>— ALRIGHT</pattern><template>Come with me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PRINCE</pattern><template>The spy? The murderer?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEE IF THERE'S ANY COMMOTION</pattern><template>Would you?</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY  TELL HIM</pattern><template>I never loved him?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DID YOU MEET HIM</pattern><template>At a… at a party.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S JUST A FRONT FOR WOLFSHEIM  A GANGSTER  TO GET HIS CLAWS INTO RESPECTABLE FOLKS LIKE WALTER CHASE</pattern><template>The only respectable thing about you, old sport, is your money.</template></category><category><pattern>— SHE IS EMBARRASSED</pattern><template>— Yes. Just as much as you are.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT A GENTLEMAN</pattern><template>From one of the finest families in the Midwest.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GO AWAY  GET OUT OF TOWN</pattern><template>Get some rest. Don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE TRIES TO BOTHER HER ABOUT THAT UNPLEASANTNESS THIS AFTERNOON  IF HE TRIES TO BOTHER HER  IF HE TRIES ANY BRUTALITY— — WAIT</pattern><template>— on her, whatsoever, — Tom— Tom won't touch her, — He's not even thinking about her, Jay.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WOMAN YOU RAN DOWN IS DEAD  JAY</pattern><template>I thought so, I… I told Daisy that I thought so.</template></category><category><pattern>— NICKY  HE'S A MAD MAN</pattern><template>— I can't help you!</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  THERE ARE PEOP— HULLO  OH CHESTER  THIS MUST BE THE COUSIN</pattern><template>Oh, you are adorable!</template></category><category><pattern>WITH A FRIEND  WITH SOMEONE LIKE YOU  HE'D NEVER SO MUCH AS LOOK AT YOUR WIFE</pattern><template>— I'm not married.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU— YOU LOVED— YOU LOVED ME  TOO</pattern><template>You loved me… Even that is a lie! She did not know that you were alive!</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY  I BEG YOUR PARDON</pattern><template>I had the wrong man.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE MATTER</pattern><template>You run out of gas?</template></category><category><pattern>HUM… I'M NOT SURE NOW'S A GOOD TIME</pattern><template>I'm just going. Uh.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S GONNA TAKE A SWING</pattern><template>— Get ready. Aim. Fore!</template></category><category><pattern>MY NEIGHBOR… YEAH</pattern><template>When I think about it, the history of the summer really began   the night I drove over to my cousin Daisy's for diner.   She lived across the bay in old moneyed East Egg.   Her husband was heir to one of America's wealthiest families.   His name was Tom Buchanan.   When we were at Yale together, he'd been a sporting star.   Now his glory days were behind him, and he contented himself with—  — Telephone, Monsieur Buchanan.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE MORNING OF THE WEDDING  DAISY RECEIVED A LETTER</pattern><template>Tell them Daisy's changed her mind!</template></category><category><pattern>MRS  BUCHANAN</pattern><template>— Charmed.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M RIGHT ACROSS FROM YOU</pattern><template>Right there.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS IN THE LETTER</pattern><template>The reason why after the war, I… I hadn't been able to return.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I CAN KEEP MYSELF AMUSED</pattern><template>In case you need to take down any addresses.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT ME</pattern><template>Always a pleasure to meet a Buchanan.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE IT MATTERS  DAISY  I'M GONNA TAKE BETTER CARE OF YOU FROM NOW ON</pattern><template>You're not taking care of Daisy anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN</pattern><template>The car's waiting.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE</pattern><template>Leave us alone.</template></category><category><pattern>RUN AWAY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>GATSBY WAS SENT OFF TO WAR</pattern><template>When the war ended, Daisy waited, but for some unknown reason, Gatsby couldn't return.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU HAVE NO BUSINESS  CLEAR OUT</pattern><template>Sir?</template></category><category><pattern>— AH  DOES IT</pattern><template>— Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>OH YES  I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU WENT TO OXFORD</pattern><template>Uh yes, I went there.</template></category><category><pattern>I WONDER WHERE THE DEVIL HE MET HER</pattern><template>— I'll find you.</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  EUROPE</pattern><template>Paris, Venice, Rome, Vienna, Zurich, Helsinki, Moscow, Istanbul, collecting jewels —chiefly rubies— hunting big game, painting a little— things for myself only.</template></category><category><pattern>WE— WE COULD TAKE MY CAR IF YOU WANT</pattern><template>— Oh, uh… It's too late, tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOODNESS</pattern><template>I can't believe it.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  I'M CERTAINLY GLAD TO SEE YOU AS WELL</pattern><template>We've… we've uh… We've met before.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A LITTLE BOY</pattern><template>You're being rude, Daisy's in there all alone, and you—  Looking over my story so far,   I'm reminded that, for the second time that summer,   I was guarding other people's secrets.   Once again, I was within… and without.  It stopped raining.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO NO  NO  NO NO NO</pattern><template>Uh. This isn't the man, Meyer.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A GODDAMN COWARD</pattern><template>Keep your voice down, please!</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WEPT</pattern><template>I'm glad it's a girl.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A GAMBLER</pattern><template>He's the man who fixed the 1919 World's Series.</template></category><category><pattern>HAPPY BIRTHDAY</pattern><template>Thirty. The promise of a decade of loneliness.   The formidable stroke of thirty died away…   as Gatsby and Daisy drove on through the cooling twilight…   towards death.  Don't you lie to me!</template></category><category><pattern>MR  CARRAWAY  THIS IS MY GOOD FRIEND  MR  MEYER WOLFSHEIM</pattern><template>A wonderful pleasure, Mr. Carraway.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY JUST LEFT</pattern><template>She asked me to tell you she had a wonderful time.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY'S ALWAYS TALKING ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>— Really?</template></category><category><pattern>— ON HER  WHATSOEVER  — TOM— TOM WON'T TOUCH HER  — HE'S NOT EVEN THINKING ABOUT HER  JAY</pattern><template>— I don't trust him.</template></category><category><pattern>A BIG YELLOW CAR</pattern><template>The damn thing came out of nowhere.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  JAY  YOU'RE UNDER ARREST</pattern><template>You be careful now, you're turning into a real jazz hound, commissioner!</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU— HAVE YOU GOT EVERYTHING YOU NEED</pattern><template>Perhaps more flowers.</template></category><category><pattern>TO THE RIGHT  IN THE LIVING ROOM</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU WON'T SEEM SO STUPID TO YOURSELF</pattern><template>Wait a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  STAND BACK  PLEASE</pattern><template>Oh God.</template></category><category><pattern>— I SUPPOSE YOU CAN  YES</pattern><template>We'll meet you at the Plaza.</template></category><category><pattern>HE READS DEEP BOOKS WITH LONG WORDS IN THEM</pattern><template>It's been proved. Scientific.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT'S A STRANGE COINCIDENCE</pattern><template>— What is?</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO NO  UH  THAT'S ALRIGHT  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Catherine's said to be very good looking, by people who oughta know.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M LEAVING</pattern><template>Ah, don't be silly, it's just two minutes to four.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW YOU'LL HAVE TO REFOLD EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM</pattern><template>You'll ruin them!</template></category><category><pattern>SADLY  ALL OF THEM ARE DEAD NOW</pattern><template>I was brought up in America, but educated at Oxford because all my ancestors had been educated there for many years, you see, it's a family tradition.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE'S COMING TO TEA  IT'S TOO— IT'S HER</pattern><template>Is this absolutely where you live, my dearest one?</template></category><category><pattern>A GUY LIKE THAT  WHO KNOWS</pattern><template>He didn't have to kill her.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  I'M ASKING YOU TO— — GET OFF ME</pattern><template>I'm fine!</template></category><category><pattern>DARLING… IT'S TIME TO TELL TOM</pattern><template>Come on boys, it's too late!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  GOODBYE</pattern><template>Jay?</template></category><category><pattern>— I KNOW ALL ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>— I see.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STILL KNOW I'M A CHAMPION GOLFER  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>— Great!</template></category><category><pattern>— AS IF IT MATTERED TO YOU</pattern><template>Of course it matters. Daisy, I'm gonna take better care of you from now on.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE RIGHT BACK</pattern><template>You know, a lot of these newly rich people are just filthy booze makers.</template></category><category><pattern>NICK  NICK</pattern><template>Nick!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  A PLEASURE</pattern><template>— Uh, Nick's a writer.</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  EVERYTHING'S JUST FINE</pattern><template>At four o'clock, she— she came at the window.</template></category><category><pattern>OH NO  THAT'S MR  DAN CODY  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>He's dead now.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  GATSBY WAS ALWAYS WATCHING ME</pattern><template>And how did you know that?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS DAISY</pattern><template>No, I… You see, after we left New York, she was… she was very nervous, she thought… that driving would steady her.</template></category><category><pattern>LEAVE US ALONE</pattern><template>Wilson.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I CAN'T COMPLAIN</pattern><template>So uh… When're ya gonna sell me that car?</template></category><category><pattern>— PLAY BALL</pattern><template>— Ain't we good enough for you?</template></category><category><pattern>— KEEP IT OPEN FOR A PERSONAL CALL</pattern><template>— A personal call? Of course.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK THERE'S MUCH GAS  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Nope, plenty o' gas.</template></category><category><pattern>— TOWN</pattern><template>— I'll be right back.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOVED ME… EVEN THAT IS A LIE  SHE DID NOT KNOW THAT YOU WERE ALIVE</pattern><template>There are things between Daisy and me, Gatsby, that you'll never know!</template></category><category><pattern>— I SEE</pattern><template>— Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>WE COULD TAKE A PLUNGE IN THE SWIMMING POOL  I HAVEN'T MADE USE OF IT ALL SUMMER</pattern><template>— I must go to bed.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL PUT A BET ON FOR YOU  JAY</pattern><template>We'll have the lobster. It's decorated with truffles and fine herbs.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED MONEY REAL BAD</pattern><template>— What?</template></category><category><pattern>GATSBY LOOKED IN THAT MOMENT AS IF HE HAD KILLED A MAN   MY… MY SINCEREST… MY SINCEREST APOLOGIES</pattern><template>I seem to… have lost my temper.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE RODE IN THE HYDROPLANE  AND I ATTENDED TWO MORE OF HIS PARTIES    EVEN MADE USE OF HIS BEACH    BUT YOU KNOW  DOCTOR    I REALIZED THAT I KNEW ABSOLUTELY NOTHING ABOUT GATSBY AT ALL    UNTIL…  IT'S PRETTY  ISN'T IT  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Haven't you ever seen it before?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE COMMISSIONER BACK THERE</pattern><template>Mr. Gatsby! You table is ready.</template></category><category><pattern>SONOFABITCH DIDN'T EVEN STOP HIS CAR</pattern><template>Hey! I saw it. It was a yellow car.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TALK SO LOUD</pattern><template>You're acting like a little boy!</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I DIDN'T KNOW DAISY THEN</pattern><template>And I'll be damned if I know how you got within a mile of her, unless you brought the groceries to the back door, but all the rest of that is a goddamn lie!</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULDN'T ASK TOO MUCH OF HER</pattern><template>— Wouldn't ask too much?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  THAT'S FROM MONTENEGRO</pattern><template>Major Jay Gatsby, for Valour Extraordinary .</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY ONE WHO CARED    AFTER GATSBY'S DEATH  NEW YORK WAS HAUNTED FOR ME    THAT CITY…   MY ONCE GOLDEN SHIMMERING MIRAGE…   NOW MADE ME SICK    ON MY LAST NIGHT IN NEW YORK    I RETURNED TO THAT HUGE INCOHERENT HOUSE ONCE MORE    WOLFSHEIM ASSOCIATES HAD CLEANED IT OUT   HE THREW ALL THOSE PARTIES  HOPING SHE WOULD WANDER IN ONE NIGHT</pattern><template>It's like an amusement park!</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  PLEASE TAKE A SEAT</pattern><template>Come on, Daisy.</template></category><category><pattern>I CHANGED MY MIND  YOU BRUTE</pattern><template>Oh come on, we'll get a great big room at the Plaza.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE BEEN SEEING HIM… FOR FIVE YEARS</pattern><template>No, no. No, not seeing.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REMIND ME OF A ROSE</pattern><template>An absolute rose, doesn't he?</template></category><category><pattern>— TAKE CARE OF MY FRIEND</pattern><template>Mr. Warden. May I ask you… Look who's here!</template></category><category><pattern>— IS EVERYTHING ALRIGHT</pattern><template>— Yes. Everything's just fine.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT YOU  MY LOVELY</pattern><template>Daisy Buchanan. The Golden Girl.   A breathless warmth flowed from her.   A promise that there was no one else in the world she so wanted to see.  Do they miss me in Chicago?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I HAVE A SECOND SIGHT SOMETIMES THAT TELLS ME WHAT TO DO</pattern><template>I've made a small investigation into this fellow.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU THINK I COME HERE TO ADMIRE THE VIEW</pattern><template>Sorry uh, I'm sick.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT I MIGHT SEE YOU HERE</pattern><template>Hello!</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT YOU ARE  I'LL KNOW YOU NEXT TIME  MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>— Excuse me!</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE HERE WAITING AND HOPING  FOR EVERY LONG DREAM OF YOU TO COME TRUE   EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Sir, Slagle's in Detroit.</template></category><category><pattern>THINGS WENT FROM BAD TO WORSE</pattern><template>I hate that word,  hulking .</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU</pattern><template>— Won't you come in, Nick.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HARD TO MAKE HER UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>— You mean about the party?</template></category><category><pattern>NICK  WOULD YOU MIND TERRIBLY</pattern><template>Of course.</template></category><category><pattern>BY WHICH I MEAN  NO ONE EXCEPT ME   EVER RECEIVED AN ACTUAL INVITATION TO GATSBY'S    YOU SEE  THE REST OF NEW YORK SIMPLY CAME UNINVITED    THE WHOLE CITY PACKED INTO AUTOMOBILES AND ALL WEEKENDS  EVERY WEEKEND    ENDED UP AT GATSBY'S    AND I MEAN  EVERYONE FROM EVERY WALK OF LIFE AND EVERY CORNER OF NEW YORK CITY    THIS KALEIDOSCOPIC CARNIVAL SPILLED THROUGH GATSBY'S DOOR   — OUT OF THE WAY</pattern><template>— My invitation.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE WILL CONFIRM ALL I HAVE TOLD YOU  AND VOUCH FOR MY GOOD CHARACTER</pattern><template>Oh, I'm sure that's not necessary.</template></category><category><pattern>— ΑU REVOIR</pattern><template>I… Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>— AIN'T WE GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>THERE SHE IS  SHE'S GOING WEST  WHETHER SHE WANTS IT OR NOT</pattern><template>— What do I owe you?</template></category><category><pattern>I UNDERSTAND  I UNDERSTAND YOU</pattern><template>It was my fault!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT SUITS ME</pattern><template>Why did I have to come alone?</template></category><category><pattern>OH NICK  I'M SORRY  I SWORE</pattern><template>I swore I wouldn't tell.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  THE MAN IN THE PINK SUIT WENT TO OXFORD</pattern><template>Tom!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOUR WIFE DOES</pattern><template>Tom was feeling the hot whips of panic.   His mistress and wife, an hour ago so secure,   were both slipping from his control.  I wised up to something funny these last two days.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  NICK</pattern><template>Mr. Gatsby, would you be good enough to take my coupé, and I'll drive everyone else in your circus wagon.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  MR  BUCHANAN  I WANTED TO BE CLOSE… DAISY AND I HAVE— — IT'S SO HOT</pattern><template>Everything's so confused!</template></category><category><pattern>GET DRESSED  WE'RE GOING TO LUNCH</pattern><template>— Oh, well.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE HAS TO GO TO TOM… AND TELL HIM THAT SHE NEVER LOVED HIM</pattern><template>I just need to give her more time, old sport. More time.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  I… — HI</pattern><template>— Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME  I'LL BE RIGHT BACK</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ONLY 32  I MIGHT STILL BE A GREAT MAN IF I CAN FORGET THAT I ONCE LOST DAISY  BUT… MY LIFE  OLD SPORT  MY LIFE… MY LIFE HAS GOT TO BE LIKE THIS</pattern><template>It's got to keep going up.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REMEMBER THIS LETTER  DO YOU</pattern><template>We can't lose each other.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHEN CODY DIED  GATSBY WAS CHEATED OF HIS INHERITANCE BY CODY'S FAMILY   HE'D BEEN LEFT WITH THE ABILITY TO PLAY THE GENTLEMAN  BUT HE WAS ONCE AGAIN DIRT POOR</pattern><template>By mid summer, Gatsby was front page news.   Where did the money come from?   That's what the whole of New York wanted to know.   And it was the same question on Tom's mind,   when he accompanied Daisy to one of Gatsby's…   …glittering parties.  Take a look around.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE… SEE  DAISY AND I ARE GONNA START OVER JUST AS IF IT WERE 5 YEARS AGO</pattern><template>I wouldn't ask too much of her.</template></category><category><pattern>— MYRTLE  BABY</pattern><template>— Stop!</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT IS THIS</pattern><template>— Daisy, please!</template></category><category><pattern>— NO</pattern><template>I just remembered… today is my birthday.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  NOT SEEING</pattern><template>Not seeing, we couldn't but… both of us loved each other all that time, didn't we?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  THIS IS CRAZY</pattern><template>We gotta get out of here.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM YOUR PERFECT IRRESISTIBLE IMAGINATION</pattern><template>I wonder where the devil he met her.</template></category><category><pattern>— DAISY  DARLING  LOOK AT ME</pattern><template>— Go on.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS THE ONLY ONE</pattern><template>By which I mean, no one except me   ever received an actual invitation to Gatsby's.   You see, the rest of New York simply came uninvited.   The whole city packed into automobiles and all weekends, every weekend,   ended up at Gatsby's.   And I mean, everyone from every walk of life and every corner of New York city.   This kaleidoscopic carnival spilled through Gatsby's door.  — Out of the way!</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID A SMALL TOWN</pattern><template>He must know what a small town is.</template></category><category><pattern>HE TALKED A LOT ABOUT THE PAST    AS IF HE WANTED TO RECOVER SOMETHING   IF I C— IF I COULD JUST GET BACK TO THE START</pattern><template>If I could just get back to the start… I could find it again.</template></category><category><pattern>A BUCKET OF ICE  A BOTTLE OF WHISKEY AND IT WILL BE FUN</pattern><template>Come on. It was your idea.</template></category><category><pattern>CHARGE</pattern><template>Gatsby was sent off to war.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE SHOULD GO</pattern><template>— Just you, me and Daddy.</template></category><category><pattern>SENATOR  I'LL CATCH YOU UP LATER  PERHAPS AT THE CRAP TABLE</pattern><template>I'd rather not be the polo player.</template></category><category><pattern>— TO THE LEFT</pattern><template>Yeah, we'll pile that stuff in the garage, it's going back to town.</template></category><category><pattern>— GO ON</pattern><template>— Daisy.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  JAY  YOU WANT TOO MUCH</pattern><template>I love you now, isn't that enough?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT HAS  HASN'T IT</pattern><template>What do you think of that, Daisy?</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER</pattern><template>Please don't.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT WAS TOO LATE</pattern><template>That day at five o'clock, Daisy Fay married Tom Buchanan with more pomp and circumstance Louisville had ever seen.</template></category><category><pattern>— THANK YOU  SIR</pattern><template>You see… She has to tell Tom that she never loved him.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU LIVE ON LONG ISLAND TOO</pattern><template>— I live in West Egg.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TALK  I WANNA HEAR WHAT HAPPENS</pattern><template>I don't care what you do…  Something happening?</template></category><category><pattern>— HI</pattern><template>— Mr. Buchanan. Candy?</template></category><category><pattern>— KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN</pattern><template>— What's wrong with you?</template></category><category><pattern>— …SHOULD ALL COME AT ONCE</pattern><template>— Do you hear yourself?</template></category><category><pattern>— DID YOU GET AN INVITATION</pattern><template>— People aren't invited to Gatsby's.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU… GET ON THE NEXT TRAIN</pattern><template>— Now?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS THERE AT A PARTY ABOUT A MONTH AGO</pattern><template>A man named Gatsbys.</template></category><category><pattern>PROMISE ME</pattern><template>Jay.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST LOST MY TEMPER  THAT'S ALL</pattern><template>He began talking excitedly.   But with every word, Daisy was drawing further and further into herself.  …to go to your parents' house in Louisville.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  REALLY I CAN'T</pattern><template>Hey! You wanna embarrass Myrtle?</template></category><category><pattern>— IT'S BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>— It's a custom Wurlitzer.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE MADE A SMALL INVESTIGATION INTO THIS FELLOW</pattern><template>And you found he was an Oxford man?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T QUITE KNOW WHERE TO START</pattern><template>You see, I didn't realize until the other night that I'd met Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>— JUST SITTING HERE</pattern><template>— Yes, I see that!</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE THE PHONE BROUGHT DOWN TO THE POOL</pattern><template>I have to go, Jay.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIVE JUST NEXT DOOR</pattern><template>Uh, he sent me an actual invitation.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT GATSBY</pattern><template>Madame, the dîner is servi.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  IF ANYTHING IS NOT YOUR LIKING  I'LL CHANGE IT</pattern><template>It's perfect.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU MUST KNOW GATSBY</pattern><template>Gatsby?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU SEE… SHE NEVER LOVED YOU</pattern><template>She only married you because I was poor and she was tired of waiting, it was a terrible, terrible mistake, but in her heart, in her heart she never loved any one but me.</template></category><category><pattern>IT ALL MAKES SENSE</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO TELL ME WHAT KIND OF CAR IT WAS</pattern><template>I know what kind of car it was.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT'S FUNNY</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SPEAK HER NAME WHEN— OH MY GOD  YOU ARE CRAZY</pattern><template>You're a whore!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THAT'S ALL</pattern><template>You're crazy!</template></category><category><pattern>— THANK YOU  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>— Lemon or sugar?</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU</pattern><template>Thank you, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>— SHE DOES THOUGH</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SUCH A BRUTE</pattern><template>— Okay, you're ready for your close up?</template></category><category><pattern>— BUSINESSMAN</pattern><template>— May I introduce Senator Gulick.</template></category><category><pattern>NONE OF THIS HAS… ANY CONSEQUENCE  I— DAISY</pattern><template>Daisy, talk to me, darling.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>WILSON  I JUST— I JUST GOT HERE FROM NEW YORK</pattern><template>Enough! Hey, Wilson!</template></category><category><pattern>IT ALL HAPPENED SO QUICKLY</pattern><template>It wasn't her fault, d'you see?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THEY HAVE ALREADY DEPARTED</pattern><template>Please. I know that she would want to be there, she would— If you'd just get a message to her, let me talk to her, please.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A TERRIBLE  TERRIBLE MISTAKE</pattern><template>You're just embarrassed, Daisy's embarrassed too.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE THINGS BETWEEN DAISY AND ME  GATSBY  THAT YOU'LL NEVER KNOW</pattern><template>Things that neither of us can ever forget!</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE WAY HE LOOKED AT HER  IS THE WAY ALL GIRLS WANT TO BE LOOKED AT</pattern><template>So. Tell me what happened.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I COULD JUST GET BACK TO THE START… I COULD FIND IT AGAIN</pattern><template>Some vision of himself that he'd put into loving Daisy.   One night in Louisville, five years ago,   Gatsby found himself at Daisy's house by colossal accident.  So I went to her house first, with some of the officers from Camp Taylor.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  NO NO</pattern><template>No, she didn't like it, she… she did not have a good time, I… feel so far away from her now.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  LET'S GO HOME</pattern><template>See, he ​​and this Wolfsheim, they bought up a lot of drugstores, and sold bootleg alcohol over the counter.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  THE EVIL GERMAN KING</pattern><template>— Really?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE'S A LOT OF CLIPPINGS I COLLECT</pattern><template>About you.</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  JUST AS MUCH AS YOU ARE</pattern><template>Don't talk so loud!</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY  I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE AN OXFORD MAN</pattern><template>No. Not exactly, no.</template></category><category><pattern>A MAN NAMED GATSBYS</pattern><template>D'you know him?</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FACE IS FAMILIAR  WEREN'T YOU IN THE THIRD DIVISION DURING THE WAR</pattern><template>Uh, yes, the ninth battalion.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST UNDERSTAND THAT I LIKE ALL THINGS THAT ARE MODERN</pattern><template>Press the orange, it all comes out there.</template></category><category><pattern>— THE TIME THAT SUITS YOU</pattern><template>Well, that's very kind of you.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SPY  THE MURDERER</pattern><template>I cannot find anyone who knows anything real about Mr. Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH JAY  IT'S SO GRAND</pattern><template>— You like it?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL GO AWAY</pattern><template>Just go away, get out of town.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALLY MUST GO</pattern><template>Myrtle, get everybody a drink before they fall asleep.</template></category><category><pattern>— HEY  WHERE ARE YOU GOING</pattern><template>— Jump!</template></category><category><pattern>— WE HAVEN'T MET FOR MANY YEARS</pattern><template>— Five years, next November.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT'S TRUE</pattern><template>— He kills for fun.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE A LITTLE RESPECT</pattern><template>If you don't have a legitimate reason to be in the building, I want you outside!</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT AN INVITATION</pattern><template>I was the only one.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT REALLY  NO</pattern><template>I gotta ask you to step back, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>— SURE</pattern><template>You must know the faces of many people you've heard of.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SHOW YOU  I'LL SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE</pattern><template>— Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THE WAR ENDED  DAISY WAITED  BUT FOR SOME UNKNOWN REASON  GATSBY COULDN'T RETURN</pattern><template>A year later, Tom Buchanan of Chicago swept in and stole her away.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS BROUGHT UP IN AMERICA  BUT EDUCATED AT OXFORD BECAUSE ALL MY ANCESTORS HAD BEEN EDUCATED THERE FOR MANY YEARS  YOU SEE  IT'S A FAMILY TRADITION</pattern><template>The way he spoke! No wonder people thought he was lying.  After my family died, I came into a great deal of money.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THIS  HUH  THIS MR  GATSBY YOU SPOKE OF  HE'S MY NEIGHBOR</pattern><template>Don't talk. I wanna hear what happens.</template></category><category><pattern>MYRTLE  MYRTLE</pattern><template>Myrtle Turtle!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I READ SOMEWHERE THAT THE SUN IS GETTING HOTTER EVERY YEAR</pattern><template>Wait a minute. It's the opposite.</template></category><category><pattern>PAY MY RESPECTS TO YOUR BOSS</pattern><template>Hey, Jay! You're under arrest!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNEW HER  EH</pattern><template>Not really. No.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>This was his opportunity, and he seized it.  And I decided right then and there, to call myself Jay Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  TOM  I CAN'T STAND IT ANYMORE</pattern><template>Why don't you two start on home, in Mr. Gatsby's car.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GIRL WITH HIM WAS A CHAMBERMAID AT THE SANTA BARBARA HOTEL</pattern><template>It got into all the papers.</template></category><category><pattern>— I CAN'T HELP YOU</pattern><template>You know you'll have to refold every single one of them!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WON'T FIND HIM</pattern><template>This house… and everything in it are all part of an elaborate disguise.</template></category><category><pattern>— HE KILLS FOR FUN</pattern><template>— Free of charge.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO THANKS</pattern><template>— It's only half past nine.</template></category><category><pattern>I SHOULD HAVE TOLD HIM WHAT I HAD JUST SEEN  BUT…   ALL I COULD MANAGE WAS:  YOU KNOW JAY  WITH EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED  YOU OUGHT TO GO AWAY</pattern><template>Tonight. They'll trace your car.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME SIR  MR  GATSBY  I'M GONNA DRAIN THE POOL TODAY  BEFORE THE LEAVES START FALLING IN</pattern><template>Not today.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT</pattern><template>— You want any?</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER BRINGS YOU EASE</pattern><template>A memory. A thought. A place.</template></category><category><pattern>OH AND MR  BUCHANAN  THE POLO PLAYER</pattern><template>No, not me.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE BACK  CLEAR THE SPACE HERE</pattern><template>Have a little respect!</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT A MONTH AGO</pattern><template>That's right!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL RUIN THEM</pattern><template>Jay, stop it!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK SO COOL</pattern><template>He always looks so cool.</template></category><category><pattern>I— I HEARD YOU FIRED ALL YOUR SERVANTS</pattern><template>Daisy comes over sometimes in the afternoon, I wanted people who wouldn't gossip until we decide what we're going to do.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T HELP WHAT'S PAST</pattern><template>I did love him once— but I loved you too.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S ABSOLUTELY NOT TO KNOW</pattern><template>You're just supposed to invite her over, so he can happen to pass by.</template></category><category><pattern>— NICK  KEEP FILMING</pattern><template>She's gonna take a swing.</template></category><category><pattern>— CHESTER MCKEE  PLEASURE TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>— Nick Carraway.</template></category><category><pattern>— ANYTHING</pattern><template>Whatever brings you ease.</template></category><category><pattern>COME HOME</pattern><template>I'll be here waiting and hoping, for every long dream of you to come true.  Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF GAME ARE YOU AND GATSBY PLAYING AT</pattern><template>— This gentleman will be joining— — Excuse me, one moment.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ALWAYS LOOKS SO COOL</pattern><template>Like the advertisement of the man in Times Square.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS BRINGING YOU THE COUPÉ</pattern><template>Sit down, sit down!</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S DEAD NOW</pattern><template>He used to be my best friend many years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>—  …LIKE A GENTLEMAN  — JAY GATSBY</pattern><template>She looks well, don't she!</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE ALL DIFFERENT FROM YOU</pattern><template>You see, we were born different.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  IT WAS AN OPPORTUNITY THEY GAVE TO SOME OF US OFFICERS WHO— WHO FOUGHT IN THE WAR</pattern><template>I wanted to get up and slap Gatsby on the back.  I'll make you a drink, Tom.</template></category><category><pattern>— I JUST HAVE TO POP INTO TOWN</pattern><template>— Town?</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  THANK YOU  — DARLING  THANK YOU</pattern><template>— Thank you, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>SELF CONTROL</pattern><template>Oh! I suppose the latest thing is to sit back and let Mr. Nobody from Nowhere make love to your wife.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS MY FAULT</pattern><template>It was my fault, this woman, she rushed out at us as if she was— See, she was trying to speak to us, it all happened so quickly!</template></category><category><pattern>— ABOUT THINGS</pattern><template>About the future.</template></category><category><pattern>'OLD SPORT'  WHERE DID YOU PICK IT UP</pattern><template>Now see here, Tom, if you're gonna make personal remarks, I won't stay here a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I WAS JUST HAVING LUNCH WITH MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>Can I help you, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU TWO START ON HOME  IN MR  GATSBY'S CAR</pattern><template>— Daisy, darling, look at me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE CAUSING A ROW</pattern><template>Please have a little self control.</template></category><category><pattern>MYRTLE  WHERE ARE YOU</pattern><template>Stop! Stop!</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF YOU SEE HER  I'LL BE LOOKING FOR HER  YOU TELL HER</pattern><template>Remember how much fun we had?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW OLD SPORT  ABOUT MISS BAKER AND THAT— THAT REQUEST WE SPOKE OF— — NICK</pattern><template>Nick!</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT'S FUNNY</pattern><template>— What's funny?</template></category><category><pattern>— TEA</pattern><template>— Yes, thank you, — Darling, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>— INDIAN COTTON</pattern><template>— Stop it, Jay!</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  SLAGLE'S IN DETROIT</pattern><template>I can't talk now, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>DOMINATE</pattern><template>Hello, Wilson. How's business?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'LL WALK YOU OUT</pattern><template>— Well, I'll call you up.</template></category><category><pattern>OH NO  MY NERVES ARE FINE  THANKS</pattern><template>I had been drunk just twice in my life.   And the second time was that afternoon.   That night in the hidden flat that Tom kept for Myrtle,   we were buoyed by a sort of chemical madness.   A willingness of the heart that burst thunderously upon us all.   And suddenly, I began to like New York.  This is better than the Yale club!</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT YOU TO GET THE WRONG IMPRESSION FROM ALL THESE— FROM ALL THESE BIZARRE ACCUSATIONS YOU MUST BE HEARING</pattern><template>A pack of lies, I guarantee.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T  I'M NOT ONE OF THOSE MODELS</pattern><template>But you can, if you want.</template></category><category><pattern>COME WITH ME</pattern><template>Coming through, please.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I ENJOYED LOOKING AT HER</pattern><template>I've been lying on that sofa for as long as I can remember.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S TAKE A LOOK</pattern><template>— Oh, must we?</template></category><category><pattern>HE KNEW HIS MIND WOULD NEVER AGAIN BE FREE TO ROMP LIKE…   THE MIND OF GOD    THAT FALLING IN LOVE WOULD CHANGE HIS DESTINY…   FOR EVER   ΑND THEN I JUST LET MYSELF GO</pattern><template>She blossomed for him like a flower…   and the incarnation was complete.  I knew it was a great mistake for a man like me to fall in love.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW WHAT KIND OF CAR IT WAS</pattern><template>— Wilson. Wilson, pull yourself together!</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON IN THERE  TALK TO CATHERINE</pattern><template>Tom, I'm not comfortable here.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DOORS  CLOSE THEM</pattern><template>Allez!</template></category><category><pattern>SO I STOPPED</pattern><template>I stopped, and I… I waited.</template></category><category><pattern>— WELL  I'LL CALL YOU UP</pattern><template>— Please do, old sport. Please do.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>Blue.</template></category><category><pattern>— OPEN THE GATES</pattern><template>I had the gates brought in from a castle in Normandy.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL BE ALRIGHT</pattern><template>— Hello, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I FIRST MADE THE PLEASURE OF MR</pattern><template>Gatsby's acquaintance just after the war, I knew I'd discovered a man of fine breeding.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR I AM THE MYSTERIOUS MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>You won't find him.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  BUT HERE I AM TANTALIZING YOU  AND I SWORE I WOULDN'T TELL</pattern><template>Just tell me.</template></category><category><pattern>— SIR  MY INVITATION</pattern><template>— This way!</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT UP WITH ME</pattern><template>The sun's almost up.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW A SINGLE PERSON THAT SIDE OF THE BAY</pattern><template>Oh! You must know Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>A WAR HERO  SUCH MEDALS  AND… A MAN  AN OXFORD MAN</pattern><template>You know Oxford?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S TAKE A SWIM</pattern><template>Have the phone brought down to the pool.</template></category><category><pattern>— ANYTHING  CROPS</pattern><template>You're making me feel uncivilized, Daisy.</template></category><category><pattern>— … AND GUITARS WITH… …THE FOXTROT</pattern><template>Mr. Buchanan.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I HOPE SHE'LL BE A FOOL</pattern><template>That's the best thing a girl in this world can be.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE THE SAME VIEW FROM MY PLACE</pattern><template>Where is your place?</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  THAT'S ALL OVER NOW  DAISY  DARLING  THAT'S ALL OVER</pattern><template>Just tell them the truth, go on.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A VERY SMART MAN</pattern><template>Now old sport, about Miss Baker and that— that request we spoke of— — Nick?</template></category><category><pattern>SLOW DOWN  SLOW DOWN</pattern><template>Bad trouble up ahead, sir!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE LOOKING AT MY TIE PIN</pattern><template>Finest specimen of human molar.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW SEE HERE  TOM  IF YOU'RE GONNA MAKE PERSONAL REMARKS  I WON'T STAY HERE A MINUTE</pattern><template>Mr. Gatsby, I understand you're an Oxford man.</template></category><category><pattern>NO THANKS  I FEEL JUST AS GOOD ON NOTHING AT ALL</pattern><template>Nerve pills. I get them from a doctor in Queens.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER WOULDN'T HAVE EXPECTED TO FIND YOU IN THIS TEMPLE OF VIRTUE</pattern><template>Well, I was just having lunch with Mr. Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>COME</pattern><template>Join us for a little lunch.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  WELL  IT HAPPENS TO BE A RATHER CONFIDENTIAL SORT OF THING  BUT YOU MIGHT MAKE A NICE BIT OF MONEY ON THE SIDE</pattern><template>Uh no, thank you, I have my hands full.</template></category><category><pattern>I STOPPED  AND I… I WAITED</pattern><template>I waited for a moment longer.</template></category><category><pattern>THOUGH I WOULDN'T GO INVESTING EVERY PENNY</pattern><template>At Yale, I dreamed of being a writer.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE EVEN WANTS TO LEAVE THAT</pattern><template>Jay! You can't repeat the past.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  NICKY  WE'RE HAVING A ROW</pattern><template>— What about?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>Charge!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HE DOES</pattern><template>And I think I'll make a point of finding out.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>No, the whispering and the— the champagne and the stars.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  BUCHANAN</pattern><template>Would you mind terribly?</template></category><category><pattern>UH NO  NO NO  I WASN'T SAYING THAT  I… WAS… IF IT'S BUSINESS  YOU SHOULD BE TALKING TO ME</pattern><template>Get some chairs, why don't you, so somebody can sit down!</template></category><category><pattern>— TO A LITTLE KIKE LIKE WOLFSHEIM</pattern><template>— It's called greed, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>— PHOTOGRAPHY</pattern><template>— Yeah. Nick's artistic.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA SHOW YOU SOMETHING</pattern><template>Have a seat.</template></category><category><pattern>GET SOME CHAIRS  WHY DON'T YOU  SO SOMEBODY CAN SIT DOWN</pattern><template>Uh, sure.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE ONLY MARRIED YOU BECAUSE I WAS POOR AND SHE WAS TIRED OF WAITING  IT WAS A TERRIBLE  TERRIBLE MISTAKE  BUT IN HER HEART  IN HER HEART SHE NEVER LOVED ANY ONE BUT ME</pattern><template>— We should go.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE IT</pattern><template>— But how do you live here all alone?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO WAIT HERE</pattern><template>I'm gonna wait here all night, if necessary.</template></category><category><pattern>D'YOU HEAR</pattern><template>I haven't seen it all afternoon.</template></category><category><pattern>TOM</pattern><template>I said I went there, didn't I?</template></category><category><pattern>IT GOT INTO ALL THE PAPERS</pattern><template>— It's a strange coincidence.</template></category><category><pattern>JOIN US FOR A LITTLE LUNCH</pattern><template>♪ Hundred, hundred, hundred dollar bills  Yeah!</template></category><category><pattern>JAY  DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT A WOMAN HAS BEEN KILLED</pattern><template>Daisy's gonna call in the morning.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU FOUND HE WAS AN OXFORD MAN</pattern><template>Oxford, New Mexico.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYONE FOR A ROUND OF GOLF</pattern><template>You still know I'm a champion golfer, don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>— LONG ISLAND</pattern><template>And you think I should?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD THE GATES BROUGHT IN FROM A CASTLE IN NORMANDY</pattern><template>— Oh Jay, it's so grand!</template></category><category><pattern>GATSBY HOPED TO INHERIT CODY'S FORTUNE   — OLD SPORT</pattern><template>But when Cody died, Gatsby was cheated of his inheritance by Cody's family.  He'd been left with the ability to play the gentleman, but he was once again dirt poor.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT  MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>You showed us some of those fine Oxford manners.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I GAVE ALL THAT UP    WITH THE SUN SHINING AND THE BURSTS OF LEAVES ON THE TREES    I PLANNED TO SPEND THE SUMMER STUDYING    AND I PROBABLY WOULD HAVE  WERE IT NOT FOR THE RIOTOUS AMUSEMENTS THAT BECKONED    FROM BEYOND THE WALLS OF THAT COLOSSAL CASTLE    OWNED BY A GENTLEMAN I HAD NOT YET MET    NAMED GATSBY   SO  HE WAS YOUR NEIGHBOR</pattern><template>My neighbor… Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>SADLY  ALL DEAD NOW</pattern><template>When I first made the pleasure of Mr.</template></category><category><pattern>— A PERSONAL CALL  OF COURSE</pattern><template>Excuse me sir, Mr. Gatsby, I'm gonna drain the pool today, before the leaves start falling in.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT OLD SPORT  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>Right you are! I'll know you next time, Mr. Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'D YOU SAY WE GO TO CONEY ISLAND  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>We— we could take my car if you want.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WORTH THE WHOLE DAMN BUNCH PUT TOGETHER</pattern><template>I was always glad I said that.   It was the only compliment I ever paid him.   That morning, Wall Street boomed its usual golden roar.   But I wasn't worth a decent stroke of work.   And I waited for Gatsby to call with news…   while he waited for Daisy.  Gatsby's?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS… THE SINGLE MOST HOPEFUL PERSON I'VE EVER MET  AND I'M EVER LIKELY TO MEET AGAIN</pattern><template>There was something about him, a sensitivity. He was like… he was like one of those machines that register earthquakes 10,000 miles away.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  DAISY  SHE— SHE JUST NEEDS TIME TO THINK THINGS THROUGH</pattern><template>Herzog! We're talking. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE GOT TO BEAT THEM DOWN</pattern><template>Buchanan residence?</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY UH  I'M SICK</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY OLD SPORT  DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>I can protect her here.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CHARLESTON</pattern><template>♪ At least I miss  ♪ Trips around the world  ♪ Don't mean a thing  ♪ If I ain't your girl  ♪ I ain't got time  ♪ For you baby  ♪ Either you're mine Or you're not  Mr. Gatsby?</template></category><category><pattern>— COME ON  DON'T YOU LIKE ME</pattern><template>— Oh! Uh! Plant!</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD NIGHT  OLD SPORT  GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY  SIR</pattern><template>Mr. Slagle is here.</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS IN LOVE WITH ME</pattern><template>Would you?</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT WOULD I WRITE ABOUT</pattern><template>— Anything.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T TRUST HIM</pattern><template>— Alright. Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD GO HOME AND GET SOME REST</pattern><template>I'm going to wait here.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAY HE'S THIRD COUSIN TO THE KAISER  AND SECOND COUSIN TO THE DEVIL</pattern><template>I'm afraid I haven't been a very good host, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>— CAN ANYONE PLAY THAT</pattern><template>— Klipspringer can.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S THE NEXT HEAVYWEIGHT CHAMPION</pattern><template>Pay my respects to your boss.</template></category><category><pattern>IF IT WASN'T FOR THE MIST  WE COULD SEE THE GREEN LIGHT</pattern><template>What green light?</template></category><category><pattern>SIT DOWN  SIT DOWN</pattern><template>Give him a drink!</template></category><category><pattern>— I MUST GO TO BED</pattern><template>Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT'S QUITE ALRIGHT</pattern><template>— I've had so much to drink.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK HERE  OLD SPORT  WHAT… WHAT IS YOUR OPINION OF ME ANYHOW</pattern><template>— My opinion?</template></category><category><pattern>— THIS IS AMAZING</pattern><template>It all makes sense!</template></category><category><pattern>WITH HIS HOUSE  AND HIS PARTIES</pattern><template>And his fancy clothes.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS ABSOLUTELY WHERE YOU LIVE  MY DEAREST ONE</pattern><template>Yes, it suits me.</template></category><category><pattern>I REMEMBER THAT FROM COLLEGE</pattern><template>— That's not what— Oh no no no, I don't make any judgment.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A LIBEL  I'M TOO POOR</pattern><template>They have to be old so they die quickly.</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS MORE FLOWERS</pattern><template>— I think they did a fine job, don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU— YOU'VE HEARD THE STORIES</pattern><template>— Oh! Well— — I will tell you God's truth.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  DON'T BE SILLY  IT'S JUST TWO MINUTES TO FOUR</pattern><template>No one's coming to tea, it's too— It's her!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'S THE BOND BUSINESS  MR  CARRAWAY</pattern><template>Fine, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>HAPPY TO DO IT</pattern><template>I'm going to call Daisy and invite her to tea.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE…  HIS SMILE WAS ONE OF THOSE RARE SMILES   THAT YOU MAY COME ACROSS FOUR OR FIVE TIMES IN LIFE    IT SEEMED TO UNDERSTAND YOU AND BELIEVE IN YOU    JUST AS YOU WOULD LIKE TO BE UNDERSTOOD AND BELIEVED IN   SORRY OLD SPORT  I THOUGH YOU KNEW</pattern><template>Please, just… I don't know what to say, please forgive me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU WERE WITH NICK  HERE</pattern><template>The barber shop.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN HAVE THE CAR</pattern><template>I'll send it over tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>— UH  MRS  WILSON</pattern><template>— Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  I KNOW YOU LIKE TO WATCH</pattern><template>I remember that from college.</template></category><category><pattern>— JUST NEXT DOOR</pattern><template>— Is that so?</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  NICK  WHEN SHE WAS BORN  TOM WAS… GOD KNOWS WHERE</pattern><template>With God knows whom.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE TRIED— I TRIED TO TURN IN TIME  BUT— — SHE</pattern><template>That was Daisy?!</template></category><category><pattern>— DO YOU HEAR YOURSELF</pattern><template>How could you?</template></category><category><pattern>— I WANNA HEAR ALL ABOUT IT</pattern><template>— I've just told you what's going on, it's been going on for five years.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D LIKE TO SHOW HER AROUND</pattern><template>You sure you want me to come?</template></category><category><pattern>NICE LITTLE DANCE</pattern><template>I believe we've met before, Mr. Buchanan.</template></category><category><pattern>CATHERINE'S SAID TO BE VERY GOOD LOOKING  BY PEOPLE WHO OUGHTA KNOW</pattern><template>Uh. Really I can't.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  IT RIPPED HER OPEN</pattern><template>I was there, I saw it!</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT SO  I… I TOLD DAISY THAT I THOUGHT SO</pattern><template>It's better that the shock— — Daisy?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN TELEPHONE FOR AN AXE</pattern><template>Will you forget about the heat?!</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  UH… IT'S TOO LATE  TONIGHT</pattern><template>We could take a plunge in the swimming pool, I haven't made use of it all summer.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST DON'T BELIEVE HE WENT THERE</pattern><template>I beg your pardon.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT FOR A WHILE</pattern><template>Whiskey. It's funny, the Senator just saw her down here.</template></category><category><pattern>A MEMORY  A THOUGHT  A PLACE</pattern><template>Write it down.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS UNIFORM HID THE TRUTH  THAT HE WAS A PENNILESS YOUNG MAN    WITH ONLY THAT GRAND VISION OF HIMSELF   — DAISY  DON'T SCAMPER</pattern><template>— I was not, mother.</template></category><category><pattern>COMING THROUGH  PLEASE</pattern><template>Pardon me.</template></category><category><pattern>AT A… AT A PARTY</pattern><template>In New York.</template></category><category><pattern>I HEAR YOU CAN BUY ANYTHING AT A DRUGSTORE NOWADAYS</pattern><template>— You take Nick and Jordan.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S CERTAINLY RICHER THAN GOD</pattern><template>You don't really believe he killed a man, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A SECOND  WOULD YA</pattern><template>Dominate, Nick!</template></category><category><pattern>THE FUTURE OF THE COLORED EMPIRES</pattern><template>It's Tom, he's wandering around the party, looking for— — Sir.</template></category><category><pattern>THIRTY  THE PROMISE OF A DECADE OF LONELINESS    THE FORMIDABLE STROKE OF THIRTY DIED AWAY…   AS GATSBY AND DAISY DROVE ON THROUGH THE COOLING TWILIGHT…   TOWARDS DEATH   DON'T YOU LIE TO ME</pattern><template>Where did you get this from?</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAW THE OPPORTUNITY  I SUPPOSE</pattern><template>He's a very smart man.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIDN'T HAVE TO KILL HER</pattern><template>Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>TOM  YOU SHOULD BE PROUD OF YOUR ACHIEVEMENTS</pattern><template>— May I show you around?</template></category><category><pattern>ALWAYS A PLEASURE TO MEET A BUCHANAN</pattern><template>Likewise.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT SO  PERHAPS YOU KNOW THAT LADY RIGHT THERE</pattern><template>It's Marlene Moon!</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU MIND TERRIBLY</pattern><template>Of course not.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW IS THE GREAT AMERICAN NOVEL COMING</pattern><template>I'm selling bonds now, with Walter Chase's outfit.</template></category><category><pattern>— UH  I'M FINE</pattern><template>— No? Ah.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH</pattern><template>Look here, old sport. What… What is your opinion of me anyhow?</template></category><category><pattern>— MR  GATSBY  SIR</pattern><template>Chicago on the wire.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY  DARLING  THAT… THAT WOULDN'T BE RESPECTABLE</pattern><template>You live around here, Nick?</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>And you have half of Wall Street out there swilling your free booze, at that fun park every weekend.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE SEEING YOU AT MY TABLE  NICKY</pattern><template>You remind me of a rose.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A MAN IN ENGLAND WHO BUYS ME CLOTHES</pattern><template>I've never seen anything like this.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WANTS TO GO TO TOWN</pattern><template>Town?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST THINK I'M PRETTY DUMB  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>But I have a second sight sometimes that tells me what to do.</template></category><category><pattern>— THESE ARE FLANNEL</pattern><template>— They're so beautiful!</template></category><category><pattern>YOUNG MEN DON'T JUST DRIFT COOLLY OUT OF NOWHERE AND BUY A PALACE ON LONG ISLAND</pattern><template>He told me once he was an Oxford man.</template></category><category><pattern>SEEMS I'M THE ONLY ONE</pattern><template>I still haven't met Mr. Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH IT COULD ALWAYS BE LIKE THIS</pattern><template>It will be.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M CATHERINE</pattern><template>Ain't we having a party?</template></category><category><pattern>— EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Come on, this is crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>CHICAGO ON THE WIRE</pattern><template>— Oh well… I'll be in just a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURPRISED THEY DIDN'T TREAT YOU TO THE STORY OF THAT LITTLE SPREE</pattern><template>Alright, that's all over now, Daisy, darling, that's all over!</template></category><category><pattern>— MAY I SHOW YOU AROUND</pattern><template>— Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS A GERMAN SPY DURING THE WAR</pattern><template>Teddy Barton, Nick Carraway.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU LIKE IT</pattern><template>I love it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>I got an invitation.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MODESTY OF IT… KIND OF TAKE YOUR BREATH AWAY  DOESN'T IT</pattern><template>Evening, sweet hearts.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WRONG</pattern><template>There had been music from my neighbor's all summer.   In his blue gardens, men and girls came and went like moths,   among the whisperings and the laughter and the stars.  — Breakfast?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE JUST EMBARRASSED  DAISY'S EMBARRASSED TOO</pattern><template>— She is embarrassed?</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Go on! Get the hell out of here!</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  NICK  TO THE YALE CLUB</pattern><template>— Nicky. Stay!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>Daisy, Daisy darling, what is it?</template></category><category><pattern>— JAY</pattern><template>— Is everything alright?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN'T WE TALK ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE</pattern><template>— We ought to have plans.</template></category><category><pattern>I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A BUSINESS CONNECTION</pattern><template>No. No no, no. No no no.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHERE DID YOU GO</pattern><template>— Slow down.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  JUST… I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY  PLEASE FORGIVE ME</pattern><template>— It's quite alright.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  WILSON WILL HAVE A LITTLE BUSINESS AT LAST</pattern><template>Let's take a look.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAVE GONE AWAY</pattern><template>Gone away! Do you know when they'll be back?</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH WE COULD JUST RUN AWAY</pattern><template>Run away?</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED YOU</pattern><template>I wish it could always be like this.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL HAVE SOMEONE TO COME REPAIR THIS IMMEDIATELY</pattern><template>Sorry about the clock.</template></category><category><pattern>— COME ON  WE'RE LEAVING</pattern><template>— This is amazing.</template></category><category><pattern>— WON'T YOU COME IN  NICK</pattern><template>— No Thanks .</template></category><category><pattern>IF ONLY IT HAD BEEN ENOUGH FOR GATSBY    JUST TO HOLD DAISY    BUT HE HAD A GRAND VISION FOR HIS LIFE AND DAISY'S PART IN IT    IT WASN'T UNTIL THE END OF THAT SUMMER  ON THE LAST NIGHT I SAW GATSBY    THAT HE TOLD ME OF THE LIFE HE HAD DREAMED FOR HIMSELF SINCE HE WAS A BOY   YOU SEE  DOCTOR  GATSBY'S REAL NAME WAS… JAMES GATZ</pattern><template>His parents were dirt poor farmers from North Dakota.   He never accepted them as his parents at all.   In his own imagination, he was a son of God.   Destined for future glory.   Chasing this destiny, a 16 year old Gatz ran far, far away.   One afternoon, off the coast of Lake Superior, he spotted a yacht in peril.   He rode out and rescued the vessel and its captain, alcoholic millionaire Dan Cody.  You're gonna hit the shoal! Come on sir, we're gonna hit the shoal!</template></category><category><pattern>ALLEZ</pattern><template>Sorry. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN EVERYWHERE AND SEEN EVERYTHING AND DONE EVERYTHING</pattern><template>I've had a very bad time, Nicky.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOTTA ASK YOU TO STEP BACK  SIR</pattern><template>So what happened?</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT TIME</pattern><template>— The time that suits you.</template></category><category><pattern>NONE OF US COULD IGNORE THAT FIFTH GUEST'S SHRILL METALLIC URGENCY</pattern><template>— Oh! Nicky.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU WOULD KNOW THAT WHEN IT COMES TO MARRIED WOMEN  A MAN LIKE THIS CAN BE TRUSTED</pattern><template>With a friend, with someone like you, he'd never so much as look at your wife.</template></category><category><pattern>FINEST SPECIMEN OF HUMAN MOLAR</pattern><template>Gentlemen?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY DECISION</pattern><template>Of course, if anything is not your liking, I'll change it.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW THAT WHEN I KISSED THIS GIRL… I WOULD BE FOREVER WED TO HER</pattern><template>So I stopped.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU'RE ANY GOOD</pattern><template>Henry! Where are you?</template></category><category><pattern>A PACK OF LIES  I GUARANTEE</pattern><template>You— you've heard the stories.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW ALRIGHT</pattern><template>The day after tomorrow?!</template></category><category><pattern>SO UH… WHEN'RE YA GONNA SELL ME THAT CAR</pattern><template>Well I've still got my man working on it.</template></category><category><pattern>TONIGHT  THEY'LL TRACE YOUR CAR</pattern><template>Go away? No. I can't leave now.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  NICK'S ARTISTIC</pattern><template>— No! No no no, not really!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I'M— I'M IN BONDS  ACTUALLY</pattern><template>I want you… get on the next train.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I HELP YOU  SIR</pattern><template>Jordan Baker, the famous sporting star? The golfer?</template></category><category><pattern>SHALL WE</pattern><template>I wish I had done everything on earth with you.</template></category><category><pattern>SUPERCHARGED ENGINE</pattern><template>Get dressed. We're going to lunch.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  NOWADAYS PEOPLE BEGIN BY SNEERING AT FAMILY LIFE AND FAMILY INSTITUTIONS  AND THE NEXT YOU'LL KNOW  WE'LL THROW EVERYTHING OVERBOARD  AND WE'LL HAVE INTERMARRIAGE BETWEEN BLACK AND WHITE</pattern><template>Your wife doesn't love you!</template></category><category><pattern>— AH</pattern><template>Oh, I'm— I'm in bonds, actually.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE JUST NEEDS TIME TO THINK— — NO  JAY… DAISY— SHE JUST NEEDS TIME TO THINK  SHE'S GOING TO CALL IN THE MORNING</pattern><template>Wait up with me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW</pattern><template>Well I… See, I— I'd want to get the grass cut.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST A LOOK</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IT WAS THE— I THINK IT WAS THE 'JOURNAL'</pattern><template>Just in to the right, gentlemen.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  HOW COULD I LOVE HIM  POSSIBLY</pattern><template>Remember our plan, tell him that you never loved him, and all this pain will be wiped out forever.</template></category><category><pattern>I SUPPOSE THAT DAISY WILL CALL TOO</pattern><template>I… Well I suppose.</template></category><category><pattern>TOM'S GOT SOME WOMAN IN NEW YORK</pattern><template>Got some woman?</template></category><category><pattern>A GIRL LIKE DAISY— YOU SHUT UP  SHUT UP</pattern><template>Gatsby looked in that moment as if he had killed a man.  My… My sincerest… My sincerest apologies.</template></category><category><pattern>I BOUGHT CAKES</pattern><template>Have you— have you got everything you need?</template></category><category><pattern>NICK</pattern><template>— Tom! Funny seeing you!</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL REJOIN YOU LATER</pattern><template>I expected him to be… — Old and fat?</template></category><category><pattern>HE CERTAINLY MUST HAVE STRAINED HIMSELF TO GET THIS MENAGERIE TOGETHER</pattern><template>I'd like to know who he is.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY  HEY— EVEN ALONE I CAN'T SAY I NEVER LOVED TOM  IT WOULDN'T BE TRUE</pattern><template>— Of course it wouldn't.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WOULD I DO THAT</pattern><template>You said yourself writing brought you solace.</template></category><category><pattern>— STOP IT  JAY</pattern><template>Linen!</template></category><category><pattern>— PLEASE</pattern><template>— Αu revoir.</template></category><category><pattern>NO POINT  SHE WAS— SHE WAS— SHE WAS KILLED INSTANTLY</pattern><template>Yes, it ripped her open!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE… SHE HAS TO TELL TOM THAT SHE NEVER LOVED HIM</pattern><template>— What?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  I HAVE MADE A SMALL INVESTIGATION INTO YOUR AFFAIRS  YOU'RE ONE OF MEYER WOLFSHEIM'S BUNCH</pattern><template>Please, let's go home!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A MARVELOUS IDEA</pattern><template>Henry, have the car brought around now.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THE WHISPERING AND THE— THE CHAMPAGNE AND THE STARS</pattern><template>But…  After Tom and Daisy's visit, Gatsby's lights went out one by one.   There were no more parties.   Daisy visited discreetly.   For the very same fame that had all summer been a source of satisfaction to Jay Gatsby,   had become a threat.  I don't wanna go home.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO CALL DAISY AND INVITE HER TO TEA</pattern><template>That's alright, I— I— I— — What day would suit you?</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU SEEN MY WIFE</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER OUR PLAN  TELL HIM THAT YOU NEVER LOVED HIM  AND ALL THIS PAIN WILL BE WIPED OUT FOREVER</pattern><template>Daisy.</template></category><category><pattern>I STILL HAVEN'T MET MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>No one's met him.</template></category><category><pattern>— CHICAGO CALLED  IT'S— — NOT NOW</pattern><template>— Keep it open for a personal call.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY  DARLING</pattern><template>None of this has… any consequence, I— Daisy.</template></category><category><pattern>MONSIEUR WILSON FROM THE GARAGE</pattern><template>Monsieur Buchanan?</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU SAW ANYTHING TONIGHT YOU'D LIKE TO TALK TO ME ABOUT  WELL  THEN YOU CAN TALK TO ME OUTSIDE</pattern><template>I don't want you in here. Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>— SHE DOES</pattern><template>— I'm sorry, Mr. Buchanan.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT THE ROYAL TOUR</pattern><template>You must understand that I like all things that are modern!</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN PROTECT HER HERE</pattern><template>Good night, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>— PEOPLE AREN'T INVITED TO GATSBY'S</pattern><template>Well I was. Seems I'm the only one.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TOO HOT TO FUSS</pattern><template>Daisy, it was your great idea!</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY'S GONNA CALL IN THE MORNING</pattern><template>Then we'll make plans, to go away together.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TOM  HE'S WANDERING AROUND THE PARTY  LOOKING FOR— — SIR</pattern><template>Mr. Gatsby, sir. It's Mr. Slagle.</template></category><category><pattern>I ASKED HER TO WAIT UNTIL I MADE SOMETHING OF MYSELF  BUT SHE WAS… SEE  I FELT MARRIED TO HER</pattern><template>That was all.</template></category><category><pattern>MAJOR JAY GATSBY  FOR VALOUR EXTRAORDINARY</pattern><template>That's right.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY COMES OVER SOMETIMES IN THE AFTERNOON  I WANTED PEOPLE WHO WOULDN'T GOSSIP UNTIL WE DECIDE WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO</pattern><template>You see, these towns are very close together, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Oh, but here I am tantalizing you, and I swore I wouldn't tell.</template></category><category><pattern>— NONSENSE</pattern><template>— I am though!</template></category><category><pattern>WE SMOKED ALL THROUGH LUNCH</pattern><template>Come on, let's have fun.</template></category><category><pattern>LADIES AND GENTLEMEN  PLEASE WELCOME TO THE STAGE  THE INCREDIBLE MS  GILDA GRAY</pattern><template>The Charleston!</template></category><category><pattern>NO NO  NO NO  HE'S THE KAIZER'S ASSASSIN</pattern><template>— I heard he killed a man once.</template></category><category><pattern>— JUST YOU  ME AND DADDY</pattern><template>Buchanan residence.</template></category><category><pattern>SWEETHEART  YOU HAVE NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT</pattern><template>Let me take care of things.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAVE TO BE OLD SO THEY DIE QUICKLY</pattern><template>Can't we talk about something else?</template></category><category><pattern>HE SENDS ME A CHRISTMAS CARD EVERY YEAR</pattern><template>I imagine he'll be at lunch too.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO GO  JAY</pattern><template>I have to work.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  OLD SPORT… I HAVEN'T USED THAT POOL ONCE ALL SUMMER</pattern><template>Let's take a swim.</template></category><category><pattern>— I'VE JUST TOLD YOU WHAT'S GOING ON  IT'S BEEN GOING ON FOR FIVE YEARS</pattern><template>You've been seeing him… for five years?</template></category><category><pattern>WHISKEY  IT'S FUNNY  THE SENATOR JUST SAW HER DOWN HERE</pattern><template>I wish we could just run away.</template></category><category><pattern>— HAND IT TO ME</pattern><template>— No!</template></category><category><pattern>POSSIBLY IT HAD OCCURRED TO GATSBY THAT THE COLOSSAL SIGNIFICANCE OF THAT LIGHT   HAD VANISHED FOREVER    NOW IT WAS ONCE AGAIN JUST A GREEN LIGHT ON A DOCK    AND HIS COUNT OF ENCHANTED OBJECT HAD DIMINISHED BY ONE   WHO IS THIS  YOUR FATHER</pattern><template>Oh No. That's Mr. Dan Cody, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE DIDN'T LIKE IT</pattern><template>— Of course she did!</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T WAIT ALL DAY</pattern><template>I'm leaving!</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  I— I'LL BE RIGHT BACK</pattern><template>God! This is a mistake!</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE  PLENTY O' GAS</pattern><template>Well, if I run out, I'll stop at a drugstore.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  SHE IS NOT LEAVING ME</pattern><template>And certainly not for a common swindler like you.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU READY</pattern><template>♪ A little party never  ♪ Killed nobody  ♪ So we gonna dance  ♪ Until we drop  ♪ A little party never killed  ♪ Nobody  ♪ Right here, right now Is all we got  ♪ A little party  ♪ Never killed nobody  Can I have this dance?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW YOU LOOKED FAMILIAR</pattern><template>Having a good time, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>THE SUN'S ALMOST UP</pattern><template>That was the night he finally told me the truth.   All of it.  You know, I thought for a while I had a lot of things, but… the truth is I'm… I'm empty.</template></category><category><pattern>— I WAS IN THE SEVENTH</pattern><template>— Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOTHING THAT YOU COULD DO  SAY  OR STEAL  OR DREAM UP  CAN EVER CHANGE THAT</pattern><template>A girl like Daisy— You shut up! Shut up!</template></category><category><pattern>LIVE IS SOMETHING YOU DOMINATE  NICK</pattern><template>If you're any good.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  HE ​​AND THIS WOLFSHEIM  THEY BOUGHT UP A LOT OF DRUGSTORES  AND SOLD BOOTLEG ALCOHOL OVER THE COUNTER</pattern><template>What about it, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>— I'M TRYING TO</pattern><template>Right, well, it happens to be a rather confidential sort of thing, but you might make a nice bit of money on the side.</template></category><category><pattern>— AND IN MY HEART I LOVE— — I LOVE HER ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>— You're revolting.</template></category><category><pattern>— OF COURSE  SIR</pattern><template>Music! And then we can dance all night.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD'S TRUTH ABOUT MYSELF</pattern><template>I am the son of very wealthy people from the Middle West.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY  EXACTLY WHO ARE YOU  ANYHOW</pattern><template>You see, I have made a small investigation into your affairs, You're one of Meyer Wolfsheim's bunch.</template></category><category><pattern>PARDON ME</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>OH YOU PENNILESS PANTYWAIST</pattern><template>Yeah!</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS GIVING IT LOTS OF THOUGHTS</pattern><template>How does a reputable banker like Walter Chase, find himself up to his eyeballs in debt— — I'll tell you how.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT AT KAPIOLANI</pattern><template>Not that day I carried you down from the Punch Bowl to keep your shoes dry?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A FAVOR  JAY  JUST A FAVOR</pattern><template>Yes. I'm happy to do it.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  YES  THE NINTH BATTALION</pattern><template>— I was in the seventh.</template></category><category><pattern>— MY OPINION</pattern><template>— Yes, yes. Your opinion.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT TAKING CARE OF DAISY ANYMORE</pattern><template>— She's leaving you.</template></category><category><pattern>HE TOLD ME ONCE HE WAS AN OXFORD MAN</pattern><template>However I don't believe it.</template></category><category><pattern>…AND WHICH IT IS NOT LIKELY I SHALL EVER FIND AGAIN   I THOUGHT OUT MY LIFE WITH DAISY IN IT  TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW WE COULD MARRY  AND STRUGGLE ALONG ON SO MANY DOLLARS A MONTH</pattern><template>What was in the letter?</template></category><category><pattern>I HATE THAT WORD   HULKING</pattern><template>Nicky, I heard a rumor that you were getting married to a girl out West.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE YOU ARE</pattern><template>What kind of game are you and Gatsby playing at?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOU TWO</pattern><template>I want the Royal Tour!</template></category><category><pattern>THE BARBER SHOP</pattern><template>That's right.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE YOU CAN</pattern><template>See, I'm gonna fix things, just the way they were before.</template></category><category><pattern>IS ALL THIS MADE ENTIRELY FROM YOUR OWN IMAGINATION</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  SHE LOVES ME</pattern><template>— You must be crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  NO NO NO  NOT REALLY</pattern><template>I write a little, but… — Really?</template></category><category><pattern>— I WAS NOT  MOTHER</pattern><template>So many dashing young officers here, and from such illustrious families.</template></category><category><pattern>— DAISY  PLEASE</pattern><template>— Hand it to me!</template></category><category><pattern>MEYER  MEYER  MEYER</pattern><template>— Smell so good. Look at you!</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD NIGHT  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>You're wrong about the past, old sport!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I'M HAPPY TO DO IT</pattern><template>— A favor?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAS HIS OPPORTUNITY  AND HE SEIZED IT   AND I DECIDED RIGHT THEN AND THERE  TO CALL MYSELF JAY GATSBY</pattern><template>He sailed the yacht out of danger and into his future.   Gatsby showed skill and ambition, and for five years, they sailed the world.  He was alright, old Dane.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY  DAISY DARLING  WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>It makes me sad.</template></category><category><pattern>BLUE</pattern><template>Here.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHERE WERE YOU</pattern><template>— With Nicky.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WRITE ABOUT IT</pattern><template>— Write about it?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF THE PAPERS SAYS THEY THOUGHT THE RAIN WOULD STOP ABOUT 4:00</pattern><template>I think it was the— I think it was the 'Journal'.</template></category><category><pattern>HIGH OVER THE CITY    OUR YELLOW WINDOWS MUST HAVE CONTRIBUTED THEIR SHARE OF HUMAN SECRETS   TO THE CASUAL WATCHER IN THE STREET    AND I WAS HIM TOO    LOOKING UP AND WONDERING  I WAS WITHIN… AND WITHOUT…  …ENCHANTED AND REPELLED… BY THE INEXHAUSTIBLE VARIETY OF LIFE</pattern><template>You have got no right to speak her name!</template></category><category><pattern>JUST THERE  ACROSS THE BAY</pattern><template>I know.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T SPEAK ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED FIVE YEARS AGO</pattern><template>Because I didn't know Daisy then.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  PLEASE  PLEASE GO ON  MR  BUCHANAN  GO ON</pattern><template>What kind of a row are you trying to cause in my house anyhow?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING'S SO CONFUSED</pattern><template>What'll we do with ourselves this afternoon or, the day after that, or for the next thirty years?</template></category><category><pattern>— JUMP</pattern><template>— What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW</pattern><template>I have the same view from my place.</template></category><category><pattern>DOMINATE  NICK</pattern><template>Dominate!</template></category><category><pattern>— I DON'T WANT TO FORGET A SINGLE MOMENT</pattern><template>You're shimmering.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY NOT LET HER ALONE  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>That's a great expression of yours, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>— I'LL BE RIGHT BACK</pattern><template>— Nick, I've… got to speak to you about something!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO  NO</pattern><template>We're different.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DON'T CARE</pattern><template>He gives large parties, and I like large parties, they're so intimate.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE CRAZY</pattern><template>I can't speak about what happened five years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  MADAM</pattern><template>Nick. Nick!</template></category><category><pattern>— BUT YOU WORK ON WALL STREET  RIGHT</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  THAT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA</pattern><template>If he tries to bother her about that unpleasantness this afternoon, if he tries to bother her, if he tries any brutality— — Wait!</template></category><category><pattern>CAN'T YOU SEE THE MAN NEEDS PEACE AND QUIET  LISTEN</pattern><template>Wilson! I just— I just got here from New York.</template></category><category><pattern>CUSTOM JOB</pattern><template>You have to tell me what kind of car it was.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T YOU CALL ME 'OLD SPORT'</pattern><template>And this drugstore business is just small change compared to this bonds stunt that you and Wolfsheim have got going.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GOD  TOM  WAIT</pattern><template>Wait a second, would ya?</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE MOVE ASIDE  EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Another swell party, Jay.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I WAS  SEEMS I'M THE ONLY ONE</pattern><template>Who is this Gatsby?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  MADE ME WHO I AM TODAY</pattern><template>Forest Hills, played the Prince of Wales.</template></category><category><pattern>— ONE OF YOUR OLD OXFORD PALS</pattern><template>— Well I was… I was able to do the commissioner a favor once.</template></category><category><pattern>AT FOUR O'CLOCK  SHE— SHE CAME AT THE WINDOW</pattern><template>She stood there, then… she turned out the lights, so… Well… Give me a hand, will you, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Listen, she was in the wrong, running out on the road.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE MUST KNOW THAT DAISY WAS DRIVING</pattern><template>Promise me.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT DO I OWE YOU</pattern><template>— A dollar. A dollar twenty.</template></category><category><pattern>— A FAVOR</pattern><template>— Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN  PLEASE</pattern><template>There was no point in stop— No point ? No point!</template></category><category><pattern>— SENATOR</pattern><template>Mrs. Buchanan.</template></category><category><pattern>HE USED TO BE MY BEST FRIEND MANY YEARS AGO</pattern><template>You never told me you had a pompadour or a yacht.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR LIFE IS ADORABLE</pattern><template>I know somebody in West Egg.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS SUMMER  I'LL FLING YOU TWO TOGETHER  I'LL PUSH YOU INTO LINEN CLOSETS  AND OUT TO SEA IN BOATS</pattern><template>I'm not listening to a word.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE SUMMER 1922    THE TEMPO OF THE CITY APPROACHED… HYSTERIA    STOCKS REACHED RECORD PEAKS    AND WALL STREET BOOMED IN A STEADY GOLDEN ROAR    THE PARTIES WERE BIGGER    THE SHOWS WERE BROADER    THE BUILDINGS WERE HIGHER    THE MODELS WERE LOOSER  AND THE BAN ON ALCOHOL HAD BACKFIRED    MAKING THE LIQUOR CHEAPER    WALL STREET WAS LURING THE YOUNG AND AMBITIOUS    AND I WAS ONE OF THEM    I RENTED A HOUSE TWENTY MILES FROM THE CITY ON LONG ISLAND    I LIVED IN WEST EGG  IN A FORGOTTEN GROUNDSKEEPER'S COTTAGE    SQUEEZED AMONG THE MANSIONS OF THE NEWLY RICH    TO GET STARTED  I BOUGHT A DOZEN VOLUMES ON CREDIT BANKING AND INVESTMENT    ALL NEW TO ME    THE STOCK MARKET HIT ANOTHER HIGH   THE MARKET'S MOVING UP  UP  UP</pattern><template>Well, of course, nothing is 100%.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF THAT'S TRUE  WHAT'S ALL THIS FOR</pattern><template>That, my dear fellow, is THE question.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  JAY</pattern><template>What is it?</template></category><category><pattern>I WASN'T ANY GOOD</pattern><template>No one need ever read it.</template></category><category><pattern>BY MID SUMMER  GATSBY WAS FRONT PAGE NEWS    WHERE DID THE MONEY COME FROM    THAT'S WHAT THE WHOLE OF NEW YORK WANTED TO KNOW    AND IT WAS THE SAME QUESTION ON TOM'S MIND    WHEN HE ACCOMPANIED DAISY TO ONE OF GATSBY'S…   …GLITTERING PARTIES   TAKE A LOOK AROUND</pattern><template>I'll be right back.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>Everything alright?</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  YES  YOUR OPINION</pattern><template>I don't want you to get the wrong impression from all these— from all these bizarre accusations you must be hearing.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ALRIGHT  I— I— I— — WHAT DAY WOULD SUIT YOU</pattern><template>— What day would suit you!?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE BEING RUDE  DAISY'S IN THERE ALL ALONE  AND YOU—  LOOKING OVER MY STORY SO FAR    I'M REMINDED THAT  FOR THE SECOND TIME THAT SUMMER    I WAS GUARDING OTHER PEOPLE'S SECRETS    ONCE AGAIN  I WAS WITHIN… AND WITHOUT   IT STOPPED RAINING</pattern><template>Yes. It has, hasn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I DEMAND A CHARLESTON</pattern><template>She makes it look so— so splendid, don't you think, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>A SCENE WAS MADE</pattern><template>What's going on with you, Jay?</template></category><category><pattern>BY THIS FELLOW  GODDARD</pattern><template>Everyone ought to read it.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT YOU IN HERE  OKAY</pattern><template>Please. Stand back. Please.</template></category><category><pattern>I… WELL I SUPPOSE</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS</pattern><template>'Old sport'. Where did you pick it up?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  MS  BAKER WILL EXPLAIN EVERYTHING WHEN YOU TAKE HER TO TEA THIS AFTERNOON</pattern><template>Jordan? What's she got to do with it?</template></category><category><pattern>MYRTLE TURTLE</pattern><template>I really must go!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE CRYING  YES  THEY'RE WAILING</pattern><template>— No. I don't believe it.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  I SAW IT  IT WAS A YELLOW CAR</pattern><template>A big yellow car.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I SPEAK TO MRS  BUCHANAN</pattern><template>It's Mr. Carraway, her cousin.</template></category><category><pattern>— I'LL FIND YOU</pattern><template>— Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>COWARD</pattern><template>He didn't even stop his car.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  I DON'T BELIEVE IT</pattern><template>— I don't believe you.</template></category><category><pattern>— NICK</pattern><template>— What?</template></category><category><pattern>AT YALE  I DREAMED OF BEING A WRITER</pattern><template>But I gave all that up.   With the sun shining and the bursts of leaves on the trees,   I planned to spend the summer studying.   And I probably would have, were it not for the riotous amusements that beckoned,   from beyond the walls of that colossal castle,   owned by a gentleman I had not yet met,   named Gatsby.  So, he was your neighbor?</template></category><category><pattern>IN EVERY IDEA</pattern><template>Every decision.</template></category><category><pattern>I ALWAYS KNEW THAT I COULD CLIMB</pattern><template>But I could only climb if I climbed alone.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  EUROPE</pattern><template>— Yes, Europe!</template></category><category><pattern>PLAIN  THANK YOU</pattern><template>— I just have to pop into town.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE THAT'S WHY HE KILLED HER</pattern><template>Yeah, maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FRIEND WALTER CHASE ISN'T TOO PROUD TO COME IN ON IT</pattern><template>I was giving it lots of thoughts.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>Move back! Clear the space here!</template></category><category><pattern>HER PARENTS ARE LOVELY PEOPLE  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>We'll be married there.</template></category><category><pattern>— BUT WHAT WAS IN THE LETTER</pattern><template>— I don't know, she wouldn't tell me.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST GOING  UH</pattern><template>Actually, there are peop— Hullo! Oh Chester, this must be the cousin.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS ALL</pattern><template>It was all for her. The house, the parties. Everything.  God sees everything.</template></category><category><pattern>— I'M NOT SURE  ASK THEM IN THE KITCHEN</pattern><template>— To the left.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>What color is your car?</template></category><category><pattern>PULL OVER  PULL OVER TO THE CURB</pattern><template>Alright old sport. Alright.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE'RE GOING ON A HOLIDAY</pattern><template>— We should go.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S SAY  AFTER DINER  YOU AND I WE GO INTO TOWN</pattern><template>— I can't.</template></category><category><pattern>GET SOME REST  DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>It'll be alright.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE HAD TOLD GATSBY THAT SHE LOVED HIM    AND TOM HAD SEEN IT   LET'S GO TO TOWN</pattern><template>I'm perfectly willing.</template></category><category><pattern>— CATCH UP WITH THE OL'WOLF PACK</pattern><template>— Big day on the job tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>I BEG YOUR PARDON  OLD SPORT  IT JUST… IT'S SO SAD BECAUSE IT IS SO HARD TO MAKE HER UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>It's so hard to make her understand.</template></category><category><pattern>— THIS WAY</pattern><template>A caravansary of billionaire playboy publishers and their blond nurses…   Heiresses comparing inheritances on Gatsby's beach.   My boss, Walter Chase, losing money at the roulette tables.   Gossip columnists alongside gangsters and governors exchanging telephone numbers.   Film stars, Broadway Directors,   morality protectors, high school defectors,   and Ewing Klipspringer, dubious descendant of Beethoven.  Do you know where I might find the host, Mr. Gatsby? I live just next door.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU RUN OUT OF GAS</pattern><template>Nick! Come and see me!</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS MY FAULT  THIS WOMAN  SHE RUSHED OUT AT US AS IF SHE WAS— SEE  SHE WAS TRYING TO SPEAK TO US  IT ALL HAPPENED SO QUICKLY</pattern><template>She tried— I tried to turn in time, but— — She?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THE PAST  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>You're wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIGHT FOOL ME  BUT YOU DON'T FOOL GOD</pattern><template>God sees everything!</template></category><category><pattern>— OH NO NO  SHE DOES THOUGH  SHE DOES  AND WHAT'S MORE  I LOVE DAISY TOO</pattern><template>Though once in a while, I— I go off on a spree, I always come back.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN WE GET THE DOG FOR THE APARTMENT</pattern><template>Whatever you want.</template></category><category><pattern>I SUPPOSE THAT'S WHY I MAKE THINGS UP ABOUT MYSELF  BUT I WANTED TO TELL YOU THE WHOLE STORY FOR A VERY LONG TIME</pattern><template>You see, I grew up terribly, terribly poor, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS MR  CARRAWAY</pattern><template>— Senator.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DO SELL BOND  DON'T YOU  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>— I'm trying to.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE NEVER LOVED YOU</pattern><template>You see, she loves me.</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT'S NOT WHAT— OH NO NO NO  I DON'T MAKE ANY JUDGMENT</pattern><template>We have all summer! Now you wanna sit on the sideline and watch, or d'you wanna play ball?</template></category><category><pattern>I WRITE A LITTLE  BUT… — REALLY</pattern><template>Do you live on Long Island too?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK SO TOO</pattern><template>I can't wait all day.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA LIVE HERE</pattern><template>In this house. You and me.</template></category><category><pattern>I EXPECTED HIM TO BE… — OLD AND FAT</pattern><template>— Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY ONE MAN WAS EXEMPT FROM MY DISGUST</pattern><template>One man… Mr. Carraway?</template></category><category><pattern>— OF COURSE IT WOULDN'T</pattern><template>— As if it mattered to you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M CERTAINLY GLAD TO SEE YOU AGAIN</pattern><template>Hi. I'm certainly glad to see you as well.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT YELLOW CAR WASN'T MINE</pattern><template>D'you hear?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HE WILL PAY</pattern><template>Coward!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I HEARD YOU</pattern><template>I'd like to know when.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY OUT</pattern><template>Can't you see the man needs peace and quiet! Listen!</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU ARE</pattern><template>You see, every night I can see that light at the end of your dock blinking.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL MAKE SOME CALLS</pattern><template>We'll go away.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A CIRCUS</pattern><template>Well, if you see her, I'll be looking for her. You tell her.</template></category><category><pattern>— I'VE HAD SO MUCH TO DRINK</pattern><template>— Yes?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S READY  THERE'S JUST… ONE THING SHE'S REQUESTING  THAT YOU AND MRS BAKER BE THERE FOR LUNCH TOMORROW AT HER HOUSE</pattern><template>Will you come, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>JAY</pattern><template>They're a rotten crowd.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  I'VE HAD ENOUGH  OF EVERYONE</pattern><template>Hello, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SMASHED UP THINGS AND PEOPLE    AND THEN RETREATED BACK INTO THEIR MONEY AND THEIR VAST CARELESSNESS   HEY  HEY</pattern><template>Get out of here!</template></category><category><pattern>BOAZ</pattern><template>— Shakespeare!</template></category><category><pattern>— OF COURSE SHE DID</pattern><template>— No, no no.</template></category><category><pattern>UH NO  THANK YOU  I HAVE MY HANDS FULL</pattern><template>But you wouldn't have to do any business with Wolfsheim, I assure you.</template></category><category><pattern>FINE  FINE  FINE</pattern><template>Open another window.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HIS FANCY CLOTHES</pattern><template>He's just a front for Wolfsheim, a gangster, to get his claws into respectable folks like Walter Chase.</template></category><category><pattern>— GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>One of the papers says they thought the rain would stop about 4:00.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE HIM A DRINK</pattern><template>That yellow car wasn't mine.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  UH  MR  GATSBY  THIS IS MR  BUCHANAN</pattern><template>It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.</template></category><category><pattern>GATSBY  I'VE NEVER SEEN MR  GATSBY  SIR</pattern><template>Why, no one has.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL WALTER CHASE  HE KEEPS HIS MOUTH SHUT OR HE DOESN'T GET A PENNY</pattern><template>We'll talk about that later.</template></category><category><pattern>WE JUST GOT HERE FROM NEW YORK</pattern><template>Yeah, they just stopped.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M STEALING HER AWAY  CARRAWAY</pattern><template>— Ladies and gentlemen!</template></category><category><pattern>JUST TELL THEM THE TRUTH  GO ON</pattern><template>That you never loved him… and this… this will all be wiped out forever.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT TO PUT YOU TO ANY TROUBLE</pattern><template>The day after tomorrow alright?</template></category><category><pattern>HE ISN'T CAUSING A ROW</pattern><template>You're causing a row.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU ARE ADORABLE</pattern><template>Oh, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN'T LOSE EACH OTHER</pattern><template>And let all this glorious love end in nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>JAY  STOP IT</pattern><template>— Right here!</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Hello? Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD NIGHT  GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>What a circus.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER I DON'T BELIEVE IT</pattern><template>— Why not?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT NOW</pattern><template>— … and guitars with… …the Foxtrot.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULDN'T CARE LESS ABOUT THE PARTIES</pattern><template>That will be all for now, gentlemen.</template></category><category><pattern>— I KNOW WHAT KIND OF CAR IT WAS</pattern><template>He's upset!</template></category><category><pattern>I'D RATHER NOT BE THE POLO PLAYER</pattern><template>Tom, you should be proud of your achievements.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  DOES DAISY WANT TO SEE GATSBY</pattern><template>She's absolutely not to know.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BETTER THAT THE SHOCK— — DAISY</pattern><template>— …should all come at once.</template></category><category><pattern>— ALRIGHT  ALRIGHT</pattern><template>You wait here.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW MR  GATSBY WILL BE VERY HAPPY THAT YOU'VE CALLED</pattern><template>Daisy… Hello ? Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>A WEEK LATER  TOM CRASHED HIS CAR</pattern><template>The girl with him was a chambermaid at the Santa Barbara hotel.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A GREASY LITTLE SCUMBAG</pattern><template>No thanks. I feel just as good on nothing at all.</template></category><category><pattern>ΒY THE TIME WE REACHED THE BRIDGE  Ι WAS IMPOSSIBLY CONFUSED    I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK    BUT THE CITY SEEN FROM THE QUEENSBORO BRIDGE   IS ALWAYS THE CITY SEEN FOR THE FIRST TIME…   IN ITS FIRST WILD PROMISE OF ALL THE MYSTERY AND THE BEAUTY IN THE WORLD    ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN    NOW THAT WE'VE SLID OVER THIS BRIDGE  I THOUGH…   ANYTHING AT ALL  EVEN GATSBY  COULD HAPPEN    YES  ABSOLUTELY</pattern><template>Have you heard about…  Aah! My boy!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YES  WE… WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE'S WIVES</pattern><template>— Other people's wives?</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID I WENT THERE  DIDN'T I</pattern><template>Oh, I heard you.</template></category><category><pattern>AIN'T WE HAVING A PARTY</pattern><template>Hum… I'm not sure now's a good time.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS NAME IS FERDIE</pattern><template>Oh my goodness!</template></category><category><pattern>— LET'S ALL GO HOME</pattern><template>— Sit down, Daisy!</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE I'D BETTER SELL IT SOMEWHERE ELSE</pattern><template>Uh no, no no, I wasn't saying that, I… was… If it's business, you should be talking to me.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I'M SURE THAT'S NOT NECESSARY</pattern><template>Oh, but it is though.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THESE THINGS EXCITE ME SO</pattern><template>Nice little dance.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YOU FORGET ABOUT THE HEAT</pattern><template>You make it worse by crabbing about it.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE NOT</pattern><template>I think I can keep myself amused.</template></category><category><pattern>JORDAN  NO ONE MUST KNOW ABOUT THIS</pattern><template>— But what was in the letter?</template></category><category><pattern>ALONE AND A LITTLE EMBARRASSED  I DECIDED TO GET ROARING DRUNK</pattern><template>I thought I might see you here.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE RAN OUT IN THE ROAD</pattern><template>Sonofabitch didn't even stop his car.</template></category><category><pattern>I— I SEE  I'VE SPOTTED HER  THANK YOU</pattern><template>There you are.</template></category><category><pattern>A WONDERFUL PLEASURE  MR  CARRAWAY</pattern><template>— My pleasure.</template></category><category><pattern>— PLEASE DO  OLD SPORT  PLEASE DO</pattern><template>I suppose that Daisy will call too.</template></category><category><pattern>— …HANDS OFF  GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME</pattern><template>— Out! Out you go!</template></category><category><pattern>SIR</pattern><template>What are you doing? Sir!</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  I KNOW THAT SHE WOULD WANT TO BE THERE  SHE WOULD— IF YOU'D JUST GET A MESSAGE TO HER  LET ME TALK TO HER  PLEASE</pattern><template>You wish to contact her… I have no further information, Monsieur.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  A LOT OF THESE NEWLY RICH PEOPLE ARE JUST FILTHY BOOZE MAKERS</pattern><template>Not Gatsby. He's a businessman, he owned a lot of drugstores.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT THE FUTURE</pattern><template>The future of the Colored Empires.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT'S CALLED GREED  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>— That's right.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  MR  BUCHANAN  YOU WANT A— YOU WANT A SODA</pattern><template>— Uh! I'm fine!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA LEAVE YOU GENTLEMEN TO TALK ABOUT YOUR SPORTS AND YOUR WOMEN</pattern><template>— Other people's wives?</template></category><category><pattern>JAY GATSBY</pattern><template>He's a crook, George. Yes… throws all those parties the papers are always talking about.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE AREN'T ANY MORE</pattern><template>Then telephone for an axe.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK IT'S WHAT YOU WANT</pattern><template>I think so too.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DID I HAVE TO COME ALONE</pattern><template>Are you in love with me?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYONE OUGHT TO READ IT</pattern><template>The idea is that it's up to us, the dominant race, to watch out or these other races will have control of things.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH WELL HE WORKS PRETTY SLOW  DON'T HE</pattern><template>Maybe I'd better sell it somewhere else.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT DO YOU MEAN</pattern><template>— Trust me!</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S HAVE SOME GAS</pattern><template>Do I have to do it myself?</template></category><category><pattern>TOM'S VERY PROFOUND LATELY</pattern><template>He reads deep books with long words in them.</template></category><category><pattern>DISGUSTED WITH EVERYONE  AND EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Only one man was exempt from my disgust.</template></category><category><pattern>— THEY'RE SO BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>— Indian cotton.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID HE MANAGE THAT</pattern><template>He saw the opportunity, I suppose.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S SO HARD TO MAKE HER UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>I've gotten all these things for her, I've gotten all these things for her, now she just… she just wants to run away.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  I'M GONNA FIX THINGS  JUST THE WAY THEY WERE BEFORE</pattern><template>Everything's been so… so confused since that night.</template></category><category><pattern>— EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>— Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANTED TO GET UP AND SLAP GATSBY ON THE BACK   I'LL MAKE YOU A DRINK  TOM</pattern><template>Then you won't seem so stupid to yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>MY LITTLE SHACK'S JUST A CARDBOARD BOX AT $80 A MONTH</pattern><template>Your life is adorable.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO IS THIS GATSBY</pattern><template>He was a German spy during the war.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THAT FOR A GIRL HE HASN'T SEEN IN FIVE YEARS</pattern><template>And now he just wants me to invite her over to tea.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVEN'T YOU EVER SEEN IT BEFORE</pattern><template>It's all a custom job.</template></category><category><pattern>— BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>You think it's too much?</template></category><category><pattern>MADAME IS NOT AVAILABLE  MONSIEUR CARRAWAY</pattern><template>If you speak to her, tell her the funeral's tomorrow.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'D LIKE TO KNOW WHEN</pattern><template>Well, Mr. Gatsby?</template></category><category><pattern>— A DOLLAR  A DOLLAR TWENTY</pattern><template>You can have the car.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  YOU WERE THERE ALL ALONG</pattern><template>In every idea.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  NO</pattern><template>— She does!</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO WITH ME</pattern><template>— What time?</template></category><category><pattern>— WE OUGHT TO HAVE PLANS</pattern><template>— Anything. Crops.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER LOVED HIM</pattern><template>Never?</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  I SEE THAT</pattern><template>Did you see any trouble out on the road?</template></category><category><pattern>JORDAN  NICK</pattern><template>— Nick?</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  WELL</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT COULD I SAY    THE PHOTOGRAPH WAS UNDOUBTEDLY AUTHENTIC    COULD IT ALL BE TRUE   BUT OF COURSE  YOU DON'T NEED TO TAKE MY WORD FOR IT  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>At lunch today, I'm going to introduce you to one of New York's most distinguished businessmen, a Mr. Meyer Wolfsheim.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D LIKE TO KNOW WHEN</pattern><template>You'd like to know when?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE THE WAY THE WHOLE FRONT CATCHES THE LIGHT LIKE THAT</pattern><template>That's splendid.</template></category><category><pattern>I BEG YOUR PARDON</pattern><template>Ms. Baker, Mr. Gatsby would like to speak to you, alone.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS IN 1919  I ONLY STAYED THERE 5 MONTHS  THAT'S WHY I CAN'T EXACTLY CALL MYSELF AN OXFORD MAN</pattern><template>You see, it was an opportunity they gave to some of us officers who— who fought in the war.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A PLEASURE TO MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE</pattern><template>I never wouldn't have expected to find you in this temple of virtue.</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  THANK YOU  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Laughter.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THANK YOU</pattern><template>— Chester McKee, pleasure to meet you.</template></category><category><pattern>— WILSON  WILSON  PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER</pattern><template>— I know what kind of car it was!</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>She ran out in the road.</template></category><category><pattern>— GET READY  AIM  FORE</pattern><template>I'm such a brute.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO IS HE ANYHOW   AN ACTOR</pattern><template>Meyer? No no no.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE ASKED ME TO TELL YOU SHE HAD A WONDERFUL TIME</pattern><template>She didn't like it.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE OFF YOUR HAT AND STAY A WHILE</pattern><template>Oh, uh Nick.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  SURE</pattern><template>Yeah, let's talk business.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT GREEN LIGHT</pattern><template>The one that burns all night at the end of your dock.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  LET'S TALK BUSINESS</pattern><template>Sure. I'll get the chairs, uh… Mirt, why don't you uh… don't you entertain.</template></category><category><pattern>— LADIES AND GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>— Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  GOOD</pattern><template>Nick, Daisy is furious.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MAKES ME SAD</pattern><template>— Why?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST WHEN I THOUGHT IT COULDN'T BE ANY MORE FANTASTICAL…  THEN CAME THE WAR  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>…he became a war hero, single handedly defeating the German army.  In the Argonne forest, I took two machine gun detachments, so far— outnumbered, five to one— there was half a mile gap on either side— there wasn't a single German soldier left standing— we stayed there two days and two nights— and we saw piles of dead— 130 men, with only 16 Lewis guns— every allied government gave me a medal — even Montenegro.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU WANNA EMBARRASS MYRTLE</pattern><template>That's rude.</template></category><category><pattern>— OTHER PEOPLE'S WIVES</pattern><template>— Hello, ladies.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I SUPPOSE THE LATEST THING IS TO SIT BACK AND LET MR  NOBODY FROM NOWHERE MAKE LOVE TO YOUR WIFE</pattern><template>Well, if that's the idea, you can count me out.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVING A GOOD TIME  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Oh, the whole thing's incredible.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE THE MAN IN THE CORNER  SMOKING TWO CIGARETTES</pattern><template>You must think I'm pretty dumb, don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>UH  THIS ISN'T THE MAN  MEYER</pattern><template>Remember this is the friend I told you about.</template></category><category><pattern>CIVILIZATION'S GOING TO PIECES</pattern><template>Have you read  The Rise of the Colored Empires ?</template></category><category><pattern>IF IT GETS IN THE PAPERS  YOU UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>They're all people Wolfsheim wanted to do something for.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  I THOUGHT EVERYBODY KNEW</pattern><template>Well, I don't.</template></category><category><pattern>— I THINK THEY DID A FINE JOB  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>— Beautiful.</template></category><category><pattern>— STAY</pattern><template>— Let's all go home.</template></category><category><pattern>— UH  NICK'S A WRITER</pattern><template>— Ah?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MAN… MR  CARRAWAY</pattern><template>Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH WELL… IT DIDN'T BRING ANYONE ELSE MUCH SOLACE</pattern><template>I wasn't any good.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M PRETTY CYNICAL ABOUT EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Your daughter, I suppose she talks and eats and everything?</template></category><category><pattern>— I AM THOUGH</pattern><template>— No no no no no.</template></category><category><pattern>— BIG DAY ON THE JOB TOMORROW</pattern><template>— Nonsense! We're going.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WANT ANY OF THIS</pattern><template>Jordan? Nick?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT IT  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Don't you call me 'old sport'!</template></category><category><pattern>— GREAT</pattern><template>— Go on.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT'S A CUSTOM WURLITZER</pattern><template>— Can anyone play that?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT THAT WOMAN</pattern><template>No point. She was— she was— she was killed instantly.</template></category><category><pattern>FOREST HILLS  PLAYED THE PRINCE OF WALES</pattern><template>What a sissy!</template></category><category><pattern>OR IS HE GONNA PLAY BALL</pattern><template>Take off your hat and stay a while.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS THE MOST FRIGHTENING PERSON I'D EVER SEEN   WELL I— I'VE SEEN YOUR FACE ON THE COVER OF SPORTING LIFE  NICK CARRAWAY</pattern><template>But I enjoyed looking at her.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW SOMEBODY IN WEST EGG</pattern><template>I don't know a single person that side of the bay.</template></category><category><pattern>FINE  HAVE IT YOUR OWN WAY  TOM</pattern><template>Come on, Jordan.</template></category><category><pattern>JORDAN BAKER  THE FAMOUS SPORTING STAR  THE GOLFER</pattern><template>I— I see, I've spotted her. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY I CAME OVER</pattern><template>It's about the butler's nose.</template></category><category><pattern>I REMEMBER FEELING TORN    WAS IT RIGHT TO BRING MY COUSIN DAISY  A MARRIED WOMAN    TOGETHER WITH A MAN I HARDLY KNEW    WHEN I RETURNED HOME  GATSBY'S WAS LIT FROM TOWER TO CELLAR   AS IF FOR ANOTHER WILD PARTY    BUT THERE WASN'T A SOUND   — THANK YOU</pattern><template>— Have a good night, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  NICKY</pattern><template>— What?</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  THIS IS A MISTAKE</pattern><template>This is a terrible, terrible mistake!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW GORGEOUS</pattern><template>They're absolutely in mourning.</template></category><category><pattern>GRASS  WHAT GRASS</pattern><template>I bought cakes.</template></category><category><pattern>— FIXED IT</pattern><template>How did he manage that?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  FOLKS  MAKE SOME ROOM  HUH</pattern><template>Make some room back there!</template></category><category><pattern>GATSBY'S ACQUAINTANCE JUST AFTER THE WAR  I KNEW I'D DISCOVERED A MAN OF FINE BREEDING</pattern><template>A war hero, such medals, and… a man, an Oxford man.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  LET'S GO FIND HIM  AND YOU CAN ASK HIM YOURSELF</pattern><template>Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome to the stage  the incredible Ms. Gilda Gray!</template></category><category><pattern>HE TAUGHT ME EVERYTHING</pattern><template>—  How to dress, act and speak…  — Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I SAVE THE NEXT DANCE</pattern><template>His uniform hid the truth, that he was a penniless young man,   with only that grand vision of himself.  — Daisy, don't scamper.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST… I'M JUST GOING  I'VE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE</pattern><template>Nonsense!</template></category><category><pattern>COME LOOK</pattern><template>— Oh Nicky, how funny.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SHE SAID IT WAS A GIRL</pattern><template>And I wept.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE ALL PEOPLE WOLFSHEIM WANTED TO DO SOMETHING FOR</pattern><template>What's the difference as long as they can cook and make beds, right?</template></category><category><pattern>— I DON'T TRUST HIM</pattern><template>I don't trust him.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT ARE WE DOING</pattern><template>— Hey, where are you going?</template></category><category><pattern>THE SUN IS GETTING COLDER EVERY YEAR</pattern><template>Oh I would like to be out on that bay today.</template></category><category><pattern>I ADORE HER PICTURES</pattern><template>Would you like me to introduce you?</template></category><category><pattern>— NEITHER</pattern><template>Plain, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME  HE IS OF NO USE TO US IF DETROIT IS HIS IDEA OF ​​A SMALL TOWN  YOU UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>We'll chat later, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>NO THANKS  I'LL WAIT OUTSIDE</pattern><template>What is the matter with you?</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN'T SHE LIKE WILSON EITHER</pattern><template>He's a greasy little scumbag.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY DON'T COME BACK</pattern><template>When I arrived home, I noticed that a figure had emerged on my neighbor's dock.   And something told me it was…   Mr. Gatsby.   He seemed to be reaching towards something out there in the dark.   The green light.  I don't wanna talk about this, doctor.</template></category><category><pattern>— WITH NICKY</pattern><template>Mr. Gatsby was showing us the grounds.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BEEN PROVED  SCIENTIFIC</pattern><template>We've got to beat them down.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I… SEE  I— I'D WANT TO GET THE GRASS CUT</pattern><template>— Well… — Uh… Look here old sport, you— you don't make much money, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>— WHY</pattern><template>— Because…  Five lost years struggled on Daisy's lips.   But all she could manage was…  Why?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MAKE IT WORSE BY CRABBING ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Why not let her alone, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>— LONG ISLAND  PLEASE</pattern><template>— Long Island.</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  I'VE HEARD OF IT</pattern><template>Then you would know that when it comes to married women, a man like this can be trusted.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  UH  PLANT</pattern><template>Myrtle? Myrtle?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST NEED TO GIVE HER MORE TIME  OLD SPORT  MORE TIME</pattern><template>Don't worry old sport, don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY  WOULD YOU BE GOOD ENOUGH TO TAKE MY COUPÉ  AND I'LL DRIVE EVERYONE ELSE IN YOUR CIRCUS WAGON</pattern><template>I don't think there's much gas, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS YOUR PLACE</pattern><template>Nick, I want you and Daisy both to come over to my house.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  DAISY</pattern><template>Daisy?</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Nick. Would you mind terribly?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT DAY AT FIVE O'CLOCK  DAISY FAY MARRIED TOM BUCHANAN WITH MORE POMP AND CIRCUMSTANCE LOUISVILLE HAD EVER SEEN</pattern><template>Congratulations, Mr. Buchanan!</template></category><category><pattern>THE FACT THAT GATSBY'S HOUSE IS JUST ACROSS THE BAY</pattern><template>It's no coincidence. He bought that house to be near her.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T GO AROUND VERY MUCH  I DON'T THINK I RECOGNIZE A SINGLE PERSON</pattern><template>Is that so? Perhaps you know that lady right there.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR PLACE LOOKS LIKE THE WORLD'S FAIR OR CONEY ISLAND</pattern><template>— Ah, does it?</template></category><category><pattern>SMALL PARTIES  THERE ISN'T ANY PRIVACY</pattern><template>But if that's true, what's all this for?</template></category><category><pattern>— OKAY  YOU'RE READY FOR YOUR CLOSE UP</pattern><template>— I don't want to forget a single moment.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO WORK</pattern><template>— I understand.</template></category><category><pattern>THINGS THAT NEITHER OF US CAN EVER FORGET</pattern><template>I just need to speak to Daisy alone. You see, you— you've got her all excited now, don't you old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>MY GOOD FRIEND</pattern><template>And he will confirm all I have told you, and vouch for my good character.</template></category><category><pattern>— NOT REALLY</pattern><template>— If you forgive me.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD TO SEE YOU</pattern><template>You be careful with those tables now, Senator.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE A SEAT</pattern><template>Here's a lot of clippings I collect.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WANT ONE</pattern><template>Oh no. My nerves are fine, thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>OUI  MONSIEUR</pattern><template>The doors! Close them.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE GONNA ARREST YOU</pattern><template>I have no clue how I got home.</template></category><category><pattern>— COME ON</pattern><template>A Jazz history of the world, and accompanying fireworks!</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  WELL— — I WILL TELL YOU GOD'S TRUTH</pattern><template>God's truth about myself.</template></category><category><pattern>— BECAUSE…  FIVE LOST YEARS STRUGGLED ON DAISY'S LIPS    BUT ALL SHE COULD MANAGE WAS…  WHY</pattern><template>Cause I've never seen such beautiful shirts before.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL I ASSURE YOU IT'S NOTHING UNDERHAND</pattern><template>Miss Baker's a honest sportswoman, she wouldn't do anything that wasn't alright.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  I DIDN'T REALIZE UNTIL THE OTHER NIGHT THAT I'D MET GATSBY</pattern><template>Five years ago. In Louisville.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE HE WAS THE ONE THAT WAS FOOLING AROUND WITH MYRTLE</pattern><template>Maybe that's why he killed her!</template></category><category><pattern>— SMELL SO GOOD  LOOK AT YOU</pattern><template>— Look at you!</template></category><category><pattern>SOME VISION OF HIMSELF THAT HE'D PUT INTO LOVING DAISY    ONE NIGHT IN LOUISVILLE  FIVE YEARS AGO    GATSBY FOUND HIMSELF AT DAISY'S HOUSE BY COLOSSAL ACCIDENT   SO I WENT TO HER HOUSE FIRST  WITH SOME OF THE OFFICERS FROM CAMP TAYLOR</pattern><template>I'd never been in such a beautiful house before.</template></category><category><pattern>JAY  YOU CAN'T REPEAT THE PAST</pattern><template>— Can't repeat the past?</template></category><category><pattern>— I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>I just don't believe he went there.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE REALIZES THAT THIS LITTLE FLIRTATION IS OVER</pattern><template>Daisy? Daisy!</template></category><category><pattern>I REMEMBER THE REST OF THAT DAY AS AN ENDLESS DRILL OF POLICE   AND PHOTOGRAPHERS AND TABLOID REPORTERS    THE HEADLINES WERE A NIGHTMARE    THEY PINNED EVERYTHING ON GATSBY    THE AFFAIR WITH MYRTLE  THE HIT AND RUN  EVERYTHING    AND THERE WAS NOTHING I COULD SAY    EXCEPT THE ONE UNUTTERABLE FACT THAT NONE OF IT WAS TRUE   DARLING  DADDY'S TAKING CARE OF HIS TWO FAVORITE GIRLS</pattern><template>— Where are we going?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU WERE NOT AVAILABLE</pattern><template>A scene was made.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TAKE CARE OF THINGS</pattern><template>Take care of you.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU IN LOVE WITH ME</pattern><template>Oh, it's the secret of Carraway castle.</template></category><category><pattern>TWO BOTTLES OF WHISKEY  WRAP THEM IN A TOWEL</pattern><template>Come on, Nick!</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING OUGHT TO BE DONE ABOUT A FELLA LIKE THAT</pattern><template>He'll pay.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE GOT NO RIGHT TO SPEAK HER NAME</pattern><template>— Daisy, Daisy, Daisy— — You got no right to speak her name!</template></category><category><pattern>…OTHER AFFAIRS   — I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU NOT TO CALL ME HERE</pattern><template>Boaz!</template></category><category><pattern>— NICK CARRAWAY</pattern><template>— Come on, don't you like me?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF A ROW ARE YOU TRYING TO CAUSE IN MY HOUSE ANYHOW</pattern><template>He isn't causing a row.</template></category><category><pattern>OH I— I'VE JUST BEEN… GLANCING INTO SOME OF THE ROOMS</pattern><template>What'd you say we go to Coney Island, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  SHE WAS IN THE WRONG  RUNNING OUT ON THE ROAD</pattern><template>Sweetheart, you have nothing to worry about.</template></category><category><pattern>BAD TROUBLE UP AHEAD  SIR</pattern><template>Good! Wilson will have a little business at last.</template></category><category><pattern>— MY PLEASURE</pattern><template>— I know all about you.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST REMEMBERED… TODAY IS MY BIRTHDAY</pattern><template>Happy birthday.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A WHORE</pattern><template>They're gonna arrest you!</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE THIS</pattern><template>Something for the lady.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THERE IS ANYTHING THAT YOU WANT… JUST ASK FOR IT  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>CAUSE I'VE NEVER SEEN SUCH BEAUTIFUL SHIRTS BEFORE</pattern><template>If it wasn't for the mist, we could see the green light.</template></category><category><pattern>— ANY LUCK  SENATOR</pattern><template>— What a gentleman.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVEN'T CALLED HER</pattern><template>Hey, uh. Mr. Gatsby, this is Mr. Buchanan.</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN ANOTHER WINDOW</pattern><template>There aren't any more.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU SEE  OLD SPORT  I'M… I'M GOING TO MAKE A VERY BIG REQUEST OF YOU TODAY</pattern><template>A big request?</template></category><category><pattern>I REMEMBERED YOU LIVE NEXT DOOR</pattern><template>It's like an amusement park!</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AROUND YOU  RICH GIRLS DON'T MARRY POOR BOYS</pattern><template>She's mine.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL YOUR CHAUFFEUR TO GO FAR AWAY</pattern><template>Come back in an hour, Ferdie.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE JUST SUPPOSED TO INVITE HER OVER  SO HE CAN HAPPEN TO PASS BY</pattern><template>I remember feeling torn.   Was it right to bring my cousin Daisy, a married woman,   together with a man I hardly knew?   When I returned home, Gatsby's was lit from tower to cellar   as if for another wild party.   But there wasn't a sound.  — Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>— DAISY  DAISY  DAISY— — YOU GOT NO RIGHT TO SPEAK HER NAME</pattern><template>I'll speak her name when— Oh my God! You are crazy!</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT…  AAH  MY BOY</pattern><template>Meyer, Meyer, Meyer.</template></category><category><pattern>PRESS THE ORANGE  IT ALL COMES OUT THERE</pattern><template>Anyone for a round of golf?</template></category><category><pattern>MS  BAKER  MR  GATSBY WOULD LIKE TO SPEAK TO YOU  ALONE</pattern><template>— With me?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T REALLY BELIEVE HE KILLED A MAN  DO YOU</pattern><template>Well, let's go find him, and you can ask him yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S IN OUR BLOOD</pattern><template>And nothing that you could do, say, or steal, or dream up, can ever change that.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY LOVED ME WHEN SHE MARRIED ME  AND SHE LOVES ME NOW</pattern><template>— No! No.</template></category><category><pattern>— WELL I WAS… I WAS ABLE TO DO THE COMMISSIONER A FAVOR ONCE</pattern><template>He sends me a Christmas card every year.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  JORDAN</pattern><template>One of them was in the car with her.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  MUST WE</pattern><template>Just a look.</template></category><category><pattern>— YES</pattern><template>Then we can go back to Louisville to her parents' house.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER THAT  I LIVED LIKE A YOUNG PRINCE IN ALL THE CAPITALS OF EUROPE</pattern><template>— Oh, Europe?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK IT'S TOO MUCH</pattern><template>I think it's what you want.</template></category><category><pattern>— I'M SORRY  MR  BUCHANAN</pattern><template>— She does though!</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Is that you, my lovely?</template></category><category><pattern>— RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>— No, Jay!</template></category><category><pattern>HE CONSTANTLY ASKED ABOUT DAISY</pattern><template>I was just the first person that knew her.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY</pattern><template>Can't you see who this guy is?</template></category><category><pattern>OH COME ON  WE'LL GET A GREAT BIG ROOM AT THE PLAZA</pattern><template>A bucket of ice, a bottle of whiskey and it will be fun.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL MEET YOU AT THE PLAZA</pattern><template>I'll be the man in the corner, smoking two cigarettes.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAILED THE YACHT OUT OF DANGER AND INTO HIS FUTURE    GATSBY SHOWED SKILL AND AMBITION  AND FOR FIVE YEARS  THEY SAILED THE WORLD   HE WAS ALRIGHT  OLD DANE</pattern><template>He taught me everything.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WILL BE ALL FOR NOW  GENTLEMEN</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  MY WORK HERE IS DONE</pattern><template>I'm gonna leave you gentlemen to talk about your sports and your women.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT THERE</pattern><template>So you are.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE… I HAPPEN TO RUN A LITTLE— A LITTLE BUSINESS ON THE SIDE  A SORT OF SIDE LINE  I MEAN  YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT I'M SAYING  RIGHT</pattern><template>You do sell bond, don't you, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE LOOK LIKE SHE COULD BE ON THE COVER OF VOGUE  DON'T YOU THINK</pattern><template>Turn on the camera!</template></category><category><pattern>— HE WON'T ANNOY YOU</pattern><template>I think he realizes that this little flirtation is over.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU MEAN ABOUT THE PARTY</pattern><template>— The party?</template></category><category><pattern>UH YES  HUH  UHM… AT LEAST A DOZEN PEOPLE SEND THEIR LOVE</pattern><template>How gorgeous.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE ARE SILK</pattern><template>— These are flannel.</template></category><category><pattern>BUCHANAN RESIDENCE</pattern><template>May I speak to Mrs. Buchanan?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT LISTENING TO A WORD</pattern><template>So Nick, Daisy tells me that you're over in West Egg.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT SOME WOMAN</pattern><template>She might have the decency not to telephone at diner time. Don't you think?</template></category><category><pattern>HE GAVE HER A STRING OF PEARLS WORTH 350 000 DOLLARS</pattern><template>But the morning of the wedding, Daisy received a letter.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT IS</pattern><template>The fact that Gatsby's house is just across the bay.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU  JAY</pattern><template>— Where were you?</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER HOW MUCH FUN WE HAD</pattern><template>I don't know why we can't just have fun like that again.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT MAKES SENSE</pattern><template>— Everything.</template></category><category><pattern>A JAZZ HISTORY OF THE WORLD  AND ACCOMPANYING FIREWORKS</pattern><template>Come on! Nick!</template></category><category><pattern>CAN'T YOU SEE WHO THIS GUY IS</pattern><template>With his house. And his parties.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU SEE ANY TROUBLE OUT ON THE ROAD</pattern><template>That woman you ran down is dead, Jay!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE STOOD THERE  THEN… SHE TURNED OUT THE LIGHTS  SO… WELL… GIVE ME A HAND  WILL YOU  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>I should have told him what I had just seen, but…   All I could manage was:  You know Jay, with everything that's happened, you ought to go away.</template></category><category><pattern>AN ABSOLUTE ROSE  DOESN'T HE</pattern><template>— So, after diner… — Well, I'm not even faintly like a rose.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD SEES EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Myrtle! Where are you?</template></category><category><pattern>— HAVE A GOOD NIGHT  SIR</pattern><template>Your place looks like the World's fair or Coney Island.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAVED MY LETTERS</pattern><template>This was my first photo of you.</template></category><category><pattern>WILSON  WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR</pattern><template>Let's have some gas!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  IT'S THE SECRET OF CARRAWAY CASTLE</pattern><template>Tell your chauffeur to go far away.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST… OH YOU SEE  I THINK EVERYTHING'S TERRIBLE ANYHOW</pattern><template>— Really?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING FOR THE LADY</pattern><template>He sends over a selection at the beginning of each season.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL THEM DAISY'S CHANGED HER MIND</pattern><template>— What is this?</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  HELLO</pattern><template>I remember the rest of that day as an endless drill of police   and photographers and tabloid reporters.   The headlines were a nightmare.   They pinned everything on Gatsby.   The affair with Myrtle, the hit and run, everything.   And there was nothing I could say,   except the one unutterable fact that none of it was true.  Darling, Daddy's taking care of his two favorite girls.</template></category><category><pattern>— KLIPSPRINGER CAN</pattern><template>— Someone, wake Ewing!</template></category><category><pattern>PHOOEY  I'VE MET HIM</pattern><template>Really? Which one?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  DON'T BE MORBID</pattern><template>Let's go to town.</template></category><category><pattern>— HELLO  LADIES</pattern><template>Who is he anyhow ? An actor?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  MONSIEUR</pattern><template>They have gone away.</template></category><category><pattern>— WRITE ABOUT IT</pattern><template>— Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT YOU NEVER LOVED HIM… AND THIS… THIS WILL ALL BE WIPED OUT FOREVER</pattern><template>Why, how could I love him, possibly!</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU'RE REVOLTING</pattern><template>Do you know why we left Chicago?</template></category><category><pattern>WITH GOD KNOWS WHOM</pattern><template>And I asked the nurse if it was a boy or a girl.</template></category><category><pattern>— I UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>Well. I'll walk you out.</template></category><category><pattern>— FREE OF CHARGE</pattern><template>He's certainly richer than God.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIDN'T EVEN STOP HIS CAR</pattern><template>You're gonna defend him now?</template></category><category><pattern>HIS PARENTS WERE DIRT POOR FARMERS FROM NORTH DAKOTA    HE NEVER ACCEPTED THEM AS HIS PARENTS AT ALL    IN HIS OWN IMAGINATION  HE WAS A SON OF GOD    DESTINED FOR FUTURE GLORY    CHASING THIS DESTINY  A 16 YEAR OLD GATZ RAN FAR  FAR AWAY    ONE AFTERNOON  OFF THE COAST OF LAKE SUPERIOR  HE SPOTTED A YACHT IN PERIL    HE RODE OUT AND RESCUED THE VESSEL AND ITS CAPTAIN  ALCOHOLIC MILLIONAIRE DAN CODY   YOU'RE GONNA HIT THE SHOAL  COME ON SIR  WE'RE GONNA HIT THE SHOAL</pattern><template>What the hell are you doing, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>THE WAY HE SPOKE  NO WONDER PEOPLE THOUGHT HE WAS LYING   AFTER MY FAMILY DIED  I CAME INTO A GREAT DEAL OF MONEY</pattern><template>After that, I lived like a young prince in all the capitals of Europe.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOWED US SOME OF THOSE FINE OXFORD MANNERS</pattern><template>Daisy, darling.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WE CAN GO BACK TO LOUISVILLE TO HER PARENTS' HOUSE</pattern><template>Her parents are lovely people, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>A GIFT THAT I HAVE NEVER FOUND IN ANY OTHER PERSON…  I NEVER REALIZED HOW EXTRAORDINARY A NICE GIRL COULD BE</pattern><template>…and which it is not likely I shall ever find again.  I thought out my life with Daisy in it, trying to figure out how we could marry, and struggle along on so many dollars a month.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE HAVE A LITTLE SELF CONTROL</pattern><template>Self control!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE'LL PILE THAT STUFF IN THE GARAGE  IT'S GOING BACK TO TOWN</pattern><template>Oh, there you are!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I DO KNOW THAT I AWOKE WITH A DISTINCTLY UNEASY FEELING   THAT GATSBY WAS WATCHING ME   WATCHING YOU</pattern><template>Yes. Gatsby was always watching me.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S PERFECT</pattern><template>From your perfect irresistible imagination.</template></category><category><pattern>MUSIC  AND THEN WE CAN DANCE ALL NIGHT</pattern><template>Will you come, old sport?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  MR  GATSBY</pattern><template>It was in 1919, I only stayed there 5 months, that's why I can't exactly call myself an Oxford man.</template></category><category><pattern>EVENING  SWEET HEARTS</pattern><template>Where're you kids going?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SHIMMERING</pattern><template>She look like she could be on the cover of Vogue, don't you think?</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW HE JUST WANTS ME TO INVITE HER OVER TO TEA</pattern><template>The modesty of it… kind of take your breath away, doesn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW COULD YOU</pattern><template>How could you do that?</template></category><category><pattern>— CHARMED</pattern><template>— Delighted.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  GATSBY  SIR  EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>— Chicago called, it's— — Not now.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE CARELESS PEOPLE  TOM AND DAISY</pattern><template>They smashed up things and people,   and then retreated back into their money and their vast carelessness.  Hey! Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I COULD ONLY CLIMB IF I CLIMBED ALONE</pattern><template>I knew that when I kissed this girl… I would be forever wed to her.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME  I HAVE TO MAKE THAT CALL</pattern><template>— Any luck, Senator ?</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY  WHICH ONE</pattern><template>The prince?</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  WILSON  HOW'S BUSINESS</pattern><template>Yeah, I can't complain.</template></category><category><pattern>MONSIEUR BUCHANAN</pattern><template>Excuse me, I'll be right back.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU READ  THE RISE OF THE COLORED EMPIRES</pattern><template>By this fellow, Goddard.</template></category><category><pattern>— FIVE YEARS  NEXT NOVEMBER</pattern><template>— Tea?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE MAKING ME FEEL UNCIVILIZED  DAISY</pattern><template>Civilization's going to pieces.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LUNCH TODAY  I'M GOING TO INTRODUCE YOU TO ONE OF NEW YORK'S MOST DISTINGUISHED BUSINESSMEN  A MR  MEYER WOLFSHEIM</pattern><template>My good friend.</template></category><category><pattern>— I LIVE IN WEST EGG</pattern><template>I was there at a party about a month ago.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY MCKEE  TAKE A PICTURE OF THAT</pattern><template>Don't, I'm not one of those models!</template></category><category><pattern>MR  WARDEN  MAY I ASK YOU… LOOK WHO'S HERE</pattern><template>You see these fists?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  IT WAS YOUR IDEA</pattern><template>Fine. Have it your own way, Tom.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BLUE</pattern><template>Coupé.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THIS HOUSE  YOU AND ME</pattern><template>Darling… It's time to tell Tom.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH WELL… I'LL BE IN JUST A MINUTE</pattern><template>I'm taking my new hydroplane out in the morning.</template></category><category><pattern>— I'M NOT MARRIED</pattern><template>— But you work on Wall Street, right?</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU WANT ANY</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT</pattern><template>You see, I know your wife.</template></category><category><pattern>♪ A LITTLE PARTY NEVER  ♪ KILLED NOBODY  ♪ SO WE GONNA DANCE  ♪ UNTIL WE DROP  ♪ A LITTLE PARTY NEVER KILLED  ♪ NOBODY  ♪ RIGHT HERE  RIGHT NOW IS ALL WE GOT  ♪ A LITTLE PARTY  ♪ NEVER KILLED NOBODY  CAN I HAVE THIS DANCE</pattern><template>Oh you penniless pantywaist!</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE TO HEAR A FAMILY SECRET</pattern><template>That's why I came over.</template></category><category><pattern>THE IDEA IS THAT IT'S UP TO US  THE DOMINANT RACE  TO WATCH OUT OR THESE OTHER RACES WILL HAVE CONTROL OF THINGS</pattern><template>Tom's very profound lately.</template></category><category><pattern>NONSENSE</pattern><template>Go on in there, talk to Catherine!</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY WAS BY FAR THE MOST POPULAR GIRL WITH THE OFFICERS FROM CAMP TAYLOR</pattern><template>Hello, Jordan.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AFRAID I HAVEN'T BEEN A VERY GOOD HOST  OLD SPORT</pattern><template>You see… I'm Gatsby.</template></category><category><pattern>SO NICK  DAISY TELLS ME THAT YOU'RE OVER IN WEST EGG</pattern><template>Throwing your lot in with those social climbing primitive new money types.</template></category><category><pattern>FIVE YEARS AGO  IN LOUISVILLE</pattern><template>That was the day I got my new English golf shoes.</template></category><category><pattern>…HE BECAME A WAR HERO  SINGLE HANDEDLY DEFEATING THE GERMAN ARMY   IN THE ARGONNE FOREST  I TOOK TWO MACHINE GUN DETACHMENTS  SO FAR— OUTNUMBERED  FIVE TO ONE— THERE WAS HALF A MILE GAP ON EITHER SIDE— THERE WASN'T A SINGLE GERMAN SOLDIER LEFT STANDING— WE STAYED THERE TWO DAYS AND TWO NIGHTS— AND WE SAW PILES OF DEAD— 130 MEN  WITH ONLY 16 LEWIS GUNS— EVERY ALLIED GOVERNMENT GAVE ME A MEDAL — EVEN MONTENEGRO</pattern><template>Here, that's from Montenegro.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR WIFE DOESN'T LOVE YOU</pattern><template>She never loved you.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO TO TOWN</pattern><template>Who wants to go to town?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TAKING MY NEW HYDROPLANE OUT IN THE MORNING</pattern><template>Would you like to go with me?</template></category><category><pattern>HE MUST BE AWAKE</pattern><template>Shall we?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST FOR A DRINK OR TWO</pattern><template>None of us could ignore that fifth guest's shrill metallic urgency.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE BEST THING A GIRL IN THIS WORLD CAN BE</pattern><template>A beautiful little fool.</template></category><category><pattern>NICK  I WANT YOU AND DAISY BOTH TO COME OVER TO MY HOUSE</pattern><template>I'd like to show her around.</template></category><category><pattern>MYRTLE  GET EVERYBODY A DRINK BEFORE THEY FALL ASLEEP</pattern><template>Tom, I'm— I'm just leaving now.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A CROOK  GEORGE  YES… THROWS ALL THOSE PARTIES THE PAPERS ARE ALWAYS TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>Maybe he was the one that was fooling around with Myrtle.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T FORGET  WE'RE GOING UP IN THAT HYDROPLANE TOMORROW MORNING</pattern><template>Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU NOW  ISN'T THAT ENOUGH</pattern><template>I can't help what's past.</template></category><category><pattern>I SWORE I WOULDN'T TELL</pattern><template>Sorry to keep her from you, old sport.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  OF COURSE  NOTHING IS 100%</pattern><template>Though I wouldn't go investing every penny.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM ONE OF THE FINEST FAMILIES IN THE MIDWEST</pattern><template>Sadly, all dead now.</template></category><category><pattern>NEITHER OF THEM CAN STAND THE PERSON THEY'RE MARRIED TO</pattern><template>Doesn't she like Wilson either?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TELEPHONE FOR A TAXI  NICK</pattern><template>Why don't you come inside and have some supper while you wait?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL SEND IT OVER TOMORROW</pattern><template>Fine! Fine, fine.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'LL WE DO WITH OURSELVES THIS AFTERNOON OR  THE DAY AFTER THAT  OR FOR THE NEXT THIRTY YEARS</pattern><template>Oh, don't be morbid.</template></category><category><pattern>NICK  DAISY'S READY</pattern><template>She's ready, there's just… one thing she's requesting, that you and Mrs Baker be there for lunch tomorrow at her house.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY NEEDS YOU</pattern><template>We need you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I ASKED THE NURSE IF IT WAS A BOY OR A GIRL</pattern><template>And she said it was a girl.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THE GRASS LOOKS FINE  IF THAT'S WHAT YOU MEAN</pattern><template>Grass? What grass?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A MINUTE</pattern><template>I wanna ask Mr. Gatsby one more question.</template></category><category><pattern>— MAY I INTRODUCE SENATOR GULICK</pattern><template>This is Mr. Carraway.</template></category><category><pattern>— SOMEONE  WAKE EWING</pattern><template>— Of course, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING ALRIGHT</pattern><template>Yes! Yes, we… we were just talking about other people's wives.</template></category><category><pattern>SO MANY DASHING YOUNG OFFICERS HERE  AND FROM SUCH ILLUSTRIOUS FAMILIES</pattern><template>I always knew that I could climb.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE BLOSSOMED FOR HIM LIKE A FLOWER…   AND THE INCARNATION WAS COMPLETE   I KNEW IT WAS A GREAT MISTAKE FOR A MAN LIKE ME TO FALL IN LOVE</pattern><template>I'm only 32, I might still be a great man if I can forget that I once lost Daisy, but… my life, old sport, my life… My life has got to be like this.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S QUITE EMOTIONAL</pattern><template>Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>A BEAUTIFUL LITTLE FOOL</pattern><template>All the bright, precious things fade so fast.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE JUST AS MUCH AS YOU  THAT MEANS WE'RE EQUAL</pattern><template>Oh, no! No.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  I'LL GET THE CHAIRS  UH… MIRT  WHY DON'T YOU UH… DON'T YOU ENTERTAIN</pattern><template>— Oh yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>MCKEE IS IN THE ARTISTIC GAME</pattern><template>— Photography.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT TONIGHT</pattern><template>Jay, do you understand that a woman has been killed?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S AN OLD CLOCK</pattern><template>— Lovely though, a lovely clock.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU  DID YOU RANSACK A GREENHOUSE</pattern><template>He IS in love with me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID YOURSELF WRITING BROUGHT YOU SOLACE</pattern><template>Yeah well… it didn't bring anyone else much solace.</template></category><category><pattern>OXFORD  NEW MEXICO</pattern><template>He wears a pink suit, for Christ sake.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD ALWAYS BURN IT</pattern><template>— What would I write about?</template></category><category><pattern>— WELL  IT'S ALL RATHER STRANGE  HE PICKS ME UP IN HIS FANCY YELLOW CAR  AND HE'S GOING ON AND ON ABOUT HIS LIFE  — PLEASE KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN  — AND THE WAR AND… — EVERYBODY CAN HEAR YOU</pattern><template>— What is this enormous request, Jordan— — He wants you to invite Daisy to tea.</template></category><category><pattern>MADAME  THE DÎNER IS SERVI</pattern><template>Would you like to hear a family secret?</template></category><category><pattern>GONE AWAY  DO YOU KNOW WHEN THEY'LL BE BACK</pattern><template>No. They have already departed.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I THINK ABOUT IT  THE HISTORY OF THE SUMMER REALLY BEGAN   THE NIGHT I DROVE OVER TO MY COUSIN DAISY'S FOR DINER    SHE LIVED ACROSS THE BAY IN OLD MONEYED EAST EGG    HER HUSBAND WAS HEIR TO ONE OF AMERICA'S WEALTHIEST FAMILIES    HIS NAME WAS TOM BUCHANAN    WHEN WE WERE AT YALE TOGETHER  HE'D BEEN A SPORTING STAR    NOW HIS GLORY DAYS WERE BEHIND HIM  AND HE CONTENTED HIMSELF WITH—  — TELEPHONE  MONSIEUR BUCHANAN</pattern><template>— It's me.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT GATSBY  HE'S A BUSINESSMAN  HE OWNED A LOT OF DRUGSTORES</pattern><template>— Businessman!</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  NO ONE HAS</pattern><template>Alone and a little embarrassed, I decided to get roaring drunk.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU TAKE NICK AND JORDAN</pattern><template>— I suppose you can, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>— WITH ME</pattern><template>— Yes, madam.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO NO NO NO NO</pattern><template>No, she is not leaving me.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'LL PAY</pattern><template>Oh, he will pay.</template></category><category><pattern>DAISY BUCHANAN  THE GOLDEN GIRL    A BREATHLESS WARMTH FLOWED FROM HER    A PROMISE THAT THERE WAS NO ONE ELSE IN THE WORLD SHE SO WANTED TO SEE   DO THEY MISS ME IN CHICAGO</pattern><template>Uh yes, huh, uhm… At least a dozen people send their love.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WAIT HERE</pattern><template>I'll see if there's any commotion.</template></category><category><pattern>PAMMY</pattern><template>Oh, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>NEW YORK'S DUMPING GROUND HALF WAY BETWEEN WEST EGG AND THE CITY    WHERE THE BURNT OUT COAL THAT POWERED THE BOOMING GOLDEN CITY WAS DISCARDED BY MEN    WHO MOVED DIMLY AND ALREADY CRUMBLING THROUGH THE POWDERY AIR    THIS FANTASTIC FARM WAS EVER WATCHED BY DR  T J  ECKLEBURG    A FORGOTTEN OCULIST WHOSE EYES BROODED OVER IT ALL    LIKE THE EYES OF GOD    TOM HAD INVITED ME TO TOWN</pattern><template>Apparently for lunch at the Yale club.   But the day took an unexpected turn.  Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GONNA SIT ON THE SIDE AND WATCH  UH</pattern><template>Or is he gonna play ball?</template></category></AIML>