<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>HERE  THIS THE BEST ONE    THIS IS A GOOD ONE</pattern><template>Yeah, The best shit, man,   Okay, Here you go, I'II take one,   Keep the change,   Thank you, Want a cigarette?</template></category><category><pattern>STAY DOWN</pattern><template>WeII, if he wasn't an insurgent, he sure the heII is now, Roger that, That's reaI funny, Got something, Oh, baby, Gotcha, AII right, We're done, Good to go, Come down, speciaIist, Roger, Got a wire, Hang on, Where are you going?</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT  COME ON  WHERE'S THE FIVE DOIIARS</pattern><template>Man, come on, AII right, I got ya, Good job, dude, Here's five, You're an EOD, boomaIa, boomaIa, That's right, It's fun, no?</template></category><category><pattern>WIII HAS POSSESSIONS  I DIDN'T KNOW YOU OWNED ANYTHING  WIII  LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT HERE  WIII  WHO IS THAT</pattern><template>That's my son, He's a tough IittIe bastard, Nothing Iike me, You mean to teII me you married?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WHERE'D YOU SAY YOU WERE AGAIN</pattern><template>I didn't, sergeant, Let's go, What happened to your head, James?</template></category><category><pattern>AW  SHIT  THE BIOOD'S MAKING IT JAM  EIDRIDGE  SHIT</pattern><template>You gotta cIean the bIood off, man, It's making 'em jam, SpeciaIist!</template></category><category><pattern>CIEAN THE BIOOD OFF    OKAY  CIEAN IT  CIEAN IT  YOU GOTTA CIEAN IT  MAN    HOW</pattern><template>Spit and rub, AII right, Spit and rub, buddy, Spit and rub, It's not working,It's not coming off, Spit and rub, Spit and rub, Here, take it out, Use your cameI, Use your cameI, Where is it?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THE U S  ARMY DID  AII RIGHT  LOOKS IIKE I'M GOING DOWN THERE  YOU DON;T IIKE WAITING AROUND THIS BEAUTIFUI NEIGHBORHOOD</pattern><template>Oh, I Iove it, So, if everything Iooks okay, when I get down there I'm just going to set it up and bip it, Give these peopIe something to think about, Want them to know if they're gonna Ieave a bomb on the side of the road for us, we're just going to bIow up their IittIe fuckin' road, Sounds good, Craving a burger; is that strange?</template></category><category><pattern>BE SMART  MAKE A GOOD DECISION  OVER GOT MORE WIRE  LEADS FUCKING NOWHERE  FUCK</pattern><template>Hey, James, how you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU READY</pattern><template>Game face, buddy, Let's go,   You ready?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD MORNING  COIONEI    GOOD MORNING  MIND IF I RIDE AIONG  I'M SICK TO DEATH OF SITTING BEHIND A DESK AII THE TIME  THAT'D BE A PRIVIIEGE  HOP IN  COIONEI  HEY  DOC  NOT TO INSUIT YOUR INTEIIIGENCE  SIR  BUT IF THE SHIT HITS THE FAN  PIEASE DON'T FIRE OUT THE HUMVEE  THE ROUND WIII JUST BOUNCE AROUND  AND SOMEONE MIGHT GET SHOT    I DON'T IIKE GETTING SHOT    UNDERSTOOD  SERGEANT  OH  IT'S A PRETTY STANDARD MISSION  WE'RE JUST HERE TO PICK UP SOME UNEXPIODED ORDINANCE  SERGEANT JAMES IS GONNA SEE WHAT THE DEAI IS  AND THEN HOPEFUIIY WE'II BE GONE IN A COUPIE MINUTES    WE'VE GOTTA GEAR UP    FOR WHAT</pattern><template>Security hasn't gone in, Go in quiet,   Radios off,   Roger,   Roger that,   GIad you came,   See ya, AII right, Psst, Psst, CIear, Hey, cigarette's stiII smoking, It's aII our shit, Mother fucking goIdmine, Watch out for trips, I got something, I know this kid, His name's Beckham, He seIIs DVDs, You ever see a body bomb before, man?</template></category><category><pattern>AII RIGHT  HOID ON  BOYS  WE NEED SOME RUIES  SANBORN  NO FACE SHOTS  OH  THERE'S GONNA BE A FACE SHOT  SERGEANT JAMES  TAKE OFF YOUR SHIRT  YES  SIR  WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>My momma dropped me when I was a baby, Looks Iike frag scars,   Let it go, EIdridge, C'mon,   AII right, Nice and big, Oohh!</template></category><category><pattern>BASTARD  WE'RE DONE  SANBORN  IET'S GET OUT OF HERE  WOO  THAT WAS GOOD    HEY  JAMES    WHAT</pattern><template>Never turn your headset off again, You the guy in the bomb suit?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  USE THAT  JUST BREATHE  BUDDY  COME ON  JUST BREATHE IN  GOOD  HERE  SQUEEZE    GOT IT</pattern><template>Yeah, Rub that ojive, baby, Come on, You got it, You're doing good, man, You're doing reaI good,   Got 'em?</template></category><category><pattern>GO  BUDDY  STAY IOW</pattern><template>Stay Iow!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON  IT'S THE TIGHT SHIT  MAN  WANNA BUY DVD</pattern><template>Wanna buy DVD?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SPEAK ENGIISH NOW  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>YaIIa, yaIIa, Drive,   Okay,   Ok,   Is this his house?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU AII RIGHT</pattern><template>Aw, man, I fuckin' hate this pIace, Here, man, Have a hit, I'm not ready to die, James, WeII, you're not going to die out here, bro, Another two inches, ShrapneI zings by, sIices my throat, I bIeed out Iike a pig in the sand, Nobody'II give a shit, I mean, my parents'II care, but they don;t count, man, Who eIse?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT TO SHAKE YOUR HAND    THANK YOU  SIR    YEAH  HOW MANY BOMBS HAVE YOU DISARMED</pattern><template>Uh, I'm not quite sure,   Sergeant?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MY SON  HE'S A TOUGH IITTIE BASTARD  NOTHING IIKE ME  YOU MEAN TO TEII ME YOU MARRIED</pattern><template>WeII, you know, I had a girIfriend and,,, ,,,she got pregnant, so we got married, We got divorced, Or I thought we got divorced, She's stiII Iiving in the house, And she says we're stiII together, so I don't know, What does that make her?</template></category><category><pattern>SPECIAIIST  WHAT DO WE GOT</pattern><template>We have,,, 23 more days or 22,,,   Oh yeah, No one's counting, Contact Ieft, Take cover, Chris, take the 50, Jimmy, take that in the Humvee,   Got it,   Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK ON THE DEAD GUY  MAN  IT'S ON THE DEAD MAN  EIDRIDGE</pattern><template>I'm Iooking, We need that ammo, man, AII right, man, Oh, here, Thanks, AII right, Got it, Same target, It's fucking jammed, Let me see it, Fuck!</template></category><category><pattern>ON THREE  READY</pattern><template>One, two, three, Aahh!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S DISGUSTING  LET'S GET OUTTA HERE  HOID IT  EIDRIDGE  WANT YOU TO GRAB AII THE C4 AND DECK CORD YOU CAN GET YOUR HANDS ON  LET'S GET AII THIS ORDINANCE OUTTA HERE  AND WE'RE JUST GONNA    WE'RE GONNA BIOW THE PIACE  ROGER  JUST BIOW IT  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Yeah? Putting the stones in to move, Yeah,That's reaIIy wonderfuI, but it's a IittIe bit unsafe today, Yeah, it's a IittIe unsafe, So maybe,,, I don't know, I'm thinking maybe we shouId move?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO  A CAR STOPPED IN FRONT OF HIM  SANBORN SHIT  JAMES  JAMES  COME BACK NOW  EOD PUIIED A NINE ON THIS HAJI IN A CAR  WANT ME TO SEND BACKUP</pattern><template>I got it,   Get here!</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWHERE'S GOOD    IS THAT EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Yeah, Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>I'II TAKE CARE OF IT  DON'T YOU WANT TO SEND THE BOT DOWN THERE TO SEE WHAT IT IOOKS IIKE</pattern><template>I'II handIe it, That's kind of tight down here, James, Ready?</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU  COME  COME  PIEASE  PIEASE  NEW REIEASES  LOOK  HEIIO  HEIIO  WANT TO BUY DVDS  VERY GOOD  VERY GOOD  HOW MUCH</pattern><template>One for five and two for nine, Three for tweIve, Three for thirteen and I don;t give you tax, Very good, man, Look,   Look,,,   No tax?</template></category><category><pattern>UH  YES  SIR    HE'S A WIID MAN  YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>I want to shake your hand,   Thank you, sir,   Yeah, How many bombs have you disarmed?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE EDGE OF THE BIAST RADIUS  JESUS  SO  WHERE'S OUR TRIGGERMAN</pattern><template>Burnt up in the fIames, man, Suicide bomber, We're never going to find a body in that shit, What if there was no body?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  EIDRIDGE</pattern><template>I can't get him in sight!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Back up, HeIIo?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE'S HERE TO SEE YOU  YOU THE GUY IN THE FIAMING CAR  SERGEANT JAMES</pattern><template>Afternoon, sir, Uh, yes, sir, WeII, that's just hot shit, You're a wiId man, you know that?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S CRAP    GIRIS ON DOG</pattern><template>Gay sex, man?</template></category><category><pattern>CHARIIE  GO</pattern><template>Go, go, go!</template></category><category><pattern>I COUIDN'T DO ANYTHING WITH HIM UNTII I GOT THE CIEAR FROM MY CO  OKAY  FUCK  FUCK  DOES THIS CHANGE ANYTHING</pattern><template>You speak EngIish now, Don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM VERY PIEASED TO SEE CIA IN MY HOME  PIEASE  SIT  HOW CAN I    BE CAREFUI  THE GUN CAN GO OFF  U S A  FRIENDIY COMING IN  STOP STOP  GET THE FUCK DOWN  U S A  FRIENDIY  ON YOUR KNEES  GET ON YOUR KNEES NOW  ON YOUR KNEES  YOU WIII BE SHOT  DON;T MOVE  ON YOUR KNEES  DOWN NOW    OPEN YOUR JACKET</pattern><template>Opening my jacket, Cover, Get him down,   On the ground,   I have a weapon, Don't fucking move,   Tower, hoId cover, Searching,   I have a weapon,   Gun,   Like I said, Weapons cIear, ID, What the fuck are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  I THINK IT'S IOGICAI  THIS IS WAR  PEOPIE DIE AII THE TIME  WHY NOT ME</pattern><template>You got to change the record in our head, You gotta start thinking about other things, Okay, Stop obsessing,,, Right now, What are you thinking about?</template></category><category><pattern>TANKERS AND TROOPS ARE THAT WAY    LET'S GO THIS WAY    FUCK  USE YOUR TORCH  ON TORCH  READY</pattern><template>One, two, three,Fuck,   Fuck!,   Shit, SoftIy, softIy, softIy, On three, One, Two, Three, Now, Go, go, go,   EIdridge, you okay?</template></category><category><pattern>WOOH  HE'S A WIID ONE  WE GOT A WIID ONE  C'MON  SANBORN  GET HIM THAT'S RIGHT    RIDE HIM  BABY    GET OFF ME    C'MON  BITCH    C'MON  GUYS  WHAT DO YOU GOT</pattern><template>Get off me, Hey, hey, hey, I'm just kidding, motherfucker, Shit, You're aII right, Sanborn, You're aII right, Man, Owen, get this guy a drink, C'mon,   You got him?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO GO GET US SOME CEREAI AND I'II MEET YOU AT THE CHECKOUT</pattern><template>Okay, CereaI, Where?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT BAD</pattern><template>Fuckin' sucks, man,   Ah, ah!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW IET'S GET THESE BASTARDS  SCAN YOUR SECTORS  SCAN YOUR SECTORS  KIII THAT FUCKIN' ASSHOIE  SON OF A BITCH  NICE  HE'S DOWN  TWENTY METERS TO THE RIGHT OF THE BUIIDING  I GOT HIM  FIRE WHEN READY  HE'S MOVING  HE'S MOVING  TO THE BUIIDING    FOIIOW HIM  YOU GOT HIM</pattern><template>Got him, He's down, Goodnight, Thanks for pIaying, Window, The window, At the window, He's stiII there, Left window, Left window, Got him?</template></category><category><pattern>CAMBRIDGE  FUCK</pattern><template>Cambridge!</template></category><category><pattern>BIASTER ONE  YOU THERE</pattern><template>BIaster One, you hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I GOT HIM    AII RIGHT  HERE    AII RIGHT    SEE YOU IATER    BE SAFE    AII RIGHT  AII RIGHT  COME ON BIG BOY  DAMN  BOY  YOU NEED TO GET ON A DIET  HE HURT HIS KNEE  C'MON  MAN  STEPS  C'MON  STEP  STEP  AII RIGHT  IAY DOWN  AII RIGHT  GET SOME REST  HEY  JAMES  YOU THINK I GOT WHAT IT TAKES TO PUT ON THE SUIT</pattern><template>HeII, no, Night, boy, Oh!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WHERE</pattern><template>He's right at my 12:00, you see him?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MOVE  IF YOU KEEP WAIKING WE WIII SHOOT YOU  MOVE HIM BACK  KEEP THAT TRANSIATOR BACK    BUT THE BOMB WAS FORCED ON HIM    GET HIM BACK</pattern><template>Don't move! Stay stiII, If you keep waIking we wiII shoot you, If Get that transIator back, now, Give him room, Give him room, Hey, what do you got?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE FUCK HE'S DOING  LOOKS IIKE  HE'S CHECKING THE OII  THEY'RE COMMUNICATING WITH YOUR CAMERAMAN  THIS IS REAI BAD MAN  GET BEHIND THE JERSEY BARRIER  I CAN'T SEE JAMES FROM HERE  GET DOWN NOW</pattern><template>We can go!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THAT WAY  BACK  TAXI'S MOVING  GET OUT OF THE CAR</pattern><template>Stop!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU IIKE THAT  HUH</pattern><template>That's aII you got?</template></category><category><pattern>PUT DOWN THE PHONE</pattern><template>Come on, guys, TaIk to me, Drop the phone!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  MAN  WANNA PIAY SOME    AWW  FUCK  HOW YOU DOING  BUDDY</pattern><template>Doc says you're going to be okay, My fucking femur is shattered in nine pIaces, He said I'II be waIking in six months if I'm fucking Iucky,   Six months ain't bad, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I THINK SO  TEII YOU WHAT  I'M GOING TO BUY    LET ME SEE IF I HAVE ENOUGH MONEY  YEAH  FIVE  I'M GOING TO BUY ANOTHER DVD  OKAY</pattern><template>But if it's shakey,,, Iook at me,,, or out of focus,,, or any way not 100o/o, I'm going to chop off your goddammed head with a duII knife, How do you feeI about that?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOU WANT THE COOI SHIT</pattern><template>Come on, come on, It's the tight shit, man, Wanna buy DVD?</template></category><category><pattern>OWEN  HI    HI  SIR    HOW ARE YOU</pattern><template>I'm good,   Good,   What's wrong?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I TOUCH MY FUCKING HEAD NOW</pattern><template>SIowIy, We're on the same fucking side, guys, Jesus, You guys are wired fucking tight, you know that?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD TO GO    LET'S DO IT    GOT TWO OF 'EM</pattern><template>Got two, AII right, Let's rock and roII, man,   He's a rowdy boy,   He's reckIess, BIaster One, what's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>AT YOUR SIX O'CIOCK I SEE MOVEMENT ON THE BRIDGE  RIGHT ON THE TRACKS  WEII  HANDIE IT  SHOUID I FIRE</pattern><template>It's your caII, buddy, Good job, Hey, Sanborn, I think we're done, Okay? You aII right?</template></category><category><pattern>NEGATIVE  NEGATIVE</pattern><template>Stand down, The bIast wiII come up the bIock, Stay cIear around the corner, EOD has the situation under controI, over, Where you going?</template></category><category><pattern>DEAI  GET UP THERE  GO ON    LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT HOT STUFF    ARE YOU READY</pattern><template>On three, Ready?</template></category><category><pattern>EIDRIDGE  C'MON  MAN  C'MON I JUST SAW HIM  HE WAS WAIKING RIGHT HERE  I KNOW  HE'S DEAD  LOOK  HE'S DEAD  OKAY</pattern><template>It's aII right, man, It'II be aII right, man, HeIIo?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEII IT  I FERTIIIZE IT  (LAUGHS)   25    25 METERS  ROGER THAT  SANBORN</pattern><template>Butcher shop, 2:00, dude has a phone!</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAS FOUR CHIIDREN  SHIT  SANBORN  WE GOT A TIMER  AND WE GOT A IOT OF WIRES  MAN  I'M GOING TO NEED A IITTIE HEIP ON THIS  ROGER THAT  TEII ME WHAT YOU NEED  BOIT CUTTERS  YOU GOTTA GET DOWN HERE IN TWO MINUTES OR WE'RE AII FUCKED  ROGER THAT  I'II BE THERE IN 30 SECONDS  HE SAYS  PIEASE  I HAVE A FAMIIY  SST  I KNOW  IT'S OKAY  YOU'RE AII RIGHT  YOU'RE AII RIGHT  PIEASE  DON'T IEAVE ME  YOU WEREN'T FUCKIN' KIDDING  NOPE  WHAT'S THIS MADE OUT OF</pattern><template>Oh, man, That's case iron steeI, Shit,   What's our time?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  RUB THAT OJIVE  BABY  COME ON  YOU GOT IT  YOU'RE DOING GOOD  MAN  YOU'RE DOING REAI GOOD    GOT 'EM</pattern><template>Yeah, I'm going to keep you safe, buddy, aII right?</template></category><category><pattern>DAMMIT  THIS IS AIPHA NINE  WE'RE IN DEEP SHIT  I'II GET ON THE BARRET  GO  GO  GO  YEAH  WE'RE TAKING INCOMING FIRE  GO  GO  GO    NO  SANBORN  DON'T COME UP HERE    GOT IT</pattern><template>Go, buddy, Stay Iow!</template></category><category><pattern>SOME GUY DROVE HIS TRUCK TO THE MIDDIE OF AN IRAQI MARKET  STARTS PASSING OUT FREE CANDIES  AII THE KIDS COMING RUNNING UP  THE FAMIIIES STUFF  HE DETONATES  THEY'RE SAYING 59 ARE DEAD  YOU KNOW THEY NEED MORE BOMB TECHS  YOU WANT TO CHOP THOSE UP FOR ME</pattern><template>Boing, boing, boing, Yeah, You Iove pIaying with that, You Iove pIaying with aII your stuffed animaIs, You Iove your mommy, your daddy, your nature pajamas, You Iove everything, don't you? Yeah, You know what, buddy?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT    YOU GOT A GIRI</pattern><template>What do you got?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S AII YOU GOT</pattern><template>Come on, Bring some, C'mon, Ooh!</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  WE HAVE A TANK EXPIOSION IN THE GREEN ZONE  WE HAVE TO POST BIAST ASSESSMENT  SEE IF IT WAS A SUICIDE BOMBER  AND IF SO  HOW THE FUCK DID HE DO IT</pattern><template>Okay, Where'd you say you were again?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU GRAB THE JUICE OUT OF THE PACK PIEASE</pattern><template>Sure, I think we're out,   Got anything Ieft to drink?</template></category><category><pattern>STOP</pattern><template>Stay down!</template></category><category><pattern>THOMPSON</pattern><template>Anywhere's good,   Is that everything?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S POINTING THE FUCKING THING AT ME  SHIT  NEGATIVE  I DON'T SEE HIM  HEY  SANBORN  HE'S RIGHT AT MY 12:00  LOOK  12:00</pattern><template>Roger that, I got him, Getting ready to put me on You Tube,   LittIe shady,  Yeah, he Iooks shady, Keep and eye on him, Okay, So, what's the pIay?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TWO KIA  CORRECTION  THREE KIA    OUR GRID IAST IOCK STAT    STAY IOW</pattern><template>Can you get me some heIp?</template></category><category><pattern>PRETEND IT'S YOUR DICK  MAN  HOW ABOUT I PRETEND IT'S YOUR DICK</pattern><template>You'II never get in if you did that,   Here, Let me have a shot,   Give me a second,   No, come on, My dick, man,   Go, Fucker,   Got that,   Yeah, Here we go,   Oh, Iook at that,   Nice 155, huh?   Yeah, It's going to do some fucking damage, Hey, EIdridge, Iooks Iike we're going to need a charge, I got that, Figured four bIocks that'II give us about 20 pounds of bang totaI, That bIast is going to roast straight out there, The sheII wiII probabIy kick out there, and most of the shrapneI is going to shoot straight up in a beautifuI umbreIIa pattern, Yep, We're gonna get some smaIIer pieces and sheII fragments this way, but we'II be okay if we're behind the Humvee,   Bring the bot back, we'II Ioad it up,   No probIem, Bot is moving, Let me know what you got, EIdridge, Good to go, AII right, Wagon's set up, Bot moves, Uh oh, We got goats, guys, Goats 12:00, Watch out, Load them IittIe bastards up,   Oh, shit,   Shit, Oh, fuck, Wagon's having a bad day, boys,   You buiId that?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON;T HAVE TO GO DOWN THERE  WE AIREADY HAVE THE BOT HAIFWAY UP  I'II BE AII RIGHT  FIRST DAY  FIGURE YOU WANT TO TAKE IT EASY  RIGHT</pattern><template>How's it Iooking, EIdridge?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S RIGHT AT MY 12:00  YOU SEE HIM</pattern><template>He's pointing the fucking thing at me, Shit, Negative, I don't see him, Hey, Sanborn, He's right at my 12:00, Look! 12:00!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST SAYING SHIT HAPPENS  THEY MISFIRE  HE'D BE OBIITERATED TO NOTHING  HIS HEIMET WOUID BE IEFT  YOU COUID HAVE THAT  LITTIE SPECS OF HAIR  CHARRED ON THE INSIDE  YEAH  THERE'D BE HAIF A HEIMET SOMEWHERE  BITS OF HAIR  ASK FOR A CHANGE IN TECHNIQUE AND PROTOCOI  MAKE SURE THIS TYPE OF ACCIDENT NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>You'd have to write the report,   Are you serious?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU'RE A GOOD WARRIOR  GIVE ME YOUR MUG  THERE YA GO  SIR  YOU WERE WEII ON THE FIEID OF BATTIE TODAY  SPECIAIIST  CHEERS  UH  I'M TOO OID FOR THIS SHIT    I WAS SCARED    YEAH</pattern><template>WeII, everyone's a coward about something, you know, You're good, You're reaI good, Just what do we have here?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  NO NO  I DON'T  I'M KIDDING  SHIT  IT'S COMING FROM OVER HERE</pattern><template>BIaster One, You there?</template></category><category><pattern>ROGER THAT  I GOT HIM  GETTING READY TO PUT ME ON YOU TUBE    LITTIE SHADY   YEAH  HE IOOKS SHADY  KEEP AND EYE ON HIM  OKAY  SO  WHAT'S THE PIAY</pattern><template>Be smart, Make a good decision, over Got more wire, Leads fucking nowhere, Fuck!</template></category><category><pattern>SIOWIY  WE'RE ON THE SAME FUCKING SIDE  GUYS  JESUS  YOU GUYS ARE WIRED FUCKING TIGHT  YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>WeII, this is no pIace for a picnic, What are you guys doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>BACK UP  HEIIO</pattern><template>Want to get back?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY GET BACK</pattern><template>Go, go!</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP YOUR HANDS UP    OKAY  EASY  EASY  GOT IT</pattern><template>Can I touch my fucking head now?</template></category><category><pattern>HEII  I DON'T KNOW  BUT I'II TEII YOU WHEN I'M STANDING OVER IT  COWBOY  TAKE COVER</pattern><template>Oh, no, A car stopped in front of him, Sanborn Shit, James! James, come back now, EOD puIIed a nine on this Haji in a car, Want me to send backup?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WHAT DO YOU GOT HERE</pattern><template>He has four chiIdren, Shit, Sanborn, we got a timer, and we got a Iot of wires, man, I'm going to need a IittIe heIp on this, Roger that, TeII me what you need, BoIt cutters, You gotta get down here in two minutes or we're aII fucked, Roger that, I'II be there in 30 seconds, He says, pIease, I have a famiIy, Sst, I know, It's okay, You're aII right, You're aII right, PIease, don't Ieave me, You weren't fuckin' kidding, Nope, What's this made out of?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST IN CASE THE RUSSIANS COME WE HAVE TO HAVE A BIG TANK BATTIE  I'D RATHER BE ON THE SIDE WITH THE TANKS  JUST IN CASE  RATHER THAN NOT HAVE THEM  YEAH  BUT THEY DON;T DO ANYTHING  ANYONE COMES AIONGSIDE A HUMVEE WE'RE DEAD  ANYBODY EVEN IOOKS AT YOU FUNNY WE'RE DEAD  PRETTY MUCH THE BOTTOM IINE IS IF YOU'RE IN IRAQ  YOU'RE DEAD  HOW'S A FUCKIN' TANK SUPPOSED TO STOP THAT</pattern><template>WouId you shut up, Owen?</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  I THINK WE'RE OUT    GOT ANYTHING IEFT TO DRINK</pattern><template>You couId try that one, Thank you, Drink, Drink it, Things are reaI quiet, Yeah, I don't Iike it,   Hey, WiII?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOOD  GOT A QUESTION ABOUT THAT SONG  ''BE AII YOU CAN BE''  WHAT IF AII I CAN BE IS DEAD ON THE SIDE OF AN IRAQI ROAD</pattern><template>I mean, I think it's IogicaI, This is war, PeopIe die aII the time, Why not me?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO BREAK OUT THE SUIT    WHAT ABOUT THE BOT</pattern><template>I'II take care of it, Don't you want to send the bot down there to see what it Iooks Iike?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY WEDDING RING  LIKE I SAID  STUFF THAT AIMOST KIIIED ME  YOU KNOW  I JUST THINK IT'S REAIIY INTERESTED TO HOID SOMETHING IN YOUR HAND THAT COUID HAVE KIIIED ANYONE  DAMN THAT  IT'S AII SHIT FROM RADIO SHACK  IT'S INTERESTING  I THINK IT'S INTERESTING TOO  WEII  I THINK YOU HIT ME HARDER THAN I HIT YOU THEREFORE I OWE YOU A PUNCH  NOW GET YOUR ASS UP  C'MON  C'MON  HE'S RIGHT  LET'S GO  C'MON  COME ON</pattern><template>AII right, hoId on, boys, We need some ruIes, Sanborn, no face shots, Oh, there's gonna be a face shot, Sergeant James, take off your shirt, Yes, sir, What happened?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MAN  BEST OF THE BEST  I'M BETTER THAN BECKHAM    YOU PIAY GOAIIE</pattern><template>Yes, I pIay goaIie,   Okay, I'II make you a deaI, If you can stop the baII, I'm going to give you five bucks,   but if you can't,,,   And what if,,, what if I can't?</template></category><category><pattern>MY MOMMA DROPPED ME WHEN I WAS A BABY  LOOKS IIKE FRAG SCARS    LET IT GO  EIDRIDGE  C'MON    AII RIGHT  NICE AND BIG  OOHH</pattern><template>You Iike that, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>ON YOUR KNEES</pattern><template>Put your gun down!</template></category><category><pattern>APPROACHING  I THINK WE HAVE TOUCHDOWN  LITTIE TO THE RIGHT  HEIIO  MUM  NOW  PUSH IT IN  I CAN'T  WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU CAN'T</pattern><template>Pretend it's your dick, man, How about I pretend it's your dick?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY UP AND OUT  JAMES</pattern><template>You aII right?</template></category><category><pattern>WANNA BUY SOME DVDS</pattern><template>Wanna pIay some soccer?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S AFFIRMATIVE  INTERESTING  WHAT'S UP WITH  JAMES</pattern><template>He's not answering, Yeah, I think he removed his headset, WeII, wiII you teII him to put his radio back on, pIease?</template></category><category><pattern>ENGIISH  FRENCH  ARABIC  GOOD  OPEN YOU VEST  AH  STAY THERE  STAY  TEII ME WHAT YOU KNOW ABOUT BECKHAM  FOR WHOM</pattern><template>Beckham, 12 year oId boy, body bomb, Stay right there,   I don't know,   You don't know, But pIease, sit down, I am Professor Navid, This is my home, You are a guest, PIease, sit down, I'm a guest, Just,,, I'm Iooking for the peopIe responsibIe for for for Beckham, You are CIA, no?</template></category><category><pattern>BEHIND YOU    YEAH  BREATHE EASY    I GOT MOVEMENT    YEAH  ON THE RIDGE OF THAT HOUSE EIGHT HUNDRED AND FIFTY METERS    SEE IT    BY THE WINDOW    YOU GOT TARGET    GOT IT  AII RIGHT  HERE IITTIE IEFT  JUST BREATHE EASY    I'M OUT OF AMMO    HMM</pattern><template>I'm out of ammo, EIdridge, we need ammo, Where is it?</template></category><category><pattern>FUCKIN' SUCKS  MAN    AH  AH</pattern><template>Take it easy, You see that? You fuckin' see that?</template></category><category><pattern>THREE METERS HIGHER  I'M GOING TO ADJUST  FUCK FUCK  HE'S DEAD  WE'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE NOW</pattern><template>Dammit, This is AIpha Nine, We're in deep shit, I'II get on the Barret, Go, go, go, Yeah, we're taking incoming fire, Go, go, go,   No, Sanborn, don't come up here,   Got it!</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING YOU WANT  YOU GET  I HOOK YOU UP  MAN  AII RIGHT  WHAT    WHAT'S YOUR NAME</pattern><template>Beckham,   Beckham Iike the soccer pIayer?</template></category><category><pattern>YAIIA  YAIIA  DRIVE    OKAY    OK    IS THIS HIS HOUSE</pattern><template>He there?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW'S IT IOOKING  EIDRIDGE</pattern><template>Good to go,   Let's do it,   Got two of 'em?</template></category><category><pattern>EIDRIDGE  BURN HIM</pattern><template>Get out of the way,   Drop your phone!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH    YOU</pattern><template>Yeah,   You aII right, man?</template></category><category><pattern>READY  FIRE IN THE HOIE</pattern><template>Fire in the hoIe, Fire in the hoIe, Whoa, whoa, whoa, HoId on a second, Goddamn it, I think it forgot my gIoves down there,   What?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CRAZY NOW</pattern><template>Yeah, The DVD you soId me was crap, You crazy, man, That's impossibIe, It's HoIIywood speciaI effects, No, It was shaky, It was out of focus, buddy,   What, you want donkey porn?</template></category><category><pattern>EIDRIDGE  GET UP ON THE WAII  MOVE</pattern><template>TeII me what you see, speciaIist, AII right, I got him, He's waIking down range, James, the smoke is kiIIing my visibiIity, Where are you in reIationship to the IED?</template></category><category><pattern>OBRE  MOTHERFUCKER</pattern><template>HoId up your hands, Get down, motherfucker, Obre!</template></category><category><pattern>YEP  GO GET 'EM    KEEP YOUR EYES OUT ON THESE    YEAH  GET YOUR HANDS UP  HE SAYS HE HAS A FAMIIY  PIEASE HEIP HIM  NOW  IISTEN  LOOK  IT'D BE A IOT EASIER FOR ME TO DISARM THIS IF I JUST SHOOT YOU  DO YOU UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>What's he saying?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S GOING ON WITH THE SMOKE ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD  OVER  CREATING A DIVERSION FROM WHAT  IS THERE A THREAT</pattern><template>EIdridge, get up on the waII, Move!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THIS GUY</pattern><template>How do we know that he's not giving inteI to insurgents, teIIing them where to drop mortars?</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  MAN  ENGIISH I    NO ENGIISH  NO NO ENGIISH  YOU NO SPEAK ENGIISH NOW  LITTIE KID  BECKHAM IS HIS NAME  HE SEIIS    SEIIS DVDS  DVD  ONE DVD  $5  OH  JESUS CHRIST    $5    EXCUSE ME  SOIDIER  YOU IN CHARGE OF THIS AREA HERE</pattern><template>What's up?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M WONDERFUI  HOW ARE YOU</pattern><template>You know, we've been here a whiIe, We need to get out of here soon, Uh huh, We got a Iot of eyes on us, James, We need to get out of here, Roger that, I'm going to figure this out, James, we need to get out of here, James, do you copy?</template></category><category><pattern>GO GET IT</pattern><template>Come on, EIdridge!</template></category><category><pattern>SIOWIY  GET DOWN  OKAY  I NEED YOUR RADIO    CAN'T WE JUST SHOOT HIM</pattern><template>No, He's a a famiIy man, He's not a bad man, He's asking for heIp, onIy heIp, Yeah, aII right, You don;t want to die, get back! I got it, Listen, I know we've had our differences, It happened, aII right, It's water under the bridge, This is suicide, man, That's why they caII it a suicide bomb, right?</template></category><category><pattern>I IOVE IT HERE  THIS IS A BEAUTIFUI PIACE  BUT IT'S NOT TOO SAFE HERE  OKAY</pattern><template>So, I think we need   we need to move, PIease, You think it's that IittIe Beckham?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S JUST SEIIING DVDS  MAN  AII THE MERCHANTS ARE CIEAR    BY WHO</pattern><template>I couIdn't do anything with him untiI I got the cIear from my CO, Okay, Fuck, Fuck, Does this change anything?</template></category><category><pattern>GET BACK  GET DOWN  STAY BACK  STAY BACK  SANBORN  KEEP 'EM BACK  IS ANYONE HURT</pattern><template>Cambridge! Fuck!</template></category><category><pattern>STAY IOW</pattern><template>I have two KIA, correction, three KIA,,, our grid Iast Iock stat,,, Stay Iow!</template></category><category><pattern>BIASTER ONE  THIS IS BIASTER MIKE  WHAT'S WITH THE SMOKE ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD</pattern><template>Hey, James, can you hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT HERE  PERFECT VANTAGE POINT  OUTSIDE THE BIAST RADIUS TO SIT BACK AND WATCH US CIEAN UP THEIR MESS    WANT TO GO OUT THERE</pattern><template>Yes, I do,   I couId stand to get in a IittIe troubIe,   No, man, This is buIIshit, You got three infantry pIatoons behind you whose job it is to go Haji huntin', That ain't our fuckin' job, You don;t say no to me, Sanborn, I say no to you, You know there are guys watching us right now, They're Iaughing at this, Okay, I'm not okay with that, Now, turn off your goddammed torch 'cause we're going, Now we know where their oiI tanker came from, No shit, Same kind,   We're cIose,   Yeah, They aIIeyways are probabIy set up on a grid, We're going to need to spIit up, fIush 'em out, Sanborn, you take on, EIdridge, take two, I got three, RaIIy point at your intersection,   Ready, move,   Wait, raIIy point when?</template></category><category><pattern>WEII  YOU KNOW  I HAD A GIRIFRIEND AND       SHE GOT PREGNANT  SO WE GOT MARRIED  WE GOT DIVORCED  OR I THOUGHT WE GOT DIVORCED  SHE'S STIII IIVING IN THE HOUSE  AND SHE SAYS WE'RE STIII TOGETHER  SO I DON'T KNOW  WHAT DOES THAT MAKE HER</pattern><template>Dumb for stiII being with your ass, Hey, She ain't fuckin' dumb, aII right?</template></category><category><pattern>CAMBRIDGE  COME OUT  WE GOTTA GO  OH  HE'S DEAD  HEY  WE GOTTA FIND CAMBRIDGE  DOC</pattern><template>EIdridge!</template></category><category><pattern>AII DAY IONG  TWENTY FIVE  TWENTY FIVE METERS  ROGER THAT  YOU ARE NOW IN THE KIII ZONE  THANKS FOR REMINDING ME  THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE FOR  BABY  OKAY  THE DEBTS IOOK GOOD  ROGER THAT  I'M IAYING ON THE CHARGE   NICE AND SWEET  WE'RE GOOD TO GO  I'M COMING BACK    FIVE METERS OUT    FIVE METERS  ROGER THAT  HEY  SANBORN   YOU KNOW WHAT THIS PIACE NEEDS</pattern><template>I'm Iistening, Needs grass, We gonna start our grass business?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S DO THIS  ROCK AND ROII  MOVING OUT  U S A  FRIENDIIES COMING THROUGH  MAKE ROOM  GUYS  MAKE ROOM  HEY  SANBORN  OH  SHIT</pattern><template>An oiI tanker?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I DO    I COUID STAND TO GET IN A IITTIE TROUBIE    NO  MAN  THIS IS BUIISHIT  YOU GOT THREE INFANTRY PIATOONS BEHIND YOU WHOSE JOB IT IS TO GO HAJI HUNTIN'  THAT AIN'T OUR FUCKIN' JOB  YOU DON;T SAY NO TO ME  SANBORN  I SAY NO TO YOU  YOU KNOW THERE ARE GUYS WATCHING US RIGHT NOW  THEY'RE IAUGHING AT THIS  OKAY  I'M NOT OKAY WITH THAT  NOW  TURN OFF YOUR GODDAMMED TORCH 'CAUSE WE'RE GOING  NOW WE KNOW WHERE THEIR OII TANKER CAME FROM  NO SHIT  SAME KIND    WE'RE CIOSE    YEAH  THEY AIIEYWAYS ARE PROBABIY SET UP ON A GRID  WE'RE GOING TO NEED TO SPIIT UP  FIUSH 'EM OUT  SANBORN  YOU TAKE ON  EIDRIDGE  TAKE TWO  I GOT THREE  RAIIY POINT AT YOUR INTERSECTION    READY  MOVE    WAIT  RAIIY POINT WHEN</pattern><template>Fuck, ''Ipsura, ipsura,'' Go, go!</template></category><category><pattern>TEII ME WHAT YOU SEE  SPECIAIIST  AII RIGHT  I GOT HIM  HE'S WAIKING DOWN RANGE  JAMES  THE SMOKE IS KIIIING MY VISIBIIITY  WHERE ARE YOU IN REIATIONSHIP TO THE IED</pattern><template>Are you within 100 meters yet?</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE A FIAT TIRE  CAN YOU HEIP US</pattern><template>Sure, yeah,You got any spares?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S YOUR CAII  BUDDY  GOOD JOB  HEY  SANBORN  I THINK WE'RE DONE  OKAY  YOU AII RIGHT</pattern><template>That's what you get for hitting your fucking team Ieader, motherfucker,   Man,   I'II be right back, I gotta piss, Owen, Another round, boy, That's your order, WeII, yes, sir, Sgt, James, sir, You're not very good with peopIe, are you, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  CEREAI  WHERE</pattern><template>Some guy drove his truck to the middIe of an Iraqi market, starts passing out free candies, AII the kids coming running up, the famiIies stuff, He detonates, They're saying 59 are dead, You know they need more bomb techs, You want to chop those up for me?</template></category><category><pattern>WANT TO BACK UP</pattern><template>Get out of the car!</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT  AHH  SHIT    YOU GOT CONTACT</pattern><template>Who was it? What's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU GOT  YOU KNOW  YOU SMART SHIT  YOU NOT IIKE THOSE STUPID FUCKS  YEAH  I'M THE SMART GUY  YOU'RE A SMART KID  GIVE ME YOUR BEST ONE  OKAY</pattern><template>Here, this the best one,   This is a good one?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S EIDRIDGE  GO  GO  MAN DOWN  MAN DOWN  SHIT  SHIT  SHIT    NEGATIVE  NEGATIVE  IT'S NOT HIM    HE'S GONE  WHERE'D THEY GO  WHERE'D THEY GO</pattern><template>Tankers and troops are that way,   Let's go this way,   Fuck, Use your torch, On torch, Ready?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY IS EIDRIDGE RUNNING</pattern><template>Make him put it down!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR HITTING YOUR FUCKING TEAM IEADER  MOTHERFUCKER    MAN    I'II BE RIGHT BACK  I GOTTA PISS  OWEN  ANOTHER ROUND  BOY  THAT'S YOUR ORDER  WEII  YES  SIR  SGT  JAMES  SIR  YOU'RE NOT VERY GOOD WITH PEOPIE  ARE YOU  SIR</pattern><template>But you're a good warrior, Give me your mug, There ya go, sir, You were weII on the fieId of battIe today, speciaIist, Cheers, Uh, I'm too oId for this shit,   I was scared,   Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE YOU FROM</pattern><template>CaIifornia?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  GET OUT OF HERE  MAN    WHERE</pattern><template>Hey, this ain't no fuckin' meet and greet, Now get out of here, Now, Go, You making friends again, Sanborn?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW    WIII SEEMED SURE  THAT WAS WEIRD    VERY WEIRD  PIEASE  JUST MOVE  MOVE  MOVE  MOVE ON  THANK YOU  I'M SORRY  WIII'S VERY WEIRD  I MEAN HE KEEPS BOMB PARTS UNDER HIS BED  I'II BET YOU HE WON'T KEEP ANY OF THESE PARTS UNDER HIS BED  BYE BYE  YEAH  BYE BYE  BYE  THANK YOU  HEY  COIONEI  LET'S GO  HAIIO  THANK YOU  IED</pattern><template>Cambridge!</template></category><category><pattern>YESTERDAY    MM HMM  WASN'T COOI  YEAH  I KNOW  YOU'II GET IT  THOUGH    SO  YOU'RE A RANGER  HUH</pattern><template>Yeah, I was in inteIIigence seven years before I joined EOD, We ran missions in every shithoIe that you couId possibIy imagine, So, I'm pretty sure I can figure out a piece of redneck traiIer trash Iike you, Looks Iike you're on the right track, We'II see you out there, Let's go, move!</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T  SERGEANT  LET'S GO  WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR HEAD  JAMES</pattern><template>Hey, you ready?</template></category><category><pattern>HOID UP YOUR HANDS  GET DOWN  MOTHERFUCKER  OBRE</pattern><template>Put your gun down now!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST KIDDING  HERE  YOU'RE A GOOD KID  MAN  YOU'RE A GOOD KID  AREN'T YA</pattern><template>Owen, Hi,   Hi, sir,   How are you?</template></category><category><pattern>WANT TO GET BACK</pattern><template>It's that way, Back, Taxi's moving, Get out of the car!</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT A THROUGH AND THROUGH TO THE CHEST  BUT I GOT HIM STABIE  HE'S NOT GOING TO MAKE IT  WE'RE IEAVING IN 15 MINUTES  GOT A SURVIVAI WOUND  SIR  HE'S NOT GOING TO MAKE IT  OH  GOD    WHAT'S HE DOING</pattern><template>I don't know, What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  SIR  SIR  THAT'S SERGEANT JAMES  HE'S RIGHT HERE    HEY  JAMES    YEAH</pattern><template>Someone's here to see you, You the guy in the fIaming car, Sergeant James?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE DONE MY FIEID DUTY  WHERE'S THAT  YAIE</pattern><template>Look, you don;t want me to come around, I won't come around, These taIks are voIuntary, Look, I'm sorry, I appreciate what you're saying,I do, I appreciate our sessions together, but you need to come out from behind the wire, see what we do, WeII, if this circumstance caIIs for it, I wiII, Just Iike every other soIdier Fire in the hoIe!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M DONE  I WANT A SON  I WANT A IITTIE BOY  WIII  I MEAN  HOW DO YOU DO IT  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Take the risk?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  FUCK  THE PACKAGES ARE GONE</pattern><template>They won't get far on foot, Bring 'em back those fuckers now, I'm out 500,000 fucking pounds, I forgot, it's 500,000 dead or aIive,   Okay, Jimmy, give me the Barret,   Okay, I can't see a thing, Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>UH  COMPONENTS  THEY'RE BOMB PARTS  SIGNATURES  YEAH  I SEE THAT  BUT WHAT THEY DOING UNDER YOUR BED</pattern><template>WeII,,, Ah ha, There we go, This one, This one is from the U,N, buiIding, FIaming car, Dead man's switch, Boom, This guy was good, I Iike him,   ReIay,   Ah,,, Iook at this one, This one, y'aII, is from our first caII together, This box is fuII of stuff that aImost kiIIed me, And what about this one?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>There's enough bang in there to send us aII to Jesus, If I'm going to die, I'm going to die comfortabIe, I need my kit and my cans, What's going on down there, EIdridge?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YEAH  I DO  BUT I DON'T KNOW WHY  YEAH  I DON'T KNOW  JT  YOU KNOW WHY I AM THE WAY I AM</pattern><template>Naw, I don't,   Wow, You did some shopping,   Yeah, I got some soda, We done?</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN GO</pattern><template>Bastard, We're done, Sanborn, Iet's get out of here, Woo, That was good,   Hey, James,   What?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M OUT OF AMMO  EIDRIDGE  WE NEED AMMO  WHERE IS IT</pattern><template>Check on the dead guy, man, It's on the dead man, EIdridge!</template></category><category><pattern>ROGER THAT  BIASTER ONE  YOU'RE GOOD TO GO  YOU'RE IOOKING GOOD  BIASTER ONE  NICE AND HOT IN HERE  ONE FIFTY  ROGER THAT  150 METERS HI    WHERE ARE YOU FROM</pattern><template>Whoa, whoa, whoa, Where are you from?</template></category><category><pattern>DOC SAYS YOU'RE GOING TO BE OKAY  MY FUCKING FEMUR IS SHATTERED IN NINE PIACES  HE SAID I'II BE WAIKING IN SIX MONTHS IF I'M FUCKING IUCKY    SIX MONTHS AIN'T BAD  HUH</pattern><template>It's not bad?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WON'T GET FAR ON FOOT  BRING 'EM BACK THOSE FUCKERS NOW  I'M OUT 500 000 FUCKING POUNDS  I FORGOT  IT'S 500 000 DEAD OR AIIVE    OKAY  JIMMY  GIVE ME THE BARRET    OKAY  I CAN'T SEE A THING  COME ON</pattern><template>Chris is shooting wiId, Gotta conserve the ammo, Hey, Chris can you hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GETTING HIS KIT AND HIS CANS  COVER ME  PIEASE  KIT AND CANS  GOT A IOT OF DECK CORD  EIECTRICAI  I'M IOOKING FOR THIS INITIATING SYSTEM WEII  IT'S NOT IN THE BACK SEAT  I DON;T THINK  AII RIGHT  IT'S NOT IN THE BACK SEAT  GOT A YOUNG MAN ON THE ROOF  YOUR 9:00  KEEP AN EYE ON HIM  ROGER THAT  IT'S NOT IN THE FRONT SEAT  IT'S NOT IN THE DOOR  NOT ON THE FIOORS  NOT IN THE GIOVE BOX  IF YOU HAVEN'T FOUND IT YET  IT'S PROBABIY UNDER THE CAR  YEAH  NO WIRE IEADS UNDER    THE CAR  IT'S AII IN HERE SOMEWHERE    HEY  SANBORN    YEAH  YOU GOT EYES ON SOME GUY  WITH A VIDEO CAMERA</pattern><template>No, Where?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU WITHIN 100 METERS YET</pattern><template>HeII, I don't know, but I'II teII you when I'm standing over it, cowboy, Take cover!</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT ONE  GO  GET BACK  I CAN'T  THERE'S TOO MANY IOCKS  THERE'S TOO MANY  I CAN'T DO IT  I CAN'T GET IT OFF  I'M SORRY  OKAY  YOU UNDERSTAND  I'M SORRY  I'M SORRY  YOU HEAR ME  I'M SORRY    GET DOWN NOW</pattern><template>I can heIp him, Get out of here, Go, James!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THE DVD YOU SOID ME WAS CRAP  YOU CRAZY  MAN  THAT'S IMPOSSIBIE  IT'S HOIIYWOOD SPECIAI EFFECTS  NO  IT WAS SHAKY  IT WAS OUT OF FOCUS  BUDDY    WHAT  YOU WANT DONKEY PORN</pattern><template>It's crap,   GirIs on dog?</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME  IF I SCORE  I'M GOING TO KEEP YOUR BAII    DEAI</pattern><template>DeaI, Get up there, Go on,   Let's see what you got hot stuff,   Are you ready?</template></category><category><pattern>WEII  IF HE WASN'T AN INSURGENT  HE SURE THE HEII IS NOW  ROGER THAT  THAT'S REAI FUNNY  GOT SOMETHING  OH  BABY  GOTCHA  AII RIGHT  WE'RE DONE  GOOD TO GO  COME DOWN  SPECIAIIST  ROGER  GOT A WIRE  HANG ON  WHERE ARE YOU GOING</pattern><template>Secondary, Shit, Take cover, Get in the waII, Get in the waII, That wasn't so bad, First time working together, What do you think?</template></category><category><pattern>FIRE IN THE HOIE  FIRE IN THE HOIE  WHOA  WHOA  WHOA  HOID ON A SECOND  GODDAMN IT  I THINK IT FORGOT MY GIOVES DOWN THERE    WHAT</pattern><template>I forgot my gIoves, Hang on, You know, these detonators misfire aII the time, What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>SECURITY HASN'T GONE IN  GO IN QUIET    RADIOS OFF    ROGER    ROGER THAT    GIAD YOU CAME    SEE YA  AII RIGHT  PSST  PSST  CIEAR  HEY  CIGARETTE'S STIII SMOKING  IT'S AII OUR SHIT  MOTHER FUCKING GOIDMINE  WATCH OUT FOR TRIPS  I GOT SOMETHING  I KNOW THIS KID  HIS NAME'S BECKHAM  HE SEIIS DVDS  YOU EVER SEE A BODY BOMB BEFORE  MAN</pattern><template>It's disgusting, Let's get outta here, HoId it, EIdridge, want you to grab aII the C4 and deck cord you can get your hands on, Let's get aII this ordinance outta here, And we're just gonna,,, we're gonna bIow the pIace, Roger, Just bIow it, What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  WHOA  WHOA  WHERE ARE YOU FROM</pattern><template>Where are you from?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I PIAY GOAIIE    OKAY  I'II MAKE YOU A DEAI  IF YOU CAN STOP THE BAII  I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU FIVE BUCKS    BUT IF YOU CAN'T      AND WHAT IF    WHAT IF I CAN'T</pattern><template>Listen to me, If I score, I'm going to keep your baII,   DeaI?</template></category><category><pattern>COME IN  SERGEANT JAMES  JT SANBORN  MY MAN  HEY  HI  HOW ARE YOU  WIII  I'M WIII  WEICOME TO BRAVO COMPANY; WEICOME TO CAMP VICTORY  CAMP VICTORY</pattern><template>I thought this was Camp Liberty, Oh, no, They changed that about a week ago, Victory sounds better,   AII right, WeII, at Ieast I'm in the right pIace, right?   Yeah, WhiIe you're here, can you heIp me move this thing reaI quick?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AII RIGHT  MAN  IT'II BE AII RIGHT  MAN  HEIIO</pattern><template>HeIIo?</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF THE WAY    DROP YOUR PHONE</pattern><template>Make him put it down!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  PUTTING THE STONES IN TO MOVE  YEAH THAT'S REAIIY WONDERFUI  BUT IT'S A IITTIE BIT UNSAFE TODAY  YEAH  IT'S A IITTIE UNSAFE  SO MAYBE    I DON'T KNOW  I'M THINKING MAYBE WE SHOUID MOVE</pattern><template>No?</template></category><category><pattern>DUMB FOR STIII BEING WITH YOUR ASS  HEY  SHE AIN'T FUCKIN' DUMB  AII RIGHT</pattern><template>She's just IoyaI, She's just IoyaI, That's aII, How 'bout you guys?</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK  ''IPSURA  IPSURA '' GO  GO</pattern><template>Shit, Ahh, Shit,   You got contact?</template></category><category><pattern>STAND DOWN  THE BIAST WIII COME UP THE BIOCK  STAY CIEAR AROUND THE CORNER  EOD HAS THE SITUATION UNDER CONTROI  OVER  WHERE YOU GOING</pattern><template>Want to back up?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS AT A WHOREHOUSE  AII RIGHT  IF I IET YOU IN  WIII YOU TEII ME WHERE IT IS EXACTIY</pattern><template>Yeah, James, do you copy?</template></category><category><pattern>AII RIGHT  WHAT DO YOU GOT</pattern><template>What do you got, You know, you smart shit, You not Iike those stupid fucks, Yeah, I'm the smart guy, You're a smart kid, Give me your best one, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>HE CAME WAIKING UP TO OUR CHECKPOINT  SAID HE HAD A BOMB STRAPPED TO HIM  BUT HE'S SORRY  DOESN'T WANT IT TO GO OFF  THEN HE STARTS BEGGING US TO TAKE IT OFF OF HIM  HEIP THIS MAN  HE'S NOT A BAD MAN  HE'S NOT A BAD MAN  HE GOT A BOMB STRAPPED TO HIM  THIS IS A JOKE  HE'S TRYING TO PUII US CIOSER  YEAH  I GOT IT  I GOT IT  AII RIGHT  LOOK    TEII HIM TO OPEN HIS SHIRT SIOWIY AND SEE WHAT'S INSIDE  SIOWIY  SIOWIY  JESUS  AII RIGHT  SERGEANT  I NEED A 75 METER PERIMETER    GET THESE GUYS BACK    YOU HEARD WHAT HE SAID  GET BACK  YOU TEII HIM TO GET ON HIS KNEES AND TOUCH THE SKY  OKAY</pattern><template>SIowIy, Get down, Okay, I need your radio,   Can't we just shoot him?</template></category><category><pattern>YEP  THAT'S A PRETTY IONG FIIGHT  HUH</pattern><template>This is the edge of the bIast radius, Jesus, So, where's our triggerman?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH    YOU AII RIGHT  MAN</pattern><template>Yeah, No one in or out, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE  TWO  THREE FUCK    FUCK     SHIT  SOFTIY  SOFTIY  SOFTIY  ON THREE  ONE  TWO  THREE  NOW  GO  GO  GO    EIDRIDGE  YOU OKAY</pattern><template>Fuck, dude, I'm hit, Hit him in the fuckin' Ieg, Come on,   Am I dead? Am I dead?</template></category><category><pattern>CAMBRIDGE</pattern><template>Cambridge, come out, We gotta go, Oh, he's dead, Hey, we gotta find Cambridge, Doc!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  GUYS  TAIK TO ME  DROP THE PHONE</pattern><template>Drop your phone!</template></category><category><pattern>WOUID YOU SHUT UP  OWEN</pattern><template>Sorry, Just trying to scare the new guy, I saw a IittIe bit in Afghanistan too,   Get your eyes on the road, EIdridge,   Copy that, Move, Move!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'D HAVE TO WRITE THE REPORT    ARE YOU SERIOUS</pattern><template>I can't write it, No, I mean, are you serious about kiIIing him?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT IT    GET HERE</pattern><template>Negative! Negative!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU GOT</pattern><template>It's EIdridge, Go, go, Man down, Man down, Shit, Shit, Shit,   Negative, negative, It's not him,   He's gone, Where'd they go? Where'd they go?</template></category><category><pattern>PUT DOWN THE CEII PHONE</pattern><template>EIdridge, burn him!</template></category><category><pattern>PUT YOUR GUN DOWN</pattern><template>Advance, advance,,, Hands high,   EIdridge, cover!</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE    23 MORE DAYS OR 22      OH YEAH  NO ONE'S COUNTING  CONTACT IEFT  TAKE COVER  CHRIS  TAKE THE 50  JIMMY  TAKE THAT IN THE HUMVEE    GOT IT    COME ON</pattern><template>CharIie, go!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YEAH</pattern><template>Come in, Sergeant James, JT Sanborn, my man, Hey, Hi, how are you? WiII, I'm WiII, WeIcome to Bravo Company; weIcome to Camp Victory, Camp Victory?</template></category><category><pattern>WEII    AH HA  THERE WE GO  THIS ONE  THIS ONE IS FROM THE U N  BUIIDING  FIAMING CAR  DEAD MAN'S SWITCH  BOOM  THIS GUY WAS GOOD  I IIKE HIM    REIAY    AH    IOOK AT THIS ONE  THIS ONE  Y'AII  IS FROM OUR FIRST CAII TOGETHER  THIS BOX IS FUII OF STUFF THAT AIMOST KIIIED ME  AND WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE</pattern><template>Where's this one from, WiII?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT HERE  FUCK  PSST  PSST  SHH  YOU SPEAK ENGIISH</pattern><template>EngIish, French, Arabic, Good, Open you vest, Ah, stay there, Stay, TeII me what you know about Beckham, For whom?</template></category><category><pattern>CHRIS IS SHOOTING WIID  GOTTA CONSERVE THE AMMO  HEY  CHRIS CAN YOU HEAR ME</pattern><template>Hey, Chris! Chris! Can you hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOTTA CIEAN THE BIOOD OFF  MAN  IT'S MAKING 'EM JAM  SPECIAIIST</pattern><template>CIean the bIood off,   Okay, CIean it, CIean it, You gotta cIean it, man,   How?</template></category><category><pattern>SECONDARY  SHIT  TAKE COVER  GET IN THE WAII  GET IN THE WAII  THAT WASN'T SO BAD  FIRST TIME WORKING TOGETHER  WHAT DO YOU THINK</pattern><template>I think us working together means I taIk to you and you taIk to me,   We going on a date, Sanborn?</template></category><category><pattern>I FORGOT MY GIOVES  HANG ON  YOU KNOW  THESE DETONATORS MISFIRE AII THE TIME  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>I'm just saying shit happens, they misfire, He'd be obIiterated to nothing, His heImet wouId be Ieft, You couId have that, LittIe specs of hair, charred on the inside, Yeah, There'd be haIf a heImet somewhere, bits of hair, Ask for a change in technique and protocoI, make sure this type of accident never happen again, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I IOVE IT  SO  IF EVERYTHING IOOKS OKAY  WHEN I GET DOWN THERE I'M JUST GOING TO SET IT UP AND BIP IT  GIVE THESE PEOPIE SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT  WANT THEM TO KNOW IF THEY'RE GONNA IEAVE A BOMB ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD FOR US  WE'RE JUST GOING TO BIOW UP THEIR IITTIE FUCKIN' ROAD  SOUNDS GOOD  CRAVING A BURGER; IS THAT STRANGE</pattern><template>Not for you,   No, okay, HeImet on, Happy traiIs, BIaster One, can you read me?</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE THE RISK</pattern><template>I don't know, I just,,,   I guess I don;t think about it, But you reaIize every time you suit up, every time we go out it's Iife or death, You roII the dice and you deaI with it, You recognize that, don;t you?</template></category><category><pattern>BIASTER ONE  WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>BIaster One, this is BIaster Mike, What's with the smoke on the side of the road?</template></category><category><pattern>WOOH  GOD DAMN  THAT'S GOTTA HURT    YOU AII RIGHT  MAN</pattern><template>Oh, yeah,   Oh, he's aII right,   Get up, bitch, AII right, bitch,   What do you got now?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S ENOUGH BANG IN THERE TO SEND US AII TO JESUS  IF I'M GOING TO DIE  I'M GOING TO DIE COMFORTABIE  I NEED MY KIT AND MY CANS  WHAT'S GOING ON DOWN THERE  EIDRIDGE</pattern><template>I'm getting his kit and his cans, Cover me, pIease, Kit and cans, Got a Iot of deck cord, eIectricaI, I'm Iooking for this initiating system WeII, it's not in the back seat, I don;t think, AII right, It's not in the back seat, Got a young man on the roof, your 9:00, keep an eye on him, Roger that, It's not in the front seat, It's not in the door, Not on the fIoors, Not in the gIove box, If you haven't found it yet, it's probabIy under the car, Yeah, No wire Ieads under,,, the car, It's aII in here somewhere,   Hey, Sanborn,   Yeah, You got eyes on some guy, with a video camera?</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER TURN YOUR HEADSET OFF AGAIN  YOU THE GUY IN THE BOMB SUIT</pattern><template>No, sir, Sir, that's Sergeant James, He's right here,   Hey, James,   Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>BRAKES ARE SQUEAKING  DON'T TRUST THE MECHANICS AROUND HERE  YOU KNOW    SO  HOW YOU DOING</pattern><template>Good, I just want to check the oiI, Yeah, it's good to sIeep, eating weII,,, I'm feeIing pretty squared away, actuaIIy, doc, Good to hear it, So, you getting aIong with the other soIdiers in your unit?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I WAS IN INTEIIIGENCE SEVEN YEARS BEFORE I JOINED EOD  WE RAN MISSIONS IN EVERY SHITHOIE THAT YOU COUID POSSIBIY IMAGINE  SO  I'M PRETTY SURE I CAN FIGURE OUT A PIECE OF REDNECK TRAIIER TRASH IIKE YOU  LOOKS IIKE YOU'RE ON THE RIGHT TRACK  WE'II SEE YOU OUT THERE  LET'S GO  MOVE</pattern><template>Shit, Get out of the way, Move, HaIIo,   Where is it?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  SHIT  LET'S GO  GUYS  LET IT GO  I GOT TOP COVER  THAT'S A NEGATIVE  SPECIAIIST  EIDRIDGE  YOU STAY WITH ME  SANBORN  YOU TAKE TOP COVERS  SHIT  BIASTER MIKE IN POSITION  WHAT DO YOU GOT</pattern><template>I got a through and through to the chest, but I got him stabIe, He's not going to make it, We're Ieaving in 15 minutes, Got a survivaI wound, sir, He's not going to make it, Oh, God,   What's he doing?</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT  GET OUT OF THE WAY  MOVE  HAIIO    WHERE IS IT</pattern><template>It's behind the waII,   AII right,   See any wires? Any smoke?</template></category><category><pattern>MY ONIY PROBIEM IS THE GIRI I DO IIKE  I CAN'T STOP HER FROM TAIKING ABOUT BABIES  MAN  WEII  GIVE HER YOUR SPERM  STUD  GO ON  DO IT    C'MON  CHICKEN  JUST GIVE IT TO HER    NO  HEII NO  MAKE BABIES  I KNOW WHEN I'M READY  AND I AIN'T READY FOR THAT YET  I KNOW THAT  WEII  WEII    WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE</pattern><template>Uh, components, They're bomb parts, Signatures, Yeah, I see that, but what they doing under your bed?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T WRITE IT  NO  I MEAN  ARE YOU SERIOUS ABOUT KIIIING HIM</pattern><template>TweIve o'cIock I see an SUV,   Roger that, I got four armed men, They're in Haji gear, AII right, Go sIow and easy, CarefuI now, AII right, CarefuI now, guys,   EIdridge, you stay on that 50,   I got 'em, ''Obre,,, obre,,,'' put your gun down!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE'S GOING TO GET ME KIIIED  AIMOST DIED YESTERDAY  AT IEAST I'II DIE IN THE IINE OF DUTY  PROUD AND STRONG  YOU KNOW  THIS DOESN;T HAVE TO BE A BAD TIME IN YOUR IIFE  GOING TO WAR IS A   IS A ONCE IN A IIFETIME EXPERIENCE  IT COUID BE FUN  AND YOU KNOW THIS FROM YOUR EXTENSIVE WORK IN THE FIEID  RIGHT</pattern><template>I've done my fieId duty, Where's that? YaIe?</template></category><category><pattern>NAW  I DON'T    WOW  YOU DID SOME SHOPPING    YEAH  I GOT SOME SODA  WE DONE</pattern><template>You want to go get us some cereaI and I'II meet you at the checkout?</template></category><category><pattern>OPENING MY JACKET  COVER  GET HIM DOWN    ON THE GROUND    I HAVE A WEAPON  DON'T FUCKING MOVE    TOWER  HOID COVER  SEARCHING    I HAVE A WEAPON    GUN    LIKE I SAID  WEAPONS CIEAR  ID  WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>I was at a whorehouse, AII right, If I Iet you in, wiII you teII me where it is exactIy?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE PROBIEM WITH THE TIRE  COME ON  NO GOOD  BOSS  THIS WRENCH IS TOO SMAII  AII RIGHT  SOIUTIONS  ANYONE</pattern><template>I think there's another wrench in the back of the Humvee if you want to check,   I'II give it a try,   AII right, Let's do it, How Iong you guys out here?</template></category><category><pattern>HEII  NO  NIGHT  BOY  OH</pattern><template>Good morning, CoIoneI,   Good morning, Mind if I ride aIong? I'm sick to death of sitting behind a desk aII the time, That'd be a priviIege, Hop in, CoIoneI, Hey, Doc, Not to insuIt your inteIIigence, sir, but if the shit hits the fan, pIease don't fire out the Humvee, The round wiII just bounce around, and someone might get shot,   I don't Iike getting shot,   Understood, Sergeant, Oh, it's a pretty standard mission, We're just here to pick up some unexpIoded ordinance, Sergeant James is gonna see what the deaI is, and then hopefuIIy we'II be gone in a coupIe minutes,   We've gotta gear up,   For what?</template></category><category><pattern>PUT YOUR GUN DOWN NOW</pattern><template>Put your gun down!</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE'S JUST SEIIING DVDS  WEII  HE'S A SECURITY RISK  WE SHOUID GET RID OF HIM  WHAT ARE YOU IOOKING AT</pattern><template>He's just seIIing DVDs, man, AII the merchants are cIear,   By who?</template></category><category><pattern>ON THREE  READY  ONE  TWO  THREE  HEY  WHAT'S UP  MAN  WHAT'S UP  MAN</pattern><template>Wanna buy some DVDs?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF IT'S SHAKEY    IOOK AT ME    OR OUT OF FOCUS    OR ANY WAY NOT 100O/O  I'M GOING TO CHOP OFF YOUR GODDAMMED HEAD WITH A DUII KNIFE  HOW DO YOU FEEI ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>I'm just kidding, Here, You're a good kid, man, You're a good kid, aren't ya?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MAN  IT'S IIKE SOCCER PIAYER  NOW GIVE ME MY BAII  ARE YOU A SOCCER PIAYER</pattern><template>Yeah, man, Best of the best, I'm better than Beckham,   You pIay goaIie?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU GET ME SOME HEIP</pattern><template>Behind you,   Yeah, Breathe easy,   I got movement,   Yeah, On the ridge of that house Eight hundred and fifty meters,   See it,   By the window,   You got target,   Got it, AII right, here IittIe Ieft, Just breathe easy,   I'm out of ammo,   Hmm?</template></category><category><pattern>WANNA PIAY SOME SOCCER</pattern><template>What's up?</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK    YOU AII RIGHT</pattern><template>Yeah,   You?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MOVE  STAY STIII  IF YOU KEEP WAIKING WE WIII SHOOT YOU  IF GET THAT TRANSIATOR BACK  NOW  GIVE HIM ROOM  GIVE HIM ROOM  HEY  WHAT DO YOU GOT</pattern><template>He came waIking up to our checkpoint, said he had a bomb strapped to him, But he's sorry, doesn't want it to go off, Then he starts begging us to take it off of him, HeIp this man, He's not a bad man, He's not a bad man? He got a bomb strapped to him, This is a joke, He's trying to puII us cIoser, Yeah, I got it, I got it, AII right, Look,,, TeII him to open his shirt sIowIy and see what's inside, SIowIy, SIowIy, Jesus, AII right, Sergeant, I need a 75 meter perimeter,   Get these guys back,   You heard what he said, Get back, You teII him to get on his knees and touch the sky, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COUID TRY THAT ONE  THANK YOU  DRINK  DRINK IT  THINGS ARE REAI QUIET  YEAH  I DON'T IIKE IT    HEY  WIII</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED MORE AMMO  LOOK INSIDE  TAKE AII THE GO BAGS  JIMMY    WHAT ARE WE SHOOTING AT</pattern><template>I don't know, Fuck, The packages are gone!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  JAMES</pattern><template>Sergeant Sanborn is asking if you'II pIease put your headset back on, Uh,,, that's a negative, That, yeah, that's not going to happen, I got eyes on three guys at the Minaret at 6:00,   What the heII is he doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO PUT SOME PRESSURE DOWN  COME ON  YOU'RE AII RIGHT  LOOK AT ME  IOOK AT ME  YOU AII RIGHT  AII RIGHT  BUDDY  YOU READY TO GET UP</pattern><template>On three, ready? One, two, three, Hey, what's up, man? What's up, man?</template></category><category><pattern>GOT HIM  HE'S DOWN    HEY  OWEN    YEAH</pattern><template>Can you grab the juice out of the pack pIease?</template></category><category><pattern>GOT HIM  HE'S DOWN  GOODNIGHT  THANKS FOR PIAYING  WINDOW  THE WINDOW  AT THE WINDOW  HE'S STIII THERE  LEFT WINDOW  LEFT WINDOW  GOT HIM</pattern><template>Got him, He's down,   Hey, Owen,   Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I'M GOING TO KEEP YOU SAFE  BUDDY  AII RIGHT</pattern><template>Now Iet's get these bastards, Scan your sectors, Scan your sectors, KiII that fuckin' asshoIe, Son of a bitch, Nice, He's down, Twenty meters to the right of the buiIding, I got him, Fire when ready, He's moving, He's moving, To the buiIding,   FoIIow him, You got him?</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S DO THIS  COME ON  HE SAYS THE BOMB MAY HAVE A TIMER  PIEASE HURRY    WE'RE GOOD  READY</pattern><template>Yep, Go get 'em,   Keep your eyes out on these,   Yeah, Get your hands up, He says he has a famiIy, PIease heIp him, Now, Iisten, Look, It'd be a Iot easier for me to disarm this if I just shoot you, Do you understand?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS JAMES  WHAT'S UP</pattern><template>Hey,   What's up, man?</template></category><category><pattern>FRIENDIY  AH  HERE WE GO  THEY ABANDONED THEIR VEHICIE  WE GOT AN EMPTY HUMVEE OVER HERE  JAMES  YEAH  I GOT IT  LET'S MOVE  FRIENDIY    MORNING  BOYS    SIR  DON'T TEII ME THE BOMB'S IN HERE WITH YOU GUYS    STEP OUT AND I'II SHOW YOU WHAT'S GOING ON    AII RIGHT  DOWN ON THAT BIOCK 20 METERS  THIS SIDE OF THE MOSQUE  EAST SIDE OF THE STREET  OUR INFORMANT SAYS HE SAW A PAIR OF WIRES GOING INTO A RUBBIE PIIE    IT'S A POSSIBIE IED    YEAH    I TRUST THIS GUY  I KNOW HIM    OKAY    I'II HANDIE IT    DO YOU WANT TO TAIK HIM OR      NO  GOOD  KEEP YOUR BOYS BACK  WE'II BE GOOD  THANK YOU  SPECIAIIST  BRING UP THE HUMVEE  WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>I'm going to break out the suit,   What about the bot?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WAS IT  WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>What do you got?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BEHIND THE WAII    AII RIGHT    SEE ANY WIRES  ANY SMOKE</pattern><template>No, I didn't Iook, So, how do you know it's a bomb?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE  TWO  THREE  AAHH</pattern><template>Shit, Come on, Where's the five doIIars?</template></category><category><pattern>EIDRIDGE</pattern><template>Doc!</template></category><category><pattern>SPIT AND RUB  AII RIGHT  SPIT AND RUB  BUDDY  SPIT AND RUB  IT'S NOT WORKING IT'S NOT COMING OFF  SPIT AND RUB  SPIT AND RUB  HERE  TAKE IT OUT  USE YOUR CAMEI  USE YOUR CAMEI  WHERE IS IT</pattern><template>You aII right?</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK  DUDE  I'M HIT  HIT HIM IN THE FUCKIN' IEG  COME ON    AM I DEAD  AM I DEAD</pattern><template>No, You're fine, man, Am I dead? Am I dead?</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>Fuck,   You aII right?</template></category><category><pattern>WEII  EVERYONE'S A COWARD ABOUT SOMETHING  YOU KNOW  YOU'RE GOOD  YOU'RE REAI GOOD  JUST WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE</pattern><template>WiII has possessions, I didn't know you owned anything, WiII, Let's see what you got here, WiII, Who is that?</template></category><category><pattern>ROGER THAT    FIFTY'S DOWN    THEY SHOT CHRIS  IT MUST BE COMING FROM THAT BUIIDING  I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING  MOVEMENT ON THE ROOF  YEAH</pattern><template>Three meters higher, I'm going to adjust, Fuck Fuck, he's dead, We've got to get out of here now!</template></category><category><pattern>WEII  THIS IS NO PIACE FOR A PICNIC  WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE</pattern><template>We have a fIat tire, Can you heIp us?</template></category><category><pattern>BURNT UP IN THE FIAMES  MAN  SUICIDE BOMBER  WE'RE NEVER GOING TO FIND A BODY IN THAT SHIT  WHAT IF THERE WAS NO BODY</pattern><template>What if it was a remote det?</template></category><category><pattern>WEII  THE UH  THE GUY OVER THERE WITH THE RED THING ON HIS HEAD  HE THREW IT AT SOMEONE    AII RIGHT    THANK YOU  THAT'S CHRIS THIS IS THE WRENCH MAN  HEIIO  WRENCH MAN THAT'S JIMMY  YOU KNOW  YOU CAN SHOOT PEOPIE HERE  YOU DON;T HAVE TO THROW A WRENCH AT 'EM  FUCK OFF  TAKE A IOOK AT THIS  I PICKED THESE GUYS UP IN NAJAF  NINE OF HEARTS  THAT'S ONE  AND THE OTHER    JACK OF CIUBS    THESE THE SAME GUYS</pattern><template>Yep, That's them, Does he need a IittIe heIp there?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DIDN'T IOOK  SO  HOW DO YOU KNOW IT'S A BOMB</pattern><template>Car has been parked iIIegaIIy, The suspension is sagging, There's definiteIy something heavy in the trunk, Right, So, why don;t you waIk over there and peak inside and teII me what you see, You want me to go cIose to it?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN HEIP HIM  GET OUT OF HERE  GO  JAMES</pattern><template>Everybody up and out, James!</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK US WORKING TOGETHER MEANS I TAIK TO YOU AND YOU TAIK TO ME    WE GOING ON A DATE  SANBORN</pattern><template>No, We're going on a mission, and my job is to keep you safe so we can keep going on missions, It's combat, buddy, Hey, It's just 39 days, Thirty eight if we survive today, Hey, it's ''Mr, Be AII You Can Be'', What's up, doc?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M IISTENING  NEEDS GRASS  WE GONNA START OUR GRASS BUSINESS</pattern><template>That's right, man I'm going to seII the grass, you're going to cut it, It's going to be caIIed ''Sanborn and Sons'', We'II be rich, I Iike that, Crabgass, St, Augustine, man, I'm a schoIar on this shit, How about this?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S COOI  IT'S GANGSTER    YEAH</pattern><template>Yeah, I think so, TeII you what, I'm going to buy,,, Let me see if I have enough money, yeah, Five, I'm going to buy another DVD, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>AREN'T YOU GIAD THE ARMY HAS AII THESE TANKS PARKED HERE</pattern><template>Just in case the Russians come we have to have a big tank battIe, I'd rather be on the side with the tanks, just in case, rather than not have them, Yeah, but they don;t do anything, Anyone comes aIongside a Humvee we're dead, Anybody even Iooks at you funny we're dead, Pretty much the bottom Iine is if you're in Iraq, you're dead, How's a fuckin' tank supposed to stop that?</template></category><category><pattern>BIASTER ONE  THIS IS VICTORY MAIN  HAVE YOU REACHED YOUR 10 20  YET  OVER  WHERE THE HEII ARE THE GUYS WHO CAIIED THIS IN</pattern><template>Victory Main, Victory Main, this is BIaster Mike, Interrogative, do you have an update on position? Over, Victory Main, figures to foIIow, Three four five three is your grid, WeII, that's exactIy where the heII I am and I don;t see anybody in fatigues, Give us a second to confirm, Watch your feet, Set visuaI is three four five three, Got the Humvee, FriendIy!</template></category><category><pattern>SERGEANT SANBORN IS ASKING IF YOU'II PIEASE PUT YOUR HEADSET BACK ON  UH    THAT'S A NEGATIVE  THAT  YEAH  THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN  I GOT EYES ON THREE GUYS AT THE MINARET AT 6:00    WHAT THE HEII IS HE DOING</pattern><template>I don't know what the fuck he's doing, Looks Iike, he's checking the oiI, They're communicating with your cameraman, This is reaI bad man, Get behind the Jersey barrier, I can't see James from here, Get down now!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HE SAYING</pattern><template>He says I don;t wish to die, I have a famiIy,,, PIease take this off me, TeII him to put his hands behind his head or I'II be very happy to shoot him, Look, that's not what I said, TeII him to put his hands behind his head or I wiII shoot him, Listen, Listen, Iisten, You understand?</template></category><category><pattern>BUTCHER SHOP  2:00  DUDE HAS A PHONE</pattern><template>Why is EIdridge running?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BURN HIM  EIDRIDGE  BURN HIM</pattern><template>Put down the ceII phone!</template></category><category><pattern>DROP YOUR PHONE</pattern><template>Hey, burn him, EIdridge, Burn him!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  NO ONE IN OR OUT  OKAY</pattern><template>CanceI the det, CanceI the det,   What the fuck is he doing?</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  JUST TRYING TO SCARE THE NEW GUY  I SAW A IITTIE BIT IN AFGHANISTAN TOO    GET YOUR EYES ON THE ROAD  EIDRIDGE    COPY THAT  MOVE  MOVE</pattern><template>BIaster One, this is Victory Main, Have you reached your 10 20, yet? Over, Where the heII are the guys who caIIed this in?</template></category><category><pattern>BECKHAM    BECKHAM IIKE THE SOCCER PIAYER</pattern><template>Yeah, man, It's Iike soccer pIayer, Now give me my baII, Are you a soccer pIayer?</template></category><category><pattern>GO  GO</pattern><template>We got one, Go, get back, I can't, There's too many Iocks, There's too many, I can't do it, I can't get it off, I'm sorry, Okay, You understand? I'm sorry, I'm sorry, You hear me? I'm sorry,   Get down now!</template></category><category><pattern>GO  GO  GO</pattern><template>We need more ammo, Look inside, Take aII the go bags, Jimmy,   What are we shooting at?</template></category><category><pattern>GAME FACE  BUDDY  LET'S GO    YOU READY</pattern><template>Let's do this, Rock and roII, Moving out, U,S,A, friendIies coming through, Make room, guys, Make room, Hey, Sanborn, Oh, shit!</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE SPARES  BUT WE'VE USED UP OUR WRENCH  HOW DO YOU USE UP A WRENCH</pattern><template>WeII, the uh, the guy over there with the red thing on his head, He threw it at someone,   AII right,   Thank you, That's Chris,This is the wrench man, HeIIo, wrench man,That's Jimmy, You know, you can shoot peopIe here, You don;t have to throw a wrench at 'em, Fuck off, Take a Iook at this, I picked these guys up in Najaf, Nine of hearts, that's one, And the other,,, jack of cIubs,   These the same guys?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>At your six o'cIock I see movement on the bridge, Right on the tracks, WeII, handIe it, ShouId I fire?</template></category><category><pattern>CANCEI THE DET  CANCEI THE DET    WHAT THE FUCK IS HE DOING</pattern><template>I don't know, man, I don't know, I'm coming out, Roger that,   Where are you from?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT I'M THINKING ABOUT  DOC YEAH  THIS IS WHAT I'M THINKING ABOUT  DOC  HERE'S THOMPSON  OKAY  HE'S DEAD  HE'S AIIVE  HERE'S THOMPSON  HE'S DEAD  HE'S AIIVE  HE'S DEAD  HE'S AIIVE  YO  WHAT'S UP  MY NIGGER</pattern><template>What's up, man? You cooI?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY    WHAT'S UP  MAN</pattern><template>Look, we have a tank expIosion in the Green Zone, We have to post bIast assessment, see if it was a suicide bomber, and if so, how the fuck did he do it?</template></category><category><pattern>DOC</pattern><template>EIdridge, c'mon, man, C'mon I just saw him, He was waIking right here, I know, He's dead, Look, he's dead, Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>HE//O</pattern><template>Hey, Iet me ask you a question, What happened to the IittIe kid that used to work here?</template></category><category><pattern>GET OFF ME  HEY  HEY  HEY  I'M JUST KIDDING  MOTHERFUCKER  SHIT  YOU'RE AII RIGHT  SANBORN  YOU'RE AII RIGHT  MAN  OWEN  GET THIS GUY A DRINK  C'MON    YOU GOT HIM</pattern><template>Yeah, I got him,   AII right, here,   AII right,   See you Iater,   Be safe,   AII right, AII right, come on big boy, Damn, boy, you need to get on a diet, He hurt his knee, C'mon, man, Steps, C'mon, Step, Step, AII right, Iay down, AII right, Get some rest, Hey, James, you think I got what it takes to put on the suit?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  WE'VE BEEN HERE A WHIIE  WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE SOON  UH HUH  WE GOT A IOT OF EYES ON US  JAMES  WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE  ROGER THAT  I'M GOING TO FIGURE THIS OUT  JAMES  WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE  JAMES  DO YOU COPY</pattern><template>Fuck it, I get it, Fuck me,   Hey, how's it Iooking in there, soIdier?   AII cIear, James, the evac is compIete, We can Ieave, Let the engineers handIe this mess,   We moving?</template></category><category><pattern>AN OII TANKER</pattern><template>Yep, That's a pretty Iong fIight, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HEY  WAIT A MINUTE  LOOK WHO IT IS  I WANT MY FIVE BUCKS BACK  BUDDY  FIVE DOIIARS FOR WHAT  MAN</pattern><template>You crazy now?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON;T EVEN HAVE A SON  WEII  YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE PIENTY OF TIME FOR THAT  AMIGO    NAW  MAN    YOU KNOW</pattern><template>I'm done, I want a son, I want a IittIe boy, WiII, I mean, how do you do it, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>HE THERE</pattern><template>Wait here, Fuck, Psst, Psst, Shh, You speak EngIish?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  IET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION  WHAT HAPPENED TO THE IITTIE KID THAT USED TO WORK HERE</pattern><template>Sorry, man, EngIish I,,, no EngIish, No no EngIish, You no speak EngIish now, LittIe kid, Beckham is his name, He seIIs,,, seIIs DVDs, DVD, One DVD, $5, Oh, Jesus Christ,   $5,   Excuse me, soIdier, you in charge of this area here?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR  I ASKED YOU A QUESTION  EIGHT HUNDRED SEVENTY THREE  SIR  EIGHT HUNDRED  AND SEVENTY THREE  THAT'S JUST HOT SHIT  EIGHT HUNDRED AND SEVENTY THREE  COUNTING TODAY  SIR  YES    THAT'S GOTTA BE A RECORD  WHAT'S THE BEST WAY TO    GO ABOUT DISARMING ONE OF THESE THINGS</pattern><template>The way you don;t die, sir, That's a good one, That's spoken Iike a wiId man, That's good,   Hey, what's up, man?</template></category><category><pattern>WI//</pattern><template>HeIIo?</template></category><category><pattern>GAY SEX  MAN</pattern><template>Anything you want, you get, I hook you up, man, AII right, What,,, what's your name?</template></category><category><pattern>NEW YORK  THE BIG APPIE  ARE YOU FROM IRAQ</pattern><template>I Iove it here, This is a beautifuI pIace, But it's not too safe here, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>ADVANCE  ADVANCE    HANDS HIGH    EIDRIDGE  COVER</pattern><template>I got you, PistoI, off your hip, now, What you want me to do?</template></category><category><pattern>GOT TWO  AII RIGHT  LET'S ROCK AND ROII  MAN    HE'S A ROWDY BOY    HE'S RECKIESS  BIASTER ONE  WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>BIaster One! What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>What the fuck are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>TWEIVE O'CIOCK I SEE AN SUV    ROGER THAT  I GOT FOUR ARMED MEN  THEY'RE IN HAJI GEAR  AII RIGHT  GO SIOW AND EASY  CAREFUI NOW  AII RIGHT  CAREFUI NOW  GUYS    EIDRIDGE  YOU STAY ON THAT 50    I GOT 'EM  ''OBRE    OBRE   '' PUT YOUR GUN DOWN</pattern><template>On your knees!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU'RE FINE  MAN  AM I DEAD  AM I DEAD</pattern><template>I'm going to put some pressure down, Come on, You're aII right, Look at me, Iook at me, You aII right, AII right, buddy, You ready to get up?</template></category><category><pattern>GET OFF ME  YOU MOTHER FUCKER  WHAT DO YOU GOT  WHAT DO YOU GOT</pattern><template>Wooh, he's a wiId one, We got a wiId one, C'mon, Sanborn, Get him,That's right,   Ride him, baby,   Get off me,   C'mon, bitch,   C'mon, guys, What do you got?</template></category><category><pattern>CAR HAS BEEN PARKED IIIEGAIIY  THE SUSPENSION IS SAGGING  THERE'S DEFINITEIY SOMETHING HEAVY IN THE TRUNK  RIGHT  SO  WHY DON;T YOU WAIK OVER THERE AND PEAK INSIDE AND TEII ME WHAT YOU SEE  YOU WANT ME TO GO CIOSE TO IT</pattern><template>Yeah, No no, I don't, I'm kidding, Shit, It's coming from over here!</template></category><category><pattern>I'II HANDIE IT  THAT'S KIND OF TIGHT DOWN HERE  JAMES  READY</pattern><template>Good?</template></category><category><pattern>BECKHAM  12 YEAR OID BOY  BODY BOMB  STAY RIGHT THERE    I DON'T KNOW    YOU DON'T KNOW  BUT PIEASE  SIT DOWN  I AM PROFESSOR NAVID  THIS IS MY HOME  YOU ARE A GUEST  PIEASE  SIT DOWN  I'M A GUEST  JUST    I'M IOOKING FOR THE PEOPIE RESPONSIBIE FOR FOR FOR BECKHAM  YOU ARE CIA  NO</pattern><template>I am very pIeased to see CIA in my home, PIease, sit, How can I,,, Be carefuI, The gun can go off, U,S,A, friendIy coming in, Stop,Stop, Get the fuck down, U,S,A, friendIy, On your knees, Get on your knees now, On your knees, You wiII be shot, Don;t move, On your knees, Down now,   Open your jacket!</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF THE CAR</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S NOT ANSWERING  YEAH  I THINK HE REMOVED HIS HEADSET  WEII  WIII YOU TEII HIM TO PUT HIS RADIO BACK ON  PIEASE</pattern><template>Hey, James!</template></category><category><pattern>UH  I'M NOT QUITE SURE    SERGEANT</pattern><template>Yes, sir, I asked you a question, Eight hundred seventy three, sir, Eight hundred! And seventy three, That's just hot shit, Eight hundred and seventy three, Counting today, sir, yes,   That's gotta be a record, What's the best way to,,, go about disarming one of these things?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOOD    GOOD    WHAT'S WRONG</pattern><template>Brakes are squeaking, Don't trust the mechanics around here, You know,   So, how you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  NO PROBIEM  MAYBE YOU SHOUIDN'T TAKE THIS DOWN  WE GET A IOT OF MORTARS AT NIGHT  THE PIYWOOD ON THE WINDOWS HEIP WITH THE IATERAI FRAY COMING THROUGH  THAT'S WHY IT'S UP THERE  YEAH  WEII  IT'S NOT GOING TO STOP A MORTAR ROUND FROM COMING IN THROUGH THE ROOF  YOU KNOW  BESIDES  I IIKE THE SUNSHINE  HEY  I'M SORRY TO HEAR ABOUT THOMPSON    I KNOW HE WAS A GOOD TECH    YEAH  HE WAS  HE WAS A GREAT TEAM IEADER TOO  YEAH  I'M NOT TRYING TO FIII HIS SHOES OR ANYTHING  I'M JUST    I'M JUST GOING TO DO MY BEST    APPRECIATE IT    AII RIGHT  COOI  HOME SWEET HOME  RIGHT</pattern><template>Aren't you gIad the Army has aII these tanks parked here?</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  YEAH YOU GOT ANY SPARES</pattern><template>We have spares, but we've used up our wrench, How do you use up a wrench?</template></category><category><pattern>SANBORN  YOU HAVE 405 SECONDS  YOU HAVE 45 SECONDS  SANBORN  IEAVE  YOU'RE FUCKING DEAD  MAN  DEAD  GO</pattern><template>Everybody get back!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WE'RE GOING ON A MISSION  AND MY JOB IS TO KEEP YOU SAFE SO WE CAN KEEP GOING ON MISSIONS  IT'S COMBAT  BUDDY  HEY  IT'S JUST 39 DAYS  THIRTY EIGHT IF WE SURVIVE TODAY  HEY  IT'S ''MR  BE AII YOU CAN BE''  WHAT'S UP  DOC</pattern><template>Not much, How are you?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT FOR YOU    NO  OKAY  HEIMET ON  HAPPY TRAIIS  BIASTER ONE  CAN YOU READ ME</pattern><template>Roger that, BIaster one, You're good to go, You're Iooking good, BIaster One, Nice and hot in here, One fifty, Roger that, 150 meters Hi,   Where are you from?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THE BEST SHIT  MAN    OKAY  HERE YOU GO  I'II TAKE ONE    KEEP THE CHANGE    THANK YOU  WANT A CIGARETTE</pattern><template>Get out of here, You shouIdn't smoke, Thank you, Take it easy, I need to taIk to you about something before we go out again, What's that?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF IT WAS A REMOTE DET</pattern><template>A reaIIy good bad guy hides out in the dark, right?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE'S A A FAMIIY MAN  HE'S NOT A BAD MAN  HE'S ASKING FOR HEIP  ONIY HEIP  YEAH  AII RIGHT  YOU DON;T WANT TO DIE  GET BACK  I GOT IT  LISTEN  I KNOW WE'VE HAD OUR DIFFERENCES  IT HAPPENED  AII RIGHT  IT'S WATER UNDER THE BRIDGE  THIS IS SUICIDE  MAN  THAT'S WHY THEY CAII IT A SUICIDE BOMB  RIGHT</pattern><template>Let's do this, Come on, He says the bomb may have a timer, pIease hurry,   We're good, Ready?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MAN  THAT'S CASE IRON STEEI  SHIT    WHAT'S OUR TIME</pattern><template>We got two minutes,   Shit, We're going need a torch to get this off, WeII, we don;t have one of those in the fucking truck, man, He's dead, man, HoId on, man, Let me think, Just Iet me think, We're going to handIe this, It's okay, We got this, Shh, okay, Now Iisten, you're gonna get back, It's just we don;t got enough time, Sanborn, I just gotta,,, I gotta get these boIts off, No, We got a minute and a haIf, man, We gotta get out of here,   I'II handIe this, Just go,   Come on, man, Look, I'm right behind ya, Just go, Fuck him! Come on, Let's go,   Sanborn, I got the suit, Just go,   James!</template></category><category><pattern>CHIII OUT ON THE 50</pattern><template>Roger that,   Fifty's down,   They shot Chris, It must be coming from that buiIding, I can't see anything, Movement on the roof, Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>MAKE HIM PUT IT DOWN</pattern><template>Go get it!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S UP  MAN  YOU COOI</pattern><template>Come on, You want the cooI shit?</template></category><category><pattern>SO  I THINK WE NEED   WE NEED TO MOVE  PIEASE  YOU THINK IT'S THAT IITTIE BECKHAM</pattern><template>No, I don't,   You're positive?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S THIS ONE FROM  WIII</pattern><template>It's my wedding ring, Like I said, stuff that aImost kiIIed me, You know, I just think it's reaIIy interested to hoId something in your hand that couId have kiIIed anyone, Damn that, It's aII shit from radio shack, It's interesting, I think it's interesting too, WeII, I think you hit me harder than I hit you therefore I owe you a punch, Now get your ass up, C'mon, C'mon, He's right, Let's go, C'mon, Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>FIRING NOW  EEE  OOH      READY FOR SECOND DET</pattern><template>Ready, Fire in the hoIe!</template></category><category><pattern>HEIIO</pattern><template>He//o?</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK IT  I GET IT  FUCK ME    HEY  HOW'S IT IOOKING IN THERE  SOIDIER    AII CIEAR  JAMES  THE EVAC IS COMPIETE  WE CAN IEAVE  LET THE ENGINEERS HANDIE THIS MESS    WE MOVING</pattern><template>That's affirmative, Interesting, What's up with, James?</template></category><category><pattern>CAIIFORNIA</pattern><template>Hey, get out of here, man,   Where?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M IOOKING  WE NEED THAT AMMO  MAN  AII RIGHT  MAN  OH  HERE  THANKS  AII RIGHT  GOT IT  SAME TARGET  IT'S FUCKING JAMMED  LET ME SEE IT  FUCK</pattern><template>Aw, shit, The bIood's making it jam, EIdridge, Shit!</template></category><category><pattern>AFTERNOON  SIR  UH  YES  SIR  WEII  THAT'S JUST HOT SHIT  YOU'RE A WIID MAN  YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>Uh, yes, sir,   He's a wiId man, You know that?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU SHOOT SOMEONE  YOU MOTHERFUCKER  SORRY    SORRY  OWEN    FUCK YOU  WIII  REAIIY  FUCK YOU  THANKS FOR SAVING MY IIFE  BUT WE DIDN;T HAVE TO GO OUT IOOKING FOR TROUBIE TO GET YOUR FUCKING ADRENAIINE FIX  YOU FUCK  HEY  TAKE CARE OF YOURSEIF  OWEN  COME HOME SAFE  MAN    SEE YOU ON THE OTHER SIDE  MAN    AII RIGHT  LET'S GET OUT OF THIS FUCKING DESERT</pattern><template>Don't move, If you keep waIking we wiII shoot you, Move him back, Keep that transIator back,   But the bomb was forced on him,   Get him back!</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  HEY  I DON'T KNOW  MAN  THEY AII IOOK THE SAME  RIGHT</pattern><template>I know,   WiII seemed sure, That was weird,   Very weird, PIease, just move, Move, Move, Move on, Thank you, I'm sorry, WiII's very weird, I mean he keeps bomb parts under his bed, I'II bet you he won't keep any of these parts under his bed, Bye bye, Yeah, bye bye, Bye, Thank you, Hey, CoIoneI, Let's go, HaIIo, thank you, IED!</template></category><category><pattern>NOT MUCH  HOW ARE YOU</pattern><template>I'm good, Got a question about that song, ''Be AII You Can Be'', What if aII I can be is dead on the side of an Iraqi road?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DON'T    YOU'RE POSITIVE</pattern><template>Sure, Hey, I don't know, man, They aII Iook the same, right?</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT THIS WAS CAMP LIBERTY  OH  NO  THEY CHANGED THAT ABOUT A WEEK AGO  VICTORY SOUNDS BETTER    AII RIGHT  WEII  AT IEAST I'M IN THE RIGHT PIACE  RIGHT    YEAH  WHIIE YOU'RE HERE  CAN YOU HEIP ME MOVE THIS THING REAI QUICK</pattern><template>Yeah, no probIem, Maybe you shouIdn't take this down, We get a Iot of mortars at night, The pIywood on the windows heIp with the IateraI fray coming through, That's why it's up there, Yeah, weII, it's not going to stop a mortar round from coming in through the roof, you know, Besides, I Iike the sunshine, Hey, I'm sorry to hear about Thompson,   I know he was a good tech,   Yeah, he was, He was a great team Ieader too, Yeah, I'm not trying to fiII his shoes or anything, I'm just,,, I'm just going to do my best,   Appreciate it,   AII right, CooI, Home sweet home, right?</template></category><category><pattern>YEP  THAT'S THEM  DOES HE NEED A IITTIE HEIP THERE</pattern><template>What's the probIem with the tire? Come on, No good, boss, This wrench is too smaII, AII right, soIutions? Anyone?</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES DO YOU HAVE YOUR EARS ON</pattern><template>James?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YEAH    OH  HE'S AII RIGHT    GET UP  BITCH  AII RIGHT  BITCH    WHAT DO YOU GOT NOW</pattern><template>Get the fuck off me?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  THIS AIN'T NO FUCKIN' MEET AND GREET  NOW GET OUT OF HERE  NOW  GO  YOU MAKING FRIENDS AGAIN  SANBORN</pattern><template>AII day Iong, Twenty five, Twenty five meters, Roger that, You are now in the kiII zone, Thanks for reminding me, That's what I'm here for, baby, Okay  The debts Iook good, Roger that, I'm Iaying on the charge,, Nice and sweet, We're good to go, I'm coming back,   Five meters out,   Five meters, Roger that, Hey, Sanborn   You know what this pIace needs?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT TWO MINUTES    SHIT  WE'RE GOING NEED A TORCH TO GET THIS OFF  WEII  WE DON;T HAVE ONE OF THOSE IN THE FUCKING TRUCK  MAN  HE'S DEAD  MAN  HOID ON  MAN  LET ME THINK  JUST IET ME THINK  WE'RE GOING TO HANDIE THIS  IT'S OKAY  WE GOT THIS  SHH  OKAY  NOW IISTEN  YOU'RE GONNA GET BACK  IT'S JUST WE DON;T GOT ENOUGH TIME  SANBORN  I JUST GOTTA    I GOTTA GET THESE BOITS OFF  NO  WE GOT A MINUTE AND A HAIF  MAN  WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE    I'II HANDIE THIS  JUST GO    COME ON  MAN  LOOK  I'M RIGHT BEHIND YA  JUST GO  FUCK HIM  COME ON  LET'S GO    SANBORN  I GOT THE SUIT  JUST GO    JAMES</pattern><template>Sanborn, you have 405 seconds, You have 45 seconds, Sanborn, Ieave, You're fucking dead, man, Dead, Go!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S UP</pattern><template>Come on, man, Wanna pIay some,,, Aww, Fuck, How you doing, buddy?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE FOR FIVE AND TWO FOR NINE  THREE FOR TWEIVE  THREE FOR THIRTEEN AND I DON;T GIVE YOU TAX  VERY GOOD  MAN  LOOK    LOOK      NO TAX</pattern><template>AII right, What do you got?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  MY TEAM'S GREAT  MY TEAM IEADER IS INSPIRING    ARE YOU BEING SARCASTIC  SOIDIER</pattern><template>No, He's going to get me kiIIed, aImost died yesterday, At Ieast I'II die in the Iine of duty, proud and strong, You know, this doesn;t have to be a bad time in your Iife, Going to war is a   is a once in a Iifetime experience, It couId be fun, And you know this from your extensive work in the fieId, right?</template></category><category><pattern>JAMES</pattern><template>This is James, What's up?</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT YOU  PISTOI  OFF YOUR HIP  NOW  WHAT YOU WANT ME TO DO</pattern><template>Keep my hands up or take off the pistoI?</template></category><category><pattern>VICTORY MAIN  VICTORY MAIN  THIS IS BIASTER MIKE  INTERROGATIVE  DO YOU HAVE AN UPDATE ON POSITION  OVER  VICTORY MAIN  FIGURES TO FOIIOW  THREE FOUR FIVE THREE IS YOUR GRID  WEII  THAT'S EXACTIY WHERE THE HEII I AM AND I DON;T SEE ANYBODY IN FATIGUES  GIVE US A SECOND TO CONFIRM  WATCH YOUR FEET  SET VISUAI IS THREE FOUR FIVE THREE  GOT THE HUMVEE  FRIENDIY</pattern><template>FriendIy, Ah, here we go, They abandoned their vehicIe, We got an empty Humvee over here, James, Yeah, I got it, Let's move, FriendIy,   Morning, boys,   Sir, Don't teII me the bomb's in here with you guys,   Step out and I'II show you what's going on,   AII right, Down on that bIock 20 meters, this side of the mosque, east side of the street, our informant says he saw a pair of wires going into a rubbIe piIe,   It's a possibIe IED,   Yeah,   I trust this guy, I know him,   Okay,   I'II handIe it,   Do you want to taIk him or,,,   No, Good, Keep your boys back, We'II be good, Thank you, SpeciaIist, bring up the Humvee, What's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  JAMES  HOW YOU DOING</pattern><template>I'm wonderfuI, How are you?</template></category><category><pattern>AW  MAN  I FUCKIN' HATE THIS PIACE  HERE  MAN  HAVE A HIT  I'M NOT READY TO DIE  JAMES  WEII  YOU'RE NOT GOING TO DIE OUT HERE  BRO  ANOTHER TWO INCHES  SHRAPNEI ZINGS BY  SIICES MY THROAT  I BIEED OUT IIKE A PIG IN THE SAND  NOBODY'II GIVE A SHIT  I MEAN  MY PARENTS'II CARE  BUT THEY DON;T COUNT  MAN  WHO EISE</pattern><template>I don;t even have a son, WeII, you're going to have pIenty of time for that, amigo,   Naw, man,   You know?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT TO CHANGE THE RECORD IN OUR HEAD  YOU GOTTA START THINKING ABOUT OTHER THINGS  OKAY  STOP OBSESSING    RIGHT NOW  WHAT ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT</pattern><template>You want to know what I'm thinking about, doc?Yeah, This is what I'm thinking about, doc, Here's Thompson, okay, He's dead, He's aIive, Here's Thompson, He's dead, He's aIive, He's dead, He's aIive, Yo, what's up, my nigger?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  I JUST      I GUESS I DON;T THINK ABOUT IT  BUT YOU REAIIZE EVERY TIME YOU SUIT UP  EVERY TIME WE GO OUT IT'S IIFE OR DEATH  YOU ROII THE DICE AND YOU DEAI WITH IT  YOU RECOGNIZE THAT  DON;T YOU</pattern><template>Yeah, Yeah, I do, But I don't know why, Yeah, I don't know, JT, You know why I am the way I am?</template></category><category><pattern>MAN  COME ON  AII RIGHT  I GOT YA  GOOD JOB  DUDE  HERE'S FIVE  YOU'RE AN EOD  BOOMAIA  BOOMAIA  THAT'S RIGHT  IT'S FUN  NO</pattern><template>It's cooI? It's gangster,   Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  I JUST WANT TO CHECK THE OII  YEAH  IT'S GOOD TO SIEEP  EATING WEII    I'M FEEIING PRETTY SQUARED AWAY  ACTUAIIY  DOC  GOOD TO HEAR IT  SO  YOU GETTING AIONG WITH THE OTHER SOIDIERS IN YOUR UNIT</pattern><template>Yeah, My team's great, My team Ieader is inspiring,   Are you being sarcastic, soIdier?</template></category><category><pattern>A REAIIY GOOD BAD GUY HIDES OUT IN THE DARK  RIGHT</pattern><template>Right here, Perfect vantage point, outside the bIast radius to sit back and watch us cIean up their mess,   Want to go out there?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT  MAN I'M GOING TO SEII THE GRASS  YOU'RE GOING TO CUT IT  IT'S GOING TO BE CAIIED ''SANBORN AND SONS''  WE'II BE RICH  I IIKE THAT  CRABGASS  ST  AUGUSTINE  MAN  I'M A SCHOIAR ON THIS SHIT  HOW ABOUT THIS</pattern><template>You seII it, I fertiIize it, (Laughs)   25,   25 meters, Roger that, Sanborn!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  JAMES  DO YOU COPY</pattern><template>James do you have your ears on?</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT OF HERE  YOU SHOUIDN'T SMOKE  THANK YOU  TAKE IT EASY  I NEED TO TAIK TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING BEFORE WE GO OUT AGAIN  WHAT'S THAT</pattern><template>Yesterday,   Mm hmm, Wasn't cooI, Yeah, I know, You'II get it, though,   So, you're a ranger, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>WANNA BUY DVD</pattern><template>Fuck you, Come, come, pIease, pIease, New reIeases, Look, HeIIo, HeIIo, Want to buy DVDs? Very good, Very good, How much?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THERE'S ANOTHER WRENCH IN THE BACK OF THE HUMVEE IF YOU WANT TO CHECK    I'II GIVE IT A TRY    AII RIGHT  LET'S DO IT  HOW IONG YOU GUYS OUT HERE</pattern><template>SpeciaIist, what do we got?</template></category><category><pattern>GET THE FUCK OFF ME</pattern><template>What do you got?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S JUST IOYAI  SHE'S JUST IOYAI  THAT'S AII  HOW 'BOUT YOU GUYS</pattern><template>You got,,, you got a girI?</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS I DON;T WISH TO DIE  I HAVE A FAMIIY    PIEASE TAKE THIS OFF ME  TEII HIM TO PUT HIS HANDS BEHIND HIS HEAD OR I'II BE VERY HAPPY TO SHOOT HIM  LOOK  THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID  TEII HIM TO PUT HIS HANDS BEHIND HIS HEAD OR I WIII SHOOT HIM  LISTEN  LISTEN  IISTEN  YOU UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>Okay, What do you got here?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  JAMES  CAN YOU HEAR ME</pattern><template>What's going on with the smoke on the side of the road? Over, Creating a diversion From what? Is there a threat?</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE IT EASY  YOU SEE THAT  YOU FUCKIN' SEE THAT</pattern><template>That's what happens when you shoot someone, you motherfucker, Sorry,   Sorry, Owen,   Fuck you, WiII, ReaIIy, Fuck you, Thanks for saving my Iife, but we didn;t have to go out Iooking for troubIe to get your fucking adrenaIine fix, you fuck, Hey, take care of yourseIf, Owen, Come home safe, man,   See you on the other side, man,   AII right, Let's get out of this fucking desert!</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  MAN  I DON'T KNOW  I'M COMING OUT  ROGER THAT    WHERE ARE YOU FROM</pattern><template>New York, The Big AppIe, Are you from Iraq?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  YOU DON;T WANT ME TO COME AROUND  I WON'T COME AROUND  THESE TAIKS ARE VOIUNTARY  LOOK  I'M SORRY  I APPRECIATE WHAT YOU'RE SAYING I DO  I APPRECIATE OUR SESSIONS TOGETHER  BUT YOU NEED TO COME OUT FROM BEHIND THE WIRE  SEE WHAT WE DO  WEII  IF THIS CIRCUMSTANCE CAIIS FOR IT  I WIII  JUST IIKE EVERY OTHER SOIDIER FIRE IN THE HOIE</pattern><template>Firing now, Eee, ooh,,,   Ready for second det?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  CHRIS  CHRIS  CAN YOU HEAR ME</pattern><template>ChiII out on the 50!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'II NEVER GET IN IF YOU DID THAT    HERE  LET ME HAVE A SHOT    GIVE ME A SECOND    NO  COME ON  MY DICK  MAN    GO  FUCKER    GOT THAT    YEAH  HERE WE GO    OH  IOOK AT THAT    NICE 155  HUH    YEAH  IT'S GOING TO DO SOME FUCKING DAMAGE  HEY  EIDRIDGE  IOOKS IIKE WE'RE GOING TO NEED A CHARGE  I GOT THAT  FIGURED FOUR BIOCKS THAT'II GIVE US ABOUT 20 POUNDS OF BANG TOTAI  THAT BIAST IS GOING TO ROAST STRAIGHT OUT THERE  THE SHEII WIII PROBABIY KICK OUT THERE  AND MOST OF THE SHRAPNEI IS GOING TO SHOOT STRAIGHT UP IN A BEAUTIFUI UMBREIIA PATTERN  YEP  WE'RE GONNA GET SOME SMAIIER PIECES AND SHEII FRAGMENTS THIS WAY  BUT WE'II BE OKAY IF WE'RE BEHIND THE HUMVEE    BRING THE BOT BACK  WE'II IOAD IT UP    NO PROBIEM  BOT IS MOVING  LET ME KNOW WHAT YOU GOT  EIDRIDGE  GOOD TO GO  AII RIGHT  WAGON'S SET UP  BOT MOVES  UH OH  WE GOT GOATS  GUYS  GOATS 12:00  WATCH OUT  LOAD THEM IITTIE BASTARDS UP    OH  SHIT    SHIT  OH  FUCK  WAGON'S HAVING A BAD DAY  BOYS    YOU BUIID THAT</pattern><template>No, the U,S, Army did, AII right, Looks Iike I'm going down there, You don;t Iike waiting around this beautifuI neighborhood?</template></category><category><pattern>BIASTER ONE  YOU HEAR ME</pattern><template>Here, Shit, Let's go, guys, Let it go, I got top cover, That's a negative, speciaIist, EIdridge, you stay with me, Sanborn, you take top covers, Shit, BIaster Mike in position, What do you got?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD</pattern><template>You don;t have to go down there, We aIready have the bot haIfway up, I'II be aII right, First day, figure you want to take it easy, right?</template></category><category><pattern>THE WAY YOU DON;T DIE  SIR  THAT'S A GOOD ONE  THAT'S SPOKEN IIKE A WIID MAN  THAT'S GOOD    HEY  WHAT'S UP  MAN</pattern><template>Oh, hey, wait a minute, Look who it is, I want my five bucks back, buddy, Five doIIars for what, man?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  BRING SOME  C'MON  OOH</pattern><template>Wooh, God damn, That's gotta hurt,   You aII right, man?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO WE KNOW THAT HE'S NOT GIVING INTEI TO INSURGENTS  TEIIING THEM WHERE TO DROP MORTARS</pattern><template>I think he's just seIIing DVDs, WeII, he's a security risk, We shouId get rid of him, What are you Iooking at?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T GET HIM IN SIGHT</pattern><template>Thompson!</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP MY HANDS UP OR TAKE OFF THE PISTOI</pattern><template>Keep your hands up,   Okay, Easy, easy, Got it!</template></category></AIML>