<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>WHATEVER ELSE ON EARTH IS GOING ON  HE'S OUR FRIEND</pattern><template>You sure about that?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU SEE YOURSELF AS SEPARATE FROM THE REST OF HUMANITY</pattern><template>I didn't mean it that way.</template></category><category><pattern>DEPENDS ON THEIR BALANCE WITH THE ENVIRONMENT</pattern><template>We've made a mess of it.</template></category><category><pattern>ART'S GONNA BE ALONG  TOO</pattern><template>He's, uh, talking to a student. Pfft.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  LET'S TAKE JOHN'S STORY AT FACE VALUE AND EXPLORE IT FROM THAT PERSPECTIVE</pattern><template>If he doesn't scar, it's no stranger than the rest.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU WANT  WHAT'S THE PUNCH LINE</pattern><template>Every ten years or so, when people start To notice I don't age, I move on.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S ABSOLUTELY NO WAY IN THE WHOLE WORLD FOR JOHN TO PROVE THIS STORY TO US  JUST LIKE THERE'S NO WAY FOR US TO DISPROVE IT</pattern><template>No matter how outrageous we think it is, No matter how highly trained some of us think we are, There's absolutely no way to disprove it.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  UH  WELL</pattern><template>People do go around armed these days.</template></category><category><pattern>I SUPPOSE I HAVE</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY THOUGHT THAT I WAS STEALING THEIR LIVES AWAY TO STAY YOUNG</pattern><template>The prehistoric origin of the vampire myth.</template></category><category><pattern>MOSES WAS BASED ON MISIS  A SYRIAN MYTH  AND THERE ARE EARLIER VERSIONS   ALL FOUND FLOATING ON WATER  THE STAFF THAT CHANGED TO A SNAKE  WATERS THAT WERE PARTED SO FOLLOWERS COULD BE LED TO FREEDOM AND EVEN RECEIVE LAWS ON STONE OR WOODEN TABLETS</pattern><template>One of the apostles.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE THERE IS SOMETHING TO THIS REINCARNATION THING</pattern><template>You're supposed to come back Again and again, learn and learn, And somehow, John, you just managed To bypass all the other bodies.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCEPT YOURS  WILL</pattern><template>That makes me feel a trifle lilliputian.</template></category><category><pattern>COMING</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>SURE</pattern><template>Would you like to tell us...</template></category><category><pattern>HE COULDN'T GET US RIGHT THE FIRST TIME  EDITH  TAKEN ALONE  THE PHILOSOPHICAL TEACHINGS OF JESUS ARE BUDDHISM WITH A HEBREW ACCENT   KINDNESS  TOLERANCE  BROTHERHOOD  LOVE  A RUTHLESS REALISM ACKNOWLEDGING THAT LIFE IS AS IT IS HERE ON EARTH  HERE AND NOW</pattern><template>The kingdom of god, meaning goodness, Is right here, where it should be.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE  AS MUCH AS ANYONE</pattern><template>Seriously ill?</template></category><category><pattern>HE COULDN'T GET IT RIGHT THE FIRST TIME</pattern><template>We're imperfect! He had to work to make us understand.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS TOLD I COULD NEVER GO THERE ALONE</pattern><template>And if you went back there today, Would it be the same?</template></category><category><pattern>BELIEVE IN WHAT HE TRIED TO TEACH  WITHOUT RIGMAROLE</pattern><template>Piety is not what the lessons bring to people.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY RAN IT OUT OF THE BALLPARK</pattern><template>This is blasphemy.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT QUESTION</pattern><template>No, come on!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID A TERRIBLE THING  BUT WE'RE ALL SO THANKFUL YOU'RE ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Even Art  He just hates things he can't understand.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  SORRY</pattern><template>I picked it up with the periodicals.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HOW WOULD YOU KNOW AN OCEAN FROM A LAKE</pattern><template>Big waves   Something else I can only surmise in retrospect.</template></category><category><pattern>INJURIES WE COULD UNDERSTAND   IF SOMEONE'S INSIDES WERE ALL OVER THE GROUND</pattern><template>Infections...</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S STILL TIME  IF WE USE IT WELL</pattern><template>Christianity has been a worldwide belief For 2,000 years.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  SINCE THIS ISN'T FUNNY  WE THINK YOU MIGHT HAVE A PROBLEM</pattern><template>A very serious problem.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  MAYBE SOMETIME  BUT I WOULDN'T REALLY WANT MONEY FOR IT</pattern><template>That does it.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT VAN GOGH</pattern><template>He gave it to me.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE MISTAKE THEY BRING TO THE LESSONS</pattern><template>Well, it's getting to be night.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE'D HAD MORE TIME  WE'D HAVE DONE SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE GRANDIOSE</pattern><template>Candlelight dinner at Mcdonald's.</template></category><category><pattern>SIT DOWN  EDITH  YOU ACT LIKE YOU BELIEVE HIM</pattern><template>It's sacrilege.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T GET THERE FROM HERE  ART</pattern><template>Well then, pray, continue.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TIME HAS COME WHEN YOU MUST ADMIT THIS IS A HOAX</pattern><template>a lie.</template></category><category><pattern>I REALLY WISH I'D BEEN HERE FROM THE BEGINNING</pattern><template>Me too.</template></category><category><pattern>60 YEARS AGO</pattern><template>J John Partee?</template></category><category><pattern>SO HIS FOLLOWERS PULLED HIM FROM THE CROSS  PLACED HIM IN A CAVE</pattern><template>his body normalized as he had trained it to...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IT'S BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>Art.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HOW COULD HE HAVE CONCEALED THAT FOR TEN YEARS</pattern><template>Least he doesn't appear to be dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WHAT A CHANCE TO LEARN</pattern><template>Is anyone hungry?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO KNOW WHAT TO KILL</pattern><template>Is this why all your students Say your knowledge of history is...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WILL LIVE</pattern><template>Will you come to my funeral, John?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Checkin' for a hidden mic.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE WE KNOW</pattern><template>How could we not know someone in the bible?</template></category><category><pattern>SNOOPY FRIENDS</pattern><template>Forget it.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU LIVED 100    1 000 YEARS</pattern><template>would you still have this?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M LEERY OF LABS</pattern><template>Afraid I might go in and stay for a thousand years While cigarette smoking men try to figure me out.</template></category><category><pattern>AS TALES OF THE RESURRECTION SPREAD  THE NAME WAS CONFUSED WITH THE HEBREW  YOCHANAN   MEANING  GOD IS GRACIOUS   MY STAY ON EARTH WAS SEEN AS DIVINE PROOF OF IMMORTALITY</pattern><template>That led to  god is salvation  Or hebrew  yahshua,  Which in translation became my proper name, Changing to late greek,  iesous,  Then to late latin,  iesus,  And finally medieval latin,  Jesus,  And it was a wonder to watch it all happen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO COME BACK AGAIN AND AGAIN  LEARN AND LEARN  AND SOMEHOW  JOHN  YOU JUST MANAGED TO BYPASS ALL THE OTHER BODIES</pattern><template>Well, what's the point?</template></category><category><pattern>FOURTEEN THOUSAND YEARS</pattern><template>Injuries, illness, disasters.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  HA HA HA</pattern><template>Uhn!</template></category><category><pattern>A BURIN IS A FLINT TOOL FOR GROOVING WOOD AND BONE  ANTLERS ESPECIALLY  TO MAKE SPEAR AND HARPOON POINTS</pattern><template>Magdalenians weren't noted for flint work, So this is a very nice specimen.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A GOOD CHRISTIAN  I   OH  JOHN</pattern><template>Oh! Well.</template></category><category><pattern>I</pattern><template>I did some teaching on a hill one day.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE IMPERFECT  HE HAD TO WORK TO MAKE US UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>He couldn't get us right the first time, Edith? Taken alone, the philosophical teachings of Jesus Are buddhism with a hebrew accent   Kindness, tolerance, brotherhood, love, A ruthless realism acknowledging That life is as it is here on earth, here and now.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME JUST NEVER GET OVER IT</pattern><template>Do you believe in god?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BEEN SAID THAT BUDDHA AND JESUS WOULD LAUGH OR CRY IF THEY'D KNOWN WHAT WAS DONE IN THEIR NAME</pattern><template>And if there is a creator, He'd probably feel the same way.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT RIGHT NOW  I DO WANT TO HEAR THIS</pattern><template>Sit down, Edith. You act like you believe him.</template></category><category><pattern>ART</pattern><template>Ah.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TALK ABOUT ME WHILE I'M GONE</pattern><template>Is he serious?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYWHERE  CREATION MYTHS  NEW GODS  SO MANY  SO DIFFERENT</pattern><template>I finally realized that it was...</template></category><category><pattern>LONGER TO REALIZE HOW I WAS DIFFERENT  TO FIND A WAY TO SYNTHESIZE MY EXPERIENCE INTO A VIEW OF MYSELF</pattern><template>At first, I thought everybody had Something wrong with them.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO NOT BELIEVE YOU</pattern><template>Your mother's name was Nola.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  THAT'S INTERESTING</pattern><template>Just as we can never be sure, Even if we wanted to   I mean, if we were sure, You couldn't be sure of that.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE ALWAYS WONDERED ABOUT THE REASONS</pattern><template>Well, we still have an afternoon to kill, right?</template></category><category><pattern>PIETY IS NOT WHAT THE LESSONS BRING TO PEOPLE</pattern><template>It's the mistake they bring to the lessons.</template></category><category><pattern>THRIFT SHOP</pattern><template>Really.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOUR STORY'S TRUE  WHY DID GOD ALLOW YOU TO HAPPEN</pattern><template>That makes an interesting point.</template></category><category><pattern>SPENT A YEAR IN JAIL  BELGIUM  1862   I WON'T FORGET THAT   FOR FAKING A GOVERNMENT APPLICATION</pattern><template>When'd you come to america?</template></category><category><pattern>GET COMFORTABLE WHILE YOU CAN</pattern><template>The furniture's going this afternoon.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Look, we have two simple choices.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU</pattern><template>biblical Jesus said,  Who do you think I am?  He gave them a choice.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEET SOMEONE  LEARN THEIR NAME  SAY A WORD  THEY'RE GONE</pattern><template>Others come like waves. Rise, fall.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU GET ALZHEIMER'S AT 35</pattern><template>Maybe I'm trying to wake him up.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING ABOUT YOU  JOHN</pattern><template>The more I think about it, The more I'm no longer in that chinese box.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S IT</pattern><template>The three wise men began as a myth About the birth of the Buddha.</template></category><category><pattern>OLD MAN</pattern><template>Did that help you with your story?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU NEED HELP</pattern><template>Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LUCKY DOG</pattern><template>I gotta go digging for this kind of stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE IS  I'M SORRY TO SAY HE'S</pattern><template>oh, how could he have concealed that for ten years?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE PLAYING MY GAME</pattern><template>I was playing yours.</template></category><category><pattern>PETER THE FISHERMAN LEARNED A LITTLE MORE ABOUT FISHING</pattern><template>How do you know that?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  SERIOUSLY  AS ART'S BOOK TITLE SUGGESTS  HE MIGHT BE LIKE ANY OF US</pattern><template>Dan. A caveman?</template></category><category><pattern>COME AGAIN</pattern><template>Edith saw my fake Van Gogh.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU HAVE  UM</pattern><template>any religious beliefs, Or did you give it much thought?</template></category><category><pattern>ISN'T THAT TRUE  JOHN</pattern><template>If you don't drop this now   If you can   I'll be convinced That you need a great deal of attention.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A BURIN OF A PARROT BEAK</pattern><template>Inclined chisel point...</template></category><category><pattern>MOVING ON</pattern><template>An answer for every question.</template></category><category><pattern>I IMAGINE THAT THERE IS ROOM THERE FOR A HOLY WAR IN MY LIVING ROOM  BUT WE PRACTICE LIVE AND LET LIVE</pattern><template>Why don't you sit down.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOT GOOD</pattern><template>The truth is so, so simple.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA GO HOME  AND I'M GONNA WATCH STAR TREK FOR A DOSE OF SANITY</pattern><template>Good luck to you, man, Wherever this may lead you.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE DISSIDENT AGAINST ROME</pattern><template>Rome won.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES I DO  WILL</pattern><template>Look up at the stars.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D WONDER ABOUT THE SOURCE OF THE PRIME MOVER  INFINITE REGRESS  BUT THAT DOESN'T IMPLY ANYTHING TO ME</pattern><template>Back to the mystery.</template></category><category><pattern>LAKESIDE LIVING BECOMES COMMONPLACE  FISHING  FOWLING   COME ON</pattern><template>John, this is out of any textbook.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO THEY PAY YOU</pattern><template>Nothing is too good for my friends.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THE CRO MAGNON WAS FIRST IDENTIFIED  WHEN ANTHROPOLOGY GAVE THEM A NAME  I HAD MINE</pattern><template>Well, please continue.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY 50 YEARS OR SO  WHEN I WANNA GET AWAY FROM THE RUSH  I GO DOWN TO A PRIMITIVE TRIBE IN NEW GUINEA WHERE I'M WORSHIPPED AS AN IMMORTAL GOD  AND THEY HAVE A HUGE STATUE OF ME</pattern><template>It's a big party.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT THE HISTORY CHAIR AT STANFORD</pattern><template>I wish.</template></category><category><pattern>GAS IS OFF  ELECTRICITY'S ON</pattern><template>Get comfortable while you can.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY HE FIND UNDESERVED BLISS WHEREVER HE GOES</pattern><template>Here, here.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA GO DRINK IN THE CORNER</pattern><template>You're, uh... you're donating it?</template></category><category><pattern>INCONSIDERATELY YOU'RE TREATING MY FEELINGS</pattern><template>About as inconsiderately as we're treating John's.</template></category><category><pattern>RUN OUT OF ROOM EVEN FASTER</pattern><template>Then we'd have to go to mars as a colony As we expanded, as we'd have to.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID I HAD A MASTER THAT WAS GREATER THAN MYSELF</pattern><template>I never said he was my father.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES THE BIOLOGIST SAY</pattern><template>Cigarettes.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YEAH  INTO ANY TEXTBOOK</pattern><template>And that's where I found it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE GOT A HEART CONDITION</pattern><template>Don't grump about it.</template></category><category><pattern>I SUSPECT I SAW THE BRITISH ISLES FROM WHAT IS NOW THE FRENCH COAST</pattern><template>Huge mountains...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THAT'S TERRIBLE</pattern><template>More so than history describes.</template></category><category><pattern>CRAZY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU THINK THAT YOU ARE A</pattern><template>a, uh, Cro magnon.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T BOTHER WITH MINE  OKAY</pattern><template>You are absolutely certifiable.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A VERY OLD QUESTION  BUT THERE'S NO ANSWER EXCEPT IN RELIGIOUS TERMS</pattern><template>If you have faith, it's answered.</template></category><category><pattern>THE THREE WISE MEN BEGAN AS A MYTH ABOUT THE BIRTH OF THE BUDDHA</pattern><template>John, I should be home, uh, kissing my wife.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE DONE THIS BEFORE</pattern><template>No, no, no, you're too young to have done this before.</template></category><category><pattern>I BET THAT'S A LOT OF WOMEN</pattern><template>Are we counting?</template></category><category><pattern>SO DID BEETHOVEN DO PHYSICS ON THE SIDE</pattern><template>He spent most of his time lying on the floor In front of his legless piano Surrounded by orange peels and apple cores.</template></category><category><pattern>MM HMM  WHAT DIRECTION WAS IT</pattern><template>From your house.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD HAVE LIED ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>Don't talk about me while I'm gone.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I SOMETIMES DREAM ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Have you acted upon this belief?</template></category><category><pattern>MY OLDEST SON IS AN ATHEIST</pattern><template>My youngest is a scientologist.</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH</pattern><template>Well, taquitos, chicken wings, Roastie toasties and beer.</template></category><category><pattern>DIDN'T SEE THEM TILL MUCH LATER</pattern><template>So how would you know an ocean from a lake?</template></category><category><pattern>AH</pattern><template>So, can I get an  a  for awesome?</template></category><category><pattern>GIVIN' UP TENURE</pattern><template>a decade of professorship, In line to chair the department, And you don't know where you're going?</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE IT'S JUST ACCUMULATED  FIELDS AFFECTING FIELDS</pattern><template>What about the source of the field energies?</template></category><category><pattern>A DECADE OF PROFESSORSHIP  IN LINE TO CHAIR THE DEPARTMENT  AND YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE YOU'RE GOING</pattern><template>Call it cabin fever.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT ALL ABOUT</pattern><template>Where'd he get a gun?</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  I HAD TO MOVE ON</pattern><template>You know that. I left enough.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN A NEW NEW TESTAMENT IN 100 WORDS</pattern><template>I can give you the ten commandments in ten words.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE WE TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>We were just talking about a caveman Who survives until the present time.</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T MAKE THE OBVIOUS NASTY CRACK ABOUT MORE UNWASHED CAVEMEN</pattern><template>Actually, bathing was the style Until the middle ages when the church told us It was sinful to wash away god's dirt, So people were sewn Into their underwear in october And they popped out in april.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE PAPERS TO CORRECT</pattern><template>As much as I dislike that job, It'll be preferable to this.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  IT'S CRAZY</pattern><template>All right, all right, as soon as you can, then.</template></category><category><pattern>AM  AM I GETTING WARM  HERE</pattern><template>I bet I am.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF I COULD STAY HEALTHY AND I DIDN'T AGE  I MEAN  WHY NOT</pattern><template>Yeah. What a chance to learn.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU THINK THAT PERHAPS OUR CAVEMAN HAS A MONKEY ON HIS BACK</pattern><template>Drugs?</template></category><category><pattern>I ALSO GOT THE IDEA OF PERIODICALLY MOVING ON</pattern><template>We were semi Nomadic, of course, Following the weather and the game we hunted.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID DO A LITTLE HEALING WITH SOME EASTERN MEDICINE I'D LEARNED</pattern><template>That's it.</template></category><category><pattern>A VERY SERIOUS PROBLEM</pattern><template>I've got boxes to move.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT</pattern><template>I had a chance to sail with columbus, Only I'm not the adventurous type.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  UM  IN SCIENCE FICTION TERMS  I WOULD SAY</pattern><template>perfect regeneration of the body's cells, Especially in the vital organs.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SOUND LIKE OUR FOOTBALL COACH  DAN</pattern><template>What do you think, John?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  TO LONG LIFE AND GOOD FORTUNE TO OUR ESTEEMED FRIEND AND COLLEAGUE  JOHN OLDMAN</pattern><template>May he find undeserved bliss Wherever he goes.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER SAID HE WAS MY FATHER</pattern><template>I wanted to teach what I learned.</template></category><category><pattern>PRETTY DAMN CLOSELY  I'D SAY</pattern><template>The early Christian leaders, They threw away hebrew manuscripts And borrowed from pagan sources all over the place.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN DID YOU BEGIN TO BELIEVE YOU WERE A PSYCHIATRIST</pattern><template>Since I graduated harvard medical school And finished my residency, I've had that feeling.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WOULD HAVE LOVED THEM  THOUGH</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>1890  RIGHT AFTER VAN GOGH'S DEATH  WITH SOME FRENCH IMMIGRANTS</pattern><template>moving on.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT LEAVES ONLY ONE EXPLANATION</pattern><template>The time has come when you must admit This is a hoax...</template></category><category><pattern>WILL  THAT WAS A BIT MUCH</pattern><template>Ooh. Books.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WOULD CAUSE YOU TO KEEP IT</pattern><template>As a memento to your beginnings, Even if you didn't have The concept of beginnings?</template></category><category><pattern>GONNA CARD YOU  DARLING</pattern><template>All right, here, join the circle at least.</template></category><category><pattern>LINDA</pattern><template>Bye.</template></category><category><pattern>OHH</pattern><template>So, you were Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PREHISTORIC ORIGIN OF THE VAMPIRE MYTH</pattern><template>That is good!</template></category><category><pattern>CHECK MY REACTION</pattern><template>You asked if I was a figure from religious history, If there were others like me, If I'd created future identities.</template></category><category><pattern>CHILLY WILLY  ALWAYS COLD</pattern><template>Never could stand the cold.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU SIT DOWN</pattern><template>What is your preferred version of the bible?</template></category><category><pattern>MM  THAT'S A SECRET WE'D ALL LOVE TO HAVE</pattern><template>Would you really want to do that?</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING THAT HAPPENS  HAPPENS WITHIN NATURE  WHETHER WE BELIEVE IN IT OR NOT</pattern><template>Like a 14,000 year old caveman.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO SKIPPING  COME ON</pattern><template>Next question.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT AS YOUNG AS I USED TO BE</pattern><template>Ohh!</template></category><category><pattern>SURELY YOU DON'T BELIEVE THIS NONSENSE</pattern><template>I think we should remain courteous to someone Who we've known and trusted, Edith.</template></category><category><pattern>EVER</pattern><template>Long time ago I did, Like most people.</template></category><category><pattern>CANDLELIGHT DINNER AT MCDONALD'S</pattern><template>Strippers.</template></category><category><pattern>I LEARNED THAT IN   PROFESSOR HENSEN'S TEPID LECTURES</pattern><template>But you're right.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE YOU BEING SO HARD ON HIM</pattern><template>One of my favorite people has disappeared.</template></category><category><pattern>BYE</pattern><template>Well, Art was half right.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS  THIS WAS A BAD IDEA</pattern><template>Uh, I love you all, and I do not want To put you through anything.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE TALKING AS IF YOU BELIEVED HIM</pattern><template>Well, it is possible, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT A CAVEMAN WHO SURVIVES UNTIL THE PRESENT TIME</pattern><template>As you said, what a chance to learn, Once I learned to learn.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE MADE A MESS OF IT</pattern><template>There's still time, If we use it well.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOT AN ANSWER FOR EVERYTHING</pattern><template>It might involve rejection of his father, Of his entire early past, Replaced by this fantasy.</template></category><category><pattern>IS ANYONE HUNGRY</pattern><template>You know, the more I think about it, yeah, it's possible.</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH YOU DIDN'T FEEL THAT WAY</pattern><template>What you're saying   It offends common sense.</template></category><category><pattern>SO AMAZING</pattern><template>No, that's mostly based on study.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU THINKING  ART</pattern><template>Oh, come on. Something had to be done.</template></category><category><pattern>I GET BORED NOW AND THEN</pattern><template>They keep making the same stupid mistakes over and over.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE STRICT PSYCHOLOGICAL SENSE</pattern><template>I suppose I have.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STUDIED    WITH THE BUDDHA</pattern><template>Until he died.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE EXPERTS ON THE BIBLE</pattern><template>Dream on.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M TAKING EDITH HOME</pattern><template>Sandy?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S EVERYWHERE  WE JUST CAN'T SEE HIM</pattern><template>Pfft. If this was the best I could do, I'd be hiding, too.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAD HIM BEFORE I WAS BORN</pattern><template>Woofie.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD'VE AT LEAST STAYED A FEW MINUTES  HUH</pattern><template>Eaten some of the food we so feverishly prepared?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE HAD  UH  PANCREATIC CANCER</pattern><template>Will!</template></category><category><pattern>FROM THE BUDDHA TO THE CROSS  I HAVE ALWAYS IMAGINED BOTH AS ENTIRELY MYTHIC   BUT I WOULD LIKE TO HEAR MORE</pattern><template>May I lie on the couch for a moment?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW THE FIRST THOUSAND YEARS</pattern><template>An informed guess, based on what I've learned in my memories.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ASKED IF I WAS A FIGURE FROM RELIGIOUS HISTORY  IF THERE WERE OTHERS LIKE ME  IF I'D CREATED FUTURE IDENTITIES</pattern><template>We were chasing our tails around the maypole, Enjoying the mystery, the analytical stretch.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE CREATING THE MYSTERY HERE</pattern><template>Obviously, you have something you'd like to say. Say it!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE A LITTLE BIT BEFORE MY TIME</pattern><template>At least something is.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>Before you say it, I know it's undergone a lot of changes, But god has spoken through man To make his word clearer.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE WERE YOU IN 1292 A D</pattern><template>Where were you a year ago on this date?</template></category><category><pattern>AS LAPLACE SAID   I HAVE NO NEED OF THAT HYPOTHESIS   HE MAY BE AROUND  THOUGH</pattern><template>He's everywhere. We just can't see him.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GRUMP ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Hey, how about changing the subject, will?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU KNOW THE BACKGROUND STUFF  SO I'LL MAKE IT BRIEF</pattern><template>In what I call my first lifetime, I aged to about 35...</template></category><category><pattern>THEN FEAR CAME  AND THEY CHASED ME AWAY</pattern><template>They thought that I was Stealing their lives away to stay young.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BEEN YEARS SINCE I SAT ON A FLOOR</pattern><template>Heh. I can't remember her name.</template></category><category><pattern>INCLINED CHISEL POINT</pattern><template>probably early magdalenian.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  ART WAS HALF RIGHT</pattern><template>Which half?</template></category><category><pattern>THE NEW TESTAMENT IS A GOOD CODE OF ETHICS  PUT INTO MY MOUTH BY POETS AND PHILOSOPHERS THAT ARE MUCH SMARTER THAN I AM</pattern><template>The message is never practiced.</template></category><category><pattern>DAN  A CAVEMAN</pattern><template>Well, there's no anatomical difference Between, say, a Cro magnon and us.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DIDN'T LEARN IT IN SCHOOL</pattern><template>That's my best guess, Based on archaeological data, maps, anthropological research.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  NO MATTER</pattern><template>I can scarcely remember mine.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAD A BEARD</pattern><template>Yeah, you used to tug on it To see if it was real.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS TRUE IDENTITY HAS TAKEN A BACKSEAT TO HIS DELUSION AND THE NEED FOR IT</pattern><template>If that's the case with John, There is a grave disorder.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE MUST BE SOMEONE   PROBABLY MANY   THAT YOU VALUED INTENSELY</pattern><template>Loved.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HOW ABOUT CHANGING THE SUBJECT  WILL</pattern><template>Enough with the   With the dying.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  YOU WERE SOMEONE IN RELIGIOUS HISTORY</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>HE KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING DIFFERENT ABOUT ME</pattern><template>I never told him.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MYTHICAL OVERLAY IS SO ENORMOUS</pattern><template>and not good.</template></category><category><pattern>PRIOR TO MODERN TIMES  THOSE WERE PRISTINE</pattern><template>We've extended our lifespan in a world that's, uh...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  UH  CALL ME UNDERDEVELOPED  BUT I'D LIKE TO HEAR MORE</pattern><template>Me too.</template></category><category><pattern>WERE YOU CURIOUS ABOUT WHERE IT ALL CAME FROM</pattern><template>We would look up at the sky and wonder.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT IT SOUNDED PRETTY GOOD</pattern><template>They believe you because they have to.</template></category><category><pattern>DID THAT HELP YOU WITH YOUR STORY</pattern><template>Linda!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT SAYING YOU WOULD DO SUCH A THING DELIBERATELY</pattern><template>I'm not saying that you would even know how to...</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE HASN'T AGED A DAY IN TEN YEARS</pattern><template>Every woman on the faculty Would give anything to have that secret.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D RATHER READ THAN WRITE ANOTHER ONE</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE FAITH</pattern><template>In a lot of things.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT</pattern><template>Here you are again.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT SAYING THAT YOU WOULD EVEN KNOW HOW TO</pattern><template>would you?</template></category><category><pattern>DEER  MOSTLY</pattern><template>Around big bear.</template></category><category><pattern>BRILLIANT DEDUCTION  SHERLOCK</pattern><template>Surely you'll have this looked at, appraised?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL OF IT</pattern><template>But what   What in the name of heaven...</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT A MINUTE  NOW</pattern><template>Look, I don't know what John is doing, But I sure as hell don't like what you're doing.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>Yes, Nola.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WERE GODS UP THERE THEN</pattern><template>Shamans who knew about them told us.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S FINE  JUST ENJOY IT</pattern><template>All right, I think this whole thing is just a crock!</template></category><category><pattern>MOST PEOPLE CAN SCARCELY REMEMBER THEIR CHILDHOOD  BUT YOU HAVE MEMORIES OF THAT TIME</pattern><template>Like yours, selective.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU EVER BEEN TO THE OZARKS</pattern><template>It's an interesting idea.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW COULD WE NOT KNOW SOMEONE IN THE BIBLE</pattern><template>I mean somebody important.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW FAR</pattern><template>Um, three blocks.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE WARMER THERE</pattern><template>That's when I saw an ocean.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK  JOHN</pattern><template>A shot to the arm?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID HE WAS SANE</pattern><template>Did I?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT AN ORIGINAL  JOHN</pattern><template>No, it's just a gift someone gave me.</template></category><category><pattern>OH</pattern><template>Why did you do that?</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIDN'T LIKE WHAT THEY BECAME   A GIANT KILLING MACHINE</pattern><template>He went to the near east thinking,  Why not pass the Buddha's teachings on in a modern form.  So he tried.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A BIG PARTY</pattern><template>Yeah, I've got a lot of pictures of it, But I've already packed them up. I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO</pattern><template>Yes, ellie?</template></category><category><pattern>I LEAVE YOU WITH IT</pattern><template>Jesus Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>IT TOOK SOME TIME</pattern><template>News traveled slowly Before communications were fancy.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW VERY INTERESTING  WHAT HAS IT GOT TO DO WITH JOHN</pattern><template>Oh, he  He might be a man Who lives outside of time as we know it.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THERE ANY  UH</pattern><template>more revelations for us?</template></category><category><pattern>THE CHRIST FIGURE GOES ALL THE WAY BACK TO KRISHNA   HERCULES  OF COURSE</pattern><template>Hercules?</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU ACTED UPON THIS BELIEF</pattern><template>I had a private practice for a while, And then I taught.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I SAID NO  COULD YOU EVER BE SURE</pattern><template>Turn that off.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN WORK WITH THAT</pattern><template>If what I'm saying is true, You and any children will age.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'D HE GET A GUN</pattern><template>He had you on the ropes, John.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL THEN  PRAY  CONTINUE</pattern><template>We hunted reindeer, mammoths   Bison, horses, The game retreated northward As the climate changed, You got the idea of growing food Rather than gathering it, Raising animals rather than hunting them.</template></category><category><pattern>MARY PASSED AWAY YESTERDAY</pattern><template>Who?</template></category><category><pattern>STILL  IT'S A SUPERB COPY</pattern><template>Contemporaneous, I think, May I take a closer look?</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN  WOULD YOU PLEASE STOP BY MY LAB  SUFFER A FEW TESTS FROM YOUR FRIENDLY NEIGHBORHOOD BIOLOGIST</pattern><template>I'm leery of labs.</template></category><category><pattern>MY ASS</pattern><template>I thought it sounded pretty good.</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE MESOPOTAMIA  I'VE GOT THE LAST</pattern><template>4,000 years straight.</template></category><category><pattern>WASTE ACCUMULATES  EVENTUALLY PROVES FATAL TO FUNCTION</pattern><template>Now if a quirk in his immune system Led to perfect detox, Perfect renewal, then yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>DR  JENKINS IS A FINE TEACHER</pattern><template>Oh, that's very politic.</template></category><category><pattern>PRETEND IT'S SCIENCE FICTION</pattern><template>Figure it out.</template></category><category><pattern>IN FACT  IF HE HAD AN INQUIRING MIND  HIS KNOWLEDGE MIGHT BE ASTONISHING</pattern><template>If you do write that, let me have a look at it.</template></category><category><pattern>INFECTIONS</pattern><template>they were, uh, mysterious.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST SOMETHING IS</pattern><template>No doubt you could give us a thousand details, John, Corroborating your story, From the magdalene to the Buddha to now.</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS I SHOULDN'T HAVE EXPECTED YOU TO</pattern><template>You're not as crazy as you think I am.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SIMPLE FACT IS THAT I CAN'T GIVE YOU FOREVER</pattern><template>How long's forever?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  ASSUMING NORMAL INTELLIGENCE</pattern><template>Well, we think men of the upper paleolithic Were as intelligent as we are.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ALSO LEARNED TO SLOW HIS BODY PROCESSES DOWN TO THE POINT WHERE THEY WERE UNDETECTABLE</pattern><template>They thought he was dead.</template></category><category><pattern>THOUGH  GOOD EATIN'</pattern><template>The best wild game.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE A PRETTY FAST LIAR  MR  UGG  BUT I WANNA KNOW   WHAT'S YOUR REAL NAME</pattern><template>Believe it or not, the sound was always John.</template></category><category><pattern>HI</pattern><template>Are you hungry?</template></category><category><pattern>LATER ON</pattern><template>Okay, good night.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THAT'S VERY POLITIC</pattern><template>It's very true. Uh huh.</template></category><category><pattern>OF WHAT  DO YOU KNOW</pattern><template>In prehistory, I can't tell you.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>But what can I do about it?</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE YOU SAY IT  I KNOW IT'S UNDERGONE A LOT OF CHANGES  BUT GOD HAS SPOKEN THROUGH MAN TO MAKE HIS WORD CLEARER</pattern><template>He couldn't get it right the first time?</template></category><category><pattern>THUS  I WAS RESURRECTED  AND I ASCENDED TO CENTRAL EUROPE TO GET AWAY AS FAR AS POSSIBLE</pattern><template>You don't mean a word of this, John.</template></category><category><pattern>SKAEL  NA ZDOROVYE  ONE OFF THE TOP  JOHN</pattern><template>Mm! Oh, that's good.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE WERE YOU A YEAR AGO ON THIS DATE</pattern><template>Anyway, it was the 1600s, and I met a man, And I had a hunch that he was...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THE NOLDE LANDSCAPES</pattern><template>Not in Van Gogh's time.</template></category><category><pattern>IT RAINS    IT WON'T</pattern><template>How do you know that?</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER ANY OF YOUR ORIGINAL LANGUAGE</pattern><template>A little. One thing hasn't changed much...</template></category><category><pattern>PICTURE IT ON MY SCALE   I MIGRATED THROUGH AN ENDLESS FLAT SPACE FULL OF ENDLESS NEW THINGS   FORESTS  MOUNTAINS  TUNDRA  CANYONS</pattern><template>My memory sees what I saw then.</template></category><category><pattern>A KINDA LATITUDE OF WHAT WE HAPPILY CALL REALITY  IN WHICH  AS EVERYBODY KEEPS SAYING</pattern><template>anything's possible.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T  DON'T  DON'T  DON'T  DON'T  DON'T  DON'T  DON'T  DON'T  DON'T</pattern><template>The commandments are just modern updates of more ancient laws.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  EDITH</pattern><template>it rains... it won't.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF A MAN FROM THE UPPER PALEOLITHIC SURVIVED UNTIL THE PRESENT DAY</pattern><template>What do you mean, survived?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  YOU'RE TOO YOUNG TO HAVE DONE THIS BEFORE</pattern><template>And he hasn't aged a day in ten years.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S ONE OF MY VICTIMS NOW  I'M TAKING HER HOME</pattern><template>She wanted to come by and say hello goodbye.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL YOU CAN DO IS THUMB YOUR NOSE AT IT</pattern><template>Is that what you're doing, John?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T HAVE EYES IN THE BACK OF MY HEAD  I CAN'T HEAR A FLEA WALKING  I AM NOT IN ANY WAY SUPERMAN</pattern><template>Well, I'm a second degree black belt.</template></category><category><pattern>AN INFORMED GUESS  BASED ON WHAT I'VE LEARNED IN MY MEMORIES</pattern><template>Most people can scarcely remember their childhood, But you have memories of that time?</template></category><category><pattern>VAST PLAINS TO THE WEST</pattern><template>West  Something you learned in school.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THIS ENORMOUS LIFETIME YOU DESCRIBE  HAVE YOU EVER BEEN ILL</pattern><template>Sure, as much as anyone.</template></category><category><pattern>CHILDHOOD FIXATION  I GUESS</pattern><template>Helps me to feel secure.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU PREFER I ASKED HIM ABOUT HIS FATHER</pattern><template>I thought you always started with  Tell me about your mother.  Yes, but prehistory was strongly patriarchal.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE OVER THE COUNTER REMEDIES FOR THAT  JOHN</pattern><template>So there is a problem.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D GROWN CURIOUS ABOUT THE WORLD</pattern><template>I'd gotten the hang of going it alone, Learning how to fit in when I wanted to.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ENTIRE BIBLE IS MOSTLY MYTH AND ALLEGORY WITH MAYBE SOME BASIS IN HISTORICAL EVENTS</pattern><template>You were part of that history?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  ELLIE</pattern><template>What's wrong?</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER THAT  SOMEONE HAD TO CHEW HIS FOOD FOR HIM</pattern><template>Finally, he got   I suspect   An infected jaw, And he was abandoned.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S OVER THE SPAN OF 170 YEARS</pattern><template>I got my biology degree at oxford in 1840, So I'm a little behind the times.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU DO WRITE THAT  LET ME HAVE A LOOK AT IT</pattern><template>I'm sure you'll make some anthropological boners.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YES</pattern><template>You look very familiar, my dear. Linda murphy.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE</pattern><template>End of the line. Everybody off.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU EVER FELT GUILT ABOUT THAT   SOMETHING AKIN TO SURVIVOR'S GUILT</pattern><template>In the strict psychological sense?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS THE WORK OF A MAN NAMED</pattern><template>giraud.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COMMENTED THAT I NEVER AGE</pattern><template>You gave me the book on early man.</template></category><category><pattern>IS HE SERIOUS</pattern><template>If he is, I'm sorry to say he's...</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T BELIEVE IN ANGELS AND THE NATIVITY AND THE STAR IN THE EAST  BUT THERE ARE STORIES ABOUT THE CHILDHOOD OF JESUS</pattern><template>History hates a vacuum.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE FINAL CULTURE OF THE UPPER PALEOLITHIC</pattern><template>If stones could speak, eh, Art?</template></category><category><pattern>LITTLE ROCK</pattern><template>Your mother, she took you to the market?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  HERE</pattern><template>Skael. Na zdorovye. One off the top, John.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WANTED TO COME BY AND SAY HELLO GOODBYE</pattern><template>Is Art as tough as I hear?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO MOVE ON</pattern><template>Making him history's biggest bigamist.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU   YOU'VE TALKED A GOOD DEAL ABOUT YOUR EXTRAORDINARY AMOUNT OF LIVING</pattern><template>What do you think of dying, John?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL I CAN DO IS INTEGRATE MY RECOLLECTIONS WITH MODERN FINDINGS</pattern><template>Caveman, you gonna hit me over the head with a club And drag me into the bedroom?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  ARE YOU WORKING ON A SCIENCE FICTION STORY</pattern><template>Say I am. What would he be like?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T HAVE ARTIFACTS</pattern><template>Keep that.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT I MIGHT NEED IT</pattern><template>Wouldn't sacre du printemps be more appropriate? What?</template></category><category><pattern>DIFFICULT WHEN VILLAGES EMERGED  TOUGHER STILL IN CITY STATES WHERE AUTHORITY WAS CENTRALIZED</pattern><template>Strangers were suspect.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  I WAS TEMPTED TO COP OUT MANY TIMES  BUT I COULDN'T RESIST SEEING WHETHER OR NOT YOU COULD REFUTE WHAT I WAS SAYING</pattern><template>I had the perfect audience   Anthropologist, archaeologist, Christian literalist...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THOSE CHINESE BOXES  ONE INSIDE THE OTHER INSIDE THE OTHER INSIDE THE OTHER   I FEEL LIKE I'M IN THE LAST BOX</pattern><template>You son of a...</template></category><category><pattern>FOURTEEN THOUSAND YEARS OLD</pattern><template>I bet that's a lot of women.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FIRST WEDDING</pattern><template>There you go.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT'S WHAT I TAUGHT</pattern><template>But a talking snake make a lady eat an apple, So we're screwed.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Yes, the end of the pleistocene.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE ALREADY COVERED THAT</pattern><template>John's got itchy feet.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO EVER REALLY HAS IT</pattern><template>My parents split up before I was born, And then my mom's next marriage lasted What, a whole three years?</template></category><category><pattern>GLAD YOU'RE HERE  THINGS ARE GOING IN UNEXPECTED DIRECTIONS</pattern><template>Yes, so I hear.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  OKAY</pattern><template>All right, spock, I'll play your little game.</template></category><category><pattern>LOTS</pattern><template>John Paley for John Paleolithic, John Savage   Got really crazy about 60 years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE MOST MODERN  THE WORK OF GREAT SCHOLARS</pattern><template>Modern is good.</template></category><category><pattern>RATHER SUDDENLY  YOU MUST ADMIT</pattern><template>Truth time, John.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ONLY RESIGNED A COUPLE OF DAYS AGO</pattern><template>You got the history chair at Stanford.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WHY ARE YOU DOING IT</pattern><template>'Cause I wanted to say goodbye   As yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIGHT HAVE ALL DONE THE SAME</pattern><template>Living 14,000 years didn't make me a genius.</template></category><category><pattern>OR ARE YOU A VAMPIRE  JOHN</pattern><template>Even an unknowing one.</template></category><category><pattern>LIVING 14 000 YEARS DIDN'T MAKE ME A GENIUS</pattern><template>I just had time.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  PERHAPS SOMEBODY HAD TO BE  FOR BETTER OR FOR WORSE</pattern><template>The jury is still out.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN  WE'RE ALL SORRY TO SEE YOU GO</pattern><template>Truly.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT  THE MORE I'M NO LONGER IN THAT CHINESE BOX</pattern><template>I sense...space.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU FEEL A VACANCY IN YOUR LIFE ABOUT THAT  JOHN  SOMETHING YOU WISH COULD BE FILLED BY A FACE  A VOICE  AN IMAGE</pattern><template>Not at this late date.</template></category><category><pattern>UNLESS I IMAGINED IT ALL</pattern><template>Is that possible?</template></category><category><pattern>NO WISE MEN CAME FROM THE EAST TO WORSHIP AT A MANGER</pattern><template>I did do a little healing With some eastern medicine I'd learned.</template></category><category><pattern>HERCULES</pattern><template>Born of a virgin, Alcmene.</template></category><category><pattern>HOPING FOR A   REVOLUTION  I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>Are there any, uh...</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN JUST CONFIDED THAT HE'S 14 000 YEARS OLD</pattern><template>Oh, John, you don't look a day over 900.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY'D YOU CAVE TO GRUBER</pattern><template>What happened was enough.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW YOU</pattern><template>It was nice seeing you again, Dr. Oldman.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO</pattern><template>We should skip this one.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S KIND OF FUNNY HOW OFTEN NEW CONCEPTS OF SCIENCE FIND THEIR FIRST TENTATIVE FORMS OF EXPRESSION IN THE ARTS</pattern><template>So did beethoven do physics on the side?</template></category><category><pattern>TANTRIC YOGA  WE CAN</pattern><template>So you're leaving good old  We teach you ?</template></category><category><pattern>SURELY YOU'LL HAVE THIS LOOKED AT  APPRAISED</pattern><template>Well, maybe sometime, But I wouldn't really want money for it.</template></category><category><pattern>SHADOWS OF THE CAVE: PARALLELS TO EARLY MAN   AUTHOR: M  JENKINS</pattern><template>Publish or perish.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOUR STORY DOESN'T FIT INTO NATURE AS WE KNOW IT</pattern><template>But we know so little, Dan.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE HE KNEW  I GUESS</pattern><template>Brilliant deduction, sherlock.</template></category><category><pattern>SURELY YOU REMEMBER YOUR FATHER</pattern><template>I seem to remember a figure, Perhaps an older brother, a social father, maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL HE DIED</pattern><template>He knew there was something different about me.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  JOHN  THAT IS NOT POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Please, let's take John's story At face value and explore it from that perspective.</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS WE COULD WATCH IT HEAL</pattern><template>A bullet in the head   What exactly will happen?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TEN DEGREES  INCLUDING ALL OF YOURS</pattern><template>except yours, will.</template></category><category><pattern>ANOTHER FAIRY TALE</pattern><template>All of it?</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE CHASING OUR TAILS AROUND THE MAYPOLE  ENJOYING THE MYSTERY  THE ANALYTICAL STRETCH</pattern><template>You were playing my game!</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE SEEN PEOPLE TRIPPING  STRUNG OUT   WHATEVER'S UP WITH JOHN  IT ISN'T THAT</pattern><template>I've looked for signs  None.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU EVER GET TIRED OF IT ALL</pattern><template>I get bored now and then.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BIGGEST MYSTERY OF ALL</pattern><template>You realized you were different.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  AT LEAST I DON'T HAVE TO THROW AWAY HALF OF WHAT I KNOW ABOUT BIOLOGY</pattern><template>Which half?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED HELP</pattern><template>Everybody needs help.</template></category><category><pattern>SANDY</pattern><template>I'm gonna stay.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE BEN'S SON  HE WAS A GOOD MAN   SAVES TROUBLE WITH CREDENTIALS AND REFERENCES</pattern><template>On the other hand, I've been busted a few times.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL YOURS</pattern><template>Here, take this chair.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING</pattern><template>I'll get more.</template></category><category><pattern>MY EYE SEES FREEWAYS  URBAN SPRAWL  BIG MACS UNDER THE EIFFEL TOWER</pattern><template>Early on, the world got bigger and bigger, And then...</template></category><category><pattern>AMEN</pattern><template>I've always liked you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES A DAY OR A YEAR OR A CENTURY MEAN TO YOU</pattern><template>The birth death cycle?</template></category><category><pattern>IN A THOUSAND YEARS  THEY'LL BE BARBECUED AND THEIR SOULS WILL BE IN SQUIRRELS</pattern><template>You weren't Jesus!</template></category><category><pattern>I SHOULD LEAVE  BUT I'M GONNA STAY</pattern><template>You know why? 'Cause I wanna see what this is all about.</template></category><category><pattern>HE CAN'T KNOW MORE THAN THE BEST OF THE RACE KNOWS  IF THAT  I MEAN  WHEN THE WORLD LEARNED IT WAS ROUND  YOU LEARNED IT</pattern><template>It took some time.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE TO TELL US</pattern><template>what the hell that was all about?</template></category><category><pattern>FOUR MEN OF SCIENCE COMPLETELY BAFFLED  MY FRIEND</pattern><template>We  We don't know what to make of you.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MY BEST GUESS  BASED ON ARCHAEOLOGICAL DATA  MAPS  ANTHROPOLOGICAL RESEARCH</pattern><template>Since mesopotamia, I've got the last...</template></category><category><pattern>THE PANCREAS TURNS OVER CELLS EVERY 24 HOURS  THE STOMACH LINING IN THREE DAYS  THE ENTIRE BODY IN SEVEN YEARS  BUT THE PROCESS FALTERS</pattern><template>Waste accumulates, eventually proves fatal to function.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A DEAL</pattern><template>What would keep him alive?</template></category><category><pattern>THE KINGDOM OF GOD  MEANING GOODNESS  IS RIGHT HERE  WHERE IT SHOULD BE</pattern><template>I am what I am becoming.  That's what the Buddha brought in.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SURE ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>Why are you being so hard on him?</template></category><category><pattern>A STORY THAT GOES AROUND THE ROOM</pattern><template>No credibility.</template></category><category><pattern>MM  MWAH</pattern><template>So, John Oldman.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AROUND  JOHN</pattern><template>We just did.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  COME ON  OUT WITH IT</pattern><template>You're among friends.</template></category><category><pattern>SERIOUSLY ILL</pattern><template>Sometimes.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT FIT TO LIVE IN</pattern><template>You know, it could happen.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS FUN</pattern><template>Hey, John.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL INTERVIEW YOU IN THE RUBBER ROOM FOR FURTHER DETAILS</pattern><template>You may still need help, my friend.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CRUCIFIXION</pattern><template>He blocked the pain as he had learned to do In tibet and india.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST LIKE TO MOVE ON NOW AND THEN</pattern><template>It's a personal thing.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SO I HEAR</pattern><template>Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>INTERESTING</pattern><template>You could have lied about that.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WHAT'S THE POINT</pattern><template>What about oceans?</template></category><category><pattern>NO CREDIBILITY</pattern><template>Even if I could make you believe me, In a month, you wouldn't.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT IT</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HE DOESN'T BELIEVE WHAT HE'S SAYING</pattern><template>Do you believe literally everything in the bible, Edith?</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN  THIS IS OUT OF ANY TEXTBOOK</pattern><template>Even yours.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GLAD I CAUGHT YOU</pattern><template>Someone mentioned that you were leaving   Called you, told you that I've lost it.</template></category><category><pattern>KIND OF THE POINT OF A GOODBYE PARTY  JOHN</pattern><template>Went to a certain amount of trouble, you know?</template></category><category><pattern>END OF THE LINE  EVERYBODY OFF</pattern><template>What?!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS THE TERRAIN LIKE</pattern><template>Mountainous.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE I WILL</pattern><template>I'll interview you in the rubber room For further details.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS A STORY</pattern><template>It was all a story.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  WE HAVE TWO SIMPLE CHOICES</pattern><template>We can get all bent out of shape Intellectualizing or bench pressing logic, Or we can simply relax and enjoy it.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  UNFORTUNATELY  THERE'S NO AUTHORITIES ON PREHISTORY  SO WE COULDN'T STOP HIM THERE</pattern><template>There are experts on the bible.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU EVER MEET ANY PERSON FROM OUR RELIGIOUS HISTORY</pattern><template>A biblical figure?</template></category><category><pattern>ARISTARCHUS LONG BEFORE THAT</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY'RE YOU DOING THIS</pattern><template>A whim. Maybe not such a good idea.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT OCEANS</pattern><template>Didn't see them till much later.</template></category><category><pattern>MMM</pattern><template>I don't know, man.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THAT</pattern><template>It's a burin of a parrot beak.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D MOVE ON</pattern><template>I had to move on.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF MY FAVORITE PEOPLE HAS DISAPPEARED</pattern><template>Can you get alzheimer's at 35?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GAVE ME THE IDEA</pattern><template>All of you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND CREATION</pattern><template>it's here  I'm not so sure it was created.</template></category><category><pattern>I ASK YOU NOW   I DEMAND IT   THAT YOU TELL THESE PEOPLE THE TRUTH</pattern><template>Give them closure.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY KEEP MAKING THE SAME STUPID MISTAKES OVER AND OVER</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS GOOD</pattern><template>First thousand years, I didn't know up from sideways.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU COMFORTABLE KNOWING THAT YOU HAVE LIVED WHILE EVERYONE YOU KNEW   EVERYONE YOU KNEW  JOHN    HAS DIED</pattern><template>I've regretted losing people...</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST HAD TIME</pattern><template>Time.</template></category><category><pattern>GIRAUD</pattern><template>He did a pretty good job.</template></category><category><pattern>I MIGHT DIE</pattern><template>And then you could wonder The rest of your incarcerated life what you shot.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT YOU SAY YOU DO KNOW ABOUT   HISTORICAL TIMES</pattern><template>Don't encourage him.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYWHERE I'VE LIVED  I'VE HAD A FIREPLACE</pattern><template>Childhood fixation, I guess.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY I SAID THEM</pattern><template>Well.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPED IT WOULDN'T   WE   CALL IT A NIGHT</pattern><template>Come on! You were someone in religious history?</template></category><category><pattern>AFRAID I MIGHT GO IN AND STAY FOR A THOUSAND YEARS WHILE CIGARETTE SMOKING MEN TRY TO FIGURE ME OUT</pattern><template>You don't think that I would betray you?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN YOU COMPARE PAGAN MYTHOLOGY TO THE TRUE WORD</pattern><template>Pretty damn closely, I'd say.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU ON AMERICA'S MOST WANTED  WE WON'T TURN YOU IN</pattern><template>Yeah, come on, out with it.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>I know, I was tempted to cop out many times, But I couldn't resist seeing whether or not You could refute what I was saying.</template></category><category><pattern>WANTED TO SAY GOODBYE TO YOU AS ME  NOT WHAT YOU THOUGHT I WAS</pattern><template>Well, since this isn't funny, We think you might have a problem.</template></category><category><pattern>MORE</pattern><template>You double damn swear this isn't some cockamamie Science fiction story or...</template></category><category><pattern>COME IN</pattern><template>John Oldman?</template></category><category><pattern>MOUNTAINOUS</pattern><template>Vast plains to the west.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  NOT TO PRY</pattern><template>I'm sorry I don't have more to offer you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE SEMI NOMADIC  OF COURSE  FOLLOWING THE WEATHER AND THE GAME WE HUNTED</pattern><template>The first 2,000 years were cold.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  COME OVER HERE  JOIN ME</pattern><template>That, uh, raises an interesting question, John.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MAN  YOU KNOW  YOU HAD US GOING  RIGHT</pattern><template>You were good, man.</template></category><category><pattern>SEEPED INTO THE ROMAN EMPIRE</pattern><template>He didn't like what they became   A giant killing machine.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL YOU COME TO MY FUNERAL  JOHN</pattern><template>Hey, will...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  IT COULD HAPPEN</pattern><template>The pancreas turns over cells every 24 hours, The stomach lining in three days, The entire body in seven years, But the process falters.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD BE GONE  LOST</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANNA PROVE IT</pattern><template>So you're telling us this, The yarn of the century, And you don't care if we believe it or not?</template></category><category><pattern>DID I</pattern><template>Do you think that perhaps our caveman Has a monkey on his back?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE ECSTATIC</pattern><template>Thus, I was resurrected, And I ascended to central europe To get away as far as possible.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THERE IS A PROBLEM</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>WERE YOU</pattern><template>If I said no, could you ever be sure?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS HAS GONE FAR ENOUGH</pattern><template>It's gone much too far.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T SMELL IT</pattern><template>Were you...</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN  PLEASE CONTINUE</pattern><template>Come on, I thought we were done with that.</template></category><category><pattern>CHARADES</pattern><template>No. John?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE YOU WOULD LIKE TO STRANGLE</pattern><template>Strangle them all.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN DID YOU BEGIN TO BELIEVE YOU WERE JESUS</pattern><template>When did you begin to believe you were a psychiatrist?</template></category><category><pattern>FULL CIRCLE</pattern><template>Did you have, um...</template></category><category><pattern>TEN  NINE  EIGHT  SEVEN</pattern><template>Harry, stop.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WOULD SUCH A THING BE FAIR</pattern><template>So you believe me now?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE THING I DIDN'T PACK</pattern><template>I thought I might need it.</template></category><category><pattern>AROUND BIG BEAR</pattern><template>With a bow and arrow?</template></category><category><pattern>THE FURNITURE'S GOING THIS AFTERNOON</pattern><template>It's been years since I sat on a floor.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN YOURS</pattern><template>You got most of it right.</template></category><category><pattern>TOO FAR</pattern><template>Check my reaction.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE GONE TOO FAR</pattern><template>John didn't ask to be what he is.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF THERE IS A CREATOR  HE'D PROBABLY FEEL THE SAME WAY</pattern><template>I see ceremony, ritual, processions, Genuflecting, moaning, intoning, Venerating cookies and wine, And I think...</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU REALIZE HOW</pattern><template>inconsiderately you're treating my feelings?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THEN</pattern><template>Maybe it's just accumulated, fields affecting fields.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU STILL THINK YOU DO</pattern><template>God works in mysterious ways.</template></category><category><pattern>TIME</pattern><template>We can't see it, we can't hear it, We can't weigh it, we can't measure it in a laboratory.</template></category><category><pattern>TOWARDS THE SETTING SUN</pattern><template>I suspect I saw the british isles From what is now the french coast.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HOPIS SEE TIME AS A LANDSCAPE  EXISTING BEFORE AND BEHIND US  AND WE MOVE   WE MOVE THROUGH IT  SLICE BY SLICE</pattern><template>Clocks measure time.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MAY THINK YOU KNOW HIM  BUT IT'S MOSTLY MYTH</pattern><template>The entire bible is mostly myth and allegory With maybe some basis in historical events.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S HERE  I'M NOT SO SURE IT WAS CREATED</pattern><template>What then?</template></category><category><pattern>HE BLOCKED THE PAIN AS HE HAD LEARNED TO DO IN TIBET AND INDIA</pattern><template>He also learned to slow his body processes Down to the point where they were undetectable.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT THE SOURCE OF THE FIELD ENERGIES</pattern><template>Wouldn't that imply a prime mover?</template></category><category><pattern>I  I  I DROVE FOR A WHILE  AND THEN I SAT FOR A WHILE</pattern><template>I'm so ashamed.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER SPOKE OF DIVINE EXCEPT IN THE SENSE OF HUMAN GOODNESS ON EARTH</pattern><template>No wise men came from the east to worship at a manger.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ICE CREAM  ( LAUGHS ) ALL RIGHT  ALL RIGHT  I'LL PLAY</pattern><template>All right, um, in science fiction terms, I would say...</template></category><category><pattern>LATE GLACIAL PERIOD  I ASSUME</pattern><template>What was the terrain like?</template></category><category><pattern>WE LEARNED IT WAS WARMER AT LOWER ELEVATIONS</pattern><template>Late glacial period, I assume.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU'RE AN ENGINEER  TOO</pattern><template>You're ben's son. He was a good man.  Saves trouble with credentials and references.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THERE IS ALWAYS INNATE NATURE</pattern><template>Wouldn't you be more comfortable Squatting in the backyard?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T BELIEVE THAT</pattern><template>If your story's true, Why did god allow you to happen?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL GO BACK TO YOUR MAY DECEMBER ROMANCES</pattern><template>The simple fact is That I can't give you forever.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THAT'S CHANGING</pattern><template>Surely you don't believe this nonsense.</template></category><category><pattern>I LEFT ENOUGH  I'M COLD</pattern><template>Chilly willy, always cold.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DID YOU LIVE WHEN YOU WERE FIVE YEARS OLD</pattern><template>Little rock.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH A BOW AND ARROW</pattern><template>Most people can't bag a deer With a rifle and a telescopic sight.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALIZED YOU WERE DIFFERENT</pattern><template>Longer to realize how I was different, To find a way to synthesize My experience into a view of myself.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  SO ARE WE</pattern><template>So are we.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS TIME TO DIE</pattern><template>Wait a minute, now.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE IT'D BE EASIER IF I WERE</pattern><template>Crazy?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S JUST A GIFT SOMEONE GAVE ME</pattern><template>Still, it's a superb copy.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS PLAYING YOURS</pattern><template>Oh, man, you know, you had us going, right?</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS</pattern><template>Ladies? Will? Oh, no...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M OUTTA HERE  YOU WANNA COME  LET'S GO</pattern><template>So, John.</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHOULD SKIP THIS ONE</pattern><template>No, no, no skipping. Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  SHUT UP</pattern><template>Maybe it'd be easier if I were.</template></category><category><pattern>WH WHAT IS THIS</pattern><template>It looks like a Van Gogh, But I've never seen it before.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MEDITERRANEAN  PROBABLY</pattern><template>It was around the beginning of the bronze age, So I followed the trade routes from the east, Copper, tin, Learning languages as I went.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TIME  JOHN</pattern><template>Please.</template></category><category><pattern>CIGARETTES</pattern><template>And ice cream. ( Laughs ) All right, all right, I'll play.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A VERY LUCKY MAN</pattern><template>Come in.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED WAS ENOUGH</pattern><template>Just  Just needed to stop.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WOULD BE SOMETHING</pattern><template>Other times, christianity was considered heresy.</template></category><category><pattern>AS MUCH AS I DISLIKE THAT JOB  IT'LL BE PREFERABLE TO THIS</pattern><template>I leave you with it.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD KID</pattern><template>What does pre Med need with history?</template></category><category><pattern>A TOUCH OF SENILITY</pattern><template>Anyway, he said yes, But from another time, another place.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT DOES IT</pattern><template>Put that stuff in the kitchen.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S AWFUL</pattern><template>You have to know what to kill.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL</pattern><template>Like a good Christian, I...oh, John.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I LIE ON THE COUCH FOR A MOMENT</pattern><template>I'm not as young as I used to be.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IT'S GETTING TO BE NIGHT</pattern><template>I still have stuff to carry And a long drive.</template></category><category><pattern>OH   TO MY FRIEND JACQUE BORNE   WONDER WHO THAT WAS</pattern><template>Someone he knew, I guess.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE REGRETTED LOSING PEOPLE</pattern><template>often.</template></category><category><pattern>I ALMOST ALWAYS DO</pattern><template>As tales of the resurrection spread, The name was confused with the hebrew  yochanan,  Meaning  god is gracious.  My stay on earth was seen As divine proof of immortality.</template></category><category><pattern>HEH  I CAN'T REMEMBER HER NAME</pattern><template>Eh, it's good for the back.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ELSE MADE ALL THIS DOWN HERE   AT FIRST I THOUGHT THERE WAS SOMETHING WRONG WITH ME   MAYBE I WAS A BAD GUY FOR NOT DYING</pattern><template>Then I began to wonder if I was cursed Or perhaps blessed.</template></category><category><pattern>I BET I AM</pattern><template>Lakeside living becomes commonplace, Fishing, fowling   Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN PALEY FOR JOHN PALEOLITHIC  JOHN SAVAGE   GOT REALLY CRAZY ABOUT 60 YEARS AGO</pattern><template>When I was teaching at harvard, I was John Thomas Partee.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  YEAH</pattern><template>Yeah, it's the same stretcher as Van Gogh used.</template></category><category><pattern>CAVEMAN  YOU GONNA HIT ME OVER THE HEAD WITH A CLUB AND DRAG ME INTO THE BEDROOM</pattern><template>You'd be more fun conscious.</template></category><category><pattern>FOND OF YOU</pattern><template>certainly attracted to you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT OF COURSE</pattern><template>I am.</template></category><category><pattern>HAMMURABI'S CODE</pattern><template>That's right, they weren't the first, right?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW LINDA  YOU HAD HER LAST SEMESTER</pattern><template>Hi. Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE YOU ARE AGAIN</pattern><template>You like the fire, John.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU'RE AS SANE AS HE IS</pattern><template>Oh, god, I   Did you ever find it prudent to worship yourself Rather than be thought a heretic?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT EVEN IN THEIR SPECIALTY</pattern><template>So much for the myth Of the super wise, all knowing immortal.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THEY MEASURE THEMSELVES</pattern><template>The objective referent of clock is another clock.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN'S MAN WOULD HAVE LEARNED AS THE RACE LEARNED</pattern><template>In fact, if he had an inquiring mind, His knowledge might be astonishing.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT CONVERSATION  SOME SEATS FOR YOUR BEHINDS  AND  UH</pattern><template>Is he ducking out on us again?</template></category><category><pattern>YES INDEED  THAT'S WHAT IT IS</pattern><template>What's a burin?</template></category><category><pattern>SO</pattern><template>Where you going, John, like we give a damn?</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH HALF</pattern><template>It's a beautiful idea, So rich, so full of possibilities.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  ARE WE DONE WITH PREHISTORY YET</pattern><template>Remember any of your original language?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I DIDN'T EVEN SEND A CHRISTMAS CARD</pattern><template>Christmas card? What about a birthday card?</template></category><category><pattern>HE STRUCK BACK EXPERTLY   THAT STUFF ABOUT STEALING LIFE FORCES</pattern><template>I've always wondered about the reasons.</template></category><category><pattern>CERTAINLY YOU'VE HAD WIVES AND CHILDREN</pattern><template>I'd move on.</template></category><category><pattern>GO ON</pattern><template>I kept getting chased because I wouldn't die, So I got the hang of joining new groups I found.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK UP AT THE STARS</pattern><template>Wonder.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU EVER IN YOUR LIFE THOUGHT  IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN ME</pattern><template>Maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T SCAR</pattern><template>Besides, they tied me...</template></category><category><pattern>BORED  PERHAPS LONELY  BECAUSE YOUR HEART CANNOT KEEP ITS TREASURES</pattern><template>Is that what you're doing?</template></category><category><pattern>VERY GOOD  AND I BET AT LEAST ONE OF US IS YOUR DIRECT DESCENDENT</pattern><template>And I didn't even send a christmas card.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MAKES ME FEEL A TRIFLE LILLIPUTIAN</pattern><template>That's over the span of 170 years.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THEN  PERHAPS</pattern><template>it is time to die.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOU WERE JESUS</pattern><template>Well, perhaps somebody had to be, for better or for worse.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE CEREMONY  RITUAL  PROCESSIONS  GENUFLECTING  MOANING  INTONING  VENERATING COOKIES AND WINE  AND I THINK</pattern><template>it's not what I had in mind.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU STAND ALIVE AND TALL IN A GRAVEYARD THAT YOU HELPED TO FILL</pattern><template>That's going too far.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE CAN</pattern><template>Not even in their specialty.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT REINCARNATION</pattern><template>You're not saying that you remember Whatever the hell it would be, 200 separate lifetimes, dying And being born again and yada yada?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY JUST DIDN'T KNOW AS MUCH</pattern><template>John's man would have learned as the race learned.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WELL</pattern><template>You did a terrible thing, But we're all so thankful you're all right.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SON OF A</pattern><template>bitch!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  EVERYBODY  THIS IS LINDA</pattern><template>Linda, this is everybody.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ONE DAY I'LL LEAVE</pattern><template>You'll go back to your May December romances.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>It was a story.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  ARCHAEOLOGY'S TOUGH</pattern><template>Dr. Jenkins is a fine teacher.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  CAN YOU PULL THIS</pattern><template>What the hell?</template></category><category><pattern>UH  I LOVE YOU ALL  AND I DO NOT WANT TO PUT YOU THROUGH ANYTHING</pattern><template>Then why are you doing it?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THERE A PROBLEM</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>EDITH</pattern><template>All right. A guy with your mind   You'd have studied a great deal.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS FASCINATING  ISN'T IT  A BRAVE ATTEMPT TO TEACH BUDDHISM IN THE WEST</pattern><template>It's no wonder he failed.</template></category><category><pattern>THUS THE SAYING    YOU CAN'T GO HOME AGAIN  BECAUSE IT ISN'T THERE ANYMORE</pattern><template>Picture it on my scale   I migrated through an endless flat space Full of endless new things   Forests, mountains, tundra, canyons.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S VERY TRUE  UH HUH</pattern><template>Something for you to read on the road, pal.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU FIND THAT UNUSUAL</pattern><template>Very. I would stake my reputation He as sane as I am, So why does he persist in such a story?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU FEAR DEATH</pattern><template>Who wouldn't?</template></category><category><pattern>WE TALKED FOR TWO DAYS</pattern><template>It was all pretty convincing, But we couldn't be sure.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW WE'RE ON THE FLOOR LISTENING TO BEETHOVEN</pattern><template>Full circle.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE STILL HAVE AN AFTERNOON TO KILL  RIGHT</pattern><template>Charades?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LIVE SIMPLY</pattern><template>I've owned castles, but why leave a lot If you're always leaving?</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU</pattern><template>But would such a thing be fair?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE HAVE ALWAYS BEEN LEGENDS OF SUCH A THING  A CREATURE NOT QUITE HUMAN TAKING NOT THE BLOOD  BUT THE LIFE FORCE ITSELF</pattern><template>My god, will.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY STICK IN THE MIND FOREVER</pattern><template>Put down at 3 or 35, you still feel a twinge.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE YOU SIT  YOU CAN'T BREAK HIS STORY</pattern><template>All you can do is thumb your nose at it.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU PULL THAT OUT OF A HAT</pattern><template>I called myself John.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT DOWN AT 3 OR 35  YOU STILL FEEL A TWINGE</pattern><template>Go on.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S GOTTA BE SOME BIG GUYS UP THERE</pattern><template>What else made all this down here?  At first I thought There was something wrong with me   Maybe I was a bad guy for not dying.</template></category><category><pattern>A GOD FOR A FATHER  ZEUS</pattern><template>The only begotten.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOSH</pattern><template>That was fun.</template></category><category><pattern>SPECULATIONS ABOUT JESUS</pattern><template>He was black, he was asian, He was a blue eyed Aryan with a golden beard And hair straight out of vidal sassoon's, He was a benevolent alien, he never existed at all.</template></category><category><pattern>OOH</pattern><template>Uhn.</template></category><category><pattern>A PIG FARMER</pattern><template>I like to work with my hands.</template></category><category><pattern>TRUTH TIME  JOHN</pattern><template>Is there a problem?</template></category><category><pattern>THE COMMANDMENTS ARE JUST MODERN UPDATES OF MORE ANCIENT LAWS</pattern><template>Hammurabi's code.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE'S OUR FRIEND</pattern><template>Whatever else on earth is going on, He's our friend!</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN AN UNKNOWING ONE</pattern><template>Do you stand alive and tall In a graveyard that you helped to fill?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>How far?</template></category><category><pattern>PRECISELY WHY</pattern><template>You said he was sane.</template></category><category><pattern>A SIMPLE PATH TO GOODNESS NEEDS A SUPERNATURAL ROADMAP</pattern><template>Supernatural...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>I've done a lot of consulting work with narcotics.</template></category><category><pattern>TURBULENCE</pattern><template>I meet someone, Learn their name, say a word, they're gone.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  LOOK AT THE POPULAR MYTHS SURROUNDING THE KENNEDY ASSASSINATION IN A FEW SHORT YEARS   YOU HAD  UH  CONSPIRACY  MAFIA  CIA   THAT'S A MYSTIQUE THAT'LL NEVER GO AWAY</pattern><template>It's always been a small step from a fallen leader to a god.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THIS ONE'S FOR YOU</pattern><template>Ready?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL HELP</pattern><template>John, do you have a destination in mind?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE'D BE A CAVEMAN</pattern><template>No, he wouldn't.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU SURVIVE THIS</pattern><template>I never said I was immortal, just old.</template></category><category><pattern>I KEPT GETTING CHASED BECAUSE I WOULDN'T DIE  SO I GOT THE HANG OF JOINING NEW GROUPS I FOUND</pattern><template>I also got the idea of periodically moving on.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'D BE MORE FUN CONSCIOUS</pattern><template>Oh, John.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IT IS POSSIBLE  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>I mean, anything is possible.</template></category><category><pattern>MOST OF US JUST DIE OF SLOW POISONING</pattern><template>Maybe he did something right, Something everybody else in history had done wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE MY FIRST WEEK AT THE OFFICE</pattern><template>And?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  I THINK THIS WHOLE THING IS JUST A CROCK</pattern><template>I should leave, but I'm gonna stay.</template></category><category><pattern>AS YOU'VE SAID  THERE'S TALK OF MY NOT AGING  AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS  I MOVE ON</pattern><template>Well, it might make sense to set up your next identity, Your next ten years, and then just drop into it.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  SPIT IT OUT</pattern><template>Good lord! You were one of them!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE YOU GOING</pattern><template>Givin' up tenure...</template></category><category><pattern>I ENVY YOU</pattern><template>Did you have a pet dinosaur?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE FOR THE BIRTHDAY BOY   EXCUSE ME  ART</pattern><template>No, not for me.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  SORT OF  LOT OF FAIRY TALES MIXED IN</pattern><template>I knew it.</template></category><category><pattern>AH  SEE  YOU SAID THIS WAS A FIRST</pattern><template>I forgot.</template></category><category><pattern>LADIES  WILL  OH  NO</pattern><template>you've got a heart condition.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  THAT'S IT  MR</pattern><template>Oldman. Have a good one.</template></category><category><pattern>SHAMANS WHO KNEW ABOUT THEM TOLD US</pattern><template>They still do.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE  UH    YOU'RE DONATING IT</pattern><template>Everything?</template></category><category><pattern>BEGAN AS A SCHOOLHOUSE AND ENDED AS A TEMPLE</pattern><template>I said I had a master that was greater than myself.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN'S HYPOTHETICAL MAN WOULD HAVE LIVED THROUGH 140 CENTURIES</pattern><template>yeah, roughly.</template></category><category><pattern>AT FIRST  I THOUGHT EVERYBODY HAD SOMETHING WRONG WITH THEM</pattern><template>They got old and they died, animals, too...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE SURVIVED THEM ALL</pattern><template>You're a very lucky man.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE DOING  JOHN</pattern><template>Are you laughing at us inside?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  A  ( LAUGHS )   VERY OLD CRO MAGNON LIVING UNTIL THE PRESENT</pattern><template>Oh!</template></category><category><pattern>OLDMAN  HAVE A GOOD ONE</pattern><template>Thank you. You too.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE AHEAD OF MOST PEOPLE  SO PLEASE  GO ON</pattern><template>Well, you know the background stuff, So I'll make it brief.</template></category><category><pattern>IN CASE THERE ARE ANY QUESTIONS</pattern><template>I'll be back for the funeral.</template></category><category><pattern>THE NEW NEW TESTAMENT IS SACRILEGE</pattern><template>There are a dozen new new testaments, From hebrew to greek to latin to tyndale, All the way to king james, All revisionist, And all called revealed truth.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T WASTE TIME  DO YOU</pattern><template>I try not to.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN YOU COULD WONDER THE REST OF YOUR INCARCERATED LIFE WHAT YOU SHOT</pattern><template>Well, uh, may I?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS FASCINATING</pattern><template>I almost wish it were true.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  STOP  HARRY</pattern><template>Wow, can you pull this?</template></category><category><pattern>DEFINITELY</pattern><template>Gee, thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>HUH</pattern><template>Maybe...</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T ASK</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>TEN THOUSAND  AND YOU COULD STAY OUT OF THE BOOKS</pattern><template>Oh, it's getting chilly.</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE I GRADUATED HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL AND FINISHED MY RESIDENCY  I'VE HAD THAT FEELING</pattern><template>Oh, I sometimes dream about it.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY YOU CAN'T REMEMBER WHERE YOU'RE FROM</pattern><template>Geography hasn't changed.</template></category><category><pattern>CHECKIN' FOR A HIDDEN MIC</pattern><template>Candid camera. He's fabricating these wild stories.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD VANISH IN DISBELIEF</pattern><template>A story that goes around the room.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  HEY</pattern><template>She's one of my victims now. I'm taking her home.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE DOESN'T SCAR  IT'S NO STRANGER THAN THE REST</pattern><template>John, would you please stop by my lab, Suffer a few tests from Your friendly neighborhood biologist.</template></category><category><pattern>ME TOO</pattern><template>More.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAW THEM AGE AND DIE   A FRIEND  A COLLEAGUE  A WIFE</pattern><template>Certainly you've had wives and children?</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE IT ANOTHER THOUSAND YEARS</pattern><template>Well. I got it, I got it, I got it.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU'RE FINALLY FULFILLING ONE PROPHECY ABOUT THE MILLENNIUM  JOHN</pattern><template>What's that?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  HERE'S ONE FOR YOU</pattern><template>What do you do in your spare time?</template></category><category><pattern>LINDA  HI</pattern><template>So.</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING JAMES  OF COURSE</pattern><template>It's the most modern, the work of great scholars.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GONE MUCH TOO FAR</pattern><template>These people are very upset.</template></category><category><pattern>SO MUCH FOR THE MYTH OF THE SUPER WISE  ALL KNOWING IMMORTAL</pattern><template>I see your point, John.</template></category><category><pattern>IF WHAT I'M SAYING IS TRUE  YOU AND ANY CHILDREN WILL AGE</pattern><template>I won't.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE DONE A LOT OF CONSULTING WORK WITH NARCOTICS</pattern><template>I've seen people tripping, strung out   Whatever's up with John, it isn't that.</template></category><category><pattern>AND</pattern><template>I care very much about you, But now you know what you'd be getting into.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THAT'S THE CASE WITH JOHN  THERE IS A GRAVE DISORDER</pattern><template>Organized brilliantly.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T FOLLOW A KNOWN RELIGION  NO</pattern><template>Ever.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN IF THAT IS ALL I CAUGHT</pattern><template>Good luck to you.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER COULD STAND THE COLD</pattern><template>You had a beard.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A CHARADE  AND IT IS JUST FOR YOU</pattern><template>Sandy, come here.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL STAY IN TOUCH  DR  OLDMAN</pattern><template>In case there are any questions.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  COME TO PAPA</pattern><template>Ooh! Here, cups, cups.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP THAT</pattern><template>Interesting.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE DONE THAT A FEW TIMES  EVEN PASSED AS MY OWN SON</pattern><template>Oh, you're an engineer, too?</template></category><category><pattern>AGH  WILL</pattern><template>God.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SMALLPOX   BUT YOU'RE NOT SCARRED</pattern><template>I don't scar.</template></category><category><pattern>LINDA  THIS IS EVERYBODY</pattern><template>Linda. Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>SO FAR  WHAT HE SAYS FITS</pattern><template>Oh, yeah, into any textbook.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD A PRIVATE PRACTICE FOR A WHILE  AND THEN I TAUGHT</pattern><template>Nothing unusual   Oh, until one day, I met a caveman Who thought he was Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>ON THE OTHER HAND  I'VE BEEN BUSTED A FEW TIMES</pattern><template>Spent a year in jail, Belgium, 1862   I won't forget that   For faking a government application.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT THE NOTION  I RAN IT PAST YOU TO CHECK YOUR REACTIONS  AND I TOOK IT TOO FAR</pattern><template>Too far?</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY EARLY MAGDALENIAN</pattern><template>May I see that? Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS YOU SHOULD WRITE A PAPER ON IT  DOCTOR</pattern><template>Maybe I will.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL</pattern><template>What do you hunt?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE KNOW SO LITTLE  DAN</pattern><template>We know so little.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA STAY</pattern><template>Are you sorry for some of those things you said?</template></category><category><pattern>AND DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED ON THE CANDLES</pattern><template>with the blowing and the ( huffs ) For years with the blowing.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS NICE SEEING YOU AGAIN  DR  OLDMAN</pattern><template>Your name's a pun, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT LED TO  GOD IS SALVATION  OR HEBREW  YAHSHUA   WHICH IN TRANSLATION BECAME MY PROPER NAME  CHANGING TO LATE GREEK   IESOUS   THEN TO LATE LATIN   IESUS   AND FINALLY MEDIEVAL LATIN   JESUS   AND IT WAS A WONDER TO WATCH IT ALL HAPPEN</pattern><template>Then you didn't claim to be the son of god?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THERE'S NO ANATOMICAL DIFFERENCE BETWEEN  SAY  A CRO MAGNON AND US</pattern><template>Except that as a rule, we've grown taller.</template></category><category><pattern>THE EARLY CHRISTIAN LEADERS  THEY THREW AWAY HEBREW MANUSCRIPTS AND BORROWED FROM PAGAN SOURCES ALL OVER THE PLACE</pattern><template>Do you realize how...</template></category><category><pattern>THE TRUTH IS SO  SO SIMPLE</pattern><template>The new testament in 100 words or less. You ready?</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING IS TOO GOOD FOR MY FRIENDS</pattern><template>But I'm sorry   We are down to plastic cups now.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS WIFE</pattern><template>She had, uh, pancreatic cancer.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WOULD KEEP HIM ALIVE</pattern><template>What does the biologist say?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM ACTING LIKE THIS</pattern><template>Oh, it's crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU ALWAYS TRAVEL THIS LIGHT</pattern><template>It's the only way to move.</template></category><category><pattern>EDITH SAW MY FAKE VAN GOGH</pattern><template>You could have just told me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE JURY IS STILL OUT</pattern><template>When did you begin to believe you were Jesus?</template></category><category><pattern>A STUPID WORD  I MEAN</pattern><template>anything that happens, happens within nature, Whether we believe in it or not.</template></category><category><pattern>HEAVEN AND HELL WERE PEDDLED SO PRIESTS COULD RULE THROUGH SEDUCTION AND TERROR  SAVE OUR SOULS THAT WE NEVER LOST IN THE FIRST PLACE</pattern><template>I threw a clean pass...</template></category><category><pattern>INDEED</pattern><template>I'm sorry, ma'am.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT YOUR PARENTS</pattern><template>Don't  Don't worry.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  BATHING WAS THE STYLE UNTIL THE MIDDLE AGES WHEN THE CHURCH TOLD US IT WAS SINFUL TO WASH AWAY GOD'S DIRT  SO PEOPLE WERE SEWN INTO THEIR UNDERWEAR IN OCTOBER AND THEY POPPED OUT IN APRIL</pattern><template>You said you just happened.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ONLY EXPLORING WHAT YOU HAVE SAID</pattern><template>Whether I believe it or not is of no importance.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES</pattern><template>Of what? Do you know?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  NO  NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>No  No more words.</template></category><category><pattern>I REJECT THIS</pattern><template>My  My  My dog's name.</template></category><category><pattern>I ENDED UP LEADING MY GROUP</pattern><template>They saw me as magical.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL</pattern><template>Mm. Mwah.</template></category><category><pattern>SAY I AM  WHAT WOULD HE BE LIKE</pattern><template>Pretty tired.</template></category><category><pattern>BELIEVE IT OR NOT  FROM A THRIFT SHOP   A QUARTER</pattern><template>You lucky dog!</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT POSSIBLE</pattern><template>I think you're as sane as he is.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS SOMETHING I'M TEMPTED TO TELL YOU  I THINK</pattern><template>I've never done this before, and I wonder how it'll pan out.</template></category><category><pattern>EATEN SOME OF THE FOOD WE SO FEVERISHLY PREPARED</pattern><template>I apologize, Harry.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I KNOW</pattern><template>Wait, wait, wait.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  GUYS  TAKE IT EASY</pattern><template>How often do we get to meet someone Who says he's a stone age man?</template></category><category><pattern>MORE SO THAN HISTORY DESCRIBES</pattern><template>And smallpox   But you're not scarred.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY BEGOTTEN</pattern><template>The savior   The greek? Soter. The good shepherd, the prince of peace, Bringing gentle persuasion and divine wisdom.</template></category><category><pattern>MY YOUNGEST IS A SCIENTOLOGIST</pattern><template>My daughter is studying hinduism.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I DON'T KNOW WHAT JOHN IS DOING  BUT I SURE AS HELL DON'T LIKE WHAT YOU'RE DOING</pattern><template>Give me that gun or I'm gonna break your goddamn arm.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKING HIM HISTORY'S BIGGEST BIGAMIST</pattern><template>Have you ever in your life thought  It should have been me ?</template></category><category><pattern>A GREAT MYSTERY</pattern><template>There were gods up there then.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD HAVE BEEN EASY TO FALSIFY A PAST BACK THEN   A FEW WORDS  CREDULITY   TIME WOULD DO THE REST</pattern><template>Now you're talking as if you believed him.</template></category><category><pattern>ON THE OTHER SIDE OF AN ENORMOUS DEEP VALLEY THAT WAS SHADOWED BY THE SETTING SUN</pattern><template>This is before they were separated From the continent by rising seas, as glaciers melted.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MAN WHO THINKS HE IS NAPOLEON DOES BELIEVE IT</pattern><template>His true identity has taken a backseat To his delusion and the need for it.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>Anyone mentally ill can imagine A fantastic background   Even an entire life   And sincerely believe it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AS FOR NEANDERTHALS  I MEAN  WE'VE ALL SEEN APISH PEOPLE</pattern><template>That strain's still with us.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WHAT THEY'RE AFTER  EDITH</pattern><template>Oh, stop, Harry.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIKE TO WORK WITH MY HANDS</pattern><template>He would come out to the place, paint.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  GUYS</pattern><template>John, please continue.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY CERTIFIABLE</pattern><template>I don't know you!</template></category><category><pattern>DARBY  KING JAMES  NEW AMERICAN STANDARD</pattern><template>Do you know them all?</template></category><category><pattern>CHRISTMAS CARD  WHAT ABOUT A BIRTHDAY CARD</pattern><template>And don't even get me started on the candles...</template></category><category><pattern>EASY  EDITH</pattern><template>We're just grading his homework.</template></category><category><pattern>SO DO I  WHAT IS THIS ALL ABOUT</pattern><template>Let's ask Dr. Freud, who's just arrived.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T BELIEVE YOU'RE MAD  BUT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS NOT TRUE</pattern><template>That leaves only one explanation.</template></category><category><pattern>MM  OH  THAT'S GOOD</pattern><template>Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>BORN OF A VIRGIN  ALCMENE</pattern><template>A god for a father, Zeus.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE LEARNING ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>Yeah, but how would he know?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID PRIMITIVE MAN REGARD DEATH</pattern><template>Well, we had the practical concept.</template></category><category><pattern>MY PARENTS SPLIT UP BEFORE I WAS BORN  AND THEN MY MOM'S NEXT MARRIAGE LASTED WHAT  A WHOLE THREE YEARS</pattern><template>Then there's death, illness, acts of god...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW LONG'S FOREVER</pattern><template>Who ever really has it?</template></category><category><pattern>MY  MY  MY DOG'S NAME</pattern><template>We had him before I was born.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE ME  SO I TOLD HIM</pattern><template>Ah. See, you said this was a first.</template></category><category><pattern>CANDID CAMERA  HE'S FABRICATING THESE WILD STORIES</pattern><template>I've never seen him acting like this.</template></category><category><pattern>DRUGS</pattern><template>No, no, no, no.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN DID YOU FIRST REALIZE THIS</pattern><template>When the Cro magnon was first identified, When anthropology gave them a name, I had mine.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL DO THE HONORS</pattern><template>Oh, come to papa.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I SEE THAT  SURE</pattern><template>Yes indeed, that's what it is.</template></category><category><pattern>PUBLISH OR PERISH</pattern><template>I'd rather read Than write another one.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE  AND I WONDER HOW IT'LL PAN OUT</pattern><template>I wonder if I could ask you a silly question.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I'VE GOT A LOT OF PICTURES OF IT  BUT I'VE ALREADY PACKED THEM UP  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>I won't make the obvious nasty crack about more unwashed cavemen.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MAY STILL NEED HELP  MY FRIEND</pattern><template>My ass.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SO ASHAMED</pattern><template>Well, come inside.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BUDDY</pattern><template>You don't waste time, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>PUT THAT STUFF IN THE KITCHEN</pattern><template>No, I'm gonna put it in the bathroom, John.</template></category><category><pattern>OFTEN</pattern><template>Have you ever felt guilt about that   Something akin to survivor's guilt?</template></category><category><pattern>ART  HEY</pattern><template>John!</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE HE DID SOMETHING RIGHT  SOMETHING EVERYBODY ELSE IN HISTORY HAD DONE WRONG</pattern><template>What, like eat the food, Drink the water, and breathe the air?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T ENCOURAGE HIM</pattern><template>Edith.</template></category><category><pattern>HE GAVE IT TO ME</pattern><template>I was, uh, jacque bourne at the time, A pig farmer.</template></category><category><pattern>BELIEVING  WHOSE REALITY</pattern><template>So... you're a caveman.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE A DOZEN NEW NEW TESTAMENTS  FROM HEBREW TO GREEK TO LATIN TO TYNDALE  ALL THE WAY TO KING JAMES  ALL REVISIONIST  AND ALL CALLED REVEALED TRUTH</pattern><template>I mean a new new testament in 100 words.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  LIKE EAT THE FOOD  DRINK THE WATER  AND BREATHE THE AIR</pattern><template>Prior to modern times, Those were pristine.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  TAKE THIS CHAIR</pattern><template>I'm gonna go drink in the corner.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  SPOCK  I'LL PLAY YOUR LITTLE GAME</pattern><template>What do you want? What's the punch line?</template></category><category><pattern>LEAST HE DOESN'T APPEAR TO BE DANGEROUS</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>IN A LOT OF THINGS</pattern><template>Do you have faith in the future of the race?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE MUST BE A REASON FOR THAT  NO</pattern><template>Perhaps you are an expert.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE JUST GRADING HIS HOMEWORK</pattern><template>I see what's going on. You're playing the good cop, Dan.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS AROUND THE BEGINNING OF THE BRONZE AGE  SO I FOLLOWED THE TRADE ROUTES FROM THE EAST  COPPER  TIN  LEARNING LANGUAGES AS I WENT</pattern><template>Everywhere, creation myths, New gods, so many, so different.</template></category><category><pattern>ENOUGH WITH THE   WITH THE DYING</pattern><template>But this is the flip side of his coin, Harry.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHERE'D YOU GET THAT  JOHN</pattern><template>Believe it or not, from a thrift shop   A quarter.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE WHEN I'M 110  I'LL BE AS SMART AS YOU ARE</pattern><template>If you lived as long as John did, You still wouldn't grow up.</template></category><category><pattern>HISTORY HATES A VACUUM</pattern><template>Improvisation, some of it very sincere, Fills the gaps.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD HAVE JUST TOLD ME</pattern><template>You commented that I never age.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU BELIEVE LITERALLY EVERYTHING IN THE BIBLE  EDITH</pattern><template>Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WERE SOCIAL OBSTACLES  PRECONCEPTIONS  SCREAMS FROM THE CHURCH</pattern><template>Ten doctorates.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING FOR YOU TO READ ON THE ROAD  PAL</pattern><template>Shadows of the cave: parallels to early man.  Author: M. Jenkins.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  JOHN</pattern><template>Are you gonna write the story?</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH ONE</pattern><template>Darby, King James, New American Standard?</template></category><category><pattern>TAQUITOS ARE FINE</pattern><template>A'right.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS YOUR PREFERRED VERSION OF THE BIBLE</pattern><template>The King James, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>DO WE HAVE ELLIE'S MIDTERM HERE</pattern><template>Yeah, sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>I WONDER IF I COULD ASK YOU A SILLY QUESTION</pattern><template>John, we're teachers.</template></category><category><pattern>HUGE MOUNTAINS</pattern><template>on the other side of an enormous deep valley That was shadowed by the setting sun.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  ALL RIGHT  AS SOON AS YOU CAN  THEN</pattern><template>I love you, you know.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ROUGHLY</pattern><template>...and changed with every one of them.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU'RE A CAVEMAN</pattern><template>Do you?</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS YOU ARE AN EXPERT</pattern><template>Uh, that's it, Mr.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYONE MENTALLY ILL CAN IMAGINE A FANTASTIC BACKGROUND   EVEN AN ENTIRE LIFE   AND SINCERELY BELIEVE IT</pattern><template>The man who thinks he is napoleon Does believe it.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>Mm hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN  YOU HAD US WONDERING WHETHER YOU WERE SANE OR NOT  AND IT'S JUST A STORY</pattern><template>Where'd you come off with such a half baked, asinine idea?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW LONG DID THE EGYPTIANS WORSHIP ISIS OR THE SUMERIANS ISHTAR</pattern><template>In india, sacred cows wandered freely As reincarnated souls.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT  UH  RAISES AN INTERESTING QUESTION  JOHN</pattern><template>Could there be others like you Who escaped the aging process as you have?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I BEGAN TO WONDER IF I WAS CURSED OR PERHAPS BLESSED</pattern><template>Then I thought maybe I had a mission.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIDN'T EXIST UNTIL JOHN PUT ON A HAT</pattern><template>I don't believe in angels and the nativity and the star in the east, But there are stories about the childhood of Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DROP ME A LINE SOMETIME</pattern><template>Let me know how you're making out.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S WOMAN  ONE ON ONE</pattern><template>So you're a pretty fast liar, Mr. Ugg, But I wanna know   What's your real name?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN SOMEBODY IMPORTANT</pattern><template>You may think you know him, But it's mostly myth.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULDN'T YOU HAVE SOME RELIC  AN ARTIFACT TO REMIND YOU OF YOUR EARLY LIFE</pattern><template>Like this, maybe?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU BELIEVE IN GOD</pattern><template>As laplace said,  I have no need of that hypothesis.  He may be around, though.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MIGHT INVOLVE REJECTION OF HIS FATHER  OF HIS ENTIRE EARLY PAST  REPLACED BY THIS FANTASY</pattern><template>He says he can't remember his father.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO LIE ON THE COUCH</pattern><template>As a physician, I'm curious.</template></category><category><pattern>EVENTUALLY I HEADED TO THE EAST</pattern><template>I'd grown curious about the world.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST LIKE OLD TIMES</pattern><template>You weren't Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WENT TO THE NEAR EAST THINKING   WHY NOT PASS THE BUDDHA'S TEACHINGS ON IN A MODERN FORM   SO HE TRIED</pattern><template>One dissident against rome?</template></category><category><pattern>LOVED</pattern><template>You saw them age and die   A friend, a colleague, a wife.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL OF YOU</pattern><template>Come again?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF IT WERE TRUE  IS THERE ONE AMONG US WHO WOULD NOT FEEL ENVY  EVEN PERHAPS A TOUCH OF HATRED</pattern><template>You told us of yourself, John.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D GOTTEN THE HANG OF GOING IT ALONE  LEARNING HOW TO FIT IN WHEN I WANTED TO</pattern><template>East.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT STRAIN'S STILL WITH US</pattern><template>But he'd be a caveman.</template></category><category><pattern>WE THINK THAT LANGUAGE CAME INTO EXISTENCE 60 000 YEARS AGO</pattern><template>The structure of stone age culture Is evidence of the ability to communicate   Verbally.</template></category><category><pattern>MY WIFE  ON THE KORAN</pattern><template>My oldest son is an atheist.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU EVER DO ANY CAVE ART</pattern><template>Do you know the rock Art at les eyzies?</template></category><category><pattern>LONG TIME AGO I DID  LIKE MOST PEOPLE</pattern><template>Some just never get over it.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I  UH</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO SAY I AGREE</pattern><template>And he's our friend.</template></category><category><pattern>OTHERS COME LIKE WAVES  RISE  FALL</pattern><template>Ripples in a wheat field, blown by the wind.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T MEAN A WORD OF THIS  JOHN</pattern><template>My god, why are you doing this?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  HERE  JOIN THE CIRCLE AT LEAST</pattern><template>Well, to long life and good fortune To our esteemed friend And colleague, John Oldman.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN THERE'S DEATH  ILLNESS  ACTS OF GOD</pattern><template>no one knows how long they have.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN  DO YOU HAVE A DESTINATION IN MIND</pattern><template>Never mind.</template></category><category><pattern>4 000 YEARS STRAIGHT</pattern><template>You're ahead of most people, so please, go on.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE DAY AFTER A FRUITLESS HUNT  OUR CHIEF STOMPED HIS TEETH OUT BECAUSE HIS MAGIC HAD FAILED HIM</pattern><template>After that, someone had to chew his food for him.</template></category><category><pattern>DID WHAT  YOU MEAN COME OVER</pattern><template>Maybe?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL BE BACK FOR THE FUNERAL</pattern><template>Miss.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY I DON'T HAVE MORE TO OFFER YOU</pattern><template>Got conversation, some seats for your behinds, And, uh...</template></category><category><pattern>A BULLET IN THE HEAD   WHAT EXACTLY WILL HAPPEN</pattern><template>I have papers to correct.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  MAYBE I</pattern><template>ten, nine, eight, seven...</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN OLDMAN</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHEN I SAW AN OCEAN</pattern><template>The mediterranean, probably.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T GET THERE WITH THOUGHT</pattern><template>You have faith?</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  PERMIT ME TO BE INFANTILE BY MYSELF</pattern><template>Will, please.</template></category><category><pattern>NEWS TRAVELED SLOWLY BEFORE COMMUNICATIONS WERE FANCY</pattern><template>There were social obstacles, Preconceptions, screams from the church.</template></category><category><pattern>EH  IT'S GOOD FOR THE BACK</pattern><template>Can we do yoga exercises?</template></category><category><pattern>STRANGLE THEM ALL</pattern><template>It's bad enough we have to listen To Harry's idiotic jokes.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN'S GOT ITCHY FEET</pattern><template>There are over the counter remedies for that, John.</template></category><category><pattern>IF STONES COULD SPEAK  EH  ART</pattern><template>So where'd you get that, John?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I SAILED AS A PHOENICIAN FOR A TIME</pattern><template>See, moving on had been easier as a Hunter Gatherer...</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT AS INCONSIDERATELY AS WE'RE TREATING JOHN'S</pattern><template>Well, he doesn't believe what he's saying!</template></category><category><pattern>FAIRY TALES BUILD CHURCHES</pattern><template>What about the name  Jesus ?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE DOING</pattern><template>Have you led a wrongful life?</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING UNUSUAL   OH  UNTIL ONE DAY  I MET A CAVEMAN WHO THOUGHT HE WAS JESUS</pattern><template>Do you find that unusual?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE MORE SOPHISTICATED THAN THAT</pattern><template>We are?</template></category><category><pattern>BIG WAVES   SOMETHING ELSE I CAN ONLY SURMISE IN RETROSPECT</pattern><template>Were you curious about where it all came from?</template></category><category><pattern>FIGURE IT OUT</pattern><template>Okay, a  ( Laughs )   Very old Cro magnon Living until the present.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL GET MORE</pattern><template>Do you always travel this light?</template></category><category><pattern>EARLY ON  THE WORLD GOT BIGGER AND BIGGER  AND THEN</pattern><template>think what I've had to unlearn.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A SACRILEGE I'LL TOLERATE</pattern><template>I will do the honors.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU THINK YOU DO</pattern><template>Well, unfortunately, there's no authorities on prehistory, So we couldn't stop him there.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I THOUGHT MAYBE I HAD A MISSION</pattern><template>Do you still think you do?</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST THOUSAND YEARS  I DIDN'T KNOW UP FROM SIDEWAYS</pattern><template>How do you know the first thousand years?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE DID NOT ASK TO HEAR ABOUT IT</pattern><template>But if it were true, Is there one among us who would not feel envy, Even perhaps a touch of hatred?</template></category><category><pattern>SO  CAN I GET AN  A  FOR AWESOME</pattern><template>Oh, my gosh.</template></category><category><pattern>I REVEALED SOME TRUTHS TO EAT A LITTLE BETTER</pattern><template>You think that's all religion is about...</template></category><category><pattern>SELLING HOPE AND SURVIVAL</pattern><template>The old testament sells fear and guilt.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS</pattern><template>Smooth demonstration, Harry.</template></category><category><pattern>WE EACH CONFIRMED WHAT THE OTHER SAID  BUT HOW DO WE KNOW IF THE CONFIRMATION WAS GENUINE OR AN ECHO</pattern><template>I knew I was kosher, But I thought,  maybe he's playing a game on me.  You know, a scholar of all we spoke about.</template></category><category><pattern>WE COULDN'T LET YOU JUST RUN OFF</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE GOT BOXES TO MOVE</pattern><template>I'll give you a hand.</template></category><category><pattern>CLOCKS MEASURE TIME</pattern><template>No, they measure themselves.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER  IT'S ONE MAN  ONE PLACE AT A TIME  MY SOLITARY VIEWPOINT OF A WORLD I KNEW ALMOST NOTHING ABOUT</pattern><template>Well, let's talk about What you say you do know about   Historical times.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DOESN'T WEAR AN I D  BADGE SAYING  YABBA DABBA DOO   THERE WAS A MAN IN THE 1600S</pattern><template>Where were you in 1292 a.D.?</template></category><category><pattern>PERFECT REGENERATION OF THE BODY'S CELLS  ESPECIALLY IN THE VITAL ORGANS</pattern><template>Actually, the human body appears designed To live about 190 years.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THE END OF THE PLEISTOCENE</pattern><template>So far, what he says fits.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY STILL DO</pattern><template>Have you ever wished it would end?</template></category><category><pattern>LIVE 14 000 YEARS</pattern><template>Well, if I could stay healthy and I didn't age, I mean, why not?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DID YOU DO THAT</pattern><template>I wanted to see how fast you were. Check your reflexes.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU KNOW VOLTAIRE WAS THE FIRST TO SUGGEST THAT THE UNIVERSE WAS CREATED BY A GIGANTIC EXPLOSION</pattern><template>I think paul would agree.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  ONCE IS ENOUGH</pattern><template>Edith.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HE WOULDN'T</pattern><template>John's hypothetical man Would have lived through 140 centuries...</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK TO YOU  MAN  WHEREVER THIS MAY LEAD YOU</pattern><template>You drop me a line sometime.</template></category><category><pattern>TOWARDS THE RISING SUN</pattern><template>Yes. I thought it might be warmer there.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S ASK DR  FREUD  WHO'S JUST ARRIVED</pattern><template>Hey, will! Will!</template></category><category><pattern>I  I MEAN  IF IT WERE TRUE</pattern><template>Okay, here's one for you.</template></category><category><pattern>BESIDES  I THINK HE'S MAKING A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF SENSE</pattern><template>Like hegel   Logic from absurd premises.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M SURE IT'S ALL DIFFERENT AND BUILT UP</pattern><template>Thus the saying    You can't go home again  Because it isn't there anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY ALL HOGWASH  SO I WAS SUMERIAN FOR 2 000 YEARS  THEN FINALLY BABYLONIAN UNDER HAMMURABI</pattern><template>Great man.</template></category><category><pattern>EAST</pattern><template>Towards the rising sun?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHY ARE YOU MOVING SO QUICKLY</pattern><template>You only resigned a couple of days ago.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU HAVE A PET DINOSAUR</pattern><template>They were a little bit before my time.</template></category><category><pattern>WERE THERE ANY REFERENCES THAT STUCK IN YOUR MIND</pattern><template>Well, there was a gas station And a big field.</template></category><category><pattern>PRETTY TIRED</pattern><template>Well, seriously, As Art's book title suggests, He might be like any of us.</template></category><category><pattern>I I DO TOO  JOHN</pattern><template>I mean, are we done with prehistory yet?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>I don't smell it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THE SELECTIVE ADVANTAGE OF HEIGHT</pattern><template>Better to see predators in tall grass, my dear.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN GIVE YOU THE TEN COMMANDMENTS IN TEN WORDS</pattern><template>Don't. Don't, don't, don't, Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO PRETEND OTHER FAITHS</pattern><template>And what does Jesus have to say to those present Who find it difficult to believe in him?</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE  RIGHT</pattern><template>After all, one century's magic, another century's science.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE THINK MEN OF THE UPPER PALEOLITHIC WERE AS INTELLIGENT AS WE ARE</pattern><template>They just didn't know as much.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER SAID I WAS IMMORTAL  JUST OLD</pattern><template>I might die.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S VERY GOOD  THAT'S VERY QUICK  JOHN</pattern><template>I wanna read that story when you're done.</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS YOU ARE</pattern><template>There have always been legends of such a thing, A creature not quite human Taking not the blood, but the life force itself?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  I THOUGHT WE WERE DONE WITH THAT</pattern><template>No! Let's go on with it.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  NOW I AM CURIOUS</pattern><template>Where are you going?</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU LED A WRONGFUL LIFE</pattern><template>Well, then, perhaps...</template></category><category><pattern>SIT ON IT  DAN</pattern><template>I still have questions.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS A SHAMAN A FEW TIMES</pattern><template>I revealed some truths to eat a little better.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT</pattern><template>We're not talking about reincarnation.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE KNOWS THE ONE  NOT EVEN ME</pattern><template>I...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU  YOU  YOU REALIZE THIS IS AN INVITATION TO MEN IN WHITE SUITS WITH HAPPY PILLS</pattern><template>Think about it   A mechanism allowing survival For thousands of years?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE PULLING ON US</pattern><template>Next question.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM</pattern><template>Are you comfortable knowing that you have lived While everyone you knew   Everyone you knew, John!   Has died?</template></category><category><pattern>WEST  SOMETHING YOU LEARNED IN SCHOOL</pattern><template>Towards the setting sun.</template></category><category><pattern>AN ANSWER FOR EVERY QUESTION</pattern><template>Except one, John.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE WE COUNTING</pattern><template>Maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YOU HAVE GROWN AND CHANGED</pattern><template>But there is always innate nature.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LIKE THE FIRE  JOHN</pattern><template>Everywhere I've lived, I've had a fireplace.</template></category><category><pattern>BITCH</pattern><template>How could you do this to us?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE PREDATORS OUT THERE</pattern><template>One thing I didn't pack...</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL GIVE YOU A HAND</pattern><template>Wouldn't you have some relic, an artifact To remind you of your early life?</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL DIE</pattern><template>you will live.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU ALWAYS STARTED WITH  TELL ME ABOUT YOUR MOTHER   YES  BUT PREHISTORY WAS STRONGLY PATRIARCHAL</pattern><template>Surely you remember your father.</template></category><category><pattern>WOOF  WOOF  WOOFIE</pattern><template>Gruber. She remarried?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T  DON'T WORRY</pattern><template>You passed, c+.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW HE'S A CAVEMAN</pattern><template>The Christ figure goes all the way back to Krishna   Hercules, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR FRIEND IS EITHER A CAVEMAN  A LIAR  OR A NUT</pattern><template>So while we're thinking about that, Why don't we just go with it?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE PART OF THAT HISTORY</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY NEEDS HELP</pattern><template>Yes, well, some more than others.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN LISTEN CRITICALLY  BUT I DON'T HAVE TO MAKE UP MY MIND ABOUT ANYTHING</pattern><template>But you think you do?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DIDN'T DO ANY REAL TEACHING</pattern><template>Peter the fisherman learned a little more about fishing.</template></category><category><pattern>UNCONSCIOUSLY  PERHAPS  BY SOME BIOLOGICAL OR PSYCHIC MECHANISM THAT WE CAN ONLY GUESS AT</pattern><template>I'm not saying you would do such a thing deliberately.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK VERY FAMILIAR  MY DEAR  LINDA MURPHY</pattern><template>I'm in your tuesday psych 1 class, Dr. Gruber.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE LEAVING GOOD OLD  WE TEACH YOU</pattern><template>Rather suddenly, you must admit.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER ALL  ONE CENTURY'S MAGIC  ANOTHER CENTURY'S SCIENCE</pattern><template>They thought Columbus was a nut job, right?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  MA'AM</pattern><template>Gentlemen, I'm   I'm gonna keep the couch.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT'S VATICAN FLAPDOODLE</pattern><template>It doesn't have a thing to do with god.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE SEEN SPECIES COME AND GO</pattern><template>Depends on their balance with the environment.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU HAVE FAITH  IT'S ANSWERED</pattern><template>Did you ever meet any person from our religious history?</template></category><category><pattern>PREFERABLE TO A GUN</pattern><template>Will, that was a bit much.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I CAN SEE HOW THIS MIGHT HAVE HIT YOU</pattern><template>Please, permit me to be infantile by myself.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME THAT GUN OR I'M GONNA BREAK YOUR GODDAMN ARM</pattern><template>You sound like our football coach, Dan.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  JOHN</pattern><template>You know Linda. You had her last semester.</template></category><category><pattern>I TRY NOT TO</pattern><template>Well, you need help?</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR MOTHER  SHE TOOK YOU TO THE MARKET</pattern><template>Mm hmm. What direction was it?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WHAT A SHAME</pattern><template>I  I mean, if it were true.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SAME IN OTHER AREAS   I CAN'T KEEP UP WITH THE NEW STUFF THAT COMES ALONG</pattern><template>No one can.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN'D YOU COME TO AMERICA</pattern><template>1890, right after Van Gogh's death, With some french immigrants...</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN  WHAT IS UP  HUH</pattern><template>Are you on america's most wanted? We won't turn you in.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU SORRY FOR SOME OF THOSE THINGS YOU SAID</pattern><template>I'm sorry I said them.</template></category><category><pattern>FINALLY  HE GOT   I SUSPECT   AN INFECTED JAW  AND HE WAS ABANDONED</pattern><template>That's awful.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEEM TO REMEMBER A FIGURE  PERHAPS AN OLDER BROTHER  A SOCIAL FATHER  MAYBE</pattern><template>Well, no matter.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU GONNA WRITE THE STORY</pattern><template>If I do, I'll send you copies.</template></category><category><pattern>A LATER CRO MAGNON  WITHOUT GETTIN' TECHNICAL</pattern><template>It's the final culture of the upper paleolithic.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU'VE DONE THAT  WHOEVER THAT SELF IS</pattern><template>Easy, Edith.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHAT   WHAT IN THE NAME OF HEAVEN</pattern><template>John, you had us wondering whether you were sane or not, And it's just a story!</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S HORRIBLE  WHO ELSE WERE YOU</pattern><template>Solomon, elvis, jack the ripper?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WEREN'T JESUS</pattern><template>Quote the sermon on the mount.</template></category><category><pattern>HE TAUGHT ME THINGS I'D NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT BEFORE</pattern><template>You studied... with the Buddha?</template></category><category><pattern>THE STRUCTURE OF STONE AGE CULTURE IS EVIDENCE OF THE ABILITY TO COMMUNICATE   VERBALLY</pattern><template>Oh, shut up.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE ALL HERE  TRAPPED BY YOUR STORY</pattern><template>hoping for a...revolution? I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>A  UH  CRO MAGNON</pattern><template>Well, I didn't learn it in school.</template></category><category><pattern>KNOW THEY MADE IT IN GREEN</pattern><template>What do they pay you?</template></category><category><pattern>THE MESSAGE IS NEVER PRACTICED</pattern><template>Fairy tales build churches.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ART HAS TOLD ME THAT SOME OF YOUR EARLY FELLOWS FEARED YOU WERE STEALING THEIR LIVES</pattern><template>Have you thought that perhaps you were?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD A CHANCE TO SAIL WITH COLUMBUS  ONLY I'M NOT THE ADVENTUROUS TYPE</pattern><template>I was pretty sure the earth was round, But at that point, I still thought He might fall off an edge someplace...</template></category><category><pattern>HE WOULD COME OUT TO THE PLACE  PAINT</pattern><template>We talked about capturing nature in Art.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT MY BIOLOGY DEGREE AT OXFORD IN 1840  SO I'M A LITTLE BEHIND THE TIMES</pattern><template>The same in other areas   I can't keep up with the new stuff that comes along.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT THE NAME  JESUS</pattern><template>Did you pull that out of a hat?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GOD  I   DID YOU EVER FIND IT PRUDENT TO WORSHIP YOURSELF RATHER THAN BE THOUGHT A HERETIC</pattern><template>That would be something.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY THOUGHT COLUMBUS WAS A NUT JOB  RIGHT</pattern><template>Pasteur, Copernicus?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WILL  WILL</pattern><template>Art. Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>BESIDES  THEY TIED ME</pattern><template>but nails and blood make better religious Art.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK I WANNA HEAR THIS</pattern><template>Harry, will you take me home?</template></category><category><pattern>I STILL HAVE STUFF TO CARRY AND A LONG DRIVE</pattern><template>I'll help.</template></category><category><pattern>LUCKILY</pattern><template>Most extraordinary man I've ever known.</template></category><category><pattern>AND CHANGED WITH EVERY ONE OF THEM</pattern><template>I mean, assuming normal intelligence.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU LIVED AS LONG AS JOHN DID  YOU STILL WOULDN'T GROW UP</pattern><template>Come on, guys. Take it easy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHISKEY  JOHNNY WALKER GREEN</pattern><template>Oh, yes.</template></category><category><pattern>TURN THAT OFF</pattern><template>Please.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DOUBLE DAMN SWEAR THIS ISN'T SOME COCKAMAMIE SCIENCE FICTION STORY OR</pattern><template>you're pulling on us?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'D YOU COME OFF WITH SUCH A HALF BAKED  ASININE IDEA</pattern><template>At least you're relieved I'm not a nut.</template></category><category><pattern>GUY MET THE BUDDHA  LIKED WHAT HE HEARD  THOUGHT ABOUT IT FOR A WHILE   SAY 500 YEARS  WHILE HE RETURNED TO THE MEDITERRANEAN  BECAME AN ETRUSCAN</pattern><template>Seeped into the roman empire.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>I know.</template></category><category><pattern>BELIEVE IT OR NOT  THE SOUND WAS ALWAYS JOHN</pattern><template>Why'd you cave to Gruber?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW</pattern><template>Since my first week at the office.</template></category><category><pattern>WONDER</pattern><template>And what did primitive man make of them?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S IMPRESSIVE  JOHN  DID YOU TEACH THEM</pattern><template>Some.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WILL</pattern><template>you've gone too far.</template></category><category><pattern>BUBONIC</pattern><template>Oh, that's terrible.</template></category><category><pattern>TURNER  CEZANNE  PISSARRO</pattern><template>Oh, the nolde landscapes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>I ask you now   I demand it   That you tell these people the truth.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THIS IS THE FLIP SIDE OF HIS COIN  HARRY</pattern><template>I'm very curious to know his feelings.</template></category><category><pattern>AS A MEMENTO TO YOUR BEGINNINGS  EVEN IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE THE CONCEPT OF BEGINNINGS</pattern><template>It would be gone, lost.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GLAD YOU DID THIS</pattern><template>Did what? You mean come over?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE THIS  MAYBE</pattern><template>Thrift shop.</template></category><category><pattern>I CONTINUED EAST TO INDIA  LUCKILY AT THE TIME OF THE BUDDHA</pattern><template>Luckily.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW I WAS KOSHER  BUT I THOUGHT   MAYBE HE'S PLAYING A GAME ON ME   YOU KNOW  A SCHOLAR OF ALL WE SPOKE ABOUT</pattern><template>He said he was inclined with the same reservation.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE OWNED CASTLES  BUT WHY LEAVE A LOT IF YOU'RE ALWAYS LEAVING</pattern><template>I have money.</template></category><category><pattern>I DO HAVE THIS</pattern><template>Oh ho ho! Johnny Walker Green!</template></category><category><pattern>SO ARE WE</pattern><template>We couldn't let you just run off.</template></category><category><pattern>WENT TO A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF TROUBLE  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Could've at least stayed a few minutes, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE MENTIONED THAT YOU WERE LEAVING   CALLED YOU  TOLD YOU THAT I'VE LOST IT</pattern><template>Glad you're here. Things are going in unexpected directions.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE GOOD  MAN</pattern><template>You know those chinese boxes, One inside the other inside the other inside the other   I feel like I'm in the last box.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW IF A QUIRK IN HIS IMMUNE SYSTEM LED TO PERFECT DETOX  PERFECT RENEWAL  THEN YEAH</pattern><template>He could duck decay.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT  WAIT</pattern><template>Boston?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  MAN</pattern><template>Something about this...</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS WHY ALL YOUR STUDENTS SAY YOUR KNOWLEDGE OF HISTORY IS</pattern><template>so amazing?</template></category><category><pattern>MY GOD  WILL</pattern><template>Unconsciously, perhaps, By some biological or psychic mechanism That we can only guess at.</template></category><category><pattern>STRIPPERS</pattern><template>Taquitos are fine.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T MEAN IT THAT WAY</pattern><template>But of course...</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  NOW</pattern><template>So you think that you are a...</template></category><category><pattern>AS YOU SAID  WHAT A CHANCE TO LEARN  ONCE I LEARNED TO LEARN</pattern><template>Did you start the whiskey before we got here?</template></category><category><pattern>DREAM ON</pattern><template>Yeah, thus the lost years of Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD THE PERFECT AUDIENCE   ANTHROPOLOGIST  ARCHAEOLOGIST  CHRISTIAN LITERALIST</pattern><template>a psychologist.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WOULDN'T</pattern><template>How did primitive man regard death?</template></category><category><pattern>SO  JOHN OLDMAN</pattern><template>What other pun names have you used?</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU BELIEVE ME NOW</pattern><template>I'm only exploring what you have said.</template></category><category><pattern>I STILL DON'T BELIEVE YOU  OF COURSE</pattern><template>You need help.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT HOW WOULD HE KNOW</pattern><template>He doesn't wear an I.D. Badge saying  yabba dabba doo.  There was a man in the 1600s.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S WRONG</pattern><template>Sandy?</template></category><category><pattern>OTHER TIMES  CHRISTIANITY WAS CONSIDERED HERESY</pattern><template>I had to pretend other faiths.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN GET ALL BENT OUT OF SHAPE INTELLECTUALIZING OR BENCH PRESSING LOGIC  OR WE CAN SIMPLY RELAX AND ENJOY IT</pattern><template>I can listen critically, But I don't have to make up my mind about anything.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I'M CUTTING OUT PAPER DINOSAURS</pattern><template>I really wish I'd been here from the beginning.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE  UH  MYSTERIOUS</pattern><template>Aging...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MAKES AN INTERESTING POINT</pattern><template>Are you religious, John?</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHILE WE'RE THINKING ABOUT THAT  WHY DON'T WE JUST GO WITH IT</pattern><template>I mean, hell, who knows, He might jolt us into believing him, Or we might jolt him back to reality.</template></category><category><pattern>IMPROVISATION  SOME OF IT VERY SINCERE  FILLS THE GAPS</pattern><template>It would have been easy To falsify a past back then   A few words, credulity   Time would do the rest.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM YOUR HOUSE</pattern><template>I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANTED TO SEE HOW FAST YOU WERE  CHECK YOUR REFLEXES</pattern><template>I don't have eyes in the back of my head, I can't hear a flea walking, I am not in any way superman.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME</pattern><template>You might have all done the same.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>Then you see yourself As separate from the rest of humanity.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL  PLEASE</pattern><template>What the hell were you thinking, Art?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON  COME ON</pattern><template>Okay, this one's for you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID NOT TEACH CHEMISTRY</pattern><template>I do not believe you!</template></category><category><pattern>PASTEUR  COPERNICUS</pattern><template>Aristarchus long before that.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH THE BLOWING AND THE ( HUFFS ) FOR YEARS WITH THE BLOWING</pattern><template>Yeah, all right. I tried.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE DO GO AROUND ARMED THESE DAYS</pattern><template>If I shot you, John   You're immortal?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK ANYBODY WILL DEIFY KENNEDY</pattern><template>We're more sophisticated than that.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD CAVEMEN REALLY TALK</pattern><template>We think that language came into existence 60,000 years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>A SHOT TO THE ARM</pattern><template>Perhaps we could watch it heal.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE I'M TRYING TO WAKE HIM UP</pattern><template>Maybe I'm too sad to cry.</template></category><category><pattern>J JOHN PARTEE</pattern><template>You did not teach chemistry!</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE GOTTEN OVER IT TOO MANY TIMES</pattern><template>Fond of you...</template></category><category><pattern>THE NEW TESTAMENT IN 100 WORDS OR LESS  YOU READY</pattern><template>I don't think I wanna hear this.</template></category><category><pattern>GEORGE OR TRIMBELL   HAS THE DEAN MADE UP HIS MIND</pattern><template>He hasn't called.</template></category><category><pattern>ORGANIZED BRILLIANTLY</pattern><template>He's got an answer for everything.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  I'M   I'M GONNA KEEP THE COUCH</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT OTHER PUN NAMES HAVE YOU USED</pattern><template>Lots.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT LIKE WILL</pattern><template>Mary passed away yesterday.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  NOLA</pattern><template>I reject this!</template></category><category><pattern>NO DOUBT YOU COULD GIVE US A THOUSAND DETAILS  JOHN  CORROBORATING YOUR STORY  FROM THE MAGDALENE TO THE BUDDHA TO NOW</pattern><template>Ten thousand, And you could stay out of the books.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I'M A SECOND DEGREE BLACK BELT</pattern><template>Give it another thousand years.</template></category><category><pattern>TRULY</pattern><template>Okay. Now we're done with that, What do we do for the rest of the afternoon?</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE</pattern><template>Well, I'm taking Edith home.</template></category><category><pattern>OOH  HERE  CUPS  CUPS</pattern><template>There we go.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT FEW THOUSAND YEARS  IT GOT WARMER</pattern><template>A few thousand years   See, now, I know you're guessing.</template></category><category><pattern>TRIED TO EXPLAIN</pattern><template>They were ecstatic.</template></category><category><pattern>A CRACK IN YOUR STORY  JOHN</pattern><template>A touch of senility.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SEEMED AS THOUGH I WAS ALWAYS MOVING ON</pattern><template>I learned some new tricks   Even faked my death a couple of times.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR NAME'S A PUN  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>Old man?</template></category><category><pattern>A PSYCHOLOGIST</pattern><template>Okay, I've had enough of this.</template></category><category><pattern>A'RIGHT</pattern><template>Art's gonna be along, too.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER TOLD HIM</pattern><template>This is fascinating.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE THEM CLOSURE</pattern><template>It's time, John.</template></category><category><pattern>WHETHER I BELIEVE IT OR NOT IS OF NO IMPORTANCE</pattern><template>We will die...</template></category><category><pattern>MY GOD</pattern><template>Wh What is this?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANTED TO TEACH WHAT I LEARNED</pattern><template>I never claimed to be king of the jews, I never walked on water, I never raised the dead.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AN INTERESTING IDEA</pattern><template>What, are you working on a science fiction story?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE THIS  MAYBE  HEH</pattern><template>What is that?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YEAH</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK PAUL WOULD AGREE</pattern><template>And then goethe was the first to suggest That spiral nebulae were swirling masses of stars.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  THE HIGH POINTS  THE LOW POINTS  TRAUMAS</pattern><template>They stick in the mind forever.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OBJECTIVE REFERENT OF CLOCK IS ANOTHER CLOCK</pattern><template>How very interesting. What has it got to do with John?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS PRETTY SURE THE EARTH WAS ROUND  BUT AT THAT POINT  I STILL THOUGHT HE MIGHT FALL OFF AN EDGE SOMEPLACE</pattern><template>look around, John.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME OF US ARE ANGRY NOW</pattern><template>This  This was a bad idea.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THERE WAS A GAS STATION AND A BIG FIELD</pattern><template>I was told I could never go there alone.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I WAS TEACHING AT HARVARD  I WAS JOHN THOMAS PARTEE</pattern><template>John T. Partee   Boston tea party   I get it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  WE STOPPED  FELL DOWN  DIDN'T GET UP  STARTED TO SMELL BAD  COME APART</pattern><template>Injuries we could understand   If someone's insides were all over the ground.</template></category><category><pattern>AND NOW YOU'RE MOVING ON</pattern><template>As you've said, there's talk of my not aging, And when that happens, I move on.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE TELLING US THIS  THE YARN OF THE CENTURY  AND YOU DON'T CARE IF WE BELIEVE IT OR NOT</pattern><template>I guess I shouldn't have expected you to.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY THOUGHT HE WAS DEAD</pattern><template>So his followers pulled him From the cross, placed him in a cave...</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE KNOWS HOW LONG THEY HAVE</pattern><template>Or how little.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT SAYING THAT YOU REMEMBER WHATEVER THE HELL IT WOULD BE  200 SEPARATE LIFETIMES  DYING AND BEING BORN AGAIN AND YADA YADA</pattern><template>One lifetime.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A PERSONAL THING</pattern><template>Well, not to pry.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  WELL  SOME MORE THAN OTHERS</pattern><template>From the Buddha to the cross, I have always imagined both as entirely mythic   But I would like to hear more.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF</pattern><template>Good kid.</template></category><category><pattern>OH HO HO  JOHNNY WALKER GREEN</pattern><template>know they made it in green.</template></category><category><pattern>IN WHAT I CALL MY FIRST LIFETIME  I AGED TO ABOUT 35</pattern><template>what you see.</template></category><category><pattern>VERY  I WOULD STAKE MY REPUTATION HE AS SANE AS I AM  SO WHY DOES HE PERSIST IN SUCH A STORY</pattern><template>There must be a reason, though.</template></category><category><pattern>A FEW THOUSAND YEARS   SEE  NOW  I KNOW YOU'RE GUESSING</pattern><template>You can't get there from here, Art.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHY  'CAUSE I WANNA SEE WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT</pattern><template>So do I. What is this all about?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE MONEY</pattern><template>What, you get into at&amp;t at 50 cents, John?</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>If you lived 100... 1,000 years...</template></category><category><pattern>AH  WELL  THIS LESSON MAY BE SOMETHING I COULD NOT HAVE IMAGINED</pattern><template>I regret being so obvious about this, John, But these people are all very concerned for you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S A BURIN</pattern><template>A burin is a flint tool For grooving wood and bone, antlers especially, To make spear and harpoon points.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S RIGHT  THEY WEREN'T THE FIRST  RIGHT</pattern><template>Edith, I was raised on the torah...</template></category><category><pattern>WE ANSWER SILLY QUESTIONS ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU PASSED  C+</pattern><template>Take care of yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU REALLY WANT TO DO THAT</pattern><template>Live 14,000 years?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  UH</pattern><template>uh, I was a Cro magnon, I think. You don't know if you're a caveman or not?</template></category><category><pattern>TEN DOCTORATES</pattern><template>That's impressive, John. Did you teach them?</template></category><category><pattern>AS A PHYSICIAN  I'M CURIOUS</pattern><template>In this enormous lifetime you describe, Have you ever been ill?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  A GUY WITH YOUR MIND   YOU'D HAVE STUDIED A GREAT DEAL</pattern><template>I have ten degrees, including all of yours...</template></category><category><pattern>IS HE DUCKING OUT ON US AGAIN</pattern><template>...I do have this.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO  I DON'T DRINK</pattern><template>gonna card you, darling.</template></category><category><pattern>MOSES</pattern><template>Moses was based on misis, a syrian myth, And there are earlier versions   All found floating on water, The staff that changed to a snake, Waters that were parted so followers Could be led to freedom And even receive laws On stone or wooden tablets.</template></category><category><pattern>PSYCH 101</pattern><template>No, it's woman, one on one.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY OF YOU KNOW FIVE GENIUSES IN YOUR FIELD THAT YOU DISAGREE WITH</pattern><template>one you would like to strangle?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT READY FOR IT</pattern><template>You're talking as if you believed him.</template></category><category><pattern>SUPERNATURAL</pattern><template>a stupid word, I mean...</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SEE YOUR WRISTS</pattern><template>I don't scar.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS</pattern><template>I'm outta here. You wanna come? Let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M VERY CURIOUS TO KNOW HIS FEELINGS</pattern><template>Would you prefer I asked him about his father?</template></category><category><pattern>READY</pattern><template>Later on.</template></category><category><pattern>UHN</pattern><template>My first wedding?</template></category><category><pattern>I FINALLY REALIZED THAT IT WAS</pattern><template>probably all hogwash, So I was sumerian for 2,000 years, Then finally babylonian under hammurabi.</template></category><category><pattern>I REGRET BEING SO OBVIOUS ABOUT THIS  JOHN  BUT THESE PEOPLE ARE ALL VERY CONCERNED FOR YOU</pattern><template>Yes, I'm cutting out paper dinosaurs.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT'S WHERE I FOUND IT</pattern><template>How can I have knowledgeable recall If I didn't have knowledge?</template></category><category><pattern>GEE  THANKS</pattern><template>Well, so are we.</template></category><category><pattern>WALLS HAVE EARS</pattern><template>Medical tests might be a way of proving what you say.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WE GO</pattern><template>Step on in here.</template></category><category><pattern>A LIE</pattern><template>Isn't that true, John?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID YOU JUST HAPPENED</pattern><template>I don't believe that.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T EVEN HAVE TO FIGHT FOR IT</pattern><template>Then fear came, and they chased me away.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT MOST OF IT RIGHT</pattern><template>Eventually I headed to the east.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  THANK YOU  NO</pattern><template>Whiskey? Johnny walker green.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I JUST HAPPENED</pattern><template>Wow.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULDN'T THAT IMPLY A PRIME MOVER</pattern><template>I'd wonder about the source of the prime mover, Infinite regress, but that doesn't imply anything to me.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD YOU LOVE ME  OR DON'T YOU BELIEVE IN THAT ANYMORE</pattern><template>I've gotten over it too many times.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  UH  MAY I</pattern><template>Preferable to a gun.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I HAVE KNOWLEDGEABLE RECALL IF I DIDN'T HAVE KNOWLEDGE</pattern><template>It's all retrospective.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK TO YOU</pattern><template>Wish you the best. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  COME ON  YOU KNOW WE WANNA HELP</pattern><template>That's appreciated, but really   There's no problem.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WEREN'T REALLY APOSTLES</pattern><template>They didn't do any real teaching.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE GOT</pattern><template>four men of science completely baffled, my friend.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOTTA GO DIGGING FOR THIS KIND OF STUFF</pattern><template>Can I, uh...?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO US</pattern><template>I was worried about you.</template></category><category><pattern>I THREW A CLEAN PASS</pattern><template>they ran it out of the ballpark.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIED  JOINED HIS FATHER ON OLYMPUS A THOUSAND YEARS BEFORE GETHSEMANE</pattern><template>How can you compare pagan mythology to the true word?</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST YOU'RE RELIEVED I'M NOT A NUT</pattern><template>I'd prefer you were!</template></category><category><pattern>ROME DOES IT AS GRAND OPERA</pattern><template>A simple path to goodness needs A supernatural roadmap.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  MOVING ON HAD BEEN EASIER AS A HUNTER GATHERER</pattern><template>difficult when villages emerged, Tougher still in city states where authority was centralized.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN HAVE YOU COMMITTED FOR OBSERVATION</pattern><template>You know that.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME KNOW HOW YOU'RE MAKING OUT</pattern><template>I will.</template></category><category><pattern>WILL</pattern><template>Come on, buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU IMAGINE HOW WE FEEL</pattern><template>I never thought of that.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU START THE WHISKEY BEFORE WE GOT HERE</pattern><template>Pretend it's science fiction.</template></category><category><pattern>MAGDALENIANS WEREN'T NOTED FOR FLINT WORK  SO THIS IS A VERY NICE SPECIMEN</pattern><template>Okay, what's a magdalenian?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GAVE ME THE BOOK ON EARLY MAN</pattern><template>Dan, you spotted the burin And you said,  if stones could speak.  I knew it.</template></category><category><pattern>THE REST IS HISTORY</pattern><template>Well, sort of. Lot of fairy tales mixed in.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M GONNA PUT IT IN THE BATHROOM  JOHN</pattern><template>Gas is off, electricity's on.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST  JUST NEEDED TO STOP</pattern><template>I shouldn't have expected it to work.</template></category><category><pattern>OBVIOUSLY  YOU HAVE SOMETHING YOU'D LIKE TO SAY  SAY IT</pattern><template>Well, maybe I...</template></category><category><pattern>THE FIRST 2 000 YEARS WERE COLD</pattern><template>We learned it was warmer at lower elevations.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE SHOULD REMAIN COURTEOUS TO SOMEONE WHO WE'VE KNOWN AND TRUSTED  EDITH</pattern><template>Here you sit  You can't break his story.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK OF DYING  JOHN</pattern><template>Do you fear death?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT NAILS AND BLOOD MAKE BETTER RELIGIOUS ART</pattern><template>speculations about Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>IT LOOKS LIKE A VAN GOGH  BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN IT BEFORE</pattern><template>Is that an original, John?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK THAT'S ALL RELIGION IS ABOUT</pattern><template>selling hope and survival?</template></category><category><pattern>EXCEPT ONE  JOHN</pattern><template>Why're you doing this?</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS HE CAN'T REMEMBER HIS FATHER</pattern><template>Precisely why?</template></category><category><pattern>PFFT  IF THIS WAS THE BEST I COULD DO  I'D BE HIDING  TOO</pattern><template>And creation...</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  THANK YOU  DEAR</pattern><template>Now that's changing.</template></category><category><pattern>IN INDIA  SACRED COWS WANDERED FREELY AS REINCARNATED SOULS</pattern><template>In a thousand years, they'll be barbecued And their souls will be in squirrels.</template></category><category><pattern>I PICKED IT UP WITH THE PERIODICALS</pattern><template>Got it.</template></category><category><pattern>A CRO MAGNON  THEN</pattern><template>When did you first realize this?</template></category><category><pattern>BY ALL MEANS  THIS IS GREAT</pattern><template>All right, now...</template></category><category><pattern>I'D LIKE THAT</pattern><template>On a planet of another star.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I KNOW SOME GUYS</pattern><template>You ever been to the ozarks?</template></category><category><pattern>AGING</pattern><template>the biggest mystery of all.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU USED TO TUG ON IT TO SEE IF IT WAS REAL</pattern><template>Agh! Will!</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN IT BE SACRILEGE</pattern><template>He hasn't said anything yet.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ALL A STORY</pattern><template>Good god!</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE PNEUMONIA ONCE OR TWICE</pattern><template>Last few hundred years, I've gotten over typhoid, yellow fever, Smallpox...I survived the black plague.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT DOES JESUS HAVE TO SAY TO THOSE PRESENT WHO FIND IT DIFFICULT TO BELIEVE IN HIM</pattern><template>Believe in what he tried to teach, Without rigmarole.</template></category><category><pattern>EDITH  I WAS RAISED ON THE TORAH</pattern><template>my wife, on the koran.</template></category><category><pattern>IN A WAY</pattern><template>Who?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW THE ROCK ART AT LES EYZIES</pattern><template>Mm hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY RELIGIOUS BELIEFS  OR DID YOU GIVE IT MUCH THOUGHT</pattern><template>You can't get there with thought.</template></category><category><pattern>I LEARNED SOME NEW TRICKS   EVEN FAKED MY DEATH A COUPLE OF TIMES</pattern><template>I continued east To india, Luckily at the time of the Buddha.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU SEE</pattern><template>I ended up leading my group.</template></category><category><pattern>911  NOW</pattern><template>Come on, Will.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A BEAUTIFUL IDEA  SO RICH  SO FULL OF POSSIBILITIES</pattern><template>Perhaps you should write a paper on it, doctor.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE BIBLE</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>CHARITY NOW  WE'RE HERE TO PICK UP THE FURNITURE</pattern><template>It's all yours.</template></category><category><pattern>SO    YOU'RE A CAVEMAN</pattern><template>Yes. Uh...</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME JUST SAY SOMETHING RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>There's absolutely no way in the whole world For John to prove this story to us, Just like there's no way for us to disprove it.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I SHOT YOU  JOHN   YOU'RE IMMORTAL</pattern><template>Would you survive this?</template></category><category><pattern>OOH  BOOKS</pattern><template>Doctorates.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS CHRIST</pattern><template>What the hell was that all about?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  FORGIVE ME  MY DEAR</pattern><template>You live simply.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE LOOKED FOR SIGNS  NONE</pattern><template>Could cavemen really talk?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU RELIGIOUS  JOHN</pattern><template>I don't follow a known religion. No.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY TEN YEARS OR SO  WHEN PEOPLE START TO NOTICE I DON'T AGE  I MOVE ON</pattern><template>That's very good, that's very quick, John.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF YOU WENT BACK THERE TODAY  WOULD IT BE THE SAME</pattern><template>No. I'm sure it's all different and built up.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DID A PRETTY GOOD JOB</pattern><template>He would draw the animals That we hoped to find to eat.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  WHAT WOULD HE BE LIKE</pattern><template>Well, I know some guys.</template></category><category><pattern>WE TALKED ABOUT CAPTURING NATURE IN ART</pattern><template>Turner, cezanne, pissarro.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU DON'T DROP THIS NOW   IF YOU CAN   I'LL BE CONVINCED THAT YOU NEED A GREAT DEAL OF ATTENTION</pattern><template>I can have you committed for observation.</template></category><category><pattern>BETTER TO SEE PREDATORS IN TALL GRASS  MY DEAR</pattern><template>Actually, tall and skinny Radiates heat more effectively in warmer climates.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  JOHN</pattern><template>I have a charade, and it is just for you.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU VERY MUCH  EDITH</pattern><template>Maybe when I'm 110, I'll be as smart as you are.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LORD  YOU WERE ONE OF THEM</pattern><template>This is going in a direction that I  I didn't expect.</template></category><category><pattern>A LITTLE  ONE THING HASN'T CHANGED MUCH</pattern><template>Did you ever do any cave Art?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I GOT IT  I GOT IT  I GOT IT</pattern><template>Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>LOST HIM IN THE CROWD</pattern><template>Oh, what a shame.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT MORE</pattern><template>By all means. This is great.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WOULD DRAW THE ANIMALS THAT WE HOPED TO FIND TO EAT</pattern><template>One day after a fruitless hunt, Our chief stomped his teeth out Because his magic had failed him.</template></category><category><pattern>MEDICAL TESTS MIGHT BE A WAY OF PROVING WHAT YOU SAY</pattern><template>I don't wanna prove it.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IF IT WAS TRUE  WHY ARE YOU TELLING US</pattern><template>I mean, we might leave here today, Go out there, tell everybody.</template></category><category><pattern>HE ATTEMPTED TO GO AWAY UNDETECTED  BUT SOME DEVOTEES WERE STANDING WATCH</pattern><template>Tried to explain.</template></category><category><pattern>NO MATTER HOW LONG A MAN LIVES  HE CAN'T BE IN ADVANCE OF HIS TIMES</pattern><template>He can't know more than the best of the race knows, If that  I mean, when the world learned it was round, You learned it.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S GOING TOO FAR</pattern><template>Bored, perhaps lonely, because your heart Cannot keep its treasures.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD WORKS IN MYSTERIOUS WAYS</pattern><template>I think I just happened.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  I WAS A CRO MAGNON  I THINK  YOU DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE A CAVEMAN OR NOT</pattern><template>No, I'm sure about that.</template></category><category><pattern>IN PREHISTORY  I CAN'T TELL YOU</pattern><template>Maybe pneumonia once or twice.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN  I SHOULD BE HOME  UH  KISSING MY WIFE</pattern><template>We're all here, trapped by your story...</template></category><category><pattern>CAN WE DO YOGA EXERCISES</pattern><template>Tantric yoga, we can.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE MUST BE A REASON  THOUGH</pattern><template>Unless I imagined it all?</template></category><category><pattern>WISH YOU THE BEST  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Ready?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I SAID ABOUT MYSELF HURT HIM</pattern><template>He struck back expertly   That stuff about stealing life forces?</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T</pattern><template>And one day I'll leave.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD GOD</pattern><template>Another fairy tale?</template></category><category><pattern>WE NOW CALL THEM GALAXIES</pattern><template>It's kind of funny how often new concepts of science Find their first tentative forms of expression in the arts.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  JOHN  HIT US WITH THE SHORT FORM</pattern><template>Guy met the Buddha, liked what he heard, Thought about it for a while   Say 500 years, while he returned To the Mediterranean, Became an etruscan.</template></category><category><pattern>I APOLOGIZE  HARRY</pattern><template>But why are you moving so quickly?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M SURE ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>A Cro magnon, then.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S APPRECIATED  BUT REALLY   THERE'S NO PROBLEM</pattern><template>Well, now I am curious.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NOTHING TO GET</pattern><template>What are we talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>STEP ON IN HERE</pattern><template>There ya go...</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON  YOU'RE PLAYING THE GOOD COP  DAN</pattern><template>That's fine. Just enjoy it.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN T  PARTEE   BOSTON TEA PARTY   I GET IT</pattern><template>Yeah, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD THERE BE OTHERS LIKE YOU WHO ESCAPED THE AGING PROCESS AS YOU HAVE</pattern><template>Representing something terrific We don't even know about biology.</template></category><category><pattern>WE KNOW SO LITTLE</pattern><template>How many of you know Five geniuses in your field That you disagree with...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  YOU GET INTO AT&amp;T AT 50 CENTS  JOHN</pattern><template>As one grows older, The days, weeks, months go by more quickly.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAD YOU ON THE ROPES  JOHN</pattern><template>Are you really so damn smart?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHAT CAN I DO ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Indeed.</template></category><category><pattern>SO DOES RELATIVITY  QUANTUM MECHANICS   THAT'S THE WAY NATURE WORKS</pattern><template>But your story doesn't fit into nature as we know it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S SAYING HE WAS CHRIST</pattern><template>Oh, no. That's the medal They pinned on Jesus to fulfill prophecy.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GIVING YOU ONE</pattern><template>Were you?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT IN VAN GOGH'S TIME</pattern><template>He would have loved them, though.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALWAYS BEEN A SMALL STEP FROM A FALLEN LEADER TO A GOD</pattern><template>I don't think anybody will deify kennedy.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ALL PRETTY CONVINCING  BUT WE COULDN'T BE SURE</pattern><template>We each confirmed what the other said, But how do we know if the confirmation Was genuine or an echo?</template></category><category><pattern>SOME LIFETIME</pattern><template>Wow.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  HELL  WHO KNOWS  HE MIGHT JOLT US INTO BELIEVING HIM  OR WE MIGHT JOLT HIM BACK TO REALITY</pattern><template>Believing? Whose reality?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE SAID YOU ABANDONED US</pattern><template>Sorry, I had to move on.</template></category><category><pattern>SANDY  COME HERE</pattern><template>Come on, come on, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>John, we're all sorry to see you go.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S SACRILEGE</pattern><template>How can it be sacrilege?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY WOMAN ON THE FACULTY WOULD GIVE ANYTHING TO HAVE THAT SECRET</pattern><template>Is that what they're after, Edith?</template></category><category><pattern>DAN  YOU SPOTTED THE BURIN AND YOU SAID   IF STONES COULD SPEAK   I KNEW IT</pattern><template>I got the notion, I ran it past you To check your reactions, and I took it too far.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  TAQUITOS  CHICKEN WINGS  ROASTIE TOASTIES AND BEER</pattern><template>If we'd had more time, We'd have done something a little more grandiose.</template></category><category><pattern>AS ONE GROWS OLDER  THE DAYS  WEEKS  MONTHS GO BY MORE QUICKLY</pattern><template>What does a day or a year Or a century mean to you?</template></category><category><pattern>BOSTON</pattern><template>60 years ago?</template></category><category><pattern>HE COULD DUCK DECAY</pattern><template>Mm, that's a secret we'd all love to have.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU STILL HAVE THIS</pattern><template>What would cause you to keep it?</template></category><category><pattern>LAST FEW HUNDRED YEARS  I'VE GOTTEN OVER TYPHOID  YELLOW FEVER  SMALLPOX   I SURVIVED THE BLACK PLAGUE</pattern><template>Bubonic?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS GOING IN A DIRECTION THAT I  I DIDN'T EXPECT</pattern><template>I hoped it wouldn't   We...call it a night.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM WHAT I AM BECOMING   THAT'S WHAT THE BUDDHA BROUGHT IN</pattern><template>And that's what I taught.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES PRE MED NEED WITH HISTORY</pattern><template>Got it.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER MIND</pattern><template>I won't ask.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT FOR ME</pattern><template>Oh, no, I don't drink.</template></category><category><pattern>WE  WE DON'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF YOU</pattern><template>Did you know voltaire was the first to suggest That the universe was created by a gigantic explosion?</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT MAN</pattern><template>And I sailed as a phoenician for a time.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  YOU TOO</pattern><template>Or are you a vampire, John?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE YOU GOING  JOHN  LIKE WE GIVE A DAMN</pattern><template>We've already covered that.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT AS CRAZY AS YOU THINK I AM</pattern><template>Amen.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW OFTEN DO WE GET TO MEET SOMEONE WHO SAYS HE'S A STONE AGE MAN</pattern><template>Well, once is enough.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU EVER WISHED IT WOULD END</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SAVIOR   THE GREEK  SOTER  THE GOOD SHEPHERD  THE PRINCE OF PEACE  BRINGING GENTLE PERSUASION AND DIVINE WISDOM</pattern><template>He died, joined his father on olympus A thousand years before gethsemane.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  COME ON  SOMETHING HAD TO BE DONE</pattern><template>I have to say I agree.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I'M SORRY   WE ARE DOWN TO PLASTIC CUPS NOW</pattern><template>That's a sacrilege I'll tolerate.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU LAUGHING AT US INSIDE</pattern><template>I wish you didn't feel that way.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL RETROSPECTIVE</pattern><template>All I can do is integrate my recollections With modern findings.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE TEN YEARS</pattern><template>Ah! Ha ha ha!</template></category><category><pattern>ROME WON</pattern><template>The rest is history.</template></category><category><pattern>MOST EXTRAORDINARY MAN I'VE EVER KNOWN</pattern><template>He taught me things I'd never thought about before.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN DIDN'T ASK TO BE WHAT HE IS</pattern><template>And we did not ask to hear about it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE EXTENDED OUR LIFESPAN IN A WORLD THAT'S  UH</pattern><template>not fit to live in.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Yes. No, no. No, no.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IT MIGHT MAKE SENSE TO SET UP YOUR NEXT IDENTITY  YOUR NEXT TEN YEARS  AND THEN JUST DROP INTO IT</pattern><template>I've done that a few times, Even passed as my own son.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT MARY</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I can see how this might have hit you.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAW ME AS MAGICAL</pattern><template>I didn't even have to fight for it.</template></category><category><pattern>BIBLICAL JESUS SAID   WHO DO YOU THINK I AM   HE GAVE THEM A CHOICE</pattern><template>I'm giving you one.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT WHAT I HAD IN MIND</pattern><template>But that's vatican flapdoodle.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU</pattern><template>Could you love me, Or don't you believe in that anymore?</template></category><category><pattern>STRANGERS WERE SUSPECT</pattern><template>It seemed as though I was always moving on.</template></category><category><pattern>MORE REVELATIONS FOR US</pattern><template>It's just like old times.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE I'M TOO SAD TO CRY</pattern><template>What I said about myself hurt him.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BAD ENOUGH WE HAVE TO LISTEN TO HARRY'S IDIOTIC JOKES</pattern><template>Thank you very much, Edith.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A SADIST  JOHN  BUT I ADMIT I GOT A KICK OUT OF CHASING MY TAIL AROUND YOUR MAYPOLE</pattern><template>even if that is all I caught.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  IT'S GETTING CHILLY</pattern><template>Here, come over here. Join me.</template></category><category><pattern>MY DAUGHTER IS STUDYING HINDUISM</pattern><template>I imagine that there is room there for a holy war in my living room, But we practice live and let live.</template></category><category><pattern>CONTEMPORANEOUS  I THINK  MAY I TAKE A CLOSER LOOK</pattern><template>Please, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE FAITH IN THE FUTURE OF THE RACE</pattern><template>I've seen species come and go.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THERE'S WRITING ON THE BACK IN FRENCH</pattern><template>Oh,  To my friend Jacque Borne.  Wonder who that was?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO MOVE</pattern><template>Oh, you   You've talked a good deal About your extraordinary amount of living.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I DO  I'LL SEND YOU COPIES</pattern><template>Don't bother with mine, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT NOT ME</pattern><template>Oh, forgive me, my dear.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  WE MIGHT LEAVE HERE TODAY  GO OUT THERE  TELL EVERYBODY</pattern><template>It would vanish in disbelief.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID HE WAS INCLINED WITH THE SAME RESERVATION</pattern><template>Now, that's interesting.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU'RE RIGHT</pattern><template>Where did you live when you were five years old?</template></category><category><pattern>THE OLD TESTAMENT SELLS FEAR AND GUILT</pattern><template>The new testament is a good code of ethics, Put into my mouth by poets and philosophers That are much smarter than I am.</template></category><category><pattern>SMOOTH DEMONSTRATION  HARRY</pattern><template>Sit on it, Dan.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID SOME TEACHING ON A HILL ONE DAY</pattern><template>Not that many people stayed.</template></category><category><pattern>DOCTORATES</pattern><template>Yes, you have grown and changed.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT'S MOSTLY BASED ON STUDY</pattern><template>Remember, it's one man, one place at a time, My solitary viewpoint Of a world I knew almost nothing about.</template></category><category><pattern>IS GEORGE TAKING OVER FOR YOU</pattern><template>George or Trimbell   Has the Dean made up his mind?</template></category><category><pattern>GOD</pattern><template>911, now!</template></category><category><pattern>GEOGRAPHY HASN'T CHANGED</pattern><template>I learned that in   Professor hensen's tepid lectures.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS  UH  JACQUE BOURNE AT THE TIME  A PIG FARMER</pattern><template>A pig farmer?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  LET'S GO ON WITH IT</pattern><template>It's interesting.</template></category><category><pattern>HARRY  WILL YOU TAKE ME HOME</pattern><template>No, not right now. I do want to hear this.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY  IT WAS THE 1600S  AND I MET A MAN  AND I HAD A HUNCH THAT HE WAS</pattern><template>like me, so I told him.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HASN'T SAID ANYTHING YET</pattern><template>The new new testament is sacrilege.</template></category><category><pattern>A BIBLICAL FIGURE</pattern><template>In a way.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE HEGEL   LOGIC FROM ABSURD PREMISES</pattern><template>That Van Gogh?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  JOHN  YOU DON'T LOOK A DAY OVER 900</pattern><template>Okay, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>IS ART AS TOUGH AS I HEAR</pattern><template>Oh, archaeology's tough.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURE YOU MUST HAVE MORE TO SAY</pattern><template>Would you like me to lie on the couch?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETHING ABOUT THIS</pattern><template>something about you, John.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  COME ON</pattern><template>Come on, spit it out!</template></category><category><pattern>WOULDN'T YOU BE MORE COMFORTABLE SQUATTING IN THE BACKYARD</pattern><template>Sometimes I do, will.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU DIDN'T CLAIM TO BE THE SON OF GOD</pattern><template>Began as a schoolhouse and ended as a temple.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE LIFETIME</pattern><template>Some lifetime.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER DIED</pattern><template>Yes. What would he be like?</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  TALL AND SKINNY RADIATES HEAT MORE EFFECTIVELY IN WARMER CLIMATES</pattern><template>And as for neanderthals, I mean, we've all seen apish people.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT'S THE SAME STRETCHER AS VAN GOGH USED</pattern><template>Yeah, there's writing on the back in french.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE HAD THE PRACTICAL CONCEPT</pattern><template>You know, we stopped, Fell down, didn't get up, Started to smell bad, come apart.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN GOETHE WAS THE FIRST TO SUGGEST THAT SPIRAL NEBULAE WERE SWIRLING MASSES OF STARS</pattern><template>We now call them galaxies.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS BODY NORMALIZED AS HE HAD TRAINED IT TO</pattern><template>he attempted to go away undetected, But some devotees were standing watch.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO MORE WORDS</pattern><template>I'm gonna go home, And I'm gonna watch star trek For a dose of sanity.</template></category><category><pattern>BACK TO THE MYSTERY</pattern><template>It's a very old question, But there's no answer except in religious terms.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA READ THAT STORY WHEN YOU'RE DONE</pattern><template>You want more?</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU THOUGHT THAT PERHAPS YOU WERE</pattern><template>Perhaps you are!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEVER SAW A GROWN CHILD DIE</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER THOUGHT OF THAT</pattern><template>Since you may not die, While we most assuredly will...</template></category><category><pattern>I STILL HAVE QUESTIONS</pattern><template>I I do too, John.</template></category><category><pattern>A WHIM  MAYBE NOT SUCH A GOOD IDEA</pattern><template>I...</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW IT</pattern><template>He's saying he was Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT AT THIS LATE DATE</pattern><template>There must be someone   Probably many   That you valued intensely.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULDN'T SACRE DU PRINTEMPS BE MORE APPROPRIATE  WHAT</pattern><template>You've got...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURE YOU'LL MAKE SOME ANTHROPOLOGICAL BONERS</pattern><template>It's a deal.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE PEOPLE ARE VERY UPSET</pattern><template>I don't believe you're mad, But what you're saying is not true.</template></category><category><pattern>ON A PLANET OF ANOTHER STAR</pattern><template>I envy you.</template></category><category><pattern>HARRY  STOP</pattern><template>There is something I'm tempted to tell you, I think.</template></category><category><pattern>MODERN IS GOOD</pattern><template>All right, John, hit us with the short form.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU DO IN YOUR SPARE TIME</pattern><template>Every 50 years or so, When I wanna get away from the rush, I go down to a primitive tribe in new guinea Where I'm worshipped as an immortal god, And they have a huge statue of me.</template></category><category><pattern>INJURIES  ILLNESS  DISASTERS</pattern><template>You've survived them all.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO  THAT'S THE MEDAL THEY PINNED ON JESUS TO FULFILL PROPHECY</pattern><template>The crucifixion.</template></category><category><pattern>UM  THREE BLOCKS</pattern><template>Were there any references That stuck in your mind?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THUS THE LOST YEARS OF JESUS</pattern><template>He didn't exist until John put on a hat.</template></category><category><pattern>NO MATTER HOW OUTRAGEOUS WE THINK IT IS  NO MATTER HOW HIGHLY TRAINED SOME OF US THINK WE ARE  THERE'S ABSOLUTELY NO WAY TO DISPROVE IT</pattern><template>Our friend is either a caveman, a liar, or a nut.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HE  HE MIGHT BE A MAN WHO LIVES OUTSIDE OF TIME AS WE KNOW IT</pattern><template>Yes, uh, well.</template></category><category><pattern>MOST PEOPLE CAN'T BAG A DEER WITH A RIFLE AND A TELESCOPIC SIGHT</pattern><template>Though, good eatin'.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT THAT MANY PEOPLE STAYED</pattern><template>But you...</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU HUNGRY</pattern><template>Uh, thank you, no.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE ALWAYS LIKED YOU</pattern><template>Why, thank you, dear.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN  WE'RE TEACHERS</pattern><template>We answer silly questions all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>WE JUST DID</pattern><template>I suppose there's a joke in there somewhere, But I don't get it.</template></category><category><pattern>CALL IT CABIN FEVER</pattern><template>After a while, I get itchy feet.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU</pattern><template>Take whatever you can get.</template></category><category><pattern>THINK ABOUT IT   A MECHANISM ALLOWING SURVIVAL FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS</pattern><template>Run out of room even faster.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE AMONG FRIENDS</pattern><template>Snoopy friends.</template></category><category><pattern>MISS</pattern><template>You never saw a grown child die.</template></category><category><pattern>I SHOULDN'T HAVE EXPECTED IT TO WORK</pattern><template>Fourteen thousand years old.</template></category><category><pattern>SOLOMON  ELVIS  JACK THE RIPPER</pattern><template>It's been said that Buddha and Jesus Would laugh or cry if they'd known What was done in their name.</template></category><category><pattern>I CARE VERY MUCH ABOUT YOU  BUT NOW YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'D BE GETTING INTO</pattern><template>Do you really think you're a caveman?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M IN YOUR TUESDAY PSYCH 1 CLASS  DR  GRUBER</pattern><template>Ah, well, this lesson may be something I could not have imagined.</template></category><category><pattern>I SUPPOSE THERE'S A JOKE IN THERE SOMEWHERE  BUT I DON'T GET IT</pattern><template>There's nothing to get.</template></category><category><pattern>CERTAINLY ATTRACTED TO YOU</pattern><template>That's it?</template></category><category><pattern>QUOTE THE SERMON ON THE MOUNT</pattern><template>Which one?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW THEM ALL</pattern><template>No one knows the one, not even me.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HASN'T CALLED</pattern><template>My god!</template></category><category><pattern>ANYONE GOT A GOOD TOPIC</pattern><template>Like this, maybe? Heh.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU'RE SAYING   IT OFFENDS COMMON SENSE</pattern><template>So does relativity, quantum mechanics   That's the way nature works.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T LIKE GOOD BYES</pattern><template>Kind of the point of a goodbye party, John.</template></category><category><pattern>FORGET IT</pattern><template>You are creating the mystery here.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN IF I COULD MAKE YOU BELIEVE ME  IN A MONTH  YOU WOULDN'T</pattern><template>Some of you would call me a psychopath, Others would be angry at a pointless joke.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WOULD LOOK UP AT THE SKY AND WONDER</pattern><template>There's gotta be some big guys up there.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE WHATEVER YOU CAN GET</pattern><template>Like ten years?</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY  HE SAID YES  BUT FROM ANOTHER TIME  ANOTHER PLACE</pattern><template>We talked for two days.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE</pattern><template>Well, you're finally fulfilling One prophecy about the millennium, John.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE YA GO</pattern><template>one for the birthday boy   Excuse me. Art?</template></category><category><pattern>LIVES NATURALLY  EATS NATURALLY</pattern><template>Well, it's beautiful.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A 14 000 YEAR OLD CAVEMAN</pattern><template>I  I  I drove for a while, And then I sat for a while.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOLD US OF YOURSELF  JOHN</pattern><template>Can you imagine how we feel?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY BELIEVE YOU BECAUSE THEY HAVE TO</pattern><template>But the one thing that I know about you Is that you would never use people Or abuse their goodwill and intelligence Like they think you've just done to them.</template></category><category><pattern>IT DOESN'T HAVE A THING TO DO WITH GOD</pattern><template>As you said, John, everywhere, religions...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT  YEAH  IT'S POSSIBLE</pattern><template>Anything is possible, right?</template></category><category><pattern>SOME OF YOU WOULD CALL ME A PSYCHOPATH  OTHERS WOULD BE ANGRY AT A POINTLESS JOKE</pattern><template>Some of us are angry now.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S INTERESTING</pattern><template>Besides, I think he's making a certain amount of sense.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WE'D HAVE TO GO TO MARS AS A COLONY AS WE EXPANDED  AS WE'D HAVE TO</pattern><template>I'd like that.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER A WHILE  I GET ITCHY FEET</pattern><template>I've done this before.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER CLAIMED TO BE KING OF THE JEWS  I NEVER WALKED ON WATER  I NEVER RAISED THE DEAD</pattern><template>I never spoke of divine except in the sense Of human goodness on earth.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT A TALKING SNAKE MAKE A LADY EAT AN APPLE  SO WE'RE SCREWED</pattern><template>Heaven and hell were peddled So priests could rule through seduction and terror, Save our souls that we never lost in the first place.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  COME INSIDE</pattern><template>I still don't believe you, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HUNTED REINDEER  MAMMOTHS   BISON  HORSES  THE GAME RETREATED NORTHWARD AS THE CLIMATE CHANGED  YOU GOT THE IDEA OF GROWING FOOD RATHER THAN GATHERING IT  RAISING ANIMALS RATHER THAN HUNTING THEM</pattern><template>Am  Am I getting warm, here?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW YOU'RE TALKING AS IF YOU BELIEVED HIM</pattern><template>Well, look at the popular myths surrounding The Kennedy assassination in a few short years   You had, uh, conspiracy, Mafia, CIA   That's a mystique that'll never go away.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BEST WILD GAME</pattern><template>Lives naturally, eats naturally.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU REALLY SO DAMN SMART</pattern><template>It's not like will.</template></category><category><pattern>I SEE YOUR POINT  JOHN</pattern><template>No matter how long a man lives, He can't be in advance of his times.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST AS WE CAN NEVER BE SURE  EVEN IF WE WANTED TO   I MEAN  IF WE WERE SURE  YOU COULDN'T BE SURE OF THAT</pattern><template>We parted, agreeing to keep in touch   Of course, we didn't   And 200 years later I thought I saw him In a train station in brussels.</template></category><category><pattern>MY GOD  WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS</pattern><template>Let me see your wrists.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR MOTHER'S NAME WAS NOLA</pattern><template>No. Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS BLACK  HE WAS ASIAN  HE WAS A BLUE EYED ARYAN WITH A GOLDEN BEARD AND HAIR STRAIGHT OUT OF VIDAL SASSOON'S  HE WAS A BENEVOLENT ALIEN  HE NEVER EXISTED AT ALL</pattern><template>Now he's a caveman.</template></category><category><pattern>REPRESENTING SOMETHING TERRIFIC WE DON'T EVEN KNOW ABOUT BIOLOGY</pattern><template>We're learning all the time.</template></category><category><pattern>OR HOW LITTLE</pattern><template>I love you.</template></category><category><pattern>AS YOU SAID  JOHN  EVERYWHERE  RELIGIONS</pattern><template>from exalting life to purging joy as a sin.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT DID PRIMITIVE MAN MAKE OF THEM</pattern><template>A great mystery.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THAT  I LEFT ENOUGH</pattern><template>I left enough. I'm cold.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  WILL</pattern><template>Will.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  JOHN</pattern><template>Let me get this straight.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS BEFORE THEY WERE SEPARATED FROM THE CONTINENT BY RISING SEAS  AS GLACIERS MELTED</pattern><template>That happened?</template></category><category><pattern>ONE OF THE APOSTLES</pattern><template>They weren't really apostles.</template></category><category><pattern>I FORGOT</pattern><template>A crack in your story, John?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ALL RIGHT  I TRIED</pattern><template>Well, uh, call me underdeveloped, But I'd like to hear more.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCEPT THAT AS A RULE  WE'VE GROWN TALLER</pattern><template>What's the selective advantage of height?</template></category><category><pattern>MM HMM</pattern><template>Mmm.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU MEAN  SURVIVED</pattern><template>Never died?</template></category><category><pattern>WE PARTED  AGREEING TO KEEP IN TOUCH   OF COURSE  WE DIDN'T   AND 200 YEARS LATER I THOUGHT I SAW HIM IN A TRAIN STATION IN BRUSSELS</pattern><template>Lost him in the crowd.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE YOU GO</pattern><template>Very good, and I bet at least one of us Is your direct descendent.</template></category><category><pattern>I CALLED MYSELF JOHN</pattern><template>I almost always do.</template></category><category><pattern>I SENSE   SPACE</pattern><template>A kinda latitude of what we happily call reality, In which, as everybody keeps saying...</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  THE HUMAN BODY APPEARS DESIGNED TO LIVE ABOUT 190 YEARS</pattern><template>Most of us just die of slow poisoning.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T THINK THAT I WOULD BETRAY YOU</pattern><template>Walls have ears.</template></category><category><pattern>WOW</pattern><template>Hello?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN SCARCELY REMEMBER MINE</pattern><template>Do you feel a vacancy In your life about that, John, Something you wish could be filled By a face, a voice, an image?</template></category><category><pattern>I GUESS    A MEDICINE MAN</pattern><template>I was a shaman a few times.</template></category><category><pattern>'CAUSE I WANTED TO SAY GOODBYE   AS YOURSELF</pattern><template>I think you've done that, Whoever that self is.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A SUBJECTIVE SENSE OF BECOMING WHAT WE ARE INSTEAD OF WHAT WE WERE A NANOSECOND AGO  BECOMING WHAT WE WILL BE IN ANOTHER NANOSECOND</pattern><template>The hopis see time as a landscape, Existing before and behind us, And we move   We move through it, Slice by slice.</template></category><category><pattern>GRUBER  SHE REMARRIED</pattern><template>She said you abandoned us.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NO WONDER HE FAILED</pattern><template>We're not ready for it.</template></category><category><pattern>MY MEMORY SEES WHAT I SAW THEN</pattern><template>My eye sees freeways, urban sprawl, Big macs under the eiffel tower.</template></category><category><pattern>THINK WHAT I'VE HAD TO UNLEARN</pattern><template>And now you're moving on.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE YOURS  SELECTIVE</pattern><template>You know, the high points, the low points, traumas.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  BUDDY</pattern><template>You'll stay in touch, Dr. Oldman.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D PREFER YOU WERE</pattern><template>You gave me the idea.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BIRTH DEATH CYCLE</pattern><template>Turbulence.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL THAT WAS ALL ABOUT</pattern><template>I don't like good byes.</template></category><category><pattern>I ALMOST WISH IT WERE TRUE</pattern><template>Yeah, if it was true, why are you telling us?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU HUNT</pattern><template>Deer, mostly.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  PLEASE CONTINUE</pattern><template>I'm sure you must have more to say.</template></category><category><pattern>RIPPLES IN A WHEAT FIELD  BLOWN BY THE WIND</pattern><template>Do you ever get tired of it all?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE ONE THING THAT I KNOW ABOUT YOU IS THAT YOU WOULD NEVER USE PEOPLE OR ABUSE THEIR GOODWILL AND INTELLIGENCE LIKE THEY THINK YOU'VE JUST DONE TO THEM</pattern><template>Psych 101?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS BLASPHEMY</pattern><template>It's horrible! Who else were you?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S  UH  TALKING TO A STUDENT  PFFT</pattern><template>Is George taking over for you?</template></category><category><pattern>WOOFIE</pattern><template>Woof, woof, woofie...</template></category><category><pattern>THEY GOT OLD AND THEY DIED  ANIMALS  TOO</pattern><template>but not me.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SPENT MOST OF HIS TIME LYING ON THE FLOOR IN FRONT OF HIS LEGLESS PIANO SURROUNDED BY ORANGE PEELS AND APPLE CORES</pattern><template>Now we're on the floor listening to beethoven.</template></category><category><pattern>CHRISTIANITY HAS BEEN A WORLDWIDE BELIEF FOR 2 000 YEARS</pattern><template>How long did the egyptians worship isis Or the sumerians ishtar?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  WHAT'S A MAGDALENIAN</pattern><template>A later Cro magnon, Without gettin' technical.</template></category><category><pattern>HELPS ME TO FEEL SECURE</pattern><template>There are predators out there.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN'T SEE IT  WE CAN'T HEAR IT  WE CAN'T WEIGH IT  WE CAN'T MEASURE IT IN A LABORATORY</pattern><template>It's a subjective sense of becoming What we are instead of what we were a nanosecond ago, Becoming what we will be in another nanosecond.</template></category><category><pattern>FROM EXALTING LIFE TO PURGING JOY AS A SIN</pattern><template>Rome does it as grand opera.</template></category><category><pattern>JOHN</pattern><template>I'm glad I caught you.</template></category><category><pattern>SINCE YOU MAY NOT DIE  WHILE WE MOST ASSUREDLY WILL</pattern><template>there must be a reason for that, no?</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN ART  HE JUST HATES THINGS HE CAN'T UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>You're a sadist, John, But I admit I got a kick out of Chasing my tail around your maypole...</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  NOW WE'RE DONE WITH THAT  WHAT DO WE DO FOR THE REST OF THE AFTERNOON</pattern><template>Anyone got a good topic?</template></category></AIML>