<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>I MEAN  NOBODY COULD LIFT IT</pattern><template>They said it was radioactive.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE VERY WELCOME</pattern><template>AGENT: Base to Team 2, we've got activity outside the town. Stay on your target. Ensure my brother does not return.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN BRING YOUR URGENT MATTER TO ME</pattern><template>Your king.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: HOW'D YOU GET INSIDE THAT CLOUD</pattern><template>DARCY: Also, how could you eat an entire box of Pop Tarts and still be this hungry?</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT4: TARGET SIGHTED  EAST TUNNEL</pattern><template>I need eyes up high, with a gun.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE MY SON</pattern><template>I wanted only to protect you from the truth.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  I KNOW THAT LOOK</pattern><template>That's the only way to ensure the safety of our borders.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS ISN'T LIKE A JOURNEY TO EARTH WHERE YOU SUMMON A LITTLE LIGHTNING AND THUNDER  AND THE MORTALS WORSHIP YOU AS A GOD</pattern><template>This is Jotunheim.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO FALL BACK  COME ON</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I COME FROM A PLACE WHERE THEY'RE ONE AND THE SAME THING</pattern><template>What is that?</template></category><category><pattern>CALL IT IN</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>SURE</pattern><template>COULSON: Wait, I need to debrief you!</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: HE'S FINE  LOOK AT HIM</pattern><template>Heimdall! I know you can hear me!</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK</pattern><template>What the hell was that?</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU THINK THAT YOU CAN DECEIVE ME</pattern><template>(LAUGHS) You must be mistaken...</template></category><category><pattern>MORE OR LESS</pattern><template>It's a good look.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOOD AT THAT</pattern><template>Don't go anywhere.</template></category><category><pattern>LOKI  WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE</pattern><template>I had to see you.</template></category><category><pattern>FANDRAL: IS THAT ANOTHER WAY OF SAYING YOU FELL ON YOUR HUGE ASS</pattern><template>VOLSTAGG: As a matter of fact, falling was a tactic lulling the Destroyer...</template></category><category><pattern>(HONKING)   HEY  YOU STILL NEED A LIFT</pattern><template>I've never done anything like this before.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: WELL  THIS  BOY  HAS GROWN TIRED OF YOUR MOCKERY</pattern><template>Thor, stop and think.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A TRUCE WITH LAUFEY  KING OF THE JOTUNS</pattern><template>He just broke your truce!</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL  OPEN THE BIFROST</pattern><template>Heimdall?</template></category><category><pattern>BARTON  TALK TO ME</pattern><template>You want me to slow him down, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>I SUSPECT THAT THE ASGARDIANS WOULD NOT TAKE KINDLY TO A KING WHO HAD MURDERED HIS PREDECESSOR</pattern><template>Once Odin is dead, I will return the Casket to you and you can return Jotunheim to all its...</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT 2: LEVELS INCREASE</pattern><template>Whosoever holds this hammer, if he be worthy, shall possess the power of Thor.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD HAVE KILLED THEM ALL WITH YOUR BARE HANDS</pattern><template>I've changed.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>If you destroy the bridge, you'll never see her again!</template></category><category><pattern>JANE  THIS IS A LOT MORE SERIOUS THAN YOU REALIZE  LET IT GO</pattern><template>Let it go? This is my life.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HURTFUL</pattern><template>In my experience, it takes someone who's received similar training to do what you did to them.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHY HAVE YOU COME HERE</pattern><template>To make peace?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE BEEN VERY KIND TO ME  AND I'VE BEEN FAR LESS GRATEFUL THAN YOU DESERVE</pattern><template>Well, I hit you with my car a couple times, so I think that kind of evens things out.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR'S GOING TO FIGHT WITH US</pattern><template>My friends, I'm just a man. I'll only be in the way, or worse, get one of you killed.</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL DEMANDS YOUR PRESENCE</pattern><template>VOLSTAGG: We're doomed.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALL KNOW WHAT WE HAVE TO DO</pattern><template>We must go.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD HAVE TOLD ME WHAT I WAS FROM THE BEGINNING  WHY DIDN'T YOU</pattern><template>You're my son.</template></category><category><pattern>S H I E L D  SHOWED UP AND HE WASN'T HEARD FROM AGAIN</pattern><template>They're not gonna do that to us.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME  IS IT JOTUNHEIM</pattern><template>Let me explain to Father.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME EXPLAIN TO FATHER</pattern><template>Father is dead.</template></category><category><pattern>I MUST GO BACK TO ASGARD  BUT I GIVE YOU MY WORD  I WILL RETURN FOR YOU</pattern><template>Deal?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  SORRY I TASED YOU</pattern><template>Excuse me, excuse me!</template></category><category><pattern>HE MAY SPEAK OF THE GOOD OF ASGARD  BUT HE'S ALWAYS BEEN JEALOUS OF THOR</pattern><template>We should be grateful to him, he saved our lives.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE CHANGED</pattern><template>So have I.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUY NEVER TELLS ME ANYTHING</pattern><template>Hello. You are using unregistered weapons technology. Identify yourself. Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>I</pattern><template>Accept.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THIS</pattern><template>If it's any consolation, I think you're right.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T SEE WHAT I SAW</pattern><template>DARCY: (GASPS) Look!</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE AFTERMATH OF THE BATTLE  I WENT INTO THE TEMPLE AND I FOUND A BABY</pattern><template>Small for a giant's offspring. Abandoned, suffering, left to die. Laufey's son. Laufey's son.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>Can we go outside?</template></category><category><pattern>DARCY  DO YOU HAVE THE S H I E L D</pattern><template>satellite codes?</template></category><category><pattern>SIF: FALL BACK</pattern><template>Go. Now. Run!</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT 3: NEGATIVE  NEGATIVE</pattern><template>I have no comms.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LONG FOR BATTLE  YOU CRAVE IT</pattern><template>You're nothing but a boy trying to prove himself a man.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  BROTHER</pattern><template>FROST GIANT: Run back home, little princess.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS NAME IS DONALD BLAKE</pattern><template>Dr. Donald Blake.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN WE ARE STRANDED</pattern><template>Heimdall!</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS YOUR SENSES HAVE WEAKENED AFTER YOUR MANY YEARS OF SERVICE</pattern><template>Or perhaps someone has found a way to hide that which he does not wish me to see.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A LOT TO WORK WITH</pattern><template>The Foster Theory.</template></category><category><pattern>IN TIME</pattern><template>What's this?</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: IT'S GONE</pattern><template>And then, with a mighty bellow, I flew into the giant metal creature and laid him low!</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOUR RELATIONSHIP TO HIM</pattern><template>I've never met him before.</template></category><category><pattern>NEITHER DID I</pattern><template>My father was trying to teach me something, but I was too stupid to see it.</template></category><category><pattern>BASE  WE'VE GOT XENA  JACKIE CHAN AND ROBIN HOOD</pattern><template>It's a beautiful theory, Jane.</template></category><category><pattern>GO</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN  ON THIS DAY  I  ODIN ALL FATHER  PROCLAIM YOU</pattern><template>The Frost Giants!</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT'S WHERE I COME FROM  THANK YOU  JANE</pattern><template>FANDRAL: Our dearest friend banished, Loki on the throne, Asgard on the brink of war, yet you've managed to consume four wild boar, six pheasant, a side of beef, and two casks of ale. Shame on you.</template></category><category><pattern>DARCY: THEY EVEN TOOK MY IPOD</pattern><template>ERIK: What about the backups?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD STRANGE OR BAD STRANGE</pattern><template>I'm not quite sure yet.</template></category><category><pattern>MY QUEEN  I'M SO SORRY FOR YOUR LOSS</pattern><template>FRIGGA: How Is he? SIF: He mourns for his brother. And... He misses her. The mortal. You'll be a wise king.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR ANCESTORS CALLED IT MAGIC  AND YOU CALL IT SCIENCE</pattern><template>Well, I come from a place where they're one and the same thing.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DESTROYER DID ITS WORK  THE CASKET IS SAFE  AND ALL IS WELL</pattern><template>All is well?</template></category><category><pattern>KNOW YOUR PLACE  BROTHER</pattern><template>You know not what your actions would unleash.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME  YOU MUST NOT GIVE UP</pattern><template>You must finish what you've started.</template></category><category><pattern>CERTAIN GROUPS PAY VERY WELL FOR A GOOD MERCENARY LIKE YOU</pattern><template>Who are you?</template></category><category><pattern>THE TRUCE WITH JOTUNHEIM IS CONDITIONAL UPON YOUR EXILE</pattern><template>Yes, but couldn't we find a way...</template></category><category><pattern>BY  APPROPRIATE   DO YOU MEAN STEAL</pattern><template>Here, this should more than compensate you for your trouble.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I CAN HELP GET THESE PEOPLE TO SAFETY</pattern><template>Well, if you're staying, then so am I.</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHOULD BE GRATEFUL TO HIM  HE SAVED OUR LIVES</pattern><template>Laufey said there were traitors in the House of Odin.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I AM NO MORE THAN ANOTHER STOLEN RELIC  LOCKED UP HERE UNTIL YOU MIGHT HAVE USE OF ME</pattern><template>Why do you twist my words?</template></category><category><pattern>LOKI</pattern><template>You saved him!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  BUT COULDN'T WE FIND A WAY</pattern><template>And Mother has forbidden your return.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS THINKING THEY'RE TAKING ME DOWN HERE TO KILL ME</pattern><template>I've been hearing about the New Mexico situation.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WILL BE TRUE HEIR TO THE THRONE</pattern><template>You can't kill an entire race!</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY  I NEVER HAVE GUESTS</pattern><template>That's not the right place for it.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST CARE ABOUT HER</pattern><template>I've seen the way she looks at you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE OUR SON  LOKI  AND WE  YOUR FAMILY</pattern><template>We mustn't lose hope that your father will return to us.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: WHY DID YOU BRING US BACK</pattern><template>ODIN: Do you realize what you've done?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S OVER</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL  I KNOW YOU CAN HEAR ME</pattern><template>Open the Bifrost!</template></category><category><pattern>STORIES WILL BE TOLD OF THIS DAY</pattern><template>Live, and tell those stories yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN 2: YOU MISSED ALL THE EXCITEMENT OUT AT THE CRATER</pattern><template>MAN 1: They're saying some kind of satellite landed out in the desert.</template></category><category><pattern>DONALD</pattern><template>I don't think you've been completely honest with me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LEAVE THIS TO ME</pattern><template>Good Heimdall...</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  DOES HE NEED CPR</pattern><template>Because I totally know CPR.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  THIS IS THE STAR ALIGNMENT FOR OUR QUADRANT THIS TIME OF YEAR  AND UNLESS URSA MINOR DECIDED TO TAKE A DAY OFF  THESE ARE SOMEONE ELSE'S CONSTELLATIONS</pattern><template>Hey! Check this out.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  LOOK WHAT'S DOWN THERE</pattern><template>You think you're just gonna walk in, grab our stuff and walk out?</template></category><category><pattern>STOLEN</pattern><template>Borrowed.</template></category><category><pattern>TO PROVE TO FATHER THAT I AM THE WORTHY SON</pattern><template>When he wakes, I will have saved his life.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DRANK  WE FOUGHT  HE MADE HIS ANCESTORS PROUD</pattern><template>Put him on the bed.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO WITHOUT DEFYING FATHER</pattern><template>No, no, no. I know that look.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FATHER IS A MURDERER AND A THIEF</pattern><template>And why have you come here?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL FATHER</pattern><template>You look weary.</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL MIGHT BE WATCHING</pattern><template>Heimdall demands your presence.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  SO YOU OWN A SATELLITE NOW</pattern><template>It's not what they say it is.</template></category><category><pattern>MMM HMM</pattern><template>COULSON: You made my men, some of the most highly trained professionals in the world, look like a bunch of minimum wage mall cops.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN WE GO OUTSIDE</pattern><template>Yes, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE HAS REFUSED TO LEAVE MY FATHER'S BEDSIDE</pattern><template>You can bring your urgent matter to me.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  DON'T THANK ME  I ONLY DID IT FOR JANE</pattern><template>Her father and I taught at university together.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL HAVE IT</pattern><template>Okay, move it, people!</template></category><category><pattern>LEAVE MY BROTHER TO ME</pattern><template>LAUFEY: It's said you can still hear and see what transpires around you.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOU JUST INTEND TO GO IN THERE AND TAKE IT</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S GOT A VISITOR</pattern><template>His name is Donald Blake?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE INVESTIGATING A SECURITY THREAT</pattern><template>We need to appropriate your records and all your atmospheric data.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAVED OUR LIVES</pattern><template>And Thor's.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DARE THREATEN ME  THOR  WITH SO PUNY A WEAPON</pattern><template>What? He was freaking me out!</template></category><category><pattern>THEN GIVE ME ONE OF THOSE LARGE ENOUGH TO RIDE</pattern><template>(HONKING)   Hey, you still need a lift?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  HE WAS FREAKING ME OUT</pattern><template>Next time you decide to taser somebody, make sure he's already in the car, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM NOT DYING FOR SIX COLLEGE CREDITS</pattern><template>DARCY: I think that was legally your fault.</template></category><category><pattern>MORE LIKE A RAINBOW BRIDGE</pattern><template>God, I hope you're not crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL HONOR MY SWORN OATH TO PROTECT THIS REALM AS ITS GATEKEEPER</pattern><template>If your return threatens the safety of Asgard, Bifrost will remain closed to you and you'll be left to die in the cold waste of Jotunheim.</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH TO KNOW HOW THAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>Then tell no one where we have gone until we've returned.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I HAD IT ALL BACKWARDS</pattern><template>I had it all wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT THE CRATER  I'M TALKING ABOUT HIM</pattern><template>But he's promising us the answers.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT TIME WITH AN ARMY</pattern><template>Exactly.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST TAKING A LITTLE BLOOD</pattern><template>How dare you attack the son of Odin?</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK  LOOK  WHAT DO YOU SEE</pattern><template>Stars.</template></category><category><pattern>VOLSTAGG: WE'RE DOOMED</pattern><template>You would defy the commands of Loki, our king, break every oath you have taken as warriors, and commit treason to bring Thor back?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT IS THIS NEWFOUND LOVE FOR THE FROST GIANTS</pattern><template>You could have killed them all with your bare hands.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I TURN ON THE RADIO</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>WELCOME TO ASGARD</pattern><template>Heimdall, open the Bifrost.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  BUT I CAN'T TAKE YOU</pattern><template>Then this is where we say goodbye.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH WAY</pattern><template>Fifty miles west of here.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: SORRY  IZZY  LITTLE ACCIDENT</pattern><template>What was that?</template></category><category><pattern>ODIN: ONCE  MANKIND ACCEPTED A SIMPLE TRUTH  THAT THEY WERE NOT ALONE IN THIS UNIVERSE  SOME WORLDS MAN BELIEVED TO BE HOME TO THEIR GODS  OTHERS  THEY KNEW TO FEAR  FROM A REALM OF COLD AND DARKNESS CAME THE FROST GIANTS  THREATENING TO PLUNGE THE MORTAL WORLD INTO A NEW ICE AGE  BUT HUMANITY WOULD NOT FACE THIS THREAT ALONE  OUR ARMIES DROVE THE FROST GIANTS BACK INTO THE HEART OF THEIR OWN WORLD  THE COST WAS GREAT  IN THE END  THEIR KING FELL  AND THE SOURCE OF THEIR POWER WAS TAKEN FROM THEM  WITH THE LAST GREAT WAR ENDED  WE WITHDREW FROM THE OTHER WORLDS AND RETURNED HOME TO THE REALM ETERNAL  ASGARD  HERE WE REMAIN AS A BEACON OF HOPE  SHINING OUT ACROSS THE STARS  AND THOUGH WE HAVE FALLEN INTO MAN'S MYTHS AND LEGENDS  IT WAS ASGARD AND ITS WARRIORS THAT BROUGHT PEACE TO THE UNIVERSE</pattern><template>But the day will come when one of you will have to defend that peace.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE MUCH TO LEARN</pattern><template>I know that now.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO SEE YOU</pattern><template>What's happened?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST DOGS  CATS  BIRDS</pattern><template>Then give me one of those large enough to ride.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ASGARD</pattern><template>And that's where I come from. Thank you, Jane.</template></category><category><pattern>I TRIED TO TELL HIM SO  BUT HE WOULDN'T LISTEN</pattern><template>It was so cruel to put the hammer within your reach, knowing that you could never lift it.</template></category><category><pattern>MY EX</pattern><template>Good with patients and bad with relationships.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FRIENDS  I'VE NEVER BEEN HAPPIER TO SEE ANYONE</pattern><template>But you should not have come.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I WANT TO KNOW WHY</pattern><template>I have a truce with Laufey, King of the Jotuns.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANTED TO SHOW YOU HOW SILLY HIS STORY WAS</pattern><template>But you're the one who's always pushing me to chase down every possibility, every alternative!</template></category><category><pattern>BREAK THEIR SPIRITS SO THEY'LL NEVER DARE TRY TO CROSS OUR BORDERS AGAIN</pattern><template>You're thinking only as a warrior.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN 1: THE USUAL  PLEASE  IZZY</pattern><template>MAN 2: You missed all the excitement out at the crater.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT YOU'RE CLEVER</pattern><template>Far more clever than anyone else in this realm.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S QUITE A LABYRINTH</pattern><template>I was thinking they're taking me down here to kill me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HOUSE OF ODIN IS FULL OF TRAITORS</pattern><template>Do not dishonor my father's name with your lies!</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IS WHAT WE'D ALL BE IF THAT GUARD HADN'T TOLD ODIN WHERE WE'D GONE</pattern><template>How did the guard even know?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN HEARING ABOUT THE NEW MEXICO SITUATION</pattern><template>Your work has impressed a lot of people who are much smarter than I am.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DO YOU TWIST MY WORDS</pattern><template>You could have told me what I was from the beginning, why didn't you?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THESE ARE THE ACTIONS OF A BOY  TREAT THEM AS SUCH</pattern><template>You and I can end this here and now, before there's further bloodshed.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I HIT YOU WITH MY CAR A COUPLE TIMES  SO I THINK THAT KIND OF EVENS THINGS OUT</pattern><template>Perhaps I had it coming.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S MOVE</pattern><template>Where are they?</template></category><category><pattern>FRIGGA: HE'S PUT IT OFF FOR SO LONG NOW  THAT I FEAR</pattern><template>How long will it last?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT EVERY NOW AND THEN  WE FIND SOMETHING THAT BELONGS TO BOTH</pattern><template>What is it?</template></category><category><pattern>NURSE: NAME</pattern><template>He said it was Thor?</template></category><category><pattern>(LAUGHS) YOU MUST BE MISTAKEN</pattern><template>THOR: Enough!</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL: SHE SEARCHES FOR YOU  NICK FURY: DR  SELVIG</pattern><template>So you're the man behind all this?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE MY WORD</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK ME STRANGE</pattern><template>Yeah, I do.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN 2: YEAH</pattern><template>Oh, my God. This is going on Facebook.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>There is always hope.</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT 2: ENTERING SOUTH TUNNEL</pattern><template>AGENT 3: Negative, negative.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE ONLY WAY TO ENSURE THE SAFETY OF OUR BORDERS</pattern><template>Thor, it's madness.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID EXACTLY WHAT YOU TOLD ME NOT TO</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU OUGHT TO BE</pattern><template>Are these your chambers?</template></category><category><pattern>I ONLY EVER WANTED TO BE YOUR EQUAL</pattern><template>I will not fight you, Brother!</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY ONE OF YOU CAN ASCEND TO THE THRONE</pattern><template>But both of you were born to be kings.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Lady Sif and the Warriors Three.</template></category><category><pattern>OH</pattern><template>It was!</template></category><category><pattern>TO HELL WITH TREASON  IT'S SUICIDE</pattern><template>Thor would do the same for us.</template></category><category><pattern>FAREWELL</pattern><template>Goodbye.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST FINISH WHAT YOU'VE STARTED</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT DISHONOR MY FATHER'S NAME WITH YOUR LIES</pattern><template>Your father is a murderer and a thief!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID</pattern><template>Yes!</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHY IS THAT</pattern><template>Because he is my king and I am sworn to obey him.</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN THE BIFROST</pattern><template>JANE: Hospital. You go, I'll stay.</template></category><category><pattern>BRING ABOUT AN ALLIANCE  BRING ABOUT PERMANENT PEACE</pattern><template>Through you.</template></category><category><pattern>SOUTHWEST AIRLINES  FLIGHT 5434</pattern><template>Reroute it like all the others.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE UNWORTHY OF THESE REALMS</pattern><template>You're unworthy of your title!</template></category><category><pattern>HE SWITCHED CAREERS AND BECAME A PHYSICIST</pattern><template>A brilliant physicist.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WELCOME</pattern><template>THOR: This mortal form has grown weak.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU DESTROY THE BRIDGE  YOU'LL NEVER SEE HER AGAIN</pattern><template>Forgive me, Jane.</template></category><category><pattern>FIFTY MILES WEST OF HERE</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE EXTREMELY THOROUGH</pattern><template>I just downloaded, like, 30 songs onto there.</template></category><category><pattern>SYSTEMS ARE BARELY COPING</pattern><template>Barton? Talk to me.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEDAY  PERHAPS  I SHALL MAKE YOU PROUD</pattern><template>You've already made me proud.</template></category><category><pattern>SATELLITE CODES</pattern><template>DARCY: Yeah. Have you seen my taser?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS</pattern><template>We have to move quickly before this all changes.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW WHAT DO WE DO</pattern><template>Look!</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE BEYOND DIPLOMACY NOW  ALL FATHER</pattern><template>He'll get what he came for.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME CONTACT ONE OF MY COLLEAGUES</pattern><template>He's had some dealings with these people before.</template></category><category><pattern>HI</pattern><template>Just taking a little blood.</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL SHE HIT HIM WITH A CAR</pattern><template>I grazed him, but she tasered him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER THEY ARE  THEY'RE GONNA DO EVERYTHING IN THEIR POWER TO MAKE SURE THIS RESEARCH NEVER SEES THE LIGHT OF DAY</pattern><template>No, Jane.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S NOT OVER</pattern><template>I mean, you're safe.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS</pattern><template>Oh.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Base, we've got Xena, Jackie Chan and Robin Hood.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE</pattern><template>No, don't thank me. I only did it for Jane.</template></category><category><pattern>BROTHER  PLEASE</pattern><template>Enough!</template></category><category><pattern>I DID</pattern><template>True, but I supported you, Sif.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN 2: YEAH  WE WERE HAVING A GOOD TIME WITH IT UNTIL THE FEDS SHOWED UP</pattern><template>JANE: Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M GOING TO FLY OUT</pattern><template>TECHNICIAN: Sir, feed from the keyhole can barely penetrate the cloud cover.</template></category><category><pattern>FANDRAL: OUR DEAREST FRIEND BANISHED  LOKI ON THE THRONE  ASGARD ON THE BRINK OF WAR  YET YOU'VE MANAGED TO CONSUME FOUR WILD BOAR  SIX PHEASANT  A SIDE OF BEEF  AND TWO CASKS OF ALE  SHAME ON YOU</pattern><template>Don't you care?</template></category><category><pattern>(ODIN SHOUTS) THOR ODINSON  YOU HAVE BETRAYED THE EXPRESS COMMAND OF YOUR KING</pattern><template>Through your arrogance and stupidity, you've opened these peaceful realms and innocent lives to the horror and desolation of war!</template></category><category><pattern>THOR WOULD DO THE SAME FOR US</pattern><template>Now shush.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HOPE IS THERE FOR THOR</pattern><template>There's always a purpose to everything your father does.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  WELL  NO MORE SMASHING</pattern><template>Deal?</template></category><category><pattern>COULSON: WAIT  I WANT TO SEE THIS  ALL RIGHT  SHOW'S OVER</pattern><template>Ground units, move in.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A BEAUTIFUL THEORY  JANE</pattern><template>But you won't be able to convince the scientific community of any of it.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  PLEASE</pattern><template>Thor Odinson, my heir, my firstborn.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL ACCEPT YOUR MOST GRACIOUS OFFER</pattern><template>Come on. Brother.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD HAVE WORDS WITH MY BROTHER</pattern><template>COULSON: Excuse me!</template></category><category><pattern>MYEU MUH  WHAT'S MYEU MUH</pattern><template>Can I have a word, Jane?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL SEE SOON ENOUGH</pattern><template>You promised me answers.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A GOOD LOOK</pattern><template>We must go to the Bifrost site.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME MORE</pattern><template>So, the Nine Realms.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE UNPREPARED</pattern><template>So why did he lie?</template></category><category><pattern>LET IT GO  THIS IS MY LIFE</pattern><template>We're investigating a security threat.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ALL I COULD GET BACK</pattern><template>I'm sorry it's not as much as I promised.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS THAT</pattern><template>It was delicious. I want another.</template></category><category><pattern>VOLSTAGG: COULDN'T YOU JUST LEAVE THE BRIDGE OPEN FOR US</pattern><template>HEIMDALL: To leave the bridge open would unleash the full power of the Bifrost and destroy Jotunheim with you upon it.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE</pattern><template>Where did he come from?</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT</pattern><template>At least make it a challenge for me!</template></category><category><pattern>POLITICAL SCIENCE</pattern><template>She was the only applicant.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW I CAN'T GO HOME</pattern><template>My father is dead because of me.</template></category><category><pattern>DARCY: I THINK THAT WAS LEGALLY YOUR FAULT</pattern><template>JANE: Get the first aid kit.</template></category><category><pattern>HUBBLE</pattern><template>Hubble Telescope.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU FOR COMING HERE</pattern><template>Farewell.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK THE BIFROST IS THE ONLY WAY IN AND OUT OF THIS REALM</pattern><template>There are secret paths between the worlds to which even you, with all your gifts, are blind.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FRIENDS  HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN ALL THAT WE HAVE DONE TOGETHER</pattern><template>Fandral, Hogun.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BIFROST WILL BUILD UNTIL IT RIPS JOTUNHEIM APART</pattern><template>Jane?</template></category><category><pattern>ODIN: DO YOU REALIZE WHAT YOU'VE DONE</pattern><template>What you've started?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU'VE STARTED</pattern><template>THOR: I was protecting my home.</template></category><category><pattern>T H O R</pattern><template>And your relationship to him?</template></category><category><pattern>EXACTLY</pattern><template>JANE: What?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I MEAN  ASK NICELY</pattern><template>I meant no disrespect.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE WE GOING</pattern><template>To get a drink.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN  WITH A MIGHTY BELLOW  I FLEW INTO THE GIANT METAL CREATURE AND LAID HIM LOW</pattern><template>FANDRAL: Is that another way of saying you fell on your huge ass?</template></category><category><pattern>THROUGH YOU</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>JANE  WE HAVE TO TAKE HIM TO THE HOSPITAL</pattern><template>Father!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAVE WE GOT</pattern><template>There's a massive electromagnetic surge coming off that thing.</template></category><category><pattern>LAST CHANCE  SIR</pattern><template>COULSON: Wait. I want to see this. All right, show's over.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WE'RE GONNA LOOK ALL OVER NEW MEXICO  RIGHT</pattern><template>Exactly.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD NO IDEA FATHER WOULD BANISH HIM FOR WHAT HE DID</pattern><template>Loki.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>Because you're right.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: THE JOTUNS MUST PAY FOR WHAT THEY'VE DONE</pattern><template>They have paid, with their lives.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT WITHOUT HARD EVIDENCE</pattern><template>Found you!</template></category><category><pattern>AND EVERYTHING I KNOW ABOUT THIS PHENOMENON IS EITHER IN THIS LAB OR IN THIS BOOK</pattern><template>And you can't just take this away... Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED A HORSE</pattern><template>We don't have horses.</template></category><category><pattern>AS KING OF ASGARD</pattern><template>But you're not king!</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK: OH  DONNY  DONNY  DONNY</pattern><template>There you are. You're gonna be all right.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT SATELLITES  BUT IT WAS HEAVY</pattern><template>I mean, nobody could lift it.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL HEAR YOU</pattern><template>I will conceal you and a handful of your soldiers, lead you into Odin's chambers, and you can slay him where he lies.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT TO CONTINUE YOUR RESEARCH</pattern><template>Would you like to see the bridge we spoke of?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT QUITE SURE YET</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT TIME YOU DECIDE TO TASER SOMEBODY  MAKE SURE HE'S ALREADY IN THE CAR  OKAY</pattern><template>Jane! Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>I TURNED MY GAZE UPON YOU IN JOTUNHEIM  BUT COULD NEITHER SEE YOU NOR HEAR YOU</pattern><template>You were shrouded from me, like the Frost Giants that entered this realm.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON HERE</pattern><template>Ms. Foster, I'm Agent Coulson with S.H.I.E.L.D.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN THIS IS WHERE WE SAY GOODBYE</pattern><template>Um...</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  THEN YOU WILL WAIT FOR MY WORD</pattern><template>If I may beg the indulgence of Your Majesty to perhaps reconsider...</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL CONCEAL YOU AND A HANDFUL OF YOUR SOLDIERS  LEAD YOU INTO ODIN'S CHAMBERS  AND YOU CAN SLAY HIM WHERE HE LIES</pattern><template>Why not kill him yourself?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF YOU'RE STAYING  THEN SO AM I</pattern><template>We'll need some time.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'LL GET WHAT HE CAME FOR</pattern><template>War and death.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR ODINSON  MY HEIR  MY FIRSTBORN</pattern><template>So long entrusted with the mighty hammer Mjolnir, forged in the heart of a dying star, its power has no equal, as a weapon to destroy or as a tool to build.</template></category><category><pattern>MOM</pattern><template>Is there a Renaissance Fair in town?</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHOULD NEVER HAVE LET HIM GO</pattern><template>There was no stopping him.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID IT WAS THOR</pattern><template>T H O R.</template></category><category><pattern>TO GET A DRINK</pattern><template>Follow them.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO</pattern><template>I'm staying here.</template></category><category><pattern>AND TO PROTECT THE REALM FROM HIS IDIOTIC RULE FOR A WHILE LONGER</pattern><template>I will hear you.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WILL NEVER BE A WISER KING THAN YOU</pattern><template>Or a better father.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS GOOD  THIS IS GOOD</pattern><template>I don't believe it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME WHERE YOU RECEIVED YOUR TRAINING</pattern><template>Pakistan? Chechnya? Afghanistan?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAID IT WAS RADIOACTIVE</pattern><template>I had my hands all over it.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST LOST MY MOST IMPORTANT PIECE OF EVIDENCE</pattern><template>Typical.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK YOU WANT TO SEE THIS</pattern><template>JANE: What is that?</template></category><category><pattern>I GRAZED HIM  BUT SHE TASERED HIM</pattern><template>Yes, I did.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOING TO NEED THIS</pattern><template>What? Wait, why?</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU SEE WHAT HE DID IN THERE</pattern><template>I'm not sure finding him is the best idea.</template></category><category><pattern>COULSON: DR  SELVIG</pattern><template>Just keep him away from the bars.</template></category><category><pattern>UM</pattern><template>Thank you?</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD HIM</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT MASSIVE ENERGY READINGS OUT OF NOWHERE AND THEN THEY JUST DISAPPEARED</pattern><template>Fifteen miles due northwest.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME  I HAVE TO DESTROY JOTUNHEIM</pattern><template>LOKI: You can't stop it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S DANGEROUS  JANE</pattern><template>I'm sorry, but I can't take you.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT WE COULD UNITE OUR KINGDOMS ONE DAY</pattern><template>Bring about an alliance, bring about permanent peace.</template></category><category><pattern>IF IT'S ANY CONSOLATION  I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT</pattern><template>About the Frost Giants, about Laufey, about everything.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE IT'S TRUE  SO THAT YOU MAY KNOW YOUR DEATH CAME AT THE HAND OF LAUFEY</pattern><template>And your death came by the son of Odin.</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL: TO LEAVE THE BRIDGE OPEN WOULD UNLEASH THE FULL POWER OF THE BIFROST AND DESTROY JOTUNHEIM WITH YOU UPON IT</pattern><template>I have no plans to die today.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M STAYING HERE</pattern><template>Thor's going to fight with us!</template></category><category><pattern>I WANTED ONLY TO PROTECT YOU FROM THE TRUTH</pattern><template>Because I'm the monster parents tell their children about at night?</template></category><category><pattern>HIDING  AS COWARDS ALWAYS DO</pattern><template>LAUFEY: You've come a long way to die, Asgardians.</template></category><category><pattern>FROST GIANT: RUN BACK HOME  LITTLE PRINCESS</pattern><template>Damn.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT THE RIGHT PLACE FOR IT</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THAT</pattern><template>My father explained it to me like this, that your world is one of the Nine Realms of the Cosmos, linked to each other by the branches of Yggdrasil, the Worlds Tree.</template></category><category><pattern>BROTHER  WHATEVER I HAVE DONE TO WRONG YOU  WHATEVER I HAVE DONE TO LEAD YOU TO DO THIS  I AM TRULY SORRY</pattern><template>But these people are innocent. Taking their lives will gain you nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>HER FATHER AND I TAUGHT AT UNIVERSITY TOGETHER</pattern><template>He was a good man.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD A SEC</pattern><template>We've got something outside the fence, west side.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HEAR ME  BROTHER</pattern><template>There's nothing you can do!</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT THE FROST GIANTS  ABOUT LAUFEY  ABOUT EVERYTHING</pattern><template>If they found a way to penetrate Asgard's defenses once, who's to say they won't try again?</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: ENOUGH</pattern><template>Heimdall, may we pass?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE THE ONLY CLOTHES I HAD THAT WOULD FIT YOU</pattern><template>They will suffice.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU TAKE ME THERE NOW  I'LL TELL YOU EVERYTHING YOU WISH TO KNOW</pattern><template>Everything?</template></category><category><pattern>ALFHEIM  NORNHEIM</pattern><template>New Mexico?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY HAVE PAID  WITH THEIR LIVES</pattern><template>The Destroyer did its work, the Casket is safe, and all is well.</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN THE BRIDGE</pattern><template>Father! We'll finish them together!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE KNEE DEEP IN JOTUN BLOOD  WHY WOULD YOU TAKE ME</pattern><template>You were an innocent child.</template></category><category><pattern>DO THE FROST GIANTS STILL LIVE</pattern><template>When I'm king, I'll hunt the monsters down and slay them all!</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT</pattern><template>What's he doing?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THAT NOW</pattern><template>Someday, perhaps, I shall make you proud.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: THAT'S NO SATELLITE CRASH</pattern><template>They would have hauled the wreckage away, they wouldn't have built a city around it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NO MATCH FOR THE MIGHTY</pattern><template>Huh.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE FOSTER  ERIK SELVIG  DARCY  FAREWELL</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME  LOKI  HOW DID YOU GET THE JOTUNS INTO ASGARD</pattern><template>You think the Bifrost is the only way in and out of this realm?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE SHROUDED FROM ME  LIKE THE FROST GIANTS THAT ENTERED THIS REALM</pattern><template>Perhaps your senses have weakened after your many years of service.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT ONE OF STARK'S</pattern><template>I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>FOLLOW THEM</pattern><template>You know, I had it all backwards.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT IT  I GOT IT</pattern><template>MAN: Come on, kick it in now!</template></category><category><pattern>AND THOR'S</pattern><template>I had no idea Father would banish him for what he did.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT POSSIBLE</pattern><template>He was on drugs or something.</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS A FIT COMPANION FOR A KING</pattern><template>I have defended Asgard and the lives of the innocent across the Nine Realms from the time of the great beginning. Though the day has come... Do you swear to guard the Nine Realms?</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  THIS SHOULD MORE THAN COMPENSATE YOU FOR YOUR TROUBLE</pattern><template>I can't just buy replacements at Radio Shack, I made most of this equipment myself!</template></category><category><pattern>YEARS OF RESEARCH  GONE</pattern><template>DARCY: They even took my iPod.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DIDN'T</pattern><template>Well, I want to know why!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE'S PROMISING US THE ANSWERS</pattern><template>He's delusional.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE WAY OR ANOTHER  WE FIND OUT WHAT WE NEED TO KNOW</pattern><template>We're good at that.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU'RE NOT KING</pattern><template>Not yet.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THE FROST GIANTS HAD STOLEN EVEN ONE OF THESE RELICS</pattern><template>They didn't.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I SAY  FOR YOUR ACT OF TREASON  YOU ARE RELIEVED OF YOUR DUTIES AS GATEKEEPER  AND NO LONGER CITIZEN OF ASGARD</pattern><template>Then I need no longer obey you.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  I HOPE YOU'RE NOT CRAZY</pattern><template>LOKI: (SOFTLY) I never get used to seeing him like this.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT FOR IT</pattern><template>Can I turn on the radio?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S UNPRECEDENTED</pattern><template>Isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE  I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT I'M SUPPOSED TO DO</pattern><template>Anyone who's ever going to find his way in this world has to start by admitting he doesn't know where the hell he is.</template></category><category><pattern>DR  DONALD BLAKE</pattern><template>You have dangerous coworkers, Dr. Selvig.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT</pattern><template>Come on. What happened to you on Earth that turned you so soft?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY KNOW YOU ARE VULNERABLE</pattern><template>What action would you take?</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE NAME OF MY FATHER AND HIS FATHER BEFORE  I  ODIN ALL FATHER  CAST YOU OUT</pattern><template>Whosoever holds this hammer, if he be worthy, shall possess the power of Thor.</template></category><category><pattern>WAR AND DEATH</pattern><template>So be it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S DELUSIONAL</pattern><template>Listen to what he's saying.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT CAN'T BE</pattern><template>I think I left something at the hospital.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T REALLY HAVE MUCH LEFT TO LOSE</pattern><template>Yeah, but you're clever.</template></category><category><pattern>LOKI  NO</pattern><template>No!</template></category><category><pattern>NEW MEXICO</pattern><template>You dare threaten me, Thor, with so puny a weapon?</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: I'M TELLING YOU  THERE'S A CONNECTION BETWEEN THESE ATMOSPHERIC DISTURBANCES AND MY RESEARCH</pattern><template>Erik, I wouldn't have asked you to fly out here if I wasn't absolutely sure.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I DO</pattern><template>Good strange or bad strange?</template></category><category><pattern>FORGIVE ME  JANE</pattern><template>I could have done it, Father!</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL E MAIL HIM AND MAYBE HE CAN HELP</pattern><template>They took your laptop, too.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW THIS SCIENTIST</pattern><template>The pioneer in gamma radiation.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID IT LOOK LIKE  THE SATELLITE</pattern><template>I don't know anything about satellites, but it was heavy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU TELL HER HOW YOU SENT THE DESTROYER TO KILL OUR FRIENDS  TO KILL ME</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>IF THEY FOUND A WAY TO PENETRATE ASGARD'S DEFENSES ONCE  WHO'S TO SAY THEY WON'T TRY AGAIN</pattern><template>Next time with an army.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR BANISHMENT  THE THREAT OF A NEW WAR  IT WAS TOO MUCH FOR HIM TO BEAR</pattern><template>You mustn't blame yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>MANY TIMES</pattern><template>But you're brave to do it.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  CHECK THIS OUT</pattern><template>No, it can't be.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST MAKE IT A CHALLENGE FOR ME</pattern><template>That's more like it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHO PROVED WRONG ALL WHO SCOFFED AT THE IDEA THAT A YOUNG MAIDEN COULD BE ONE OF THE FIERCEST WARRIORS THIS REALM HAS EVER KNOWN</pattern><template>I did.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  IF THERE IS AN EINSTEIN ROSEN BRIDGE  THEN THERE'S SOMETHING ON THE OTHER SIDE</pattern><template>And advanced beings could have crossed it!</template></category><category><pattern>HE SHOULD BE FLOGGED FOR TAKING SO LONG</pattern><template>We should never have reached Jotunheim.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'LL HELP US</pattern><template>I am bound by honor to our king.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  MS  FOSTER  BUT WE'RE THE GOOD GUYS</pattern><template>So are we!</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU SAY THERE WAS A SATELLITE CRASH</pattern><template>MAN 2: Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>LOKI: (SOFTLY) I NEVER GET USED TO SEEING HIM LIKE THIS</pattern><template>FRIGGA: He's put it off for so long now, that I fear...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  LOKI</pattern><template>Loki, no.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THERE A RENAISSANCE FAIR IN TOWN</pattern><template>Call it in.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE SECRET PATHS BETWEEN THE WORLDS TO WHICH EVEN YOU  WITH ALL YOUR GIFTS  ARE BLIND</pattern><template>But I have need of them no longer, now that I am king.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TELL ME IT WAS THAT WOMAN</pattern><template>Oh!</template></category><category><pattern>I KNEW YOU'D RETURN TO US</pattern><template>Why don't you tell her how you sent the Destroyer to kill our friends, to kill me?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN TELL NO ONE WHERE WE HAVE GONE UNTIL WE'VE RETURNED</pattern><template>Understand?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE YOU'RE RIGHT</pattern><template>Here, look.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE HE IS MY KING AND I AM SWORN TO OBEY HIM</pattern><template>He was your king and you're sworn to obey me now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A TALENTED LIAR  BROTHER</pattern><template>Always have been.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BUT NOT OUR STARS</pattern><template>See, this is the star alignment for our quadrant this time of year, and unless Ursa Minor decided to take a day off, these are someone else's constellations.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM SORRY</pattern><template>Thank you for coming here.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD</pattern><template>I don't believe it!</template></category><category><pattern>IF WE CAN FIGURE OUT HOW TO TAP IT  MAYBE UNLIMITED POWER</pattern><template>Well, I guess that's worth a look.</template></category><category><pattern>WEST SIDE PERIMETER  GO CHECK IT OUT  THERE IT IS</pattern><template>Delancey, Jackson. Report.</template></category><category><pattern>LAUFEY SAID THERE WERE TRAITORS IN THE HOUSE OF ODIN</pattern><template>A master of magic could bring three Jotuns into Asgard.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>Why, it must have been enforcing Father's last command.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE DANGEROUS COWORKERS  DR  SELVIG</pattern><template>He was distraught when he found out that you've taken all our research.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS ALFHEIM</pattern><template>Vanaheim. Jotunheim.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE  COME ON</pattern><template>NURSE: Name?</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU ARE AN OLD MAN AND A FOOL</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  WAIT  WHY</pattern><template>Now stay here.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DARE YOU ATTACK THE SON OF ODIN</pattern><template>MALE NURSE: I need some help!</template></category><category><pattern>JANE  YOU HAVE TO LEAVE</pattern><template>What are you gonna do?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THAT YOU LOVED HIM</pattern><template>I tried to tell him so, but he wouldn't listen.</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE ODIN IS DEAD  I WILL RETURN THE CASKET TO YOU AND YOU CAN RETURN JOTUNHEIM TO ALL ITS</pattern><template>Glory.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE DONE</pattern><template>I need a horse!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  THIS IS GREAT  THIS IS</pattern><template>I don't have to start from scratch now.</template></category><category><pattern>HE KEPT THE TRUTH FROM YOU SO THAT YOU WOULD NEVER FEEL DIFFERENT</pattern><template>You are our son, Loki, and we, your family.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST DID</pattern><template>No, I mean, ask nicely.</template></category><category><pattern>SO NOW WHAT</pattern><template>We find him.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE THE MAN BEHIND ALL THIS</pattern><template>It's quite a labyrinth.</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK: WHAT ABOUT THE BACKUPS</pattern><template>JANE: They took our backups.</template></category><category><pattern>GUARDS</pattern><template>Guards, please, help!</template></category><category><pattern>WE MUST GO</pattern><template>We must find Thor.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE UNWORTHY OF YOUR TITLE</pattern><template>You're unworthy of the loved ones you have betrayed.</template></category><category><pattern>SO TAKE MINE AND END THIS</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: HOSPITAL  YOU GO  I'LL STAY</pattern><template>You. What realm is this?</template></category><category><pattern>I AM BOUND BY HONOR TO OUR KING</pattern><template>I cannot open the bridge to you.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER WAS</pattern><template>Loki, this is madness.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE</pattern><template>I knew this scientist.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY NOT</pattern><template>And what is this newfound love for the Frost Giants?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>The guy never tells me anything.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW YOU SEE IT EVERY DAY WITHOUT REALIZING</pattern><template>The images glimpsed through...</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'D YOU FIND THIS</pattern><template>ERIK: The children's section.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE A VAIN  GREEDY  CRUEL BOY</pattern><template>And you are an old man and a fool!</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: THIS MORTAL FORM HAS GROWN WEAK</pattern><template>I need sustenance.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD  THIS IS GOING ON FACEBOOK</pattern><template>Smile.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE'VE GOT A COMMERCIAL AIRCRAFT COMING RIGHT OVER US</pattern><template>Southwest Airlines, flight 5434.</template></category><category><pattern>DO ME A FAVOR AND DON'T BE DEAD</pattern><template>Whoa. Does he need CPR?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL OF US MUST STAND TOGETHER FOR THE GOOD OF ASGARD</pattern><template>Yes, of course.</template></category><category><pattern>TO RUIN MY BROTHER'S BIG DAY</pattern><template>And to protect the realm from his idiotic rule for a while longer.</template></category><category><pattern>FATHER</pattern><template>JANE: He's fine, look at him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  IT MUST HAVE BEEN ENFORCING FATHER'S LAST COMMAND</pattern><template>You're a talented liar, Brother.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Back to work.</template></category><category><pattern>LOKI  THIS IS MADNESS</pattern><template>Is it madness?</template></category><category><pattern>THROUGH YOUR ARROGANCE AND STUPIDITY  YOU'VE OPENED THESE PEACEFUL REALMS AND INNOCENT LIVES TO THE HORROR AND DESOLATION OF WAR</pattern><template>You are unworthy of these realms!</template></category><category><pattern>WE MUST FIND THOR</pattern><template>It's treason.</template></category><category><pattern>BORROWED</pattern><template>Of course, you can have your equipment back.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU COULD HAVE JUST SAID SO</pattern><template>I just did.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HE DOING</pattern><template>Brother, whatever I have done to wrong you, whatever I have done to lead you to do this, I am truly sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE YOU GOING</pattern><template>Fifty miles west of here.</template></category><category><pattern>A BRILLIANT PHYSICIST</pattern><template>He's a wonderful man.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU SWEAR TO CAST ASIDE ALL SELFISH AMBITION AND TO PLEDGE YOURSELF ONLY TO THE GOOD OF THE REALMS</pattern><template>I swear!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST RETURN TO ASGARD</pattern><template>You have to stop Loki.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE ANSWERS YOU SEEK WILL BE YOURS ONCE I RECLAIM MJOLNIR</pattern><template>Myeu muh? What's Myeu muh?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TREASON</pattern><template>To hell with treason, it's suicide.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THESE PEOPLE ARE INNOCENT  TAKING THEIR LIVES WILL GAIN YOU NOTHING</pattern><template>So take mine and end this.</template></category><category><pattern>GLORY</pattern><template>I...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID YOU CALL IT</pattern><template>This Hooble Telescope.</template></category><category><pattern>DARCY: ALSO  HOW COULD YOU EAT AN ENTIRE BOX OF POP TARTS AND STILL BE THIS HUNGRY</pattern><template>This drink, I like it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOUR BROTHER</pattern><template>What hope is there for Thor?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  SIR</pattern><template>We got massive energy readings out of nowhere and then they just disappeared.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T HAVE TO START FROM SCRATCH NOW</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>LADY SIF AND THE WARRIORS THREE</pattern><template>My friends, I've never been happier to see anyone.</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS I HAD IT COMING</pattern><template>Oh, my God!</template></category><category><pattern>HUH</pattern><template>ERIK: You don't think this was just a magnetic storm, do you? Look, the lensing around these edges is characteristic of an Einstein Rosen Bridge.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CANNOT EVEN PROTECT YOUR FRIENDS</pattern><template>How can you hope to protect a kingdom?</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOUR RETURN THREATENS THE SAFETY OF ASGARD  BIFROST WILL REMAIN CLOSED TO YOU AND YOU'LL BE LEFT TO DIE IN THE COLD WASTE OF JOTUNHEIM</pattern><template>VOLSTAGG: Couldn't you just leave the bridge open for us?</template></category><category><pattern>A WHAT</pattern><template>I thought you were a science major?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO PLANS TO DIE TODAY</pattern><template>None do.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: I WAS PROTECTING MY HOME</pattern><template>You cannot even protect your friends!</template></category><category><pattern>ENOUGH</pattern><template>Look at you, the Mighty Thor, with all your strength, and what good does it do you now, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD IT ALL WRONG</pattern><template>It's not a bad thing finding out that you don't have all the answers.</template></category><category><pattern>ONCE I HAVE MJOLNIR  I WILL RETURN THE ITEMS THEY'VE STOLEN FROM YOU</pattern><template>Deal?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU START ASKING THE RIGHT QUESTIONS</pattern><template>For the first time in my life, I have no idea what I'm supposed to do.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>We drank, we fought, he made his ancestors proud.</template></category><category><pattern>A BIG  FACELESS ORGANIZATION LIKE YOURS COMING IN WITH THEIR JACKBOOTED THUGS AND</pattern><template>That's how he put it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WILL FIND THE BREACH IN OUR DEFENSES AND IT WILL BE SEALED</pattern><template>As King of Asgard...</template></category><category><pattern>MS  FOSTER  I'M AGENT COULSON WITH S H I E L D</pattern><template>Is that supposed to mean something to me?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED EYES UP HIGH  WITH A GUN</pattern><template>Moving north!</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'M SURE I CAN SUE YOU FOR VIOLATING MY CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS</pattern><template>I'm sorry, Ms. Foster, but we're the good guys.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PIONEER IN GAMMA RADIATION</pattern><template>S.H.I.E.L.D. showed up and he wasn't heard from again.</template></category><category><pattern>FATHER HAS FALLEN INTO THE ODIN SLEEP</pattern><template>Mother fears he may never awaken again.</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL  WE NEED YOU NOW  HEIMDALL</pattern><template>I must go back to Asgard, but I give you my word, I will return for you.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  OUR DATA CAN'T TELL US WHAT IT WAS LIKE TO BE INSIDE THAT EVENT  AND HE CAN  SO  WE'RE GONNA FIND HIM</pattern><template>DARCY: Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S ODIN</pattern><template>Father has fallen into the Odin sleep.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T GO ANYWHERE</pattern><template>Loki! What are you doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>HAMMER</pattern><template>Yeah, we can tell you're hammered.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FRIENDS</pattern><template>Where's Odin?</template></category><category><pattern>HE NEVER LISTENED</pattern><template>Neither did I.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I HAVE NEED OF THEM NO LONGER  NOW THAT I AM KING</pattern><template>And I say, for your act of treason, you are relieved of your duties as Gatekeeper, and no longer citizen of Asgard.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S HAD SOME DEALINGS WITH THESE PEOPLE BEFORE</pattern><template>I'll e mail him and maybe he can help.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS DELICIOUS  I WANT ANOTHER</pattern><template>Well, you could have just said so.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S ALWAYS A PURPOSE TO EVERYTHING YOUR FATHER DOES</pattern><template>JANE: That's no satellite crash!</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT YOU WERE A SCIENCE MAJOR</pattern><template>Political science.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  FOR A CRAZY HOMELESS PERSON  HE'S PRETTY CUT</pattern><template>Hey, sorry I tased you!</template></category><category><pattern>DELANCEY  JACKSON  REPORT</pattern><template>Agent down.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR ALL OF US</pattern><template>No, Loki.</template></category><category><pattern>DID IT WORK</pattern><template>Sir, we found it.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE CAN TELL YOU'RE HAMMERED</pattern><template>It's pretty obvious.</template></category><category><pattern>GET CLOSER</pattern><template>Right. Good one.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YES  EXACTLY  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Mmm hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL</pattern><template>Where are we going?</template></category><category><pattern>I COME UP HERE SOMETIMES WHEN I CAN'T SLEEP OR I'M TRYING TO RECONCILE PARTICLE DATA  OR WHEN DARCY'S DRIVING ME CRAZY</pattern><template>I come up here a lot, actually, now that I think about it.</template></category><category><pattern>LAUFEY: WE KNOW WHO YOU ARE</pattern><template>How did your people get into Asgard?</template></category><category><pattern>COME</pattern><template>Oh. My. God.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CASKET WASN'T THE ONLY THING YOU TOOK FROM JOTUNHEIM THAT DAY  WAS IT</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>MY KING  WE WOULD ASK THAT YOU END THOR'S BANISHMENT</pattern><template>My first command cannot be to undo the All fathers last.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY HAVE YOU DONE THIS</pattern><template>To prove to Father that I am the worthy son.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE ALREADY MADE ME PROUD</pattern><template>So Earth is lost to us.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WROTE SCIENCE FICTION</pattern><template>A precursor to science fact!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW FIGHT ME</pattern><template>I never wanted the throne!</template></category><category><pattern>LAUFEY  END THIS NOW</pattern><template>Your boy sought this out.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>You're very welcome.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS THE ONLY APPLICANT</pattern><template>An Einstein Rosen Bridge is a theoretical connection between two different points of space time.</template></category><category><pattern>COULSON: YOU MADE MY MEN  SOME OF THE MOST HIGHLY TRAINED PROFESSIONALS IN THE WORLD  LOOK LIKE A BUNCH OF MINIMUM WAGE MALL COPS</pattern><template>That's hurtful.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  YOU'RE SAFE</pattern><template>We're safe.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WILL SUFFICE</pattern><template>You're welcome.</template></category><category><pattern>SIF  SIF  YOU'VE DONE ALL YOU CAN</pattern><template>No. I will die a warrior's death.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  IT'S GREAT  RIGHT</pattern><template>Another!</template></category><category><pattern>THEN GO</pattern><template>Run!</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: I CAN'T JUST LEAVE HIM THERE</pattern><template>ERIK: Why?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD MY HANDS ALL OVER IT</pattern><template>Which way?</template></category><category><pattern>S H I E L D</pattern><template>Whatever they are, they're gonna do everything in their power to make sure this research never sees the light of day.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THE NINE REALMS</pattern><template>Now, there is Midgard, which is Earth.</template></category><category><pattern>FANDRAL: WELL  AT LEAST HE'S ONLY BANISHED  NOT DEAD</pattern><template>Which is what we'd all be if that guard hadn't told Odin where we'd gone.</template></category><category><pattern>(BRAKES SQUEALING)   (HONKING) DRIVER: DUMBASS</pattern><template>Where are you going?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HE IS  OR HE WAS</pattern><template>He switched careers and became a physicist.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY BROKE INTO THE WEAPONS VAULT</pattern><template>If the Frost Giants had stolen even one of these relics...</template></category><category><pattern>FATHER IS DEAD</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>DARCY: OKAY</pattern><template>So we're gonna look all over New Mexico, right?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M ON THE VERGE OF UNDERSTANDING SOMETHING EXTRAORDINARY</pattern><template>And everything I know about this phenomenon is either in this lab or in this book.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO COMMS</pattern><template>AGENT4: Target sighted, east tunnel!</template></category><category><pattern>PAKISTAN  CHECHNYA  AFGHANISTAN</pattern><template>No, you strike me more as the soldier of fortune type.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYONE WHO'S EVER GOING TO FIND HIS WAY IN THIS WORLD HAS TO START BY ADMITTING HE DOESN'T KNOW WHERE THE HELL HE IS</pattern><template>Thank you for what you've done.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP IT DISTRACTED</pattern><template>For Asgard!</template></category><category><pattern>FOR YOU</pattern><template>For all of us!</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: WHAT</pattern><template>I'm so sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT YET</pattern><template>It's unwise to be in my company right now, Brother.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: GET THE FIRST AID KIT</pattern><template>Do me a favor and don't be dead.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THEY JUST STOLE MY ENTIRE LIFE'S WORK</pattern><template>I don't really have much left to lose.</template></category><category><pattern>FAR MORE CLEVER THAN ANYONE ELSE IN THIS REALM</pattern><template>Realm ?  Realm ?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S GOOD TO HAVE YOU BACK</pattern><template>Now if you'll excuse me, I have to destroy Jotunheim.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME  EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>What is this?</template></category><category><pattern>HE JUST WENT NUTS</pattern><template>DARCY: Oh, my God.</template></category><category><pattern>FRIGGA: HOW IS HE  SIF: HE MOURNS FOR HIS BROTHER  AND    HE MISSES HER  THE MORTAL  YOU'LL BE A WISE KING</pattern><template>There will never be a wiser king than you.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE NOT GONNA DO THAT TO US</pattern><template>I'm gonna get everything back.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAS AN ACT OF WAR</pattern><template>It was the act of but a few, doomed to fail.</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL: BE WARNED</pattern><template>I will honor my sworn oath to protect this realm as its Gatekeeper.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR WORK HAS IMPRESSED A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO ARE MUCH SMARTER THAN I AM</pattern><template>I have a lot to work with.</template></category><category><pattern>SO SORRY  BYE</pattern><template>AGENT 1: Bravo quadrant, move!</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S FINE  NOT INJURED AT ALL</pattern><template>(GROANS)   I'm sorry, my friend.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S TALKING ABOUT MJOLNIR AND THOR AND BIFROST</pattern><template>It's the stories I grew up with as a child.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL IS WELL</pattern><template>They broke into the weapons vault!</template></category><category><pattern>TECH'S BARELY WORKING AS IT IS  WITH ALL THE INTERFERENCE THAT THING'S GIVING OFF</pattern><template>And we've got a commercial aircraft coming right over us.</template></category><category><pattern>VOLSTAGG: WHAT</pattern><template>This isn't like a journey to Earth where you summon a little lightning and thunder, and the mortals worship you as a god.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU AND I CAN END THIS HERE AND NOW  BEFORE THERE'S FURTHER BLOODSHED</pattern><template>We are beyond diplomacy now, All father.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP</pattern><template>We all know what we have to do.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVING NORTH</pattern><template>What have we got?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHO ARE YOU</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>I DO</pattern><template>Go now, while I still allow it.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT YOUR BROTHER</pattern><template>I never was.</template></category><category><pattern>SILENCE</pattern><template>All father.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I GUESS THAT'S WORTH A LOOK</pattern><template>Well, I guess that's worth a look.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS SO CRUEL TO PUT THE HAMMER WITHIN YOUR REACH  KNOWING THAT YOU COULD NEVER LIFT IT</pattern><template>The burden of the throne has fallen to me now.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS DRINK  I LIKE IT</pattern><template>I know. It's great, right?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE GOT A PERIMETER BREACH</pattern><template>You've reached Dr. Erik Selvig.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS</pattern><template>Well, maybe, when we're finished here, I'll pay her a visit myself!</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR KING</pattern><template>My King, we would ask that you end Thor's banishment.</template></category><category><pattern>IN MY EXPERIENCE  IT TAKES SOMEONE WHO'S RECEIVED SIMILAR TRAINING TO DO WHAT YOU DID TO THEM</pattern><template>Why don't you tell me where you received your training?</template></category><category><pattern>OR ARE YOU SENDING IN MORE GUYS FOR HIM TO BEAT UP</pattern><template>I'll let you know.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M REALLY GLAD YOU'RE SAFE</pattern><template>You've been very kind to me, and I've been far less grateful than you deserve.</template></category><category><pattern>HUBBLE TELESCOPE</pattern><template>Tell me more.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE</pattern><template>Why have you done this?</template></category><category><pattern>DARCY: JANE</pattern><template>I think you want to see this.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST GOING TO DRIVE HIM  THAT'S IT</pattern><template>He's dangerous, Jane.</template></category><category><pattern>ANOTHER</pattern><template>JANE: Sorry, Izzy. Little accident.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR  STOP AND THINK</pattern><template>Look around you, we're outnumbered.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU AND I  WE FIGHT FOR THE SAME CAUSE  THE PROTECTION OF THIS WORLD</pattern><template>From this day forward, you can count me as your ally if you return the items you have taken from Jane.</template></category><category><pattern>I STILL DON'T THINK YOU'RE THE GOD OF THUNDER</pattern><template>But you ought to be.</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK  I WOULDN'T HAVE ASKED YOU TO FLY OUT HERE IF I WASN'T ABSOLUTELY SURE</pattern><template>DARCY: Jane?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HAPPENED</pattern><template>Tell me. Is it Jotunheim?</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOUR DEATH CAME BY THE SON OF ODIN</pattern><template>Loki!</template></category><category><pattern>I COME UP HERE A LOT  ACTUALLY  NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT</pattern><template>I'm really glad you're safe.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE STORIES I GREW UP WITH AS A CHILD</pattern><template>I'm just going to drive him. That's it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE HERE TO TAKE YOU HOME</pattern><template>You know I can't go home.</template></category><category><pattern>FANDRAL  HOGUN</pattern><template>Who led you into the most glorious of battles?</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I LEFT SOMETHING AT THE HOSPITAL</pattern><template>It's not possible!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA GET EVERYTHING BACK</pattern><template>Come on, please.</template></category><category><pattern>A PRIMITIVE CULTURE LIKE THE VIKINGS MIGHT HAVE WORSHIPPED THEM AS DEITIES</pattern><template>Yes! Yes, exactly. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>SO EARTH IS LOST TO US</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE YOU</pattern><template>One way or another, we find out what we need to know.</template></category><category><pattern>GET HIM TO THE HEALING ROOM</pattern><template>Leave my brother to me.</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR I'M NOT DOING THIS ON PURPOSE</pattern><template>I got it, I got it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU WILL OPEN THE BIFROST TO NO ONE UNTIL I HAVE REPAIRED THE DAMAGE THAT MY BROTHER HAS DONE</pattern><template>He's fine. Not injured at all.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS IT</pattern><template>Power, Doctor.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SO SORRY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE BIG</pattern><template>Fought bigger.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO CONVINCE THE SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY OF ANY OF IT</pattern><template>Not without hard evidence.</template></category><category><pattern>LAUFEY: IT'S SAID YOU CAN STILL HEAR AND SEE WHAT TRANSPIRES AROUND YOU</pattern><template>I hope it's true, so that you may know your death came at the hand of Laufey.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S UNWISE TO BE IN MY COMPANY RIGHT NOW  BROTHER</pattern><template>This was to be my day of triumph.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT SURE FINDING HIM IS THE BEST IDEA</pattern><template>Well, our data can't tell us what it was like to be inside that event, and he can. So, we're gonna find him.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I HAVE A WORD  JANE</pattern><template>Please don't do this.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE DON'T DO THIS</pattern><template>You saw what I saw last night.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE AN INNOCENT CHILD</pattern><template>No. You took me for a purpose.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE  LOOK</pattern><template>Your ancestors called it magic, and you call it science.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: HOW IS SHE  ERIK: IN THE CAR  COME ON  JANE</pattern><template>HEIMDALL: She searches for you. NICK FURY: Dr. Selvig.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR BOY SOUGHT THIS OUT</pattern><template>You're right.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS A GOOD MAN</pattern><template>He never listened.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE DEFENDED ASGARD AND THE LIVES OF THE INNOCENT ACROSS THE NINE REALMS FROM THE TIME OF THE GREAT BEGINNING  THOUGH THE DAY HAS COME    DO YOU SWEAR TO GUARD THE NINE REALMS</pattern><template>I swear.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT HIM ON THE BED</pattern><template>I still don't think you're the God of Thunder.</template></category><category><pattern>WHILE YOU WAIT AND BE PATIENT  THE NINE REALMS LAUGH AT US</pattern><template>The old ways are done.</template></category><category><pattern>TECHNICIAN: SIR</pattern><template>It says here that he's an M.D.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A WONDERFUL MAN</pattern><template>He's a man in pain.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE THINKING ONLY AS A WARRIOR</pattern><template>This was an act of war!</template></category><category><pattern>NONE DO</pattern><template>We shouldn't be here.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE  EASY  EASY  JANE</pattern><template>Thank you for your cooperation.</template></category><category><pattern>COMPLICATED FELLOW  ISN'T HE</pattern><template>Now what do we do?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT AM I</pattern><template>You're my son.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP IT  BOTH OF YOU</pattern><template>Stop.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE THOR MORE DEARLY THAN ANY OF YOU  BUT YOU KNOW WHAT HE IS</pattern><template>He's arrogant.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER WANTED THE THRONE</pattern><template>I only ever wanted to be your equal.</template></category><category><pattern>SMILE</pattern><template>What did it look like, the satellite?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOSOEVER HOLDS THIS HAMMER  IF HE BE WORTHY  SHALL POSSESS THE POWER OF THOR</pattern><template>Jane!</template></category><category><pattern>I COULD HAVE DONE IT  FATHER</pattern><template>I could have done it!</template></category><category><pattern>ARE THESE YOUR CHAMBERS</pattern><template>It's more of a temporary living situation.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE THEY</pattern><template>Hiding, as cowards always do.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I DON'T USUALLY HAVE GUESTS</pattern><template>Actually, I never have guests.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD HIM TO GO TO ODIN AFTER WE'D LEFT</pattern><template>He should be flogged for taking so long.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE GREAT POWER  HEIMDALL</pattern><template>Did Odin ever fear you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO STOP LOKI</pattern><template>What about you?</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT: DELANCEY  JACKSON</pattern><template>West side perimeter. Go check it out. There it is.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M READY  FATHER</pattern><template>So am I.</template></category><category><pattern>THE JOTUNS MUST LEARN TO FEAR ME  JUST AS THEY ONCE FEARED YOU</pattern><template>ODIN: That's pride and vanity talking, not leadership.</template></category><category><pattern>LOKI: YOU CAN'T STOP IT</pattern><template>The Bifrost will build until it rips Jotunheim apart.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FIRST COMMAND CANNOT BE TO UNDO THE ALL FATHERS LAST</pattern><template>We're on the brink of war with Jotunheim.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T KILL AN ENTIRE RACE</pattern><template>Why not?</template></category><category><pattern>OR A BETTER FATHER</pattern><template>I have much to learn.</template></category><category><pattern>DEAL</pattern><template>Get him to the healing room!</template></category><category><pattern>DESTROY EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Mom?</template></category><category><pattern>GROUND UNITS  MOVE IN</pattern><template>ERIK: He committed a crime. He's in jail!</template></category><category><pattern>I CANNOT OPEN THE BRIDGE TO YOU</pattern><template>Complicated fellow, isn't he?</template></category><category><pattern>ODIN: NO</pattern><template>What am I?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST AS YOU DID  FATHER</pattern><template>A wise king never seeks out war.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED SUSTENANCE</pattern><template>We should never have let him go.</template></category><category><pattern>MALE NURSE: I NEED SOME HELP</pattern><template>Call security!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT TROUBLES YOU  GATEKEEPER</pattern><template>I turned my gaze upon you in Jotunheim, but could neither see you nor hear you.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FOSTER THEORY</pattern><template>A gateway to another dimension.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULD HAVE DONE IT</pattern><template>For you!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T DO THIS</pattern><template>Jane!</template></category><category><pattern>A GATEWAY TO ANOTHER DIMENSION</pattern><template>It's unprecedented.</template></category><category><pattern>HE JUST BROKE YOUR TRUCE</pattern><template>They know you are vulnerable!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S ALWAYS PUSHING ME TO CHASE DOWN EVERY POSSIBILITY  EVERY ALTERNATIVE</pattern><template>I'm talking about science, not magic!</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO APPROPRIATE YOUR RECORDS AND ALL YOUR ATMOSPHERIC DATA</pattern><template>By  appropriate,  do you mean steal?</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER IS DEAD BECAUSE OF ME</pattern><template>And I must remain in exile.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GOING TO JOTUNHEIM</pattern><template>VOLSTAGG: What?</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T HAVE HORSES</pattern><template>Just dogs, cats, birds...</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE DELUSIONAL OR IF YOU'RE PULLING SOME KIND OF CON  I DON'T CARE</pattern><template>I just care about her.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT WORRY  MY FRIENDS  I HAVE A PLAN</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK: JANE  YOU'RE AN ASTROPHYSICIST  NOT SOME STORM CHASER</pattern><template>JANE: I'm telling you, there's a connection between these atmospheric disturbances and my research.</template></category><category><pattern>DARCY: (GASPS) LOOK</pattern><template>Look, it's Myeu muh.</template></category><category><pattern>REALM    REALM</pattern><template>You think me strange.</template></category><category><pattern>POWER  DOCTOR</pattern><template>If we can figure out how to tap it, maybe unlimited power.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  MAYBE  WHEN WE'RE FINISHED HERE  I'LL PAY HER A VISIT MYSELF</pattern><template>Thor!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW NOT WHAT YOUR ACTIONS WOULD UNLEASH</pattern><template>I do.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T LET THEM TOUCH YOU</pattern><template>Thor!</template></category><category><pattern>IT SAYS HERE THAT HE'S AN M D</pattern><template>Well, he is! Or he was.</template></category><category><pattern>SO AM I</pattern><template>Only one of you can ascend to the throne.</template></category><category><pattern>BACK TO WORK</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR TO YOU  MOTHER  THAT THEY WILL PAY FOR WHAT THEY'VE DONE TODAY</pattern><template>THOR: Loki.</template></category><category><pattern>TO GET WHAT BELONGS TO ME</pattern><template>Oh, so you own a satellite now?</template></category><category><pattern>GO  HURRY  YOU CAN EAT LATER</pattern><template>Keep it distracted.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN UNDERSTAND HOW A MAN COULD GO OFF LIKE THAT</pattern><template>A big, faceless organization like yours coming in with their jackbooted thugs and...</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR</pattern><template>Then, on this day, I, Odin All father, proclaim you...</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF I DO  THEN WHAT</pattern><template>I love Thor more dearly than any of you, but you know what he is.</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK: THE CHILDREN'S SECTION</pattern><template>I just wanted to show you how silly his story was.</template></category><category><pattern>SO ARE WE</pattern><template>I'm on the verge of understanding something extraordinary.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS GOODBYE  BROTHER</pattern><template>I'm so sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS ALWAYS HOPE</pattern><template>Can you see her?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT YOU  THE MIGHTY THOR  WITH ALL YOUR STRENGTH  AND WHAT GOOD DOES IT DO YOU NOW  HUH</pattern><template>Do you hear me, Brother?</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: WHAT IS THAT</pattern><template>ERIK: I thought you said it was a subtle aurora!</template></category><category><pattern>MAN 1: WELL  I WOULDN'T WASTE MY TIME</pattern><template>Looked like the whole Army was coming when we left.</template></category><category><pattern>SMALL FOR A GIANT'S OFFSPRING  ABANDONED  SUFFERING  LEFT TO DIE  LAUFEY'S SON  LAUFEY'S SON</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>AN EINSTEIN ROSEN BRIDGE IS A THEORETICAL CONNECTION BETWEEN TWO DIFFERENT POINTS OF SPACE TIME</pattern><template>It's a wormhole.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM THOR ODINSON</pattern><template>LAUFEY: We know who you are.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  THERE IS MIDGARD  WHICH IS EARTH</pattern><template>This is Alfheim.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR ASGARD</pattern><template>SIF: Fall back!</template></category><category><pattern>SILVER TONGUE TURN TO LEAD</pattern><template>HEIMDALL: Be warned.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW STAY HERE</pattern><template>Once I have Mjolnir, I will return the items they've stolen from you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY YOU FAVORED THOR ALL THESE YEARS</pattern><template>Because no matter how much you claim to love me, you could never have a Frost Giant sitting on the throne of Asgard!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT MORE THAN THAT</pattern><template>The Casket wasn't the only thing you took from Jotunheim that day, was it?</template></category><category><pattern>THOR  IT'S MADNESS</pattern><template>Madness? What sort of madness?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I MUST REMAIN IN EXILE</pattern><template>Thor, your father still lives.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S WRONG</pattern><template>S.H.I.E.L.D.</template></category><category><pattern>DARCY: YEAH  HAVE YOU SEEN MY TASER</pattern><template>THOR: How is she? ERIK: In the car. Come on, Jane!</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK HOW FAR THEY GOT</pattern><template>We will find the breach in our defenses and it will be sealed.</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL HAVE DESTROYED THAT RACE OF MONSTERS</pattern><template>And I will be true heir to the throne!</template></category><category><pattern>ARTHUR C  CLARKE</pattern><template>Who wrote science fiction.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S GO TAKE A LOOK</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>Wait!</template></category><category><pattern>ISN'T IT</pattern><template>Legend tells us one thing, history, another.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>Do not worry, my friends. I have a plan.</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL</pattern><template>If you can hear me, we need you now!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>That's my stuff!</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS ON DRUGS OR SOMETHING</pattern><template>He just went nuts.</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT 1: BRAVO QUADRANT  MOVE</pattern><template>AGENT 2: Entering south tunnel!</template></category><category><pattern>FROM THIS DAY FORWARD  YOU CAN COUNT ME AS YOUR ALLY IF YOU RETURN THE ITEMS YOU HAVE TAKEN FROM JANE</pattern><template>Stolen.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKED LIKE THE WHOLE ARMY WAS COMING WHEN WE LEFT</pattern><template>(BRAKES SQUEALING)   (HONKING) DRIVER: Dumbass!</template></category><category><pattern>KNOW THIS  SON OF COUL</pattern><template>You and I, we fight for the same cause, the protection of this world.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU EVER DONE ANYTHING LIKE THIS BEFORE</pattern><template>Many times.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'LL NEED SOME TIME</pattern><template>You'll have it!</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE AN EINSTEIN ROSEN BRIDGE</pattern><template>More like a Rainbow Bridge.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Hammer?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY  GOD</pattern><template>So, is this how you normally look?</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR TO YOU  I MEAN HER NO HARM</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>AND VOLSTAGG  TO DELICACIES SO SUCCULENT  YOU THOUGHT YOU'D DIED AND GONE TO VALHALLA</pattern><template>You did.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FRIENDS  I'M JUST A MAN  I'LL ONLY BE IN THE WAY  OR WORSE  GET ONE OF YOU KILLED</pattern><template>But I can help get these people to safety.</template></category><category><pattern>COULSON: EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Donald?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO LED YOU INTO THE MOST GLORIOUS OF BATTLES</pattern><template>You did.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE YOU ARE  YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>I'm taking you home now.</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHOULDN'T BE HERE</pattern><template>Let's move.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID THE GUARD EVEN KNOW</pattern><template>I told him.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WOULD DEFY THE COMMANDS OF LOKI  OUR KING  BREAK EVERY OATH YOU HAVE TAKEN AS WARRIORS  AND COMMIT TREASON TO BRING THOR BACK</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE MUST ALWAYS BE READY FOR IT</pattern><template>I'm ready, Father.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU'RE BRAVE TO DO IT</pattern><template>Well, they just stole my entire life's work.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT MADNESS</pattern><template>Is it?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW SHUSH</pattern><template>Heimdall might be watching.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO MOVE QUICKLY BEFORE THIS ALL CHANGES</pattern><template>Jane, we have to take him to the hospital.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE LEAVE ME A MESSAGE  HI  ERIK  IT'S ME  DON'T WORRY  I'M FINE  BUT JUST IN CASE YOU DON'T HEAR FROM ME IN THE NEXT HOUR  JUST COME BY THE CRATER SITE AND TRY AND FIND ME  OKAY</pattern><template>I did exactly what you told me not to.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WOULD JUST BE LOOKING FOR ANSWERS</pattern><template>It is forbidden!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE UNWORTHY OF THE LOVED ONES YOU HAVE BETRAYED</pattern><template>I now take from you your power!</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER EXPLAINED IT TO ME LIKE THIS  THAT YOUR WORLD IS ONE OF THE NINE REALMS OF THE COSMOS  LINKED TO EACH OTHER BY THE BRANCHES OF YGGDRASIL  THE WORLDS TREE</pattern><template>Now you see it every day without realizing.</template></category><category><pattern>THE OLD WAYS ARE DONE</pattern><template>You'd stand giving speeches while Asgard falls.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T BELIEVE IT</pattern><template>Oh, excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN HE WAKES  I WILL HAVE SAVED HIS LIFE</pattern><template>I will have destroyed that race of monsters.</template></category><category><pattern>FIFTEEN MILES DUE NORTHWEST</pattern><template>Let's go take a look.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I NEED NO LONGER OBEY YOU</pattern><template>Get somebody from Linguistics down here.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST KEEP HIM AWAY FROM THE BARS</pattern><template>I will!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW GO</pattern><template>You must return to Asgard.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I MAY BEG THE INDULGENCE OF YOUR MAJESTY TO PERHAPS RECONSIDER</pattern><template>We're done!</template></category><category><pattern>UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>What happened?</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>You'll see soon enough.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  THIS TIME IT'S DIFFERENT</pattern><template>We were unprepared.</template></category><category><pattern>FANDRAL: LOKI'S ALWAYS BEEN ONE FOR MISCHIEF  BUT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE ENTIRELY</pattern><template>ODIN: Stop!</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN SOMETHING TO ME</pattern><template>You can't do this!</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL LET YOU KNOW</pattern><template>You're big.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU SEE HER</pattern><template>Yes. ERIK: I have the particle detectors!</template></category><category><pattern>ODIN: THAT'S PRIDE AND VANITY TALKING  NOT LEADERSHIP</pattern><template>You've forgotten everything I taught you about a warrior's patience.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A WORMHOLE</pattern><template>Erik, look. What do you see?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T YOU CARE</pattern><template>Do not mistake my appetite for apathy!</template></category><category><pattern>DID ODIN EVER FEAR YOU</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TO FIND OUT WHAT'S IN THAT CRATER</pattern><template>But I'm not talking about the crater, I'm talking about him.</template></category><category><pattern>MARCH INTO JOTUNHEIM AS YOU ONCE DID</pattern><template>Teach them a lesson.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK WEARY</pattern><template>Laufey, end this now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST GO TO THE ALL FATHER AND CONVINCE HIM TO CHANGE HIS MIND</pattern><template>And if I do, then what?</template></category><category><pattern>WE MUST GO TO THE BIFROST SITE</pattern><template>I would have words with my brother.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WHAT ASGARD NEEDS FROM ITS KING</pattern><template>He may speak of the good of Asgard, but he's always been jealous of Thor.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR</pattern><template>He's got a visitor.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAW WHAT I SAW LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>This is no coincidence.</template></category><category><pattern>TRUE  BUT I SUPPORTED YOU  SIF</pattern><template>My friends, we're going to Jotunheim.</template></category><category><pattern>MADNESS  WHAT SORT OF MADNESS</pattern><template>We're going to Jotunheim.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS THE ACT OF BUT A FEW  DOOMED TO FAIL</pattern><template>Look how far they got!</template></category><category><pattern>TWO BOILERMAKERS</pattern><template>LAUFEY: Kill him.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: MY FRIENDS</pattern><template>This is good! This is good.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WHATEVER IT IS  THE GOVERNMENT SEEMS TO THINK IT'S THEIRS</pattern><template>So, you just intend to go in there and take it?</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL NOT FIGHT YOU  BROTHER</pattern><template>I'm not your brother.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS A FOOL TO THINK YOU WERE READY</pattern><template>Father...</template></category><category><pattern>TYPICAL</pattern><template>So now what?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS YOUR KING AND YOU'RE SWORN TO OBEY ME NOW</pattern><template>Yes?</template></category><category><pattern>BETTER CALL IT  COULSON  'CAUSE I'M STARTING TO ROOT FOR THIS GUY</pattern><template>Last chance, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BURDEN OF THE THRONE HAS FALLEN TO ME NOW</pattern><template>Can I come home?</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: LOKI</pattern><template>Thor!</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  YOU CAN HAVE YOUR EQUIPMENT BACK</pattern><template>You're gonna need it to continue your research.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ADVANCED BEINGS COULD HAVE CROSSED IT</pattern><template>Jane.</template></category><category><pattern>WE FIND HIM</pattern><template>Did you see what he did in there?</template></category><category><pattern>LAUFEY: KILL HIM</pattern><template>After all I've done for you?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOOK YOUR LAPTOP  TOO</pattern><template>All father, we must speak with you urgently.</template></category><category><pattern>TO MAKE PEACE</pattern><template>You long for battle. You crave it.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LAST 17 OCCURRENCES HAVE BEEN PREDICTABLE TO THE SECOND</pattern><template>ERIK: Jane, you're an astrophysicist, not some storm chaser.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS YEARS OF HIS LIFE  GONE</pattern><template>You can understand how a man could go off like that.</template></category><category><pattern>FOUGHT BIGGER</pattern><template>Better call it, Coulson, 'cause I'm starting to root for this guy.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  PLEASE</pattern><template>Let me contact one of my colleagues.</template></category><category><pattern>INCOMING</pattern><template>Jane, you have to leave.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS FORBIDDEN</pattern><template>My friends, have you forgotten all that we have done together?</template></category><category><pattern>GO NOW  WHILE I STILL ALLOW IT</pattern><template>We will accept your most gracious offer.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THOSE PLANS NO LONGER MATTER</pattern><template>So I am no more than another stolen relic, locked up here until you might have use of me.</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK: WHY</pattern><template>You didn't see what I saw!</template></category><category><pattern>THEN I'M SURE YOU CAN DO IT AGAIN</pattern><template>And I'm sure I can sue you for violating my constitutional rights!</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  YOU ARE USING UNREGISTERED WEAPONS TECHNOLOGY  IDENTIFY YOURSELF  HERE WE GO</pattern><template>Incoming!</template></category><category><pattern>VOLSTAGG: AS A MATTER OF FACT  FALLING WAS A TACTIC LULLING THE DESTROYER</pattern><template>My Queen, I'm so sorry for your loss.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MORE LIKE IT</pattern><template>Don't let them touch you!</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY OUT  USE THE BACK DOOR</pattern><template>Go, hurry! You can eat later.</template></category><category><pattern>SO BE IT</pattern><template>THOR: Why did you bring us back?</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN</pattern><template>Next?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL FATHER  WE MUST SPEAK WITH YOU URGENTLY</pattern><template>My friends.</template></category><category><pattern>GUARDS  PLEASE  HELP</pattern><template>JANE: How'd you get inside that cloud?</template></category><category><pattern>LEGEND TELLS US ONE THING  HISTORY  ANOTHER</pattern><template>But every now and then, we find something that belongs to both.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST GOT BACK</pattern><template>Sir?</template></category><category><pattern>GET SOMEBODY FROM LINGUISTICS DOWN HERE</pattern><template>Was somebody else coming?</template></category><category><pattern>MAN: COME ON  KICK IT IN NOW</pattern><template>Did it work?</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT 1: WE'RE SPIKING</pattern><template>AGENT 2: Levels increase!</template></category><category><pattern>ALWAYS HAVE BEEN</pattern><template>It's good to have you back.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE SAFE</pattern><template>It's over.</template></category><category><pattern>GO  NOW  RUN</pattern><template>Sif. Sif, you've done all you can.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN: SECURITY TO ER 3  STAT</pattern><template>You're no match for the Mighty...</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT A BAD THING FINDING OUT THAT YOU DON'T HAVE ALL THE ANSWERS</pattern><template>You start asking the right questions.</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK: JANE  YOU CAN'T KEEP DOING THIS</pattern><template>The last 17 occurrences have been predictable to the second.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FROST GIANTS</pattern><template>THOR: The Jotuns must pay for what they've done!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT BOTH OF YOU WERE BORN TO BE KINGS</pattern><template>Oh, please.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE SEEN THE WAY SHE LOOKS AT YOU</pattern><template>I swear to you, I mean her no harm.</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL  HE DOESN'T ANSWER</pattern><template>Then we are stranded.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  ERIK: I HAVE THE PARTICLE DETECTORS</pattern><template>Darcy, do you have the S.H.I.E.L.D.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW LONG WILL IT LAST</pattern><template>I don't know. This time it's different.</template></category><category><pattern>LAUFEY: YOU'VE COME A LONG WAY TO DIE  ASGARDIANS</pattern><template>I am Thor Odinson!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE REACHED DR  ERIK SELVIG</pattern><template>Please leave me a message. Hi, Erik, it's me. Don't worry, I'm fine, but just in case you don't hear from me in the next hour, just come by the crater site and try and find me, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>STEROIDS  HE'S A BIT OF A FITNESS NUT</pattern><template>TECHNICIAN: Sir?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT</pattern><template>I don't know, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEANT NO DISRESPECT</pattern><template>All right. Well, no more smashing.</template></category><category><pattern>DARCY: OH  MY GOD</pattern><template>I just lost my most important piece of evidence.</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Did you say there was a satellite crash?</template></category><category><pattern>ODIN: STOP</pattern><template>LOKI: Am I cursed?</template></category><category><pattern>ACCEPT</pattern><template>What troubles you, Gatekeeper?</template></category><category><pattern>JANE: THEY TOOK OUR BACKUPS</pattern><template>They took the backups of our backups.</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK: YOU DON'T THINK THIS WAS JUST A MAGNETIC STORM  DO YOU  LOOK  THE LENSING AROUND THESE EDGES IS CHARACTERISTIC OF AN EINSTEIN ROSEN BRIDGE</pattern><template>A what?</template></category><category><pattern>I NOW TAKE FROM YOU YOUR POWER</pattern><template>In the name of my father and his father before, I, Odin All father, cast you out!</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE NO MATTER HOW MUCH YOU CLAIM TO LOVE ME  YOU COULD NEVER HAVE A FROST GIANT SITTING ON THE THRONE OF ASGARD</pattern><template>Guards!</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I TOTALLY KNOW CPR</pattern><template>Where did he come from?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE NEVER MET HIM BEFORE</pattern><template>Until she hit him with a car.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE THE BRIDGE WE SPOKE OF</pattern><template>Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>STARS</pattern><template>Yeah, but not our stars.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MOTHER HAS FORBIDDEN YOUR RETURN</pattern><template>This is goodbye, Brother.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  MOVE IT  PEOPLE</pattern><template>Everybody out! Use the back door.</template></category><category><pattern>COULSON: WAIT  I NEED TO DEBRIEF YOU</pattern><template>Welcome to Asgard.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT ME TO SLOW HIM DOWN  SIR</pattern><template>Or are you sending in more guys for him to beat up?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'D STAND GIVING SPEECHES WHILE ASGARD FALLS</pattern><template>You are a vain, greedy, cruel boy!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE WAS IT  SOUTH AFRICA</pattern><template>Certain groups pay very well for a good mercenary like you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU SHOULD NOT HAVE COME</pattern><template>We're here to take you home.</template></category><category><pattern>THE IMAGES GLIMPSED THROUGH</pattern><template>What did you call it?</template></category><category><pattern>THOR  YOUR FATHER STILL LIVES</pattern><template>Tell me, Loki, how did you get the Jotuns into Asgard?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT STILL DOESN'T EXPLAIN HOW HE MANAGED TO TEAR THROUGH OUR SECURITY</pattern><template>Steroids! He's a bit of a fitness nut.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR PEOPLE NEED A SENSE OF CONTINUITY  IN ORDER TO FEEL SAFE IN THESE DIFFICULT TIMES</pattern><template>All of us must stand together for the good of Asgard.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AROUND YOU  WE'RE OUTNUMBERED</pattern><template>Know your place, Brother.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD YOU PLEASE STOP WITH YOUR IPOD</pattern><template>Who are these people?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE RIGHT</pattern><template>And these are the actions of a boy, treat them as such.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I DID</pattern><template>Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  IT'S MYEU MUH</pattern><template>Where'd you find this?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU STRIKE ME MORE AS THE SOLDIER OF FORTUNE TYPE</pattern><template>Where was it? South Africa?</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT MISTAKE MY APPETITE FOR APATHY</pattern><template>Stop it, both of you!</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU FOR YOUR COOPERATION</pattern><template>Years of research, gone.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HOW HE PUT IT</pattern><template>That still doesn't explain how he managed to tear through our security.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WAS TO BE MY DAY OF TRIUMPH</pattern><template>It'll come.</template></category><category><pattern>SO LONG ENTRUSTED WITH THE MIGHTY HAMMER MJOLNIR  FORGED IN THE HEART OF A DYING STAR  ITS POWER HAS NO EQUAL  AS A WEAPON TO DESTROY OR AS A TOOL TO BUILD</pattern><template>'Tis a fit companion for a king.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I COME HOME</pattern><template>The truce with Jotunheim is conditional upon your exile.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A BOY TRYING TO PROVE HIMSELF A MAN</pattern><template>THOR: Well, this  boy  has grown tired of your mockery.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAW HOW HE WAS TODAY</pattern><template>Is that what Asgard needs from its king?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOLD THE GUARD</pattern><template>I saved our lives.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>Come!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TALKING ABOUT SCIENCE  NOT MAGIC</pattern><template>Well, magic's just science that we don't understand yet.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MY STUFF</pattern><template>What the hell is going on here?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MORE OF A TEMPORARY LIVING SITUATION</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I don't usually have guests.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU CAN'T JUST TAKE THIS AWAY    HEY</pattern><template>Jane! Easy! Easy. Jane...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU TOOK ME FOR A PURPOSE</pattern><template>What was it?</template></category><category><pattern>TEACH THEM A LESSON</pattern><template>Break their spirits so they'll never dare try to cross our borders again.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE GOT SOMETHING OUTSIDE THE FENCE  WEST SIDE</pattern><template>AGENT: Delancey, Jackson.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I'M THE MONSTER PARENTS TELL THEIR CHILDREN ABOUT AT NIGHT</pattern><template>No, no.</template></category><category><pattern>MAN 1: THEY'RE SAYING SOME KIND OF SATELLITE LANDED OUT IN THE DESERT</pattern><template>MAN 2: Yeah, we were having a good time with it until the Feds showed up.</template></category><category><pattern>VANAHEIM  JOTUNHEIM</pattern><template>And Asgard.</template></category><category><pattern>WE MUSTN'T LOSE HOPE THAT YOUR FATHER WILL RETURN TO US</pattern><template>And your brother.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE ON THE BRINK OF WAR WITH JOTUNHEIM</pattern><template>Our people need a sense of continuity, in order to feel safe in these difficult times.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT DRESSED WARMLY ENOUGH</pattern><template>I'm sorry?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY IT'S NOT AS MUCH AS I PROMISED</pattern><template>No, no, this is great! This is...</template></category><category><pattern>AND DO YOU SWEAR TO PRESERVE THE PEACE</pattern><template>I swear.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS HOOBLE TELESCOPE</pattern><template>Hubble.</template></category><category><pattern>GET HIM TO THE HEALING ROOM  NOW</pattern><template>THOR: There won't be a kingdom to protect if you're afraid to act.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID YOUR PEOPLE GET INTO ASGARD</pattern><template>The House of Odin is full of traitors.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  JANE</pattern><template>Listen to me. You must not give up.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU PROMISED ME ANSWERS</pattern><template>What you seek, it's a bridge.</template></category><category><pattern>SO YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SHOWED US THE WAY INTO ASGARD</pattern><template>That was just a bit of fun, really.</template></category><category><pattern>MOTHER FEARS HE MAY NEVER AWAKEN AGAIN</pattern><template>We would speak with her.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR: THERE WON'T BE A KINGDOM TO PROTECT IF YOU'RE AFRAID TO ACT</pattern><template>The Jotuns must learn to fear me, just as they once feared you.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THAT CASE  I'LL BUY YOU ANOTHER ROUND  AND YOU LEAVE TOWN TONIGHT</pattern><template>Two boilermakers.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU  WHAT REALM IS THIS</pattern><template>Alfheim? Nornheim?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST DOWNLOADED  LIKE  30 SONGS ONTO THERE</pattern><template>Could you please stop with your iPod?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUSTN'T BLAME YOURSELF</pattern><template>I know that you loved him.</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT DOWN</pattern><template>We've got a perimeter breach.</template></category><category><pattern>REROUTE IT LIKE ALL THE OTHERS</pattern><template>Hold a sec.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER WAS TRYING TO TEACH ME SOMETHING  BUT I WAS TOO STUPID TO SEE IT</pattern><template>I don't know if you're delusional or if you're pulling some kind of con, I don't care.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOOK THE BACKUPS OF OUR BACKUPS</pattern><template>They were extremely thorough.</template></category><category><pattern>LOKI: AM I CURSED</pattern><template>ODIN: No.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  GOOD ONE</pattern><template>Go!</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A MASSIVE ELECTROMAGNETIC SURGE COMING OFF THAT THING</pattern><template>Systems are barely coping.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY NOT KILL HIM YOURSELF</pattern><template>I suspect that the Asgardians would not take kindly to a king who had murdered his predecessor.</template></category><category><pattern>LIVE  AND TELL THOSE STORIES YOURSELF</pattern><template>Now go.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS NO COINCIDENCE</pattern><template>We have to find out what's in that crater.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FRIENDS  WE'RE GOING TO JOTUNHEIM</pattern><template>You leave this to me.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS JOTUNHEIM</pattern><template>My father fought his way into Jotunheim, defeated their armies and took their Casket.</template></category><category><pattern>AGENT: BASE TO TEAM 2  WE'VE GOT ACTIVITY OUTSIDE THE TOWN  STAY ON YOUR TARGET  ENSURE MY BROTHER DOES NOT RETURN</pattern><template>Destroy everything.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK YOU'VE BEEN COMPLETELY HONEST WITH ME</pattern><template>Know this, Son of Coul.</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK: I THOUGHT YOU SAID IT WAS A SUBTLE AURORA</pattern><template>Go!</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO WHAT HE'S SAYING</pattern><template>He's talking about Mjolnir and Thor and Bifrost.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS JUST A BIT OF FUN  REALLY</pattern><template>To ruin my brother's big day.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  WE FOUND IT</pattern><template>You know, for a crazy homeless person, he's pretty cut.</template></category><category><pattern>TECHNICIAN: SIR  FEED FROM THE KEYHOLE CAN BARELY PENETRATE THE CLOUD COVER</pattern><template>Tech's barely working as it is, with all the interference that thing's giving off.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S RECKLESS  HE'S DANGEROUS</pattern><template>You saw how he was today.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS NO STOPPING HIM</pattern><template>FANDRAL: Well, at least he's only banished, not dead.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS SOMEBODY ELSE COMING</pattern><template>Is that one of Stark's?</template></category><category><pattern>CALL SECURITY</pattern><template>MAN: Security to ER 3, stat!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK YOU'RE JUST GONNA WALK IN  GRAB OUR STUFF AND WALK OUT</pattern><template>No. I'm going to fly out.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I WILL DIE A WARRIOR'S DEATH</pattern><template>Stories will be told of this day.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU ON EARTH THAT TURNED YOU SO SOFT</pattern><template>Don't tell me it was that woman.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WOULD SPEAK WITH HER</pattern><template>She has refused to leave my father's bedside.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN YOU HOPE TO PROTECT A KINGDOM</pattern><template>Get him to the healing room! Now!</template></category><category><pattern>(GROANS)   I'M SORRY  MY FRIEND</pattern><template>What happened?</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE NEVER DONE ANYTHING LIKE THIS BEFORE</pattern><template>Have you ever done anything like this before?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A MAN IN PAIN</pattern><template>ERIK: Oh, Donny, Donny, Donny!</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER FOUGHT HIS WAY INTO JOTUNHEIM  DEFEATED THEIR ARMIES AND TOOK THEIR CASKET</pattern><template>We would just be looking for answers.</template></category><category><pattern>FATHER  WE'LL FINISH THEM TOGETHER</pattern><template>Silence!</template></category><category><pattern>OR PERHAPS SOMEONE HAS FOUND A WAY TO HIDE THAT WHICH HE DOES NOT WISH ME TO SEE</pattern><template>You have great power, Heimdall.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  IT ALL MAKES SENSE NOW</pattern><template>Why you favored Thor all these years!</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER ALL I'VE DONE FOR YOU</pattern><template>So you're the one who showed us the way into Asgard.</template></category><category><pattern>A PRECURSOR TO SCIENCE FACT</pattern><template>In some cases, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>A MASTER OF MAGIC COULD BRING THREE JOTUNS INTO ASGARD</pattern><template>FANDRAL: Loki's always been one for mischief, but you're talking about something else entirely.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD HEIMDALL</pattern><template>You're not dressed warmly enough.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHY DID HE LIE</pattern><template>He kept the truth from you so that you would never feel different.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  IS THIS HOW YOU NORMALLY LOOK</pattern><template>More or less.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S ARROGANT</pattern><template>He's reckless. He's dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE FORGOTTEN EVERYTHING I TAUGHT YOU ABOUT A WARRIOR'S PATIENCE</pattern><template>While you wait and be patient, the Nine Realms laugh at us.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  OF COURSE</pattern><template>I come up here sometimes when I can't sleep or I'm trying to reconcile particle data, or when Darcy's driving me crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS IT</pattern><template>I thought we could unite our kingdoms one day.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  MAGIC'S JUST SCIENCE THAT WE DON'T UNDERSTAND YET</pattern><template>Arthur C. Clarke.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD WITH PATIENTS AND BAD WITH RELATIONSHIPS</pattern><template>They're the only clothes I had that would fit you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DID HE COME FROM</pattern><template>You all right?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T JUST BUY REPLACEMENTS AT RADIO SHACK  I MADE MOST OF THIS EQUIPMENT MYSELF</pattern><template>Then I'm sure you can do it again.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TAKING YOU HOME NOW</pattern><template>COULSON: Dr. Selvig!</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS DISTRAUGHT WHEN HE FOUND OUT THAT YOU'VE TAKEN ALL OUR RESEARCH</pattern><template>That was years of his life, gone!</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ACTION WOULD YOU TAKE</pattern><template>March into Jotunheim as you once did.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I'M KING  I'LL HUNT THE MONSTERS DOWN AND SLAY THEM ALL</pattern><template>Just as you did, Father.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL COME</pattern><template>In time.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WOULD HAVE HAULED THE WRECKAGE AWAY  THEY WOULDN'T HAVE BUILT A CITY AROUND IT</pattern><template>You're going to need this.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU SEEK  IT'S A BRIDGE</pattern><template>Like an Einstein Rosen Bridge?</template></category><category><pattern>HEIMDALL  MAY WE PASS</pattern><template>Never has an enemy slipped my watch until this day.</template></category><category><pattern>FOUND YOU</pattern><template>THOR: My friends!</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU CAN HEAR ME  WE NEED YOU NOW</pattern><template>Heimdall! We need you now! Heimdall!</template></category><category><pattern>RUN</pattern><template>Thor!</template></category><category><pattern>WE SHOULD NEVER HAVE REACHED JOTUNHEIM</pattern><template>You told the guard?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAVED HIM</pattern><template>I swear to you, Mother, that they will pay for what they've done today.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HAVE I</pattern><template>Now fight me.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE DAY WILL COME WHEN ONE OF YOU WILL HAVE TO DEFEND THAT PEACE</pattern><template>Do the Frost Giants still live?</template></category><category><pattern>ERIK: HE COMMITTED A CRIME  HE'S IN JAIL</pattern><template>JANE: I can't just leave him there!</template></category><category><pattern>IN SOME CASES  YEAH</pattern><template>Well, if there is an Einstein Rosen Bridge, then there's something on the other side.</template></category><category><pattern>GOODBYE</pattern><template>I just got back.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD</pattern><template>So you'll help us?</template></category><category><pattern>A WISE KING NEVER SEEKS OUT WAR</pattern><template>But he must always be ready for it.</template></category><category><pattern>THOR</pattern><template>Brother, please.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT WHAT THEY SAY IT IS</pattern><template>Well, whatever it is, the government seems to think it's theirs.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO</pattern><template>You know, it all makes sense now!</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER HAS AN ENEMY SLIPPED MY WATCH UNTIL THIS DAY</pattern><template>I wish to know how that happened.</template></category></AIML>