<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>I DON'T HAVE TO BE MUSLIM TO FIND THE IMAGES BEAUTIFUL  POETRY MOVING</pattern><template>Is it worth it?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T SHOOT  PLEASE DON'T SHOOT</pattern><template>Hold your fire!</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NO LONGER STANDING  BECAUSE IF I AM</pattern><template>...you'll all be dead before you've reloaded.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS TO YOU</pattern><template>Oh, I merely played my part.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DOES HE WEAR A GUY FAWKES MASK</pattern><template>Didn't Fawkes try to blow up Parliament?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STOLE THEM</pattern><template>Heavens, no.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS LOYALTY IS NOT IN QUESTION</pattern><template>But mine is?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M MERELY REMARKING UPON THE PARADOX OF ASKING A MASKED MAN WHO HE IS</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN ASSURE YOU  I MEAN YOU NO HARM</pattern><template>Who are you?</template></category><category><pattern>PUCKER UP  HERE COMES THE FINGER</pattern><template>Yeah. Get going. I'll handle him.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW WHERE YOU WERE BORN  WHO YOUR PARENTS WERE</pattern><template>...if you had any brothers or sisters.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT SHALL WE DO</pattern><template>No response from Command.</template></category><category><pattern>MOST AWARDED STARS   IN THE HISTORY OF THE BTN         A MAN KNOWN TO THE ENTIRE NATION   AS  THE VOICE OF LONDON          PASSED AWAY LATE LAST NIGHT   FROM APPARENT HEART FAILURE     SHE'S LYING</pattern><template>How do you know?</template></category><category><pattern>SURE</pattern><template>Even if it was someone working for this government?</template></category><category><pattern>I'D APPRECIATE IT IF YOU COULD HAVE A LOOK AT IT</pattern><template>Any information could be helpful.</template></category><category><pattern>BENEATH THIS MASK THERE IS MORE THAN FLESH</pattern><template>Beneath this mask there is an idea, Mr. Creedy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LOOK WELL</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN THEY THREATENED TO KILL YOU UNLESS YOU GAVE WHAT THEY WANTED</pattern><template>...you told them you'd rather die.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU PREFER A LIE OR THE TRUTH</pattern><template>Did you have anything to do with that?</template></category><category><pattern>FOR WHAT HAPPENED AT ST  MARY'S AND THREE WATERS</pattern><template>...if our own government was responsible for the deaths of almost 100,000 people...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS WHEN EVERYTHING CHANGED</pattern><template>My brother was one of the students   at St. Mary's.   After he died ,  my parents became political.   They protested the war   and the Reclamation.   When Sutler was appointed high chancellor ,  they were at the riot in Leeds.   I watched on the television...   ...thinking I was going   to see my parents killed.   I remember them arguing at night.   Mum wanted to leave the country.   Dad refused.   He said if we ran away, they would win.   Win, like...   ...it was a game.  Evey, quick, hide!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT MINE IS</pattern><template>Your mother was Irish, wasn't she?</template></category><category><pattern>TAUGHT ME HOW TO EAT  HOW TO DRINK  HOW TO BREATHE</pattern><template>I thought I'd die with all the hate in my veins.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD IS IN THE RAIN</pattern><template>V.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT A CHANCE TO TALK TO HER BEFORE SHE DISAPPEARS INTO ONE OF CREEDY'S BLACK BAGS</pattern><template>Who's that?</template></category><category><pattern>BRING HIM DOWN</pattern><template>Tonight we must remain steadfast.   We must remain determined.   But most of all ,  we must remain united.   Those caught tonight   in violation of curfew...   ...will be considered in league   with our enemy...   ...and prosecuted as a terrorist   without leniency or exception.  I want to see his face.</template></category><category><pattern>'TIS TOO MUCH PROVED</pattern><template>That with devotion's visage and pious action we do sugar o'er the devil himself.</template></category><category><pattern>AND EVERYTHING THAT WAS GOING TO HAPPEN</pattern><template>Hey, you!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I NEED TO KNOW THAT THIS QUESTION WILL NOT LEAVE THIS OFFICE</pattern><template>Yeah, of course, inspector, but...</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP  I DON'T WANT TO HEAR YOUR LIES</pattern><template>Your own father said that artists use lies to tell the truth.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I SHOULD GO</pattern><template>May I ask where?</template></category><category><pattern>BENEATH THIS MASK THERE IS AN IDEA  MR  CREEDY</pattern><template>And ideas are bulletproof.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S PAST CURFEW  YOU KNOW</pattern><template>My uncle, he's very sick.</template></category><category><pattern>THROUGH IT  OUR POLITICIAN WAS ULTIMATELY APPOINTED</pattern><template>...to the newly created position of high chancellor.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU ALREADY HAVE THE INFORMATION</pattern><template>All the names and dates are inside your head.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T CARE IF YOU ANSWER ME OR NOT</pattern><template>I just wanna say this aloud.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE GO</pattern><template>I did it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GONNA DIE HERE</pattern><template>Why protect someone who doesn't give a shit about you?</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD IT  STOP RIGHT THERE</pattern><template>You're Evey Hammond, aren't you?</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  MY FRIEND  HE'S KIND OF SICK</pattern><template>Ain't you?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A LIFT</pattern><template>It'll take us to the roof.</template></category><category><pattern>AGAIN  FROM WHAT WE'VE BEEN TOLD   BY AUTHORITIES  THE DANGER IS NOW OVER    THE TERRORIST IS DEAD   RIGHT THERE  WHAT'S HE THINKING</pattern><template>Is he considering leaving her?</template></category><category><pattern>SO DO YOU KNOW WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN</pattern><template>No. It was a feeling.</template></category><category><pattern>CHANCELLOR  I KNOW NO ONE SEEMS TO WANT TO DISCUSS THIS</pattern><template>...but if we're to be prepared for any eventuality...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU</pattern><template>It was you?</template></category><category><pattern>I UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>CAST VICARIOUSLY AS BOTH VICTIM AND VILLAIN BY THE VICISSITUDES OF FATE</pattern><template>This visage, no mere veneer of vanity...</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK SO</pattern><template>I should be getting home.</template></category><category><pattern>GOTTA GO</pattern><template>I don't recall getting stood up by a more attractive woman.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>We're interrupting your regularly scheduled   program to bring you this terrifying report...   ...of a terrorist takeover of Jordan Tower   which ended only moments ago.   A psychotic terrorist ,  identified only as the letter v...   ...attacked the control booth with   high powered explosives and weapons...   ...that he used against unarmed civilians   in order to broadcast a message of hate.   We've just received this footage   of a daring police raid.   Stop! Stop, stay where you are ,  or we'll shoot! Stay where you are!   Now, this is only an initial report...   ...but at this time, it's believed   that during this heroic raid...   ...the terrorist was shot and killed.  Bollocks.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WORE A UNIFORM IN THOSE DAYS</pattern><template>You.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY  BECAUSE AFTER THAT  ALL RECORD OF HER SEEMS TO STOP</pattern><template>She changed her name.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WON'T CRY LIKE HIM  WILL YOU</pattern><template>You're not afraid of death.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THE NAMES AND DATES ARE INSIDE YOUR HEAD</pattern><template>What you want, what you really need, is a story.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>Not as sorry as I am.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT</pattern><template>You're wondering why...</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT UNLESS YOU ARE READY TO OFFER YOUR COOPERATION  YOU ARE TO BE EXECUTED</pattern><template>Do you understand what I'm telling you?</template></category><category><pattern>V</pattern><template>Eyes and ears have detected movement heading to Trafalgar Square.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT BECAUSE YOU BELIEVED IT  YOU FOUND SOMETHING TRUE ABOUT YOURSELF</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANNA SAY THIS ALOUD</pattern><template>But I need to know that this question will not leave this office.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS CHRIST  MERCY</pattern><template>We are oft to blame in this...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  CAMCOS WERE CUT</pattern><template>It's the same m.o. As before.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THIS SHOULD BALANCE IT OUT</pattern><template>What are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THIS WORLD IS SCREWED UP</pattern><template>Believe me, I know it better than most.</template></category><category><pattern>GET THEIR MASKS OFF</pattern><template>Please hurry!</template></category><category><pattern>AND A TAP ON EVERY PHONE</pattern><template>Bollocks.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T</pattern><template>May I show you something before you go?</template></category><category><pattern>SPARE US YOUR PROFESSIONAL ANNOTATIONS    MR  FINCH  THEY ARE IRRELEVANT   APOLOGIES  CHANCELLOR</pattern><template>Gentlemen, this is a test.   Moments such as these   are matters of faith.   To fail is to invite doubt   into everything we believe...   ...everything we have fought for.   Doubt will plunge this country back   into chaos, and I will not let that happen.   Gentlemen, I want this terrorist found...   ...and I want him to understand   what terror really means.   England prevails.  England prevails.</template></category><category><pattern>HAS EVERYTHING BEEN ARRANGED</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN A YEAR FROM NOW</pattern><template>I have to stay here for a year?</template></category><category><pattern>AND FOUND TRACES OF THE EXPLOSIVES USED AT BOTH SITES</pattern><template>Unfortunately it appears that despite the heavy level of sophistication...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA FIND HIM NOW</pattern><template>Inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NOT COME FOR WHAT YOU HOPED TO DO</pattern><template>I've come for what you did.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S GETTING THE PICTURE</pattern><template>No, please, I didn't know. I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKES YOU WISH THAT NO ONE WOULD SHOW UP TONIGHT</pattern><template>But if they do, what do you think will happen?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE WE READY FOR IT</pattern><template>I missed this song.</template></category><category><pattern>CHRIST</pattern><template>I want anyone caught   with one of those masks arrested!  Give me the money!</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL GO HOME</pattern><template>I won't do it again, I swear! Please!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF WE'RE TO BE PREPARED FOR ANY EVENTUALITY</pattern><template>...then it can't be ignored any longer.</template></category><category><pattern>UNHAND ME  I AM YOUR CHANCELLOR    HOW DARE YOU  I AM THE CHANCELLOR    IMPOSTER    SOLDIERS  THAT MAN IS THE TERRORIST      I ORDER YOU TO SHOOT THAT TRAITOR      LIAR      FAKER      FRAUD      READY      AIM      FIRE      FIRE   WHAT ARE THEY GONNA DO  FINE US</pattern><template>Big deal. We've got the most watched show on air.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU BELIEVED THAT WAS ALL THERE WAS  DIDN'T YOU</pattern><template>The only thing you had left was your life, but it wasn't.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS THERE A SPECIFIC PROFILE FOR THOSE BEING SENT THERE</pattern><template>Usual undesirables, I should think.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  GET GOING  I'LL HANDLE HIM</pattern><template>Creedy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNEW THAT ONE DAY IT'D BE YOU OR HIM</pattern><template>That's why Sutler's been kept underground for security purposes.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T TOUCH ME</pattern><template>Look, Willy, kitty's got claws.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY DAY  I WANTED TO END IT</pattern><template>But each time you refused to give in, I knew I couldn't.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE DIED IN A HUNGER STRIKE</pattern><template>He died when the military retook the shed.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW EVERY COP'S LOOKING FOR ME</pattern><template>I know it's horrible of me to put you in this situation.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HE WAS MY FATHER</pattern><template>...and my mother.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE BEING BURIED BENEATH THE AVALANCHE   OF YOUR INADEQUACIES  MR  CREEDY   I'LL GET IT</pattern><template>Eric Finch?</template></category><category><pattern>HE PUT MASKS ON ALL OF US</pattern><template>Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  DASCOMB    WHAT ARE WE DOING ABOUT THAT   WE'RE CALLING IT AN EMERGENCY DEMOLITION</pattern><template>We have spin coverage on the network and throughout the InterLink.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR SUCH DISGUISE AS HAPLY SHALL BECOME THE FORM OF MY INTENT</pattern><template>Twelfth Night .</template></category><category><pattern>MY UNCLE  HE'S VERY SICK</pattern><template>Sick uncle? What you think on that, Willy?</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT</pattern><template>We're gonna need backup, but keep it minimal.</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH I WAS</pattern><template>...but I'm not.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DIED WHEN THE MILITARY RETOOK THE SHED</pattern><template>And that ain't the worst of it.</template></category><category><pattern>I FELT</pattern><template>Yes?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY DAY  I SAW IN MYSELF EVERYTHING YOU SEE IN ME NOW</pattern><template>Every day, I wanted to end it.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS ON MY WAY HERE  AND</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR 20 YEARS I SOUGHT ONLY THIS DAY</pattern><template>Nothing else existed...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE INSANE</pattern><template>I dare do all that may become a man.</template></category><category><pattern>I REMEMBER HOW THE MEANING OF WORDS   BEGAN TO CHANGE    HOW UNFAMILIAR WORDS LIKE  COLLATERAL    AND  RENDITION  BECAME FRIGHTENING         WHILE THINGS LIKE  NORSEFIRE  AND THE    ARTICLES OF ALLEGIANCE  BECAME POWERFUL    I REMEMBER HOW  DIFFERENT    BECAME DANGEROUS    I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND IT         WHY THEY HATE US SO MUCH    THEY TOOK RUTH   WHILE SHE WAS OUT BUYING FOOD    I'VE NEVER CRIED SO HARD IN MY LIFE    IT WASN'T LONG TILL THEY CAME FOR ME    IT SEEMS STRANGE THAT MY LIFE SHOULD END   IN SUCH A TERRIBLE PLACE    BUT FOR THREE YEARS    I HAD ROSES AND APOLOGIZED TO NO ONE    I SHALL DIE HERE    EVERY INCH OF ME SHALL PERISH    EVERY INCH         BUT ONE    AN INCH    IT IS SMALL  AND IT IS FRAGILE         AND IT IS THE ONLY THING   IN THE WORLD WORTH HAVING    WE MUST NEVER LOSE IT OR GIVE IT AWAY    WE MUST NEVER LET THEM TAKE IT FROM US    I HOPE THAT  WHOEVER YOU ARE    YOU ESCAPE THIS PLACE    I HOPE THAT THE WORLD TURNS   AND THAT THINGS GET BETTER    BUT WHAT I HOPE MOST OF ALL   IS THAT YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT I MEAN         WHEN I TELL YOU THAT   EVEN THOUGH I DO NOT KNOW YOU         AND EVEN THOUGH   I MAY NEVER MEET YOU         LAUGH WITH YOU  CRY WITH YOU         OR KISS YOU         I LOVE YOU    WITH ALL MY HEART         I LOVE YOU    VALERIE   I'M INSTRUCTED TO INFORM YOU THAT YOU HAVE BEEN CONVICTED BY SPECIAL TRIBUNAL</pattern><template>...and that unless you are ready to offer your cooperation, you are to be executed.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER  REMEMBER   THE 5TH OF NOVEMBER   THE GUNPOWDER TREASON AND PLOT   I KNOW OF NO REASON   WHY THE GUNPOWDER TREASON   SHOULD EVER BE FORGOT   BUT WHAT OF THE MAN    I KNOW HIS NAME WAS GUY FAWKES         AND I KNOW IN 1605  HE ATTEMPTED   TO BLOW UP THE HOUSES OF PARLIAMENT    BUT WHO WAS HE REALLY    WHAT WAS HE LIKE    WE ARE TOLD TO REMEMBER THE IDEA   AND NOT THE MAN    BECAUSE A MAN CAN FAIL    HE CAN BE CAUGHT    HE CAN BE KILLED AND FORGOTTEN    BUT 400 YEARS LATER         AN IDEA CAN STILL CHANGE THE WORLD    I HAVE WITNESSED FIRSTHAND   THE POWER OF IDEAS    I'VE SEEN PEOPLE KILL   IN THE NAME OF THEM         AND DIE DEFENDING THEM    BUT YOU CANNOT KISS AN IDEA         CANNOT TOUCH IT OR HOLD IT    IDEAS DO NOT BLEED    THEY DO NOT FEEL PAIN    THEY DO NOT LOVE    AND IT IS NOT AN IDEA THAT I MISS    IT IS A MAN    A MAN THAT MADE ME REMEMBER   THE 5TH OF NOVEMBER    A MAN THAT I WILL NEVER FORGET    SO I READ THAT THE FORMER UNITED STATES   IS SO DESPERATE FOR MEDICAL SUPPLIES         THAT THEY HAVE ALLEGEDLY SENT SEVERAL   CONTAINERS FILLED WITH WHEAT AND TOBACCO    A GESTURE  THEY SAID  OF GOODWILL    YOU WANNA KNOW WHAT I THINK    WELL  YOU'RE LISTENING TO MY SHOW    SO I WILL ASSUME YOU DO    IT'S HIGH TIME WE LET THE COLONIES KNOW   WHAT WE REALLY THINK OF THEM    I THINK IT'S PAYBACK TIME FOR A LITTLE TEA PARTY   THEY THREW FOR US A FEW HUNDRED YEARS AGO    I SAY WE GO DOWN TO THOSE DOCKS TONIGHT   AND DUMP THAT CRAP         WHERE EVERYTHING FROM   THE ULCERED SPHINCTER OF ASS ERICA BELONGS    WHO'S WITH ME  WHO'S BLOODY WITH ME     DID YOU LIKE THAT    U S A   ULCERED SPHINCTER OF ASS ERICA    I MEAN  WHAT ELSE CAN YOU SAY    HERE WAS A COUNTRY THAT HAD EVERYTHING    ABSOLUTELY EVERYTHING         AND NOW  20 YEARS LATER  IS WHAT    THE WORLD'S BIGGEST LEPER COLONY  WHY    GODLESSNESS    LET ME SAY THAT AGAIN    GODLESSNESS    IT WASN'T THE WAR THEY STARTED    IT WASN'T THE PLAGUE THEY CREATED    IT WAS JUDGMENT    NO ONE ESCAPES THEIR PAST    NO ONE ESCAPES JUDGMENT    YOU THINK HE'S NOT UP THERE    YOU THINK HE'S NOT WATCHING OVER   THIS COUNTRY    HOW ELSE CAN YOU EXPLAIN IT    HE TESTED US  BUT WE CAME THROUGH    WE DID WHAT WE HAD TO DO    ISLINGTON  ENFIELD    I WAS THERE  I SAW IT ALL    IMMIGRANTS  MUSLIMS         HOMOSEXUALS  TERRORISTS    DISEASE RIDDEN DEGENERATES    THEY HAD TO GO    STRENGTH THROUGH UNITY    UNITY THROUGH FAITH    I AM A GOD FEARING ENGLISHMAN    AND I'M GODDAMN PROUD OF IT   THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH OF THAT  THANK YOU VERY MUCH</pattern><template>Oh, shit.</template></category><category><pattern>OR FROM THE HIGH CHANCELLOR</pattern><template>Why are you doing this?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE GOT TO REWRITE IT  OKAY</pattern><template>Gotta go.</template></category><category><pattern>KILL HIM</pattern><template>My turn.</template></category><category><pattern>ARRESTS ARE AS HIGH AS THEY'VE BEEN SINCE THE RECLAMATION</pattern><template>I want more than arrests. I want results.    What's all this about?</template></category><category><pattern>KEEP COMMUNICATION TIGHT</pattern><template>I won't have this getting any more bollixed up than it already is.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  MOVE</pattern><template>May 27th.   Commander Prothero toured the lab   with a priest, Father Lilliman...   ...who I was told is here to monitor   for Rules and Rights violations.   It made me nervous, but the commander   assured me there wouldn't be a problem.   June 2nd.   I keep wondering if these people knew   how they might be helping their country...   ...if they would act any differently.   They're so weak and pathetic.   They never look you in the eye.   I find myself hating them.   August the 18th.   Of the original four dozen ,  over 75 percent are now deceased.   No controllable pattern has yet emerged.   September the 18th.   There is one case that continues   to give me hope.   He exhibits none of the immune system   pathologies the other subjects developed.   I've discovered cellular anomalies in his   blood that I've been unable to categorize.   The mutations seem to have triggered...   ...the abnormal development   of basic kinesthesia and reflexes.   The subject said   he could no longer remember...   ...who he was or where he was from.   Whoever he was ,  he is now the key to our dream...   ...and the hope that all of this   will not have been in vain.   November the 5th.   It started last night, around midnight.   The first explosions tore open   the entire medical section.   All my work, gone.   I was trying to understand how   it could've happened when I saw him.   The man from room 5.   He looked at me.   Not with eyes. There were no eyes.   But I know he was looking at me   because I felt it.   Oh, God...   ...what have I done?  What is that you're making?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF THEY DO  WHAT DO YOU THINK WILL HAPPEN</pattern><template>What usually happens when people without guns...</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>This whole thing started the night he blew up the old Bailey.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MEANS THAT WE EXERCISE OUR OWN JUDICIAL DISCRETION</pattern><template>And you get to swallow it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS DONE TO ME CREATED ME</pattern><template>It's a basic principle of the universe...</template></category><category><pattern>HE BELIEVES HE DID</pattern><template>Cost me more than this house, but no matter how bad I feel...</template></category><category><pattern>THEY PUT YOU IN A CELL AND TOOK EVERYTHING THEY COULD TAKE EXCEPT YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>And you believed that was all there was, didn't you?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M CELEBRATING</pattern><template>Celebrating what?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO MORE TRICKS  NO MORE LIES</pattern><template>Only truth.</template></category><category><pattern>AND  FOR BETTER OR WORSE  SHE'S STUCK WITH HIM</pattern><template>You scared me.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THERE'S NO WAY I CAN CONVINCE YOU   THIS IS NOT ONE OF THEIR TRICKS         BUT I DON'T CARE    I AM ME    MY NAME IS VALERIE    I DON'T THINK I'LL LIVE MUCH LONGER    AND I WANTED TO TELL SOMEONE ABOUT MY LIFE    THIS IS THE ONLY AUTOBIOGRAPHY   THAT I WILL EVER WRITE AND  GOD         I'M WRITING IT ON TOILET PAPER    I WAS BORN IN NOTTINGHAM IN 1985    I DON'T REMEMBER MUCH OF THOSE EARLY YEARS    BUT I DO REMEMBER THE RAIN    MY GRANDMOTHER OWNED A FARM   IN TOTTLE BROOK         AND SHE USED TO TELL ME   THAT GOD WAS IN THE RAIN    I PASSED MY 11 PLUS   AND WENT TO GIRLS' GRAMMAR    IT WAS AT SCHOOL   THAT I MET MY FIRST GIRLFRIEND    HER NAME WAS SARAH    IT WAS HER WRISTS    THEY WERE BEAUTIFUL    I THOUGHT WE WOULD   LOVE EACH OTHER FOREVER    I REMEMBER OUR TEACHER TELLING US         THAT IT WAS AN ADOLESCENT PHASE   THAT PEOPLE OUTGREW    SARAH DID    I DIDN'T    IN 2002  I FELL IN LOVE   WITH A GIRL NAMED CHRISTINA    THAT YEAR I CAME OUT TO MY PARENTS    I COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT   WITHOUT CHRIS HOLDING MY HAND    MY FATHER WOULDN'T LOOK AT ME    HE TOLD ME TO GO AND NEVER COME BACK    MY MOTHER SAID NOTHING    BUT I'D ONLY TOLD THEM THE TRUTH    WAS THAT SO SELFISH    OUR INTEGRITY SELLS FOR SO LITTLE    BUT IT IS ALL WE REALLY HAVE    IT IS THE VERY LAST INCH OF US    BUT WITHIN THAT INCH         WE ARE FREE   IT ENDS WHENEVER YOU WANT IT TO</pattern><template>Just tell us where he is.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU A MUSLIM</pattern><template>No, I'm in television.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY VERDICT IS VENGEANCE  A VENDETTA</pattern><template>...held as a votive not in vain, for the value and veracity of such...</template></category><category><pattern>THANK GOD</pattern><template>I'm sorry, I can't get a response   from that number.   There's a problem with the connection.  Jesus Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>THE REST  AS THEY SAY  IS HISTORY</pattern><template>Can you prove any of this?</template></category><category><pattern>AND TO REPAY HIM IN KIND FOR ALL THAT HE'S DONE</pattern><template>V, wait!</template></category><category><pattern>VIADOXIC AND ST  MARY'S IN LESS THAN A WEEK  COINCIDENCE</pattern><template>When you're at this as long as I've been, you stop believing in coincidence.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M UPSET</pattern><template>You just said you killed Lewis Prothero.</template></category><category><pattern>STEALING IMPLIES OWNERSHIP</pattern><template>You can't steal from the censor.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY  BECAUSE WHILE THE TRUNCHEON   MAY BE USED IN LIEU OF CONVERSATION         WORDS WILL ALWAYS RETAIN THEIR POWER    WORDS OFFER THE MEANS TO MEANING         AND  FOR THOSE WHO WILL LISTEN    THE ENUNCIATION OF TRUTH    AND THE TRUTH IS         THERE IS SOMETHING TERRIBLY WRONG   WITH THIS COUNTRY  ISN'T THERE   YOU DESIGNED IT  WANTED IT FOOLPROOF</pattern><template>You said every television in London!</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS  AND SPEAKING OF THE DEVIL</pattern><template>...I was wondering if your offer to help was still standing.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE LIES A DANGEROUS KILLING MACHINE WITH A FETISH FOR FAWKESIAN MASKS</pattern><template>That is not funny, Gordon.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  DON'T  I'M FINISHED AND GLAD OF IT</pattern><template>Don't say that.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN DO THIS</pattern><template>Hi.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEY</pattern><template>...may I ask you for something?</template></category><category><pattern>BLOODY HELL</pattern><template>How many went out?</template></category><category><pattern>MY BROTHER WAS ONE OF THE STUDENTS   AT ST  MARY'S    AFTER HE DIED    MY PARENTS BECAME POLITICAL    THEY PROTESTED THE WAR   AND THE RECLAMATION    WHEN SUTLER WAS APPOINTED HIGH CHANCELLOR    THEY WERE AT THE RIOT IN LEEDS    I WATCHED ON THE TELEVISION         THINKING I WAS GOING   TO SEE MY PARENTS KILLED    I REMEMBER THEM ARGUING AT NIGHT    MUM WANTED TO LEAVE THE COUNTRY    DAD REFUSED    HE SAID IF WE RAN AWAY  THEY WOULD WIN    WIN  LIKE         IT WAS A GAME   EVEY  QUICK  HIDE</pattern><template>Mummy!</template></category><category><pattern>IT APPEARS THAT THE ORIGINAL ELECTRONIC RECORDS HAVE ALL BEEN LOST</pattern><template>Probably during the Reclamation.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>Okay. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DAY AFTER THE ST  MARY'S OUTBREAK</pattern><template>...Percy gives his Beretta a blowjob, Keyes dies in a fire...</template></category><category><pattern>MY FAVORITE FILM:  THE COUNT OF MONTE CRISTO   WITH ROBERT DONAT AS EDMOND DANTES</pattern><template>It is not my sword, Mondego ,  but your past that disarmed you.  It gets me every time.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T STEAL FROM THE CENSOR</pattern><template>I merely reclaimed them.</template></category><category><pattern>OVER LAST MONTH'S POSITIVE MENTION IN ALL FOUR QUADRANTS</pattern><template>Mr. Creedy?    We're handling it as best we can.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FAT  METAL FRIEND</pattern><template>Mondego.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  YES  YES  I'M FINE</pattern><template>Can I ask what happened?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT</pattern><template>But on this most auspicious of nights...</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  OF COURSE  INSPECTOR  BUT</pattern><template>Because of the terrorist?</template></category><category><pattern>SOME PART OF HIM'S HUMAN</pattern><template>And, for better or worse, she's stuck with him.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CUT MY HAIR</pattern><template>You tortured me?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE LOOKED AT ME RIGHT IN THE EYES</pattern><template>...didn't recognize me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DIDN'T TAKE IT  DID YOU</pattern><template>Would you prefer a lie or the truth?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT HE WANTS</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>I HADN'T EXPECTED YOU TO BE QUITE SO JOHNNY ON THE SPOT</pattern><template>We were here before you even started.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HAS VOWED TO VANQUISH THESE VENAL AND VIRULENT VERMIN VANGUARDING VICE</pattern><template>...and vouchsafing the violently vicious and voracious violation of volition.</template></category><category><pattern>CHANCELLOR  CHANCELLOR  CHANCELLOR         I UNDERSTAND YOU'VE BEEN UNDER   TREMENDOUS STRAIN LATELY         SINCE THE BEGINNING   OF THIS WHOLE TERRORISM BUSINESS         AND WE THOUGHT IT WOULD BE A NICE IDEA   TO TRY AND HELP YOU RELAX  GIRLS    WARM MILK  THERE'S NOTHING BETTER    I UNDERSTAND YOU ENJOY A GLASS   EVERY NIGHT  CHANCELLOR    SINCE I WAS A BOY    BUT YOU'RE WRONG  MR  DEITRICH      THE TERRORIST WAS NEVER A SERIOUS CONCERN      OH  REALLY      CHANCELLOR  CHANCELLOR</pattern><template>It's him.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEEDED YOU</pattern><template>What's he doing in the dark there?</template></category><category><pattern>TANKS  ANTI AIRCRAFT  INFANTRY</pattern><template>Makes you wish that no one would show up tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D SAY SO  TWENTY YEARS NOW   GODDAMN IT</pattern><template>That son of a bitch sat there...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN LARKHILL</pattern><template>Major Wilson is a friend of the high chancellor.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I DON'T THINK YOU'LL UNDERSTAND WHY UNLESS YOU KNOW A FEW THINGS ABOUT ME</pattern><template>My father was a writer.</template></category><category><pattern>THE QUESTION I HAVE TO ASK  IS: WHAT IF THE WORST</pattern><template>...the most horrifying biological attack in this country's history...</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE HE WAS THE VOICE OF LONDON</pattern><template>Drugs?</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER THAT  THERE WERE NO ROSES ANYMORE    NOT FOR ANYONE   YOU WON'T LAST MUCH LONGER</pattern><template>You're gonna die here.</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY THE ILLUSION OF COINCIDENCE</pattern><template>I have another rose.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD HAVE ENDED IT</pattern><template>You could have given in, but you didn't.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'VE SENT A NEW GIRL WHO  I'M AFRAID  IS A LITTLE OLDER THAN USUAL</pattern><template>Older?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE COME TO KILL ME</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU READY TO COOPERATE</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU REALLY WANNA KNOW</pattern><template>This has to be the bloody coldest   March in years.   Keep talking like that ,  we'll lose our party status.     They're a pack of lying, greedy hypocrites!     Keep it down, will you?  Based on random audio sweeps, I've projected that right now...</template></category><category><pattern>COULD BE DEVASTATING TO OUR CREDIBILITY</pattern><template>Perhaps a stroke?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THAT  MUM</pattern><template>whereby important events of the past...   ...usually associated with someone's death   or the end of some awful, bloody struggle...   ...are celebrated with a nice holiday...   ...I thought we could mark   this November the 5th...   ...a day that is, sadly ,  no longer remembered...   ...by taking some time out of our daily lives   to sit down and have a little chat.   There are, of course ,  those who do not want us to speak.  Let me think, let me think.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SHE DID  THAT SHE DID</pattern><template>You know what that means, don't you?</template></category><category><pattern>MR  CREEDY</pattern><template>Disgusting.</template></category><category><pattern>TREASON AND SEDITION  THE PENALTY FOR WHICH IS DEATH BY FIRING SQUAD</pattern><template>You have one chance, and only one chance, to save your life.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD UNDOUBTEDLY FIND MYSELF WITHOUT A HOME  LET ALONE A TELEVISION SHOW</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS ON MY WAY LAST NIGHT  BUT THERE WERE FINGERMEN</pattern><template>...and I got scared and went home.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I JUST THOUGHT YOU WERE FIGHTING</pattern><template>I mean, for real.</template></category><category><pattern>AIN'T YOU</pattern><template>Real sick. Bad case of the blues.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN WE FIRST MET  ALL THOSE YEARS AGO</pattern><template>You wore a uniform in those days.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHO WILL THAT BE</pattern><template>You, Mr. Creedy.</template></category><category><pattern>TRY TO FEEL NOW WHAT YOU FELT THEN</pattern><template>Oh, God.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I GOT SCARED AND WENT HOME</pattern><template>Sadly, after last night, I think our curfew will only get worse.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAID I WOULD</pattern><template>You look well.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS GIVEN ONE OF YOUR ROSES TODAY</pattern><template>I wasn't sure you were the terrorist until I saw it.</template></category><category><pattern>ME</pattern><template>If you accept, put an X on your front door.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>His music.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SURE ABOUT THAT  SIR</pattern><template>I want a chance to talk to her before she disappears into one of Creedy's black bags.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS WHOLE THING STARTED THE NIGHT HE BLEW UP THE OLD BAILEY</pattern><template>I was on my way here, and...</template></category><category><pattern>DEFIANT TO THE END  HUH</pattern><template>You won't cry like him, will you?</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE  HE WAS RIGHT  WASN'T HE</pattern><template>There is something wrong with this country.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN NOT LONG AFTER THE ELECTION    LO AND BEHOLD  A MIRACLE    SOME BELIEVED IT WAS THE WORK   OF GOD HIMSELF    BUT IT WAS A PHARMACEUTICAL COMPANY   CONTROLLED BY CERTAIN PARTY MEMBERS         THAT MADE THEM ALL OBSCENELY RICH   A YEAR LATER  SEVERAL EXTREMISTS ARE TRIED  FOUND GUILTY AND EXECUTED</pattern><template>...while a memorial is built to canonize their victims.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  WE ARE BOTH FUGITIVES IN OUR OWN WAY</pattern><template>But...</template></category><category><pattern>A FAREWELL GIFT</pattern><template>For all the things you've done, for the things you might have done...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE UPSET</pattern><template>I'm upset?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST TELL US WHERE HE IS</pattern><template>I don't know.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT TOO LATE</pattern><template>He's still got another 16 hours.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH OLD ODD ENDS STOLEN FORTH FROM HOLY WRIT</pattern><template>...and seem a saint, when most I play the devil.</template></category><category><pattern>SEVERAL EXPERTS HAVE BEEN LINED UP TO TESTIFY AGAINST THE BAILEY'S STRUCTURAL INTEGRITY</pattern><template>I want Prothero to speak on   the dangers of these old buildings...   ...and how we must avoid clinging   to the edifice of a decadent past.   He should conclude that the New Bailey   will become the symbol of our time...   ...and the future   that our conviction has rewarded us.   Mr. Heyer.  Our surveillance cameras captured several images of the terrorist...</template></category><category><pattern>OR FROM PARTY LEADER CREEDY</pattern><template>Or from the high chancellor.</template></category><category><pattern>UNFORTUNATELY IT APPEARS THAT DESPITE THE HEAVY LEVEL OF SOPHISTICATION</pattern><template>...these devices were homemade with over the counter chemicals...</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE UNDER SIEGE HERE</pattern><template>The whole city's gone mad.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S USING OUR SMOKE MACHINES</pattern><template>Cover the exits.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAME WHEN THEY OPENED IT</pattern><template>It gave me the collywobbles.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN IF IT WAS SOMEONE WORKING FOR THIS GOVERNMENT</pattern><template>That's my question.</template></category><category><pattern>COVER THE EXITS</pattern><template>No one gets out.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T FEEL ANYTHING ANYMORE</pattern><template>Don't run from it, Evey.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE GOT NOTHING</pattern><template>Nothing but your bloody knives and your fancy karate gimmicks.</template></category><category><pattern>PROTECT ME</pattern><template>I should've hired him to be my mother.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A DELIGHTFUL MIND YOU HAVE</pattern><template>I hope the rest of you is just as interesting.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>Did you know her?</template></category><category><pattern>ANY LEADS ON FINDING THIS GUY</pattern><template>Nothing yet. But there's something else you can help me with.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S THERE</pattern><template>After what happened, after what they did...</template></category><category><pattern>BOLLOCKS</pattern><template>What are you gonna do, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>I MISSED THIS SONG</pattern><template>I didn't think you'd come.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S MY QUESTION</pattern><template>If our own government was responsible...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU IMAGINE THAT'S GONNA HAPPEN</pattern><template>With my hands around your neck.</template></category><category><pattern>ATTENTION  ATTENTION    WILL ALL PERSONNEL PLEASE   EVACUATE THE BUILDING    THIS IS NOT A DRILL    WILL ALL PERSONNEL EVACUATE THE BUILDING   WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON</pattern><template>It's jammed.</template></category><category><pattern>HE LEAVES THEM AT THE CRIME SCENES</pattern><template>I'd appreciate it if you could have a look at it.</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY THE THINGS THAT MATTER</pattern><template>What if they come after you?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DID I DO THAT</pattern><template>You did what you thought was right.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS LIKE A PERFECT PATTERN LAID OUT IN FRONT OF ME</pattern><template>...and I realized that we were all a part of it...</template></category><category><pattern>OUR STORY BEGINS  AS THESE STORIES OFTEN DO</pattern><template>...with a young, up and coming politician.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN LET ME MAKE THIS PERFECTLY CLEAR TO YOU    THE CONTENTS OF THIS DOCUMENT   ARE A MATTER OF NATIONAL SECURITY         CONSTITUTING AN ASSAULT ON THE CHARACTER   OF SEVERAL IMPORTANT PARTY MEMBERS         AS WELL AS A BLATANT VIOLATION   OF THE ARTICLES OF ALLEGIANCE    AS THE AUTHENTICITY OF THIS DOCUMENT   CANNOT BE VERIFIED         IT COULD BE AN ELABORATE FORGERY   CREATED BY THE TERRORIST         AS EASILY AS IT COULD BE THE DERANGED   FANTASY OF A FORMER PARTY MEMBER         WHO RESIGNED   FOR PSYCHOLOGICAL REASONS    ANY DISCUSSION OF THIS DOCUMENT   OR ITS CONTENTS         WILL BE REGARDED  AT THE VERY LEAST    AS AN ACT OF SEDITION         IF NOT A WILLFUL ACT OF TREASON      IS THAT UNDERSTOOD  MR  FINCH     YES  SIR</pattern><template>You would do well, inspector...   ...to put it out of your mind.   May 23rd.   My first batch of subjects arrived today...   ...and I have to admit   that I'm very excited.   This could be the dawn of a new age.   Nuclear power is meaningless...   ...in a world where a virus   can kill an entire population...   ...and leave its wealth intact.    Stay together!</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS EDMOND DANTES</pattern><template>And he was my father...</template></category><category><pattern>CONCEAL ME WHAT I AM  AND BE MY AID</pattern><template>...for such disguise as haply shall become the form of my intent.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BEGIN TO LOSE MORE THAN JUST YOUR APPETITE</pattern><template>You wear a mask for so long, you forget who you were beneath it.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW IT'S HORRIBLE OF ME TO PUT YOU IN THIS SITUATION</pattern><template>Evey...</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T SHOOT ME  PLEASE  IT'S HIM  IT'S HIM</pattern><template>On your knees! On your knees!</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU</pattern><template>It was like a perfect pattern laid out in front of me...</template></category><category><pattern>ALL BUT ONE</pattern><template>Who is she?</template></category><category><pattern>VERY WELL</pattern><template>Escort Miss Hammond back to her cell.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I SEE</pattern><template>There's no court in this country for men like Prothero.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>Enemy is approaching fast.</template></category><category><pattern>SO I PICKED YOU UP AND CARRIED YOU TO THE ONLY PLACE I KNEW YOU'D BE SAFE: HERE  TO MY HOME</pattern><template>I won't tell anyone, I swear.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO</pattern><template>Evey!</template></category><category><pattern>COST ME MORE THAN THIS HOUSE  BUT NO MATTER HOW BAD I FEEL</pattern><template>...it always cheers me up.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BEAUTIFUL UP HERE</pattern><template>A more perfect stage could not be asked for.</template></category><category><pattern>A MAN SEEMINGLY   WITHOUT A CONSCIENCE         FOR WHOM THE ENDS   ALWAYS JUSTIFY THE MEANS    HE SUGGESTS THAT THEIR TARGET   SHOULD NOT BE AN ENEMY OF THE COUNTRY         BUT RATHER  THE COUNTRY ITSELF    THREE TARGETS ARE CHOSEN   TO MAXIMIZE THE EFFECT OF THE ATTACK:   A SCHOOL  A TUBE STATION   AND A WATER TREATMENT PLANT    SEVERAL HUNDRED DIE   WITHIN THE FIRST FEW WEEKS   THREE WATERS HAS  IN FACT  BEEN CONTAMINATED</pattern><template>Authorities are attempting to control its deadly spread.</template></category><category><pattern>MY BROTHER</pattern><template>My friend.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I SHOW YOU SOMETHING BEFORE YOU GO</pattern><template>She was real.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW IT'S UNDERGROUND</pattern><template>You know the color of the stone.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SHOW YOU THE FIRMNESS OF MY BELIEFS</pattern><template>Stop it! Get off of me!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD BE IN TERRIBLE TROUBLE</pattern><template>Evey, listen to me.</template></category><category><pattern>IT TOOK NEARLY 10 YEARS TO CLEAR THE TRACKS AND LAY A BIT OF MY OWN</pattern><template>Let me show you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU LITTLE BITCH  YOU FUCKING LITTLE WHORE</pattern><template>Reverend.</template></category><category><pattern>ALMOST</pattern><template>Stop. Get your hand off that lever.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A DEEPLY RELIGIOUS MAN AND A MEMBER OF THE CONSERVATIVE PARTY</pattern><template>He's completely single minded   and has no regard for the political process.   The more power he attains ,  the more obvious his zealotry...   ...and the more aggressive   his supporters become.   Eventually, his party launches a special   project in the name of national security.   At first it's believed to be a search   for biological weapons...   ...and it's pursued without regard   to its cost.   However, the true goal   of this project is power.   Complete and total   hegemonic domination.   The project, however, ends violently.   But the efforts of those involved   are not in vain...   ...for a new ability to wage war is born   from the blood of one of the victims.  Imagine a virus, the most terrifying virus you can...</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER YOU DID TO ME WORKED BETTER THAN I'D HAVE IMAGINED</pattern><template>I have a gift for you, Evey...</template></category><category><pattern>OF CODE NAME V</pattern><template>If your information leads to his capture...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M LEAVING TO YOU TO DO WITH WHAT YOU WILL</pattern><template>Is this another trick, V?</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SHOW YOU</pattern><template>These tracks lead to Parliament.</template></category><category><pattern>ALONE  A SYMBOL IS MEANINGLESS  BUT WITH ENOUGH PEOPLE</pattern><template>...blowing up a building can change the world.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT THEY'D ARREST HIM</pattern><template>...but when they found a Koran in his house, they had him executed.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MY MOTHER</pattern><template>My brother.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW YOU MAY NEVER FORGIVE ME</pattern><template>...but nor will you understand how hard it was for me.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHO WAS</pattern><template>I cannot recall specific names, but if you look through our records...</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE I NO LONGER BELIEVED I COULD</pattern><template>V, I don't want you to die.</template></category><category><pattern>SEVERAL HUNDRED THOUSAND  AT LEAST</pattern><template>Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>I UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU DID FOR ME  AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW I AM GRATEFUL</pattern><template>Your hands.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN IT REALLY HAPPENED  DIDN'T IT</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE SPIN COVERAGE ON THE NETWORK AND THROUGHOUT THE INTERLINK</pattern><template>Several experts have been lined up to testify against the Bailey's structural integrity.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURE YOU WOULD</pattern><template>But if you want that recording, you'll do what I tell you to do.</template></category><category><pattern>HI</pattern><template>I've been thinking...</template></category><category><pattern>BLOODY COINCIDENCES ARE MAKING ME SICK TO MY STOMACH</pattern><template>Rookwood.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Bloody hell.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE LISTENED TO THEM ALL  BUT I'VE NEVER DANCED TO ANY OF THEM</pattern><template>Did you hear me?</template></category><category><pattern>A RATHER INTIMATE UNDERSTANDING OF OUR SYSTEM</pattern><template>The chancellor suspects there might be an informer.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE LONG CHAIN OF EVENTS THAT STRETCHED   ALL THE WAY BACK BEFORE LARKHILL   I FELT LIKE I COULD SEE EVERYTHING THAT HAD HAPPENED</pattern><template>...and everything that was going to happen.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WERE THREE MEN</pattern><template>Covert intel.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH SMOKED WITH BLOODY EXECUTION</pattern><template>We're Fingermen, pal.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE LET ME KNOW</pattern><template>If you wish.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY  I'VE MADE SURE OUR REUNION WON'T BE DISTURBED BY</pattern><template>...any pesky late night phone calls, commander.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S MY HOME</pattern><template>I call it the Shadow Gallery.</template></category><category><pattern>NO PRINTS  NO HAIR  NO FIBERS</pattern><template>The guy is like a ghost.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO TREE WAITING FOR ME</pattern><template>All I want, all I deserve, is at the end of that tunnel.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SCARED ME</pattern><template>My apologies.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD EVENING  COMMANDER PROTHERO</pattern><template>Oh, my God! How did you get in here?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  PLEASE</pattern><template>You found something else.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE JUST THREATENED US</pattern><template>That she did, that she did.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GETTING BACK AT THEM FOR WHAT THEY DID TO HER</pattern><template>And to you.</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY UNTIL I'M DONE</pattern><template>After the 5th, I no longer think it'll matter.</template></category><category><pattern>AND DEITRICH IS READY FOR HIS TEA</pattern><template>I don't get it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WILL BE RELEASED FROM THIS FACILITY IMMEDIATELY</pattern><template>Do you understand what I'm telling you?</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU KNOW LEWIS PROTHERO WAS ONE OF THE RICHEST MEN IN THE COUNTRY</pattern><template>...before he was the Voice of London?</template></category><category><pattern>A STORY CAN BE TRUE OR FALSE</pattern><template>I leave such judgments to you, inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M AFRAID THAT WON'T WORK EITHER</pattern><template>You have to understand, Evey, I didn't want this for either of us...</template></category><category><pattern>DAMN IT</pattern><template>The terrorist obviously wanted us to have it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF YOU WANT THAT RECORDING  YOU'LL DO WHAT I TELL YOU TO DO</pattern><template>Put Creedy under 24 hour surveillance.</template></category><category><pattern>ALTHOUGH THE DEMOLITION HAD BEEN   PLANNED FOR SOME TIME         THE MUSIC AND THE FIREWORKS WERE    ACCORDING TO THE CREW CHIEF            DEFINITELY NOT ON THE SCHEDULE       WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK   DO YOU BELIEVE THAT LOAD OF BOLLOCKS</pattern><template>I mean, there was no bloody demolition.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO</pattern><template>You should've left me alone.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE</pattern><template>You've been charged with three counts of murder...</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY I'M NOT A STRONGER PERSON</pattern><template>Sorry I'm not like my parents.</template></category><category><pattern>MY GOD  HE'S KILLED THEM ALL</pattern><template>All but one.</template></category><category><pattern>I SHOULD BE GETTING HOME</pattern><template>I promise you, it'll be like nothing you've ever seen.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE ENEMY CONTACT</pattern><template>Hold it. Stop right there.</template></category><category><pattern>HELP  STORM  HELP   DON'T TOUCH IT</pattern><template>Dad, what's wrong with the telly?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WON'T BELIEVE WHAT THEY FOUND ON PROTHERO</pattern><template>Drugs?</template></category><category><pattern>IS EVERYTHING A JOKE TO YOU</pattern><template>Only the things that matter.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WONDERING WHY</pattern><template>...you were invited here to supper in the first place...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHY WOULD YOU KEEP IT</pattern><template>I don't have to be Muslim to find the images beautiful, poetry moving.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY THING YOU HAD LEFT WAS YOUR LIFE  BUT IT WASN'T</pattern><template>Oh, please.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THE STRINGS</pattern><template>Listen carefully, can you hear it?</template></category><category><pattern>I SHOULD'VE HIRED HIM TO BE MY MOTHER</pattern><template>You're mad.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD BE AN AIRBORNE ATTACK</pattern><template>A separate report has been filed...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT NOR WILL YOU UNDERSTAND HOW HARD IT WAS FOR ME</pattern><template>Every day, I saw in myself everything you see in me now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR RECORDS ARE EITHER DELETED  OMITTED OR MISSING</pattern><template>As head of the Detention Program at that...</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT I'D DIE WITH ALL THE HATE IN MY VEINS</pattern><template>But then something happened.</template></category><category><pattern>IS A VESTIGE OF THE VOX POPULI  NOW VACANT  VANISHED</pattern><template>However, this valorous visitation of a bygone vexation stands vivified...</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL HAVE TO MAKE SOME KIND OF APOLOGY  DO SOME BORING FUNDRAISER</pattern><template>In the meantime, our ratings will go through the roof. It'll be fine. Trust me.</template></category><category><pattern>MY NOSE LOOKS LIKE BIG FUCKING BEN</pattern><template>Listen to me, you bleeding sod, England prevails because I say it does!</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GOD  NO  PLEASE DON'T DO THIS</pattern><template>I'll go home.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT CREEDY UNDER 24 HOUR SURVEILLANCE</pattern><template>When I feel safe he can't pick his nose without you knowing...</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE</pattern><template>Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>TILL SHE APPLIED FOR AN OVERSEAS VISA  WHICH WAS DENIED</pattern><template>Running away?</template></category><category><pattern>HE ALWAYS TOLD THE BEST STORIES</pattern><template>Until my brother died.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ON MY WAY TO GIVE A VERY SPECIAL PERFORMANCE</pattern><template>What kind of musician?</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE PURSUIT OF FINDING ME</pattern><template>After what you did, I couldn't let that happen...</template></category><category><pattern>WHY</pattern><template>Because this world...</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKS LIKE HE WAS PROMOTED</pattern><template>He's a bishop now.</template></category><category><pattern>BE IN PLAYS  MOVIES</pattern><template>When I was 9, I played Viola in  Twelfth Night . Mum was very proud.</template></category><category><pattern>MEN THAT CAN BE COUNTED ON</pattern><template>All you have to do is say the word.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL IS THIS</pattern><template>Just put them over there until I can figure out what they're for.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FRIEND</pattern><template>He was you...</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I ARRIVE IN THE MORNING  THE PADDY WILL BE GONE</pattern><template>I'm looking at the tape right now, and he has no idea how to light me.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  CREEDY  I AM HOLDING YOU   PERSONALLY RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS SITUATION    THE PROBLEM IS THAT HE KNOWS US   BETTER THAN WE KNOW OURSELVES   THAT'S WHY I WENT TO LARKHILL LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>That's outside quarantine.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU HAD ANY BROTHERS OR SISTERS</pattern><template>I don't even know what you really look like.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ME</pattern><template>He was all of us.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO</pattern><template>Who is but the form following the function of what...</template></category><category><pattern>NOVEMBER THE 4TH</pattern><template>Not anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GOING TO KILL ME NOW</pattern><template>I killed you 10 minutes ago...</template></category><category><pattern>WHILE POLITICIANS USED THEM TO COVER THE TRUTH UP</pattern><template>A man after my own heart.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS  RATHER  MY FINAL REMITTANCE THAT I WAS INTERESTED IN</pattern><template>My last little joy.</template></category><category><pattern>CREEDY</pattern><template>What are you doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THEY DID WAS ONLY POSSIBLE BECAUSE OF YOU</pattern><template>Oppenheimer was able to change more than the course of a war.</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR TO YOU</pattern><template>Read my journal.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MUSIC</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THIS COULD BE THE BEST SHOW WE'VE EVER DONE</pattern><template>Very good evening ,  ladies and gentlemen.   Listen, we've got an extraordinary   show for you tonight.   You're not gonna believe it.   As a matter of fact, I don't think I do.   Will you please give   a very warm welcome...   ...to our own Chancellor Adam Sutler!    No way!</template></category><category><pattern>DISDAINING FORTUNE  WITH HIS BRANDISH'D STEEL</pattern><template>...which smoked with bloody execution.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR GRACE</pattern><template>To think that I doubted your loveliness for an instant.</template></category><category><pattern>PERCUSSION INSTRUMENTS ARE MY SPECIALITY</pattern><template>But tonight I intend to call upon the entire orchestra for this event...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT MADE ME FEEL SORRY FOR MERCEDES</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO SEE IT</pattern><template>There wasn't much left.   But when I was there, it was strange.  I suddenly had this feeling that everything was connected.</template></category><category><pattern>JUVENILE RECLAMATION PROJECT</pattern><template>...for five years.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT SUTLER HAD IT DESTROYED</pattern><template>He believes he did.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DID YOU GET IT</pattern><template>A government supply train on its way to Chancellor Sutler.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE A LOOK AT THIS</pattern><template>Prothero's military record.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING WE'VE GOT ON LARKHILL IS IN THERE</pattern><template>Thanks. This is a great help.</template></category><category><pattern>TWELFTH NIGHT</pattern><template>Viola.</template></category><category><pattern>DISGUSTING</pattern><template>Now that's done with...</template></category><category><pattern>I MUST CONFESS  EVERY TIME I HEARD A SIREN  I WORRIED ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>I worried about myself for a while.</template></category><category><pattern>HOME  I HAVE TO GO HOME</pattern><template>They're looking for you. If they know where you work, they know where you live.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS A STRANGE COINCIDENCE</pattern><template>Although there's an obvious explanation.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOOK YOUR PARENTS FROM YOU</pattern><template>They took your brother from you.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU'RE MY AGENT  THAT'S WHAT I PAY YOU FOR</pattern><template>Protect me.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS GENERAL ACKROYD</pattern><template>Keep communication tight.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LAST  WE FINALLY MEET</pattern><template>I have something for you, chancellor.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT WHAT</pattern><template>That this country needs more than a building right now. It needs hope.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO DARES MORE IS NONE</pattern><template>Macbeth.    Very good.</template></category><category><pattern>AND FOR THE ONLY THING YOU HAVE LEFT</pattern><template>Goodbye, chancellor.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS CAPTAIN CLARK         OF THE 137TH WARD AT SOUTHEND      WE FOUND HIM     FOUND WHO</pattern><template>William Rookwood ,  the one you're looking for.   I saw your report a couple weeks back ,  thought I'd run it through our John Does.   I hooked him. Perfect dental match.   A floater. Fishermen picked him up.   No ID, never solved. Till now, that is.    William Rookwood is dead?</template></category><category><pattern>INSPECTOR</pattern><template>It's all gone wrong, hasn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THERE YOU HAVE IT</pattern><template>This is a matter of some urgency, major.</template></category><category><pattern>IS HE CONSIDERING LEAVING HER</pattern><template>After she just saved him?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THAT BEEN X RAYED</pattern><template>Nope. They're filled with bombs.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I ASK WHERE</pattern><template>Home. I have to go home.</template></category><category><pattern>MAJOR WILSON IS A FRIEND OF THE HIGH CHANCELLOR</pattern><template>His loyalty is not in question.</template></category><category><pattern>I MUST HAVE BEEN OUT OF MY MIND</pattern><template>Is that what you really think, or what they'd want you to think?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE DETAINED WHEN SHE WAS 12</pattern><template>What happened to her?</template></category><category><pattern>GET OUT THE WAY</pattern><template>Damn it!</template></category><category><pattern>INTERESTING</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU WANT  WHAT YOU REALLY NEED  IS A STORY</pattern><template>A story can be true or false.</template></category><category><pattern>AND EVER SINCE  I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO ACT</pattern><template>Be in plays, movies.</template></category><category><pattern>THE UNDERGROUND</pattern><template>I thought they closed this all down.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I WERE YOU  CHIEF INSPECTOR</pattern><template>...I'd find the terrorist...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT EACH TIME YOU REFUSED TO GIVE IN  I KNEW I COULDN'T</pattern><template>You're sick! You're evil!</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD YOUR FIRE</pattern><template>Freeze! Nobody move!</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE NOT  I WASN'T STATIONED THERE</pattern><template>Do you know who was?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT EVERY ACTION WILL CREATE AN EQUAL AND OPPOSING REACTION</pattern><template>Is that how you see it?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT</pattern><template>You're getting back at them for what they did to her.</template></category><category><pattern>AUTHORITIES ARE ATTEMPTING TO CONTROL ITS DEADLY SPREAD</pattern><template>Sent destruction through the Underground.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU SEE</pattern><template>Iraq, Kurdistan, Syria, before and after, Sudan.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE FINGERMEN</pattern><template>She's getting the picture.</template></category><category><pattern>ESCORT MISS HAMMOND BACK TO HER CELL</pattern><template>Arrange a detail of six men...</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS</pattern><template>You could let it go.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THAT</pattern><template>It's a copy of the Koran, 14th century.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  FOR REAL</pattern><template>My favorite film:  The Count of Monte Cristo , with Robert Donat as Edmond Dantes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT TO ME</pattern><template>You did this to me?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T SHOOT</pattern><template>Wait!</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANT TO DIE   THIS IS SURVEILLANCE 109</pattern><template>We have an emergency.</template></category><category><pattern>IF OUR OWN GOVERNMENT WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE DEATHS OF ALMOST 100 000 PEOPLE</pattern><template>...would you really wanna know?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS NO ORDINARY SITUATION AND REQUIRES MORE THAN YOUR ORDINARY ATTENTION</pattern><template>The chancellor demanded my immediate involvement.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHEN THEY DO</pattern><template>...things will turn nasty.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE BEEN CHARGED WITH THREE COUNTS OF MURDER</pattern><template>...the bombing of government property, conspiracy to commit terrorism...</template></category><category><pattern>HER BROTHER WAS AT ST  MARY'S</pattern><template>Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR HANDS</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>NOPE  THEY'RE FILLED WITH BOMBS</pattern><template>Well, wait till commercials to set them off, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  INSPECTOR  I SIMPLY CANNOT RECALL</pattern><template>Was there a specific profile for those being sent there?</template></category><category><pattern>WILLIAM ROOKWOOD    THE ONE YOU'RE LOOKING FOR    I SAW YOUR REPORT A COUPLE WEEKS BACK    THOUGHT I'D RUN IT THROUGH OUR JOHN DOES    I HOOKED HIM  PERFECT DENTAL MATCH    A FLOATER  FISHERMEN PICKED HIM UP    NO ID  NEVER SOLVED  TILL NOW  THAT IS     WILLIAM ROOKWOOD IS DEAD</pattern><template>I'd say so. Twenty years now.  Goddamn it!</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT</pattern><template>Hold your fire!</template></category><category><pattern>IT BUILT MY WORLD  IMPRISONED ME</pattern><template>...taught me how to eat, how to drink, how to breathe.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE TRACKS LEAD TO PARLIAMENT</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY PROTECT SOMEONE WHO DOESN'T GIVE A SHIT ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>I remember how the meaning of words   began to change.   How unfamiliar words like  collateral    and  rendition  became frightening...   ...while things like  Norsefire  and the    Articles of Allegiance  became powerful.   I remember how  different    became dangerous.   I still don't understand it...   ...why they hate us so much.   They took Ruth   while she was out buying food.   I've never cried so hard in my life.   It wasn't long till they came for me.   It seems strange that my life should end   in such a terrible place.   But for three years ,  I had roses and apologized to no one.   I shall die here.   Every inch of me shall perish.   Every inch...   ...but one.   An inch.   It is small, and it is fragile...   ...and it is the only thing   in the world worth having.   We must never lose it or give it away.   We must never let them take it from us.   I hope that, whoever you are ,  you escape this place.   I hope that the world turns   and that things get better.   But what I hope most of all   is that you understand what I mean...   ...when I tell you that   even though I do not know you...   ...and even though   I may never meet you...   ...laugh with you, cry with you...   ...or kiss you...   ...I love you.   With all my heart...   ...I love you.   Valerie.  I'm instructed to inform you that you have been convicted by special tribunal...</template></category><category><pattern>MY MUM  SHE USED TO READ ALL HIS PLAYS TO ME</pattern><template>...and ever since, I've always wanted to act.</template></category><category><pattern>A REVOLUTION WITHOUT DANCING IS A REVOLUTION NOT WORTH HAVING</pattern><template>I'd love to.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S SOMETHING I WANT TO ASK YOU</pattern><template>...but I don't think you'll understand why unless you know a few things about me.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK OUTSIDE  MOMMY</pattern><template>They're playing music!</template></category><category><pattern>THESE COINCIDENCES  AND I HAVE TO ASK: WHAT IF THAT ISN'T WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>What if someone else unleashed that virus?</template></category><category><pattern>AND AFTERWARDS  YOU'LL RETURN HOME SAFELY</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WORLD THAT I'M A PART OF AND THAT I HELPED SHAPE  WILL END TONIGHT</pattern><template>And tomorrow, a different world will begin...</template></category><category><pattern>AND I REALIZED THAT WE WERE ALL A PART OF IT</pattern><template>...and all trapped by it.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT THEY WERE GOING TO DO</pattern><template>I swear to you.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT YOU REALLY LOOK LIKE</pattern><template>Evey, please.</template></category><category><pattern>ASTHMA  WHEN I WAS LITTLE</pattern><template>Listen to me, Evey.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M LEAVING</pattern><template>There are 872 songs in here.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU HURT</pattern><template>No, I'm fine.</template></category><category><pattern>SADLY  AFTER LAST NIGHT  I THINK OUR CURFEW WILL ONLY GET WORSE</pattern><template>Gotcha.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT ABOUT KILLING MYSELF</pattern><template>But I knew that one day you'd come for me.</template></category><category><pattern>WE COULD LEAVE HERE TOGETHER</pattern><template>No. You were right about what I am.</template></category><category><pattern>IT GAVE ME THE COLLYWOBBLES</pattern><template>Still does.</template></category><category><pattern>DR  DIANA STANTON CHANGED HER NAME TO DELIA SURRIDGE</pattern><template>The coroner?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STOLE THIS FROM CHANCELLOR SUTLER</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  INSPECTOR  IT'S FOR YOU</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO COURT IN THIS COUNTRY FOR MEN LIKE PROTHERO</pattern><template>And are you going to kill more people?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I AM</pattern><template>I know this world is screwed up.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S ALL THAT</pattern><template>Not sure. They just arrived.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL I WANT  ALL I DESERVE  IS AT THE END OF THAT TUNNEL</pattern><template>That's not true.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE AN EQUATION</pattern><template>What was done to me was monstrous.</template></category><category><pattern>PUT THE SWORD AWAY</pattern><template>Forensics just wrapped.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS ONLY CHANCE WILL BE TO OFFER THEM SOMEONE ELSE  SOME OTHER PIECE OF MEAT</pattern><template>And who will that be?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THIS COUNTRY NEEDS MORE THAN A BUILDING RIGHT NOW  IT NEEDS HOPE</pattern><template>Bloody hell, stand down! Stand down!</template></category><category><pattern>TO CLOSE THE REMAINING TUBE STATIONS PASSED WITH</pattern><template>After that, there were no roses anymore.   Not for anyone.  You won't last much longer.</template></category><category><pattern>WONDERFUL</pattern><template>It's a game I've never played!</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  THIS IS A TEST    MOMENTS SUCH AS THESE   ARE MATTERS OF FAITH    TO FAIL IS TO INVITE DOUBT   INTO EVERYTHING WE BELIEVE         EVERYTHING WE HAVE FOUGHT FOR    DOUBT WILL PLUNGE THIS COUNTRY BACK   INTO CHAOS  AND I WILL NOT LET THAT HAPPEN    GENTLEMEN  I WANT THIS TERRORIST FOUND         AND I WANT HIM TO UNDERSTAND   WHAT TERROR REALLY MEANS    ENGLAND PREVAILS   ENGLAND PREVAILS</pattern><template>You think people will buy this?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  THAT IS INTERESTING</pattern><template>Looks like he was promoted.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE SWEPT THIS PLACE</pattern><template>You've got nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU'LL CERTAINLY BE THE SOREST</pattern><template>Oh, God, no. Please don't do this.</template></category><category><pattern>BUGGER OFF</pattern><template>Disdaining fortune, with his brandish'd steel...</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT WHAT YOU REALLY THINK  OR WHAT THEY'D WANT YOU TO THINK</pattern><template>I think I should go.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MIGHT EXPLAIN THE CONNECTION BETWEEN HIM AND THE HAMMOND GIRL</pattern><template>Problem is, I can't find any other record of it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL TAKE US TO THE ROOF</pattern><template>God is in the rain.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S DELICIOUS</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU HAVE BULLETS AND THE HOPE THAT WHEN YOUR GUNS ARE EMPTY</pattern><template>...I'm no longer standing, because if I am...</template></category><category><pattern>OUR JOB IS TO REPORT THE NEWS  NOT FABRICATE IT</pattern><template>That's the government's job.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY PUT HIM IN CHARGE OF A DETENTION FACILITY AT LARKHILL</pattern><template>Well, no good deed goes unpunished.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT BEFORE I GIVE IT TO YOU  I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU SOMETHING</pattern><template>Would you dance with me?</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  IF THEY EVER FIND THIS PLACE</pattern><template>I suspect if they do, a few bits of art will be the least of my worries.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DO YOU THINK I'M STILL ALIVE</pattern><template>All right. We'd like to take you into protective custody, Mr. Rookwood.</template></category><category><pattern>MY TURN</pattern><template>Die! Die!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT CAN'T BE</pattern><template>We threw out the censor approved script and shot one I wrote this morning.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT'S NOT ME</pattern><template>I'm no more that face than I am the muscles beneath it...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WASN'T REAL</pattern><template>Is Gordon...?</template></category><category><pattern>THE BOMBING OF GOVERNMENT PROPERTY  CONSPIRACY TO COMMIT TERRORISM</pattern><template>...treason and sedition, the penalty for which is death by firing squad.</template></category><category><pattern>ERIC FINCH</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>GOODBYE  CHANCELLOR</pattern><template>Mr. Creedy.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SECURITY OF INFORMATION IS PARAMOUNT</pattern><template>In these volatile times...</template></category><category><pattern>AND I DELIVERED IT TO YOU AS IT HAD BEEN DELIVERED TO ME</pattern><template>Then it really happened, didn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  LAST NIGHT I WAS</pattern><template>Yeah, that's right. You went to see Daddy Deitrich, didn't you?</template></category><category><pattern>I MIGHT HAVE KILLED THE FINGERMEN THAT ATTACKED YOU  I HEARD NO OBJECTION</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>ALAN PERCY  ROBERT KEYES  WILLIAM ROOKWOOD</pattern><template>The day after the St. Mary's outbreak...</template></category><category><pattern>MY APOLOGIES</pattern><template>Are you feeling all right?</template></category><category><pattern>THE QUESTION THAT'S KEPT ME UP FOR THE LAST 24 HOURS</pattern><template>...the question I have to ask, is: What if the worst...</template></category><category><pattern>YOUNG AND ATTRACTIVE LADIES LIKE YOURSELF</pattern><template>Because in this world, if I were to invite who I desired...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS VIOLENT AND UNPARALLELED ASSAULT   TO OUR SECURITY         WILL NOT GO UNDEFENDED   WHERE IS HE</pattern><template>Or unpunished.  Penny for the Guy.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU WANT</pattern><template>Sutler.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T RUN FROM IT  EVEY</pattern><template>You've been running all your life.</template></category><category><pattern>HATE WAS ALL I KNEW</pattern><template>It built my world, imprisoned me...</template></category><category><pattern>TONIGHT</pattern><template>Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN IT'S OVER</pattern><template>Almost.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  WILLY  KITTY'S GOT CLAWS</pattern><template>She just threatened us.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO I GET OUT OF THIS DEAL</pattern><template>Me.</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH I BELIEVED THAT WAS POSSIBLE</pattern><template>But every time I've seen this world change, it's always been for the worse.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE VERY SCARED RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>I heard Sutler's going to make a public statement tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE AT IT EARLY</pattern><template>Is something wrong?</template></category><category><pattern>A GOVERNMENT SUPPLY TRAIN ON ITS WAY TO CHANCELLOR SUTLER</pattern><template>You stole this from Chancellor Sutler?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS</pattern><template>Because he was right.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  EVEY</pattern><template>No, I'm the one that's sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE LOOKING FOR YOU  IF THEY KNOW WHERE YOU WORK  THEY KNOW WHERE YOU LIVE</pattern><template>I have friends, I could stay with them.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  THAT'S RIGHT  YOU WENT TO SEE DADDY DEITRICH  DIDN'T YOU</pattern><template>Evey, there you are.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO LIVE WITHOUT FEAR</pattern><template>I wish there'd been an easier way...</template></category><category><pattern>ANY PESKY LATE NIGHT PHONE CALLS  COMMANDER</pattern><template>Stop. Why do you keep calling me that?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF SOMEONE ELSE KILLED ALL THOSE PEOPLE</pattern><template>Would you really wanna know who it was?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE STILL WORKING FOR ME</pattern><template>Sorry, Patricia.</template></category><category><pattern>JONES  GET ANYONE NOT WEARING A MASK OUT</pattern><template>Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE THING IS TRUE OF ALL GOVERNMENTS: THE MOST RELIABLE RECORDS ARE TAX RECORDS</pattern><template>It appears that the original electronic records have all been lost.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO WE DO</pattern><template>I'm a cop. I have to know.</template></category><category><pattern>SEEMS I'VE CAPTURED A DANGEROUS TERRORIST</pattern><template>Now, how best to procure her confession?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE LIKE ME</pattern><template>The only thing you and I have in common, Mr. Creedy, is we're both about to die.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY WON'T YOU DIE</pattern><template>Beneath this mask there is more than flesh.</template></category><category><pattern>FUELED BY THE MEDIA    FEAR AND PANIC SPREAD QUICKLY         FRACTURING AND DIVIDING THE COUNTRY UNTIL    AT LAST  THE TRUE GOAL COMES INTO VIEW   BEFORE THE ST  MARY'S CRISES</pattern><template>...no one would have predicted the results of the election that year. No one.</template></category><category><pattern>MY PARENTS TOOK ME TO IT WHEN THEY HUNG IT AT GALLERY 12</pattern><template>I thought Sutler had it destroyed.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THE COLOR OF THE STONE</pattern><template>That'd be enough for a clever man.</template></category><category><pattern>I BELIEVE YOU WILL</pattern><template>Another doctor. Why does a detention facility need so many doctors?</template></category><category><pattern>THE WHOLE CITY'S GONE MAD</pattern><template>This is exactly what he wants.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER  THIS VALOROUS VISITATION OF A BYGONE VEXATION STANDS VIVIFIED</pattern><template>...and has vowed to vanquish these venal and virulent vermin vanguarding vice...</template></category><category><pattern>A QUIET  DIGNIFIED DEATH IN HIS SLEEP</pattern><template>We got any eyes or ears on this?</template></category><category><pattern>UNFORTUNATELY  A MAN IN MY POSITION IS EXPECTED TO ENTERTAIN</pattern><template>...young and attractive ladies like yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THREE WATERS</pattern><template>The question that's kept me up for the last 24 hours...</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN IMAGINE THAT YOU AND YOU ALONE HAVE THE CURE</pattern><template>But if your ultimate goal is power ,  how best to use such a weapon?  Well, it's at this point in our story that along comes a spider.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS NOT MY SWORD  MONDEGO    BUT YOUR PAST THAT DISARMED YOU    MAY WE COME UP    YOU FIND YOUR OWN TREE   WE GOT CREEPY PINNED LIKE A BUTTERFLY FOR WEEKS</pattern><template>Still no word. What's he waiting for?</template></category><category><pattern>OUTSIDE THE QUARANTINE ZONE  A NEW   AIRBORNE PATHOGEN HAS KILLED 27 PEOPLE    AUTHORITIES UNCOVERED NEW EVIDENCE LINKING   THE TERRORIST ORGANIZATION CALLED V         TO THE ST  MARY'S VIRAL ATTACK   ON LONDON 14 YEARS AGO   MY FRIEND INSIDE THE FINGER CAME UP WITH SOMETHING</pattern><template>There were three men.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  DEAR  SHE'S NOT TOO OLD  I TRUST</pattern><template>That is for Your Grace to decide.</template></category><category><pattern>SO DOES EVERY LAZY CUNT ON THIS SHOW  AND THAT INCLUDES YOU</pattern><template>Find another DoP or find yourself another job.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE BLINKS A LOT WHEN SHE DOES A STORY SHE KNOWS IS FALSE</pattern><template>It came as no surprise   to those who knew him...   ...that his body was at his office...   ...where he often worked long hours   after everyone else had gone home.   Lewis, you will be sorely missed.  V, yesterday I couldn't find my ID.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU WATCH THAT SHIT</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>I MACED THAT DETECTIVE</pattern><template>Why did I do that?</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER</pattern><template>I'm so sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>MAJOR STOCKHOLDER IN VIADOXIC PHARMACEUTICAL</pattern><template>Viadoxic and St. Mary's in less than a week. Coincidence?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD</pattern><template>I know you may never forgive me...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  BUT A MAN IN MY POSITION SURVIVES BY TAKING EVERY PRECAUTION</pattern><template>You have information for us?</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I ASK YOU FOR SOMETHING</pattern><template>If I had one wish, I would wish to see you again, if only once...</template></category><category><pattern>SPARE THE ROD  SPOIL THE CHILD</pattern><template>Help me! Someone help!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WASN'T LYING  IT IS YOU</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE YOU GO ANY FURTHER  LET ME REMIND YOU THINGS WERE VERY CHAOTIC BACK THEN</pattern><template>Now we don't have the problems we had back then.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I CAN'T GET A RESPONSE   FROM THAT NUMBER    THERE'S A PROBLEM WITH THE CONNECTION   JESUS CHRIST</pattern><template>He's there.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW BEAUTIFUL  IS IT NOT</pattern><template>Gentlemen, you have had four hours.   You had better have results. Mr. Creedy.  The Bailey area is quarantined.</template></category><category><pattern>AND TOMORROW  A DIFFERENT WORLD WILL BEGIN</pattern><template>...that different people will shape, and this choice belongs to them.</template></category><category><pattern>TONIGHT  I WILL SPEAK DIRECTLY   TO THESE PEOPLE         AND MAKE THE SITUATION   PERFECTLY CLEAR TO THEM    THE SECURITY OF THIS NATION DEPENDS   ON COMPLETE AND TOTAL COMPLIANCE    TONIGHT  ANY PROTESTOR    ANY INSTIGATOR OR AGITATOR         WILL BE MADE EXAMPLE OF   CHANCELLOR  THERE IS A CONTINGENCY THAT HAS NOT BEEN ADDRESSED</pattern><template>And what is that, Mr. Dascomb?    Should the terrorist succeed...</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I CREATED A LIE</pattern><template>But because you believed it, you found something true about yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>This is my gift to you, Evey.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU SEE IT</pattern><template>No. Last night I was...</template></category><category><pattern>HE CHANGED THE ENTIRE COURSE OF HUMAN HISTORY</pattern><template>Is it wrong to hold on to that kind of hope?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW</pattern><template>She blinks a lot when she does a story she knows is false.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT I AM IS A MAN IN A MASK</pattern><template>Oh, I can see that.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT PROTHERO TO SPEAK ON   THE DANGERS OF THESE OLD BUILDINGS         AND HOW WE MUST AVOID CLINGING   TO THE EDIFICE OF A DECADENT PAST    HE SHOULD CONCLUDE THAT THE NEW BAILEY   WILL BECOME THE SYMBOL OF OUR TIME         AND THE FUTURE   THAT OUR CONVICTION HAS REWARDED US    MR  HEYER   OUR SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS CAPTURED SEVERAL IMAGES OF THE TERRORIST</pattern><template>...though the mask obviously makes retinal identification impossible.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE OFF YOUR MASK</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS SOMETHING WRONG WITH THIS COUNTRY</pattern><template>Morning, inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D LOVE TO</pattern><template>Tonight, I will speak directly   to these people...   ...and make the situation   perfectly clear to them.   The security of this nation depends   on complete and total compliance.   Tonight, any protestor ,  any instigator or agitator...   ...will be made example of!  Chancellor, there is a contingency that has not been addressed.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS NOT THE WORK OF RELIGIOUS EXTREMISTS</pattern><template>Well, I don't understand. We know it was.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  WHAT HAVE I DONE</pattern><template>I Maced that detective.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WAS REAL</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE OFT TO BLAME IN THIS</pattern><template>'Tis too much proved.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I SEE THIS CHAIN OF EVENTS</pattern><template>...these coincidences, and I have to ask: What if that isn't what happened?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW WE DON'T HAVE THE PROBLEMS WE HAD BACK THEN</pattern><template>We all did what we had to do.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I KNEW THAT ONE DAY YOU'D COME FOR ME</pattern><template>I didn't know what they were going to do.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MOST LOGICAL DELIVERY SYSTEM FOR THE TERRORIST TO USE</pattern><template>...would be an airborne attack.</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL MY BROTHER DIED</pattern><template>That was when everything changed.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOUR INFORMATION LEADS TO HIS CAPTURE</pattern><template>...you will be released from this facility immediately.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT ON THIS MOST AUSPICIOUS OF NIGHTS</pattern><template>...permit me then, in lieu of the more commonplace sobriquet...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN FEEL THEM</pattern><template>Don't touch me!</template></category><category><pattern>IF I HAD ONE WISH  I WOULD WISH TO SEE YOU AGAIN  IF ONLY ONCE</pattern><template>...before the 5th.</template></category><category><pattern>OR UNPUNISHED   PENNY FOR THE GUY</pattern><template>Our enemy is an insidious one ,  seeking to divide us...   ...and destroy the very foundation   of our great nation.  I have kept my side of the bargain, but have you kept yours?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN  AFTER WHAT YOU'VE DONE</pattern><template>God, what have I done?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS TRUE IN THAT CELL IS TRUE NOW</pattern><template>What you felt in there has nothing to do with me.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S  GOD SAVE THE QUEEN</pattern><template>My parents took me to it when they hung it at Gallery 12.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE WOULD HAVE PREDICTED THE RESULTS OF THE ELECTION THAT YEAR  NO ONE</pattern><template>And then not long after the election ,  lo and behold, a miracle.   Some believed it was the work   of God himself.   But it was a pharmaceutical company   controlled by certain party members...   ...that made them all obscenely rich.  A year later, several extremists are tried, found guilty and executed...</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE COME FOR WHAT YOU DID</pattern><template>It's funny.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  CREEDY     WE'RE HANDLING IT AS BEST WE CAN</pattern><template>Arrests are as high as they've been since the Reclamation.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD GET THESE POISONS FROM ANY HOUSE IN LONDON</pattern><template>Thanks, Delia.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY THERE ARE EYES AND EARS IN EVERY ROOM OF THIS HOUSE</pattern><template>...and a tap on every phone.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SAID EVERY TELEVISION IN LONDON</pattern><template>Cruelty and injustice ,  intolerance and oppression.   And where once   you had the freedom to object...   ...to think and speak as you saw fit...   ...you now have censors and surveillance   coercing your conformity...  ... and soliciting submission .</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D COME</pattern><template>I said I would.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW YOU CAN TRUST ME</pattern><template>I'm sorry, but I can't take that risk.</template></category><category><pattern>SUTLER</pattern><template>Come, now, Mr. Creedy, you knew this was coming.</template></category><category><pattern>CELEBRATING WHAT</pattern><template>I think this could be the best show we've ever done.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME GUESS</pattern><template>She's in deep, inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY NOT</pattern><template>This is the BTN.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW</pattern><template>I'd always known   what I wanted to do with my life...   ...and in 2015 I starred in my first film , The Salt Flats.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FACED YOUR DEATH  EVEY</pattern><template>You were calm. You were still.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY WE COME UP      YOU FIND YOUR OWN TREE     YOU FIND YOUR OWN TREE</pattern><template>Did you like it?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT HOW YOU SEE IT</pattern><template>Like an equation?</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER I DESTROY PARLIAMENT</pattern><template>...his only chance will be to offer them someone else, some other piece of meat.</template></category><category><pattern>SYMBOLS ARE GIVEN POWER BY PEOPLE</pattern><template>Alone, a symbol is meaningless, but with enough people...</template></category><category><pattern>FIND ANOTHER DOP OR FIND YOURSELF ANOTHER JOB</pattern><template>I'll tell you what I wish.   I wish I'd been there.   I wish I'd had the chance   for a face to face.   Just one chance, that's all I'd need.   This so called v and his accomplice ,  Evey Hammond...   ...neo demagogues ,  spouting their message of hate.   A delusional and aberrant voice   delivering a terrorist's ultimatum.   An ultimatum that was met   with swift and surgically precise justice.    No mercy!</template></category><category><pattern>I UNLOCKED THE WINDOW IN THE ROOM WHERE DENIS TOLD ME TO GET READY</pattern><template>Wonderful!</template></category><category><pattern>TERRORIST SEEMS TO HAVE</pattern><template>...a rather intimate understanding of our system.</template></category><category><pattern>IF  INDEED  JORDAN TOWER WAS AN ACCIDENT</pattern><template>What does that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>IT ALWAYS CHEERS ME UP</pattern><template>What is that?</template></category><category><pattern>LASER LASS IS BANGING</pattern><template>What's all that?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T SEE ANY INSTRUMENTS</pattern><template>Your powers of observation continue to serve you well.</template></category><category><pattern>VIOLENCE CAN BE USED FOR GOOD</pattern><template>What are you talking about?</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH THERE'D BEEN AN EASIER WAY</pattern><template>...but there wasn't.</template></category><category><pattern>PERMIT ME THEN  IN LIEU OF THE MORE COMMONPLACE SOBRIQUET</pattern><template>...to suggest the character of this dramatis persona.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT YOU FELT IN THERE HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH ME</pattern><template>I can't feel anything anymore!</template></category><category><pattern>THE MORAL  LADIES AND GENTLEMEN  IS:  GOOD GUYS WIN  BAD GUYS LOSE</pattern><template>...and, as always, England prevails!</template></category><category><pattern>WORTH A SHOT</pattern><template>One thing is true of all governments: The most reliable records are tax records.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THESE VOLATILE TIMES</pattern><template>...mistakes like Jordan Tower can no longer be tolerated...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT EVERY TIME I'VE SEEN THIS WORLD CHANGE  IT'S ALWAYS BEEN FOR THE WORSE</pattern><template>I'll tell you what I know.   I know this is not a man.    What is he?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE YOU GOING</pattern><template>The time has come for me to meet my maker...</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU SAYING THAT I HAVE TO STAY HERE</pattern><template>Only until I'm done.</template></category><category><pattern>HURRY UP  YOU LOT  COME ON</pattern><template>Everybody out!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL ALL BE DEAD BEFORE YOU'VE RELOADED</pattern><template>That's impossible!</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY TRUTH</pattern><template>And the truth is, you made me understand that I was wrong...</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A MATTER OF SOME URGENCY  MAJOR</pattern><template>We need to know if there was anything different about this facility.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S COMPLETELY SINGLE MINDED   AND HAS NO REGARD FOR THE POLITICAL PROCESS    THE MORE POWER HE ATTAINS    THE MORE OBVIOUS HIS ZEALOTRY         AND THE MORE AGGRESSIVE   HIS SUPPORTERS BECOME    EVENTUALLY  HIS PARTY LAUNCHES A SPECIAL   PROJECT IN THE NAME OF NATIONAL SECURITY    AT FIRST IT'S BELIEVED TO BE A SEARCH   FOR BIOLOGICAL WEAPONS         AND IT'S PURSUED WITHOUT REGARD   TO ITS COST    HOWEVER  THE TRUE GOAL   OF THIS PROJECT IS POWER    COMPLETE AND TOTAL   HEGEMONIC DOMINATION    THE PROJECT  HOWEVER  ENDS VIOLENTLY    BUT THE EFFORTS OF THOSE INVOLVED   ARE NOT IN VAIN         FOR A NEW ABILITY TO WAGE WAR IS BORN   FROM THE BLOOD OF ONE OF THE VICTIMS   IMAGINE A VIRUS  THE MOST TERRIFYING VIRUS YOU CAN</pattern><template>...and then imagine that you and you alone have the cure.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS NOT MY SWORD  MONDEGO    BUT YOUR PAST THAT DISARMED YOU   IT GETS ME EVERY TIME</pattern><template>Never seen it.</template></category><category><pattern>AT WHICH POINT  ALL V NEEDS TO DO IS KEEP HIS WORD</pattern><template>And then...</template></category><category><pattern>OLDER</pattern><template>Oh, dear. She's not too old, I trust?</template></category><category><pattern>REVEREND</pattern><template>Oh, my God.</template></category><category><pattern>TILL THEN  CHEERIO</pattern><template>Rookwood...</template></category><category><pattern>THEN IT CAN'T BE IGNORED ANY LONGER</pattern><template>The red report in front of you has been vetted by several demolition specialists.</template></category><category><pattern>I PROMISE YOU  IT'LL BE LIKE NOTHING YOU'VE EVER SEEN</pattern><template>And afterwards, you'll return home safely.</template></category><category><pattern>BELIEVE ME  I KNOW IT BETTER THAN MOST</pattern><template>Which is why I wanted to ask, if there is anything I can do to help make it right...</template></category><category><pattern>VERILY  THIS VICHYSSOISE OF VERBIAGE VEERS MOST VERBOSE</pattern><template>So let me simply add that it's my very good honor to meet you...</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME  DO YOU KNOW WHAT DAY IT IS  EVEY</pattern><template>November the 4th?</template></category><category><pattern>BY THE POWER OF TRUTH  I  WHILE LIVING  HAVE CONQUERED THE UNIVERSE     PERSONAL MOTTO</pattern><template>From  Faust.  That's about trying to cheat the devil, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>CREEPY CREEDY  NOT SURE I WANNA KNOW</pattern><template>Sutler can no longer trust you, can he, Mr. Creedy?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Dr. Diana Stanton changed her name to Delia Surridge.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME THE FUCKING MONEY</pattern><template>We're under siege here.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S OUTSIDE QUARANTINE</pattern><template>I had to see it.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE HURRY</pattern><template>There's a bomb in the control booth.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU'LL FIND SOMETHING HERE</pattern><template>Worth a shot.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR MOTHER WAS IRISH  WASN'T SHE</pattern><template>Terrible what St. Mary's did to Ireland, wasn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHAT I'M GUESSING</pattern><template>I put a call in to the registry, but I haven't heard back.</template></category><category><pattern>MUCH OF IT FROM THE VAULTS OF THE MINISTRY OF OBJECTIONABLE MATERIALS</pattern><template>You stole them?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY GOD  HOW DID YOU GET IN HERE</pattern><template>Don't worry, I've made sure our reunion won't be disturbed by...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN RETURN TO YOUR LIFE  MISS HAMMOND</pattern><template>All you have to do is cooperate.</template></category><category><pattern>V  I DON'T WANT YOU TO DIE</pattern><template>That's the most beautiful thing...</template></category><category><pattern>DO IT NOW OR I SHOOT</pattern><template>I must say that I am rather astonished by the response time of London's finest.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO YOU DO THAT</pattern><template>Wait.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T PISS ME ABOUT  YOU SHOW ME ID  OR I'LL GET STORM SAXON ON YOUR ASS</pattern><template>Fucking hell.</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT OF THINGS WENT MISSING BACK THEN</pattern><template>But I found this hard copy filed in the cold vault.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU WISH</pattern><template>Do you really think you'll find something here?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  BUT I CAN'T TAKE THAT RISK</pattern><template>But I don't even know where this is.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SURE  THEY JUST ARRIVED</pattern><template>Marked for Stage 3.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HOW'D HE KNOW IT WAS YOU</pattern><template>What do we do?</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING ELSE   WE LOCATED THE FIREWORKS LAUNCH</pattern><template>...and found traces of the explosives used at both sites.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN THE PRISONER OF THE TERRORIST V FOR THE PAST SEVERAL WEEKS</pattern><template>I'm telling you that any moment, he's going to come through that door.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T KNOW  BUT THIS IS INTERESTING</pattern><template>The highest paid person at the camp was a priest.</template></category><category><pattern>GENTLEMEN  YOU HAVE HAD FOUR HOURS    YOU HAD BETTER HAVE RESULTS  MR  CREEDY   THE BAILEY AREA IS QUARANTINED</pattern><template>All significant witnesses have been detained.</template></category><category><pattern>AND VOUCHSAFING THE VIOLENTLY VICIOUS AND VORACIOUS VIOLATION OF VOLITION</pattern><template>The only verdict is vengeance, a vendetta...</template></category><category><pattern>UNTIL I SAW YOU</pattern><template>Then everything changed.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU'RE WEARING A MASK  GET DOWN ON YOUR KNEES</pattern><template>Get their masks off.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT THE WHEREABOUTS OF ALL OF THEM</pattern><template>Tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU SAYING THAT HE'S NOT STILL ALIVE   AND ACTIVE    THE TERRORIST HAS BEEN NEUTRALIZED    OH  MY GOD  CHANCELLOR  LOOK    THE TERRORIST    THE TERRORIST    GET HIM    OH  DEAR    AT LAST    AND NOW  FOR ALL THE WORLD TO SEE   IT'S HIM</pattern><template>Unhand me! I am your chancellor!   How dare you! I am the chancellor!   Imposter!   Soldiers! That man is the terrorist!     I order you to shoot that traitor!     Liar!     Faker!     Fraud!     Ready!     Aim!     Fire!     Fire!  What are they gonna do, fine us?</template></category><category><pattern>CALL THEM AGAIN  I WANT THAT NAME</pattern><template>What? Are you sure about that?</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU'LL MAKE THAT HAPPEN BY BLOWING UP A BUILDING</pattern><template>The building is a symbol, as is the act of destroying it.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS MUSIC</pattern><template>Who was he?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE HELL</pattern><template>Bugger off!</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALL DID WHAT WE HAD TO DO</pattern><template>And in those circumstances, we did the best we could.</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT  HE MUST HAVE HAD A HIDDEN TRIP ON HIS FILE AT THE FINGER</pattern><template>But how'd he know it was you?</template></category><category><pattern>HELP ME  SOMEONE HELP</pattern><template>The multiplying villainies of nature do swarm upon him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS DONE TO ME WAS MONSTROUS</pattern><template>And they created a monster.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS THE MOST IMPORTANT ROLE OF MY LIFE    NOT BECAUSE OF MY CAREER         BUT BECAUSE THAT WAS HOW I MET RUTH    THE FIRST TIME WE KISSED         I KNEW I NEVER WANTED TO KISS   ANY OTHER LIPS BUT HERS AGAIN    WE MOVED TO A SMALL FLAT   IN LONDON TOGETHER    SHE GREW SCARLET CARSONS FOR ME   IN OUR WINDOW BOX         AND OUR PLACE ALWAYS SMELT OF ROSES    THOSE WERE THE BEST YEARS OF MY LIFE    BUT AMERICA'S WAR GREW WORSE AND WORSE    AND EVENTUALLY CAME TO LONDON   THE BILL PROPOSED BY THE UNDERSECRETARY FOR DEFENSE  ADAM SUTLER</pattern><template>...to close the remaining tube stations passed with...</template></category><category><pattern>LAST NIGHT  I SOUGHT TO END THAT SILENCE    LAST NIGHT    I DESTROYED THE OLD BAILEY         TO REMIND THIS COUNTRY   OF WHAT IT HAS FORGOTTEN    MORE THAN 400 YEARS AGO  A GREAT CITIZEN   WISHED TO IMBED THE 5TH OF NOVEMBER         FOREVER IN OUR MEMORY    HIS HOPE WAS TO REMIND THE WORLD   THAT FAIRNESS  JUSTICE AND FREEDOM         ARE MORE THAN WORDS    THEY ARE PERSPECTIVES    SO IF YOU'VE SEEN NOTHING         IF THE CRIMES OF THIS GOVERNMENT   REMAIN UNKNOWN TO YOU         THEN I WOULD SUGGEST THAT YOU ALLOW   THE 5TH OF NOVEMBER TO PASS UNMARKED    BUT IF YOU SEE WHAT I SEE         IF YOU FEEL AS I FEEL    AND IF YOU WOULD SEEK AS I SEEK         THEN I ASK YOU TO STAND BESIDE ME    ONE YEAR FROM TONIGHT         OUTSIDE THE GATES OF PARLIAMENT    AND TOGETHER  WE SHALL GIVE THEM   A 5TH OF NOVEMBER         THAT SHALL NEVER  EVER BE FORGOT   KEROSENE FOG</pattern><template>He's using our smoke machines.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>Put the sword away.</template></category><category><pattern>MEA CULPA  MY CHILD</pattern><template>Mea culpa.</template></category><category><pattern>MAKING THEM VERY DIFFICULT TO TRACE</pattern><template>Whoever he is, chancellor, he's very good.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THUS I CLOTHE MY NAKED VILLAINY</pattern><template>...with old odd ends stolen forth from holy writ...</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT WORTH IT</pattern><template>If they found that here...</template></category><category><pattern>THE DCD WAS TCHAIKOVSKY'S  1812 OVERTURE</pattern><template>Add it to the blacklist.   I never want to hear that again.  Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>MARKED FOR STAGE 3</pattern><template>Must be Prothero.</template></category><category><pattern>DAD  WHAT'S WRONG WITH THE TELLY</pattern><template>Good evening, London.     Allow me first to apologize...    That's the emergency channel!</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT MEANINGLESS TO APOLOGIZE</pattern><template>Never.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF YOUR ULTIMATE GOAL IS POWER    HOW BEST TO USE SUCH A WEAPON   WELL  IT'S AT THIS POINT IN OUR STORY THAT ALONG COMES A SPIDER</pattern><template>A man seemingly   without a conscience...   ...for whom the ends   always justify the means.   He suggests that their target   should not be an enemy of the country...   ...but rather, the country itself.   Three targets are chosen   to maximize the effect of the attack:   A school, a tube station   and a water treatment plant.   Several hundred die   within the first few weeks.  Three Waters has, in fact, been contaminated.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS  I JUST SAW HER</pattern><template>It's you, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>MAY 27TH    COMMANDER PROTHERO TOURED THE LAB   WITH A PRIEST  FATHER LILLIMAN         WHO I WAS TOLD IS HERE TO MONITOR   FOR RULES AND RIGHTS VIOLATIONS    IT MADE ME NERVOUS  BUT THE COMMANDER   ASSURED ME THERE WOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM    JUNE 2ND    I KEEP WONDERING IF THESE PEOPLE KNEW   HOW THEY MIGHT BE HELPING THEIR COUNTRY         IF THEY WOULD ACT ANY DIFFERENTLY    THEY'RE SO WEAK AND PATHETIC    THEY NEVER LOOK YOU IN THE EYE    I FIND MYSELF HATING THEM    AUGUST THE 18TH    OF THE ORIGINAL FOUR DOZEN    OVER 75 PERCENT ARE NOW DECEASED    NO CONTROLLABLE PATTERN HAS YET EMERGED    SEPTEMBER THE 18TH    THERE IS ONE CASE THAT CONTINUES   TO GIVE ME HOPE    HE EXHIBITS NONE OF THE IMMUNE SYSTEM   PATHOLOGIES THE OTHER SUBJECTS DEVELOPED    I'VE DISCOVERED CELLULAR ANOMALIES IN HIS   BLOOD THAT I'VE BEEN UNABLE TO CATEGORIZE    THE MUTATIONS SEEM TO HAVE TRIGGERED         THE ABNORMAL DEVELOPMENT   OF BASIC KINESTHESIA AND REFLEXES    THE SUBJECT SAID   HE COULD NO LONGER REMEMBER         WHO HE WAS OR WHERE HE WAS FROM    WHOEVER HE WAS    HE IS NOW THE KEY TO OUR DREAM         AND THE HOPE THAT ALL OF THIS   WILL NOT HAVE BEEN IN VAIN    NOVEMBER THE 5TH    IT STARTED LAST NIGHT  AROUND MIDNIGHT    THE FIRST EXPLOSIONS TORE OPEN   THE ENTIRE MEDICAL SECTION    ALL MY WORK  GONE    I WAS TRYING TO UNDERSTAND HOW   IT COULD'VE HAPPENED WHEN I SAW HIM    THE MAN FROM ROOM 5    HE LOOKED AT ME    NOT WITH EYES  THERE WERE NO EYES    BUT I KNOW HE WAS LOOKING AT ME   BECAUSE I FELT IT    OH  GOD         WHAT HAVE I DONE   WHAT IS THAT YOU'RE MAKING</pattern><template>We called it  eggie in the basket.  My mum made them.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DID YOU GET ALL THIS STUFF</pattern><template>Oh, here and there.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD LET IT GO</pattern><template>We could leave here together.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU ACCEPT  PUT AN X ON YOUR FRONT DOOR</pattern><template>Why should I trust you?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS VISAGE  NO MERE VENEER OF VANITY</pattern><template>...is a vestige of the vox populi, now vacant, vanished.</template></category><category><pattern>IN VIEW  A HUMBLE VAUDEVILLIAN VETERAN</pattern><template>...cast vicariously as both victim and villain by the vicissitudes of fate.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU  YOU'D BE THE LEAST OF MY WORRIES</pattern><template>Thank you, Gordon.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I KNOW</pattern><template>I'm useless without a studio audience.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE YOU ANY IDEA HOW LONG IT WOULD TAKE TO REBUILD THIS FACILITY</pattern><template>Do you have any idea what you're doing?</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING YET  BUT THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE YOU CAN HELP ME WITH</pattern><template>You started as a botanist, didn't you?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO IS SHE  MR  FINCH     NOT SURE YET  SIR</pattern><template>But we're working on several leads.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>There isn't much time.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DID THIS HAPPEN  WHO'S TO BLAME    CERTAINLY THERE ARE THOSE   WHO ARE MORE RESPONSIBLE THAN OTHERS    AND THEY WILL BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE    BUT AGAIN  TRUTH BE TOLD    IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR THE GUILTY         YOU NEED ONLY LOOK INTO A MIRROR    I KNOW WHY YOU DID IT    I KNOW YOU WERE AFRAID    WHO WOULDN'T BE  WAR  TERROR  DISEASE    THERE WERE A MYRIAD OF PROBLEMS   WHICH CONSPIRED         TO CORRUPT YOUR REASON   AND ROB YOU OF YOUR COMMON SENSE    FEAR GOT THE BEST OF YOU    AND IN YOUR PANIC  YOU TURNED TO   THE NOW HIGH CHANCELLOR ADAM SUTLER    HE PROMISED YOU ORDER    HE PROMISED YOU PEACE         AND ALL HE DEMANDED IN RETURN   WAS YOUR SILENT  OBEDIENT CONSENT     INSPECTOR  THEY'RE ALMOST THROUGH</pattern><template>Last night, I sought to end that silence.   Last night ,  I destroyed the Old Bailey...   ...to remind this country   of what it has forgotten.   More than 400 years ago, a great citizen   wished to imbed the 5th of November...   ...forever in our memory.   His hope was to remind the world   that fairness, justice and freedom...   ...are more than words.   They are perspectives.   So if you've seen nothing...   ...if the crimes of this government   remain unknown to you...   ...then I would suggest that you allow   the 5th of November to pass unmarked.   But if you see what I see...   ...if you feel as I feel ,  and if you would seek as I seek...   ...then I ask you to stand beside me ,  one year from tonight...   ...outside the gates of Parliament.   And together, we shall give them   a 5th of November...   ...that shall never, ever be forgot.  Kerosene fog.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  DEITRICH</pattern><template>Gordon, please.</template></category><category><pattern>STILL NO WORD  WHAT'S HE WAITING FOR</pattern><template>Yeah? Inspector, it's for you.</template></category><category><pattern>LEGAL ONES</pattern><template>Major stockholder in Viadoxic Pharmaceutical.</template></category><category><pattern>I KILLED YOU 10 MINUTES AGO</pattern><template>...while you slept.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU  ONLY TRUTH</pattern><template>For 20 years I sought only this day.</template></category><category><pattern>AND CONCENTRATE ON THE CONCERNS OF OUR PRESENT</pattern><template>You mean Larkhill?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD ARRIVE IN PERTH IN TIME FOR MASS</pattern><template>You're most diligent, Denis...</template></category><category><pattern>FOR FIVE YEARS</pattern><template>Shit.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO KNOW IF THERE WAS ANYTHING DIFFERENT ABOUT THIS FACILITY</pattern><template>I'm sorry, inspector, I simply cannot recall.</template></category><category><pattern>USUAL UNDESIRABLES  I SHOULD THINK</pattern><template>But do you know?</template></category><category><pattern>IF OUR OWN GOVERNMENT WAS RESPONSIBLE</pattern><template>...for what happened at St. Mary's and Three Waters...</template></category><category><pattern>DIDN'T RECOGNIZE ME</pattern><template>Whatever you did to me worked better than I'd have imagined.</template></category><category><pattern>DRUGS</pattern><template>Legal ones.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT A STRANGE COINCIDENCE  THAT I SHOULD BE GIVEN ONE TODAY</pattern><template>There are no coincidences, Delia.</template></category><category><pattern>GET YOUR HANDS ON YOUR HEAD</pattern><template>Do it now or I shoot.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THAT'S DONE WITH</pattern><template>...it's time to have a look at your face.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS</pattern><template>Yes, Evey.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GOD</pattern><template>I felt...</template></category><category><pattern>LARKHILL  LARKHILL  I CANNOT RECALL THAT PARTICULAR FACILITY  INSPECTOR</pattern><template>You're welcome to review our records.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF SOMEONE ELSE UNLEASHED THAT VIRUS</pattern><template>What if someone else killed all those people?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A BOMB IN THE CONTROL BOOTH</pattern><template>Oh, no.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU REALLY WANNA KNOW WHO IT WAS</pattern><template>Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S CLEARLY ONE OF THE PEOPLE IN CHARGE AT LARKHILL</pattern><template>But after they shut it down, she disappeared for two years.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S NO CERTAINTY  ONLY OPPORTUNITY</pattern><template>You can be pretty certain that if anyone does show up...</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  EVEY</pattern><template>I didn't know what else to do.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE WROTE THE LETTER JUST BEFORE SHE DIED</pattern><template>And I delivered it to you as it had been delivered to me.</template></category><category><pattern>PROCESS HER</pattern><template>I know there's no way I can convince you   this is not one of their tricks...   ...but I don't care.   I am me.   My name is valerie.   I don't think I'll live much longer ,  and I wanted to tell someone about my life.   This is the only autobiography   that I will ever write and, God...   ...I'm writing it on toilet paper.   I was born in Nottingham in 1985.   I don't remember much of those early years ,  but I do remember the rain.   My grandmother owned a farm   in Tottle Brook...   ...and she used to tell me   that God was in the rain.   I passed my 11 Plus   and went to girls' grammar.   It was at school   that I met my first girlfriend.   Her name was Sarah.   It was her wrists.   They were beautiful.   I thought we would   love each other forever.   I remember our teacher telling us...   ...that it was an adolescent phase   that people outgrew.   Sarah did.   I didn't.   In 2002, I fell in love   with a girl named Christina.   That year I came out to my parents.   I couldn't have done it   without Chris holding my hand.   My father wouldn't look at me.   He told me to go and never come back.   My mother said nothing.   But I'd only told them the truth.   Was that so selfish?   Our integrity sells for so little ,  but it is all we really have.   It is the very last inch of us.   But within that inch...   ...we are free.  It ends whenever you want it to.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST LEAVE ME ALONE</pattern><template>Anything else on the parents?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M LOOKING AT THE TAPE RIGHT NOW  AND HE HAS NO IDEA HOW TO LIGHT ME</pattern><template>My nose looks like Big fucking Ben.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL GONE WRONG  HASN'T IT</pattern><template>The Underground?</template></category><category><pattern>SAME BASIC TOXICOLOGY AS PROTHERO</pattern><template>You could get these poisons from any house in London.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE REASON WHY YOU'RE BEING WATCHED RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>...why there are eyes and ears in every room of this house...</template></category><category><pattern>I'D FIND THE TERRORIST</pattern><template>...and I'd find him soon.</template></category><category><pattern>IS SOMETHING WRONG</pattern><template>You don't look so good, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEY  LISTEN TO ME</pattern><template>If the government ever searched my house, you would be the least of my problems.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEY  GOOD GOD</pattern><template>I'm sorry. I didn't know where else to go.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  IT'S TOO HORRIFIC</pattern><template>A quiet, dignified death in his sleep.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE HE'S JUST GETTING STARTED</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>THOUGH THE MASK OBVIOUSLY MAKES RETINAL IDENTIFICATION IMPOSSIBLE</pattern><template>We also managed to get a picture of the girl that Creedy's men were detaining.</template></category><category><pattern>LILLIMAN</pattern><template>Was paid almost 200 grand a month.</template></category><category><pattern>ORIGINAL BLACK BAGGERS  ALL UNDER CREEDY</pattern><template>Alan Percy, Robert Keyes, William Rookwood.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE</pattern><template>Kill him.</template></category><category><pattern>I WENT BY PARLIAMENT</pattern><template>Never seen anything like it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID THIS TO ME</pattern><template>You cut my hair?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY WORD</pattern><template>You really think blowing up Parliament's going to make this country a better place?</template></category><category><pattern>STILL DOES</pattern><template>That's close enough, inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU MAY CALL ME V</pattern><template>Are you, like, a crazy person?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>You can do this.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT MORE THAN ARRESTS  I WANT RESULTS     WHAT'S ALL THIS ABOUT</pattern><template>I'm celebrating.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANTED TO APOLOGIZE FOR MY REACTION LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>I understand what you did for me, and I want you to know I am grateful.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR ENEMY IS AN INSIDIOUS ONE    SEEKING TO DIVIDE US         AND DESTROY THE VERY FOUNDATION   OF OUR GREAT NATION   I HAVE KEPT MY SIDE OF THE BARGAIN  BUT HAVE YOU KEPT YOURS</pattern><template>Bring him down.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S IN DEEP  INSPECTOR</pattern><template>V?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR</pattern><template>Pucker up, here comes the Finger.</template></category><category><pattern>STAND UP TO PEOPLE WITH GUNS</pattern><template>Pull over here.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE COMES THE CRESCENDO</pattern><template>How beautiful, is it not?</template></category><category><pattern>COME  NOW  MR  CREEDY  YOU KNEW THIS WAS COMING</pattern><template>You knew that one day it'd be you or him.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WANTED US TO KNOW THE STORY  OR AT LEAST A PART OF IT</pattern><template>Am I to understand that you have read   this document, inspector?    Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S STILL GOT ANOTHER 16 HOURS</pattern><template>Maybe he's just getting started.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY WENT OUT</pattern><template>So far we count eight boxcars.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TERRORIST OBVIOUSLY WANTED US TO HAVE IT</pattern><template>He wanted us to know the story, or at least a part of it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE GOT AN ELEVATOR LOG ID</pattern><template>Let me guess.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE BTN</pattern><template>Our job is to report the news, not fabricate it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DID</pattern><template>It took nearly 10 years to clear the tracks and lay a bit of my own.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  NO GOOD DEED GOES UNPUNISHED</pattern><template>You think there's a connection between our boy and Larkhill?</template></category><category><pattern>ADD IT TO THE BLACKLIST    I NEVER WANT TO HEAR THAT AGAIN   YES  SIR</pattern><template>We also doubled our random sweeps and are monitoring phone surveillance...</template></category><category><pattern>A MAN DOES NOT THREATEN INNOCENT CIVILIANS    HE'S WHAT EVERY GUTLESS    FREEDOM HATING TERRORIST IS:   A GODDAMN COWARD   THERE WILL BE NO NEGOTIATION</pattern><template>When I arrive in the morning, the Paddy will be gone.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS YOU</pattern><template>...and me.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE GETS OUT</pattern><template>The rest of you, follow me.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE SEEN PEOPLE GO TO JAIL FOR LESS THAN THAT</pattern><template>Of course, he was right, wasn't he?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TELLING YOU THAT ANY MOMENT  HE'S GOING TO COME THROUGH THAT DOOR</pattern><template>I unlocked the window in the room where Denis told me to get ready.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'D IMPRISON YOU  TORTURE YOU  AND  IN ALL PROBABILITY  KILL YOU</pattern><template>...in the pursuit of finding me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUY IS LIKE A GHOST</pattern><template>You won't believe what they found on Prothero.</template></category><category><pattern>RUN EVERY NAME IN THAT FILE</pattern><template>I want the whereabouts of all of them.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE THIS WORLD</pattern><template>...the world that I'm a part of and that I helped shape, will end tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>LEAVE ME ALONE  I HATE YOU</pattern><template>That's it! See, at first, I thought it was hate too.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING ELSE EXISTED</pattern><template>...until I saw you.</template></category><category><pattern>RUNNING AWAY</pattern><template>Probably, because after that, all record of her seems to stop.</template></category><category><pattern>FINCH  IT'S DASCOMB     DASCOMB</pattern><template>I've already called the chancellor.     We have to get control of the situation.    What situation?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEN SOMETHING HAPPENED</pattern><template>It happened to me just as it happened to you.</template></category><category><pattern>SPARE THE ROD</pattern><template>I can assure you, I mean you no harm.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M TELLING YOU THIS</pattern><template>...because I want some kind of protection or amnesty.</template></category><category><pattern>REMEMBER  REMEMBER   THE 5TH OF NOVEMBER   THE GUNPOWDER TREASON AND PLOT   I KNOW OF NO REASON   WHY THE GUNPOWDER TREASON   SHOULD EVER BE FORGOT  FIRST  THE OVERTURE</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS A STROKE</pattern><template>No, no, it's too horrific.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALLY THINK BLOWING UP PARLIAMENT'S GOING TO MAKE THIS COUNTRY A BETTER PLACE</pattern><template>There's no certainty, only opportunity.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE SOMETHING I MUST GIVE YOU</pattern><template>I went by Parliament.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S CLOSE ENOUGH  INSPECTOR</pattern><template>We're not wired.</template></category><category><pattern>80 PERCENT OF THE PUBLIC BELIEVE THE TERRORIST IS STILL ALIVE</pattern><template>We're also showing a 12 percent increase...</template></category><category><pattern>SEEMS THAT THE CREW RESPONSIBLE FOR THE DEMOLITION OF THE OLD BAILEY</pattern><template>...wanted to give the old girl a grand, albeit improvised, sendoff.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR OWN FATHER SAID THAT ARTISTS USE LIES TO TELL THE TRUTH</pattern><template>Yes, I created a lie.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO ARE YOU</pattern><template>Who?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WHAT'S THIS</pattern><template>most awarded stars   in the history of the BTN...   ...a man known to the entire nation   as  The voice of London ...   ...passed away late last night   from apparent heart failure.    She's lying.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WEIRD</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU  MR  CREEDY</pattern><template>A man as smart as you has probably considered this.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE BEEN RUNNING ALL YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>I can't... Can't breathe.</template></category><category><pattern>HELD AS A VOTIVE NOT IN VAIN  FOR THE VALUE AND VERACITY OF SUCH</pattern><template>...shall one day vindicate the vigilant and the virtuous.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  ALL THEY WANT IS ONE LITTLE PIECE OF INFORMATION</pattern><template>Just give them something, anything.</template></category><category><pattern>I WASN'T SURE YOU WERE THE TERRORIST UNTIL I SAW IT</pattern><template>What a strange coincidence, that I should be given one today.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS BLOODY CHRIST</pattern><template>It's time.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SO SORRY</pattern><template>Damn it.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE OF THE TERRORIST</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN A PARTY MEMBER FOR 27 YEARS</pattern><template>If I were you, chief inspector...</template></category><category><pattern>CRUELTY AND INJUSTICE    INTOLERANCE AND OPPRESSION    AND WHERE ONCE   YOU HAD THE FREEDOM TO OBJECT         TO THINK AND SPEAK AS YOU SAW FIT         YOU NOW HAVE CENSORS AND SURVEILLANCE   COERCING YOUR CONFORMITY         AND SOLICITING SUBMISSION</pattern><template>Cameras. We need cameras.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE TRUTH IS  YOU MADE ME UNDERSTAND THAT I WAS WRONG</pattern><template>...that the choice to pull this lever is not mine to make.</template></category><category><pattern>LEFT</pattern><template>You go right.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T</pattern><template>My fellow Englishmen...   ...tonight, our country...   ...that which we stand for...   ...and all that we hold dear...   ...faces a grave and terrible threat.  The area's clean, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT I'M TELLING YOU</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD'VE STARTED HIS OWN HOSPITAL</pattern><template>Interesting.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN</pattern><template>Tonight's your big night.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY DURING THE RECLAMATION</pattern><template>A lot of things went missing back then.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  PLEASE  I DIDN'T KNOW  I'M SORRY</pattern><template>Not yet you're not. But you will be.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL THING</pattern><template>...you could have ever given me.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS</pattern><template>Don't shoot!</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER SEEN IT</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE NO COINCIDENCES  DELIA</pattern><template>Only the illusion of coincidence.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD  I HAVEN'T HAD REAL BUTTER SINCE I WAS A LITTLE GIRL</pattern><template>Where did you get it?</template></category><category><pattern>ENEMY IS APPROACHING FAST</pattern><template>Requesting orders.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  PLEASE  YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME</pattern><template>Oh, I do, I do, I do.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEY  PLEASE</pattern><template>There is a face beneath this mask...</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S IT  SEE  AT FIRST  I THOUGHT IT WAS HATE TOO</pattern><template>Hate was all I knew.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK  LADS</pattern><template>Spare the rod, spoil the child.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CHANCELLOR DEMANDED MY IMMEDIATE INVOLVEMENT</pattern><template>It'll be hard to investigate if you're detaining all my witnesses.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M DIZZY</pattern><template>I need air.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MY</pattern><template>Your Grace.</template></category><category><pattern>OR THE BONES BENEATH THEM</pattern><template>I understand.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  EVEY</pattern><template>I am V.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I CAN GUESS</pattern><template>With so much chaos, someone will do something stupid.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE ANY EVIDENCE   TO SUPPORT THIS CONCLUSION  MR  FINCH   NO  SIR  JUST A FEELING</pattern><template>If I am sure of anything, inspector...   ...it is that this government will not survive   if it is to be subject to your feelings.   Mr. Dascomb ,  what we need right now...   ...is a clear message   to the people of this country.   This message must be read   in every newspaper...   ...heard on every radio ,  seen on every television.   This message must resound   throughout the entire InterLink!   I want this country to realize   that we stand on the edge of oblivion.   I want every man, woman and child   to understand how close we are to chaos.   I want everyone...   ...to remember why they need us!   In the former United States, civil war   continues to devastate the Midwest.   Scientists attribute this water shortage   to the lack of rainfall the last two years.   Ministry officials expect   water coupon prices to rise.   Police have arrested nine suspects...  Can you believe this shit?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS YOU</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>DIDN'T FAWKES TRY TO BLOW UP PARLIAMENT</pattern><template>It's not too late.</template></category><category><pattern>I DARE DO ALL THAT MAY BECOME A MAN</pattern><template>Who dares more is none.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I KNOW    I KNOW THIS IS NOT A MAN     WHAT IS HE</pattern><template>A man does not wear a mask.    What is he?</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL DO MY BEST</pattern><template>I believe you will.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  I NEED TO BE OUTSIDE</pattern><template>There's a lift.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS MAY BE THE MOST IMPORTANT MOMENT OF YOUR LIFE  COMMIT TO IT</pattern><template>They took your parents from you.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  GORDON</pattern><template>Thank you so much.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GO RIGHT</pattern><template>Spread out.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME YOUR SINS</pattern><template>This isn't a game, Your Grace.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY WERE EXECUTED  I KNOW</pattern><template>And maybe that's really what happened.</template></category><category><pattern>TONIGHT'S YOUR BIG NIGHT</pattern><template>You ready for it?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  CHIEF INSPECTOR</pattern><template>Same basic toxicology as Prothero.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S YOU  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>You've come to kill me.</template></category><category><pattern>MY LAST LITTLE JOY</pattern><template>I'm sorry, Your Grace.</template></category><category><pattern>I MERELY RECLAIMED THEM</pattern><template>God, if they ever find this place...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEN  ONE DAY  I WAS AT A MARKET</pattern><template>...and a friend, someone I had worked with at the BTN, got in line behind me.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NOT TONIGHT  BISHOP</pattern><template>Not tonight.   Don't do this, I beg of you.  Well, then. Children's hour at the abbey.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WON'T   I UNDERSTAND THAT IT IS HIGHLY UNLIKELY  BUT IF HE DOES</pattern><template>If he does, and something happens   to that building...   ...the only thing that will change ,  the only difference it will make...   ...is that tomorrow morning ,  instead of a newspaper...   ...I will be reading   Mr. Creedy's resignation!  You've been busy.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH THAT</pattern><template>Yes, I killed him.</template></category><category><pattern>MORNING  INSPECTOR</pattern><template>You're at it early.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU WON'T FIND ANY MORE LOCKED DOORS HERE</pattern><template>I thought about keeping this...</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE I WANT SOME KIND OF PROTECTION OR AMNESTY</pattern><template>I had nothing to do with the Bailey and made a mistake in the Jordan Tower.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FRIEND PICKED IT UP</pattern><template>...and handed it to me.</template></category><category><pattern>SUTLER CAN NO LONGER TRUST YOU  CAN HE  MR  CREEDY</pattern><template>And we both know why.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE'RE WORKING ON SEVERAL LEADS</pattern><template>Anything else?  We located the fireworks launch...</template></category><category><pattern>PERCY GIVES HIS BERETTA A BLOWJOB  KEYES DIES IN A FIRE</pattern><template>Rookwood goes missing.</template></category><category><pattern>ANOTHER DOCTOR  WHY DOES A DETENTION FACILITY NEED SO MANY DOCTORS</pattern><template>I don't know, but this is interesting.</template></category><category><pattern>SUGGESTING A TRAIN  DESPITE THE FACT THAT THE TUNNELS SURROUNDING PARLIAMENT</pattern><template>...have been sealed shut.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I'D RATHER DIE BEHIND THE CHEMICAL SHEDS</pattern><template>Then you have no fear anymore.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I COULDN'T SEE ANY OTHER WAY</pattern><template>You were unconscious and I had to make a decision.</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A BISHOP NOW</pattern><template>Your Grace.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S FUNNY</pattern><template>I was given one of your roses today.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE INTERNED AT BELMARSH</pattern><template>Oh, no.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES IT HAVE A HAPPY ENDING</pattern><template>As only celluloid can deliver.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WILL IF YOU WANT IT TO</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>IS GORDON</pattern><template>I'm sorry, but Mr. Deitrich's dead.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE YOU COULD LOOK AFTER US BEFORE GETTING BACK TO YOUR UNCLE</pattern><template>See, my friend, he's kind of sick.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR ALL THE THINGS YOU'VE DONE  FOR THE THINGS YOU MIGHT HAVE DONE</pattern><template>...and for the only thing you have left.</template></category><category><pattern>THE REST OF YOU FOLLOW ME</pattern><template>Attention. Attention.   Will all personnel please   evacuate the building.   This is not a drill.   Will all personnel evacuate the building.  What the hell's going on?</template></category><category><pattern>MACBETH     VERY GOOD</pattern><template>My mum, she used to read all his plays to me...</template></category><category><pattern>SO WE KNOW HER STORY  NOW WE NEED HIS</pattern><template>V?</template></category><category><pattern>I SAW IT  THE WHOLE THING</pattern><template>Did you see it?</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU DANCE WITH ME</pattern><template>Now? On the eve of your revolution?</template></category><category><pattern>TELL ME</pattern><template>...do you like music, Mr. Finch?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THERE WASN'T</pattern><template>Oh, my God.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT AFTER ALL THAT</pattern><template>...they put him in charge of a detention facility at Larkhill.</template></category><category><pattern>A CONFESSION</pattern><template>I love the confessional game.</template></category><category><pattern>AT THIS TIME  IT WOULD BEHOOVE YOU</pattern><template>...to cease any investigation of matters that have long since passed...</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN NOW  ORDERS ARE BEING SHOUTED   INTO TELEPHONES         AND MEN WITH GUNS   WILL SOON BE ON THEIR WAY     IT'S CHANCELLOR SUTLER</pattern><template>Damn it!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STARTED AS A BOTANIST  DIDN'T YOU</pattern><template>It's... It's a Scarlet Carson.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THERE ANY PAIN</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>BLOODY HELL  STAND DOWN  STAND DOWN</pattern><template>Jesus bloody Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE ANOTHER ROSE</pattern><template>And this one is for you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT KIND OF MUSICIAN</pattern><template>Percussion instruments are my speciality.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I FEEL SAFE HE CAN'T PICK HIS NOSE WITHOUT YOU KNOWING</pattern><template>...I'll contact you again.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT PLAY WITH DICE AND DO NOT BELIEVE IN COINCIDENCE</pattern><template>Are you hurt?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE TO STAY HERE FOR A YEAR</pattern><template>Sorry, Evey.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALSO MANAGED TO GET A PICTURE OF THE GIRL THAT CREEDY'S MEN WERE DETAINING</pattern><template>Who is she, Mr. Finch?    Not sure yet, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE FRIENDS  I COULD STAY WITH THEM</pattern><template>I'm afraid that won't work either.</template></category><category><pattern>THE REST OF YOU  FOLLOW ME</pattern><template>Left.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TRUTH IS  AFTER SO MANY YEARS</pattern><template>...you begin to lose more than just your appetite.</template></category><category><pattern>SO FAR WE COUNT EIGHT BOXCARS</pattern><template>Several hundred thousand, at least.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  A MAN AS SMART AS YOU  I THINK  KNOWS OTHERWISE</pattern><template>What do you want?</template></category><category><pattern>I CANNOT RECALL SPECIFIC NAMES  BUT IF YOU LOOK THROUGH OUR RECORDS</pattern><template>Your records are either deleted, omitted or missing.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THE BRASS</pattern><template>I can hear it!</template></category><category><pattern>AND TAKE HER OUT BEHIND THE CHEMICAL SHED AND SHOOT HER</pattern><template>It's time.</template></category><category><pattern>MUMMY</pattern><template>Evey!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M THE ONE THAT'S SORRY</pattern><template>Sorry I'm not a stronger person.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT YOU'RE DOING</pattern><template>Wait, wait!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I'M NOT</pattern><template>I wish I wasn't afraid all the time...</template></category><category><pattern>I DO  LIKE MANY OF YOU  APPRECIATE   THE COMFORTS OF THE EVERYDAY ROUTINE         THE SECURITY OF THE FAMILIAR    THE TRANQUILITY OF REPETITION   BLOODY HELL</pattern><template>I enjoy them as much as any bloke.   But in the spirit of commemoration ...</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I ASK ABOUT WHAT YOU SAID ON THE TELLY</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>CHEERS</pattern><template>I know every cop's looking for me.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY CREATED A MONSTER</pattern><template>Do you know where you'll go?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN HEAR IT</pattern><template>Look outside, Mommy!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID WHAT YOU THOUGHT WAS RIGHT</pattern><template>No, I shouldn't have done that.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S HIM</pattern><template>Are you saying that he's not still alive   and active?   The terrorist has been neutralized.   Oh, my God! Chancellor, look!   The terrorist!   The terrorist!   Get him!   Oh, dear.   At last!   And now, for all the world to see.  It's him!</template></category><category><pattern>HAS ANYONE ELSE READ IT     NO  SIR</pattern><template>Then let me make this perfectly clear to you.   The contents of this document   are a matter of national security...   ...constituting an assault on the character   of several important party members...   ...as well as a blatant violation   of the Articles of Allegiance.   As the authenticity of this document   cannot be verified...   ...it could be an elaborate forgery   created by the terrorist...   ...as easily as it could be the deranged   fantasy of a former party member...   ...who resigned   for psychological reasons.   Any discussion of this document   or its contents...   ...will be regarded, at the very least ,  as an act of sedition...   ...if not a willful act of treason.     Is that understood, Mr. Finch?    Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SEEM A SAINT  WHEN MOST I PLAY THE DEVIL</pattern><template>Oh, please, have mercy.</template></category><category><pattern>BEEN GOING ON ALL SUMMER</pattern><template>Outside the quarantine zone, a new   airborne pathogen has killed 27 people.   Authorities uncovered new evidence linking   the terrorist organization called v...   ...to the St. Mary's viral attack   on London 14 years ago.  My friend inside the Finger came up with something.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I KNOW    I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I KNOW    I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I KNOW    ENGLAND PREVAILS     CLEAR THE HALLS</pattern><template>Sir.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  SHIT</pattern><template>A yellow coded curfew is now in effect.   Any unauthorized personnel   will be subject to arrest.   This is for your protection.   A yellow coded curfew is now in effect.   Any unauthorized personnel   will be subject to arrest.   This is for your protection.    Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST PUT THEM OVER THERE UNTIL I CAN FIGURE OUT WHAT THEY'RE FOR</pattern><template>This looks serious.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE I COULD SEE THE WHOLE THING</pattern><template>One long chain of events that stretched   all the way back before Larkhill.  I felt like I could see everything that had happened...</template></category><category><pattern>I CALL IT THE SHADOW GALLERY</pattern><template>It's beautiful.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT PLAN IS THE REASON SUTLER NO LONGER TRUSTS YOU</pattern><template>It's the reason why you're being watched right now...</template></category><category><pattern>THE MOST HORRIFYING BIOLOGICAL ATTACK IN THIS COUNTRY'S HISTORY</pattern><template>...was not the work of religious extremists?</template></category><category><pattern>BAD LUCK  CHUMMY</pattern><template>I don't know about that.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED AIR</pattern><template>Please, I need to be outside.</template></category><category><pattern>I TELL YOU WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN</pattern><template>I'll have to make some kind of apology, do some boring fundraiser.</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE YOU CAN</pattern><template>I'm not questioning your powers of observation.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER SHE JUST SAVED HIM</pattern><template>He's a terrorist. You can't expect him to act like you or me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WEAR A MASK FOR SO LONG  YOU FORGET WHO YOU WERE BENEATH IT</pattern><template>I'm sorry, chief inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>HARD TO BELIEVE  ISN'T IT  THAT BENEATH THIS WRINKLED  WELL FED EXTERIOR</pattern><template>...there lies a dangerous killing machine with a fetish for Fawkesian masks.</template></category><category><pattern>TO SUGGEST THE CHARACTER OF THIS DRAMATIS PERSONA</pattern><template>Voil!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU'LL NEVER GET IT APPROVED</pattern><template>You've got to rewrite it, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS  THIS IS A GREAT HELP</pattern><template>By the power of truth, I, while living, have conquered the universe.    Personal motto?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY THING YOU AND I HAVE IN COMMON  MR  CREEDY  IS WE'RE BOTH ABOUT TO DIE</pattern><template>How do you imagine that's gonna happen?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT REALLY VERY GOOD TABLE CONVERSATION</pattern><template>Now, would you care for a cup of tea with your egg?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T GET IT</pattern><template>Why does he wear a Guy Fawkes mask?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T LOOK SO GOOD  SIR</pattern><template>I wanna ask a question, Dominic.</template></category><category><pattern>THE FIRST MORNING I WAS WITH HIM  HE MADE ME EGGS JUST LIKE THIS</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEVER SAW THEM AGAIN   IT WAS LIKE THOSE BLACK BAGS ERASED THEM FROM THE FACE OF THE EARTH</pattern><template>I'm sorry, Evey.</template></category><category><pattern>MUST BE PROTHERO</pattern><template>I wish someone had the balls to tell that brat this station ain't his playground.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW</pattern><template>Well, you won't find any more locked doors here.</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR</pattern><template>That is a strange coincidence.</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I INQUIRE AS TO HOW YOU'VE AVOIDED DETECTION</pattern><template>A fake ID works better than a Guy Fawkes mask.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE NOT WIRED</pattern><template>I'm sorry, but a man in my position survives by taking every precaution.</template></category><category><pattern>AM I TO UNDERSTAND THAT YOU HAVE READ   THIS DOCUMENT  INSPECTOR     YES  SIR</pattern><template>Has anyone else read it?    No, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THIS ANOTHER TRICK  V</pattern><template>No. No more tricks. No more lies.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GOD  WE HAVE TO STOP YOUR BLEEDING</pattern><template>Please, don't. I'm finished and glad of it.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  PATRICIA</pattern><template>I need two espressos and three coffees.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE  THAT'S BETTER</pattern><template>I hope I didn't put you off your appetite.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE ONE CHANCE  AND ONLY ONE CHANCE  TO SAVE YOUR LIFE</pattern><template>You must tell us the identity or whereabouts...</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOTHING BUT BAD LUCK HERE</pattern><template>So we know her story. Now we need his.</template></category><category><pattern>THE QUESTION I WANT TO ASK IS ABOUT ST  MARY'S</pattern><template>...and Three Waters.</template></category><category><pattern>WHITEHALL IS SECURE  OVER</pattern><template>This is General Ackroyd.</template></category><category><pattern>QUICK  EVEY  HIDE</pattern><template>Not so funny now, is it, funnyman?</template></category><category><pattern>EITHER THAT OR I WASN'T BREAST FED</pattern><template>Is everything a joke to you?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOEVER HE IS  CHANCELLOR  HE'S VERY GOOD</pattern><template>Spare us your professional annotations ,  Mr. Finch. They are irrelevant.  Apologies, chancellor.</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN YOUR MOUTH   AND STICK OUT YOUR TONGUE     WHAT THE</pattern><template>I don't want to die!  This is Surveillance 109.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S LATE  OR EARLY</pattern><template>Call them again. I want that name.</template></category><category><pattern>A FAKE ID WORKS BETTER THAN A GUY FAWKES MASK</pattern><template>I must confess, every time I heard a siren, I worried about you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  I'M A MUSICIAN OF SORTS</pattern><template>...and on my way to give a very special performance.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  GOD  I HOPE I DIDN'T WAKE YOU</pattern><template>No, I just thought you were fighting.</template></category><category><pattern>EYES AND EARS HAVE DETECTED MOVEMENT HEADING TO TRAFALGAR SQUARE</pattern><template>This is perimeter one.</template></category><category><pattern>ROOKWOOD</pattern><template>...why didn't you come forward before?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOLD THEM YOU'D RATHER DIE</pattern><template>You faced your death, Evey.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TRUSTED ME</pattern><template>It would be terrible manners for me not to trust you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IN THOSE CIRCUMSTANCES  WE DID THE BEST WE COULD</pattern><template>That's all I have to say about that.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT TELL ME  DO YOU ENJOY MUSIC  EVEY</pattern><template>I suppose.</template></category><category><pattern>SO LET ME SIMPLY ADD THAT IT'S MY VERY GOOD HONOR TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>...and you may call me V.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  WOULD YOU CARE FOR A CUP OF TEA WITH YOUR EGG</pattern><template>Yes, thank you. I'm starving, actually.</template></category><category><pattern>AND A FRIEND  SOMEONE I HAD WORKED WITH AT THE BTN  GOT IN LINE BEHIND ME</pattern><template>I was so nervous that when the cashier asked me for my money, I dropped it.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT ANYMORE</pattern><template>Remember, remember   The 5th of November   The gunpowder treason and plot   I know of no reason   Why the gunpowder treason   Should ever be forgot  First, the overture.</template></category><category><pattern>IT APPEARS UNFORESEEN CIRCUMSTANCES</pattern><template>...have accelerated my original plan.</template></category><category><pattern>BREAK IT DOWN</pattern><template>Dominic!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT DO YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Of course not. I wasn't stationed there.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHAT IS IT  CHIEF  WHAT'S GOING ON</pattern><template>The question I want to ask is about St. Mary's...</template></category><category><pattern>WANTED TO GIVE THE OLD GIRL A GRAND  ALBEIT IMPROVISED  SENDOFF</pattern><template>Although the demolition had been   planned for some time...   ...the music and the fireworks were ,  according to the crew chief...     ... definitely not on the schedule.      We'll be right back.  Do you believe that load of bollocks?</template></category><category><pattern>FORTUNATELY  I GOT TO YOU BEFORE THEY DID</pattern><template>You got to me?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  WE'D LIKE TO TAKE YOU INTO PROTECTIVE CUSTODY  MR  ROOKWOOD</pattern><template>I'm sure you would.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS JUST</pattern><template>It's past curfew, you know.</template></category><category><pattern>SENT DESTRUCTION THROUGH THE UNDERGROUND</pattern><template>Fueled by the media ,  fear and panic spread quickly...   ...fracturing and dividing the country until ,  at last, the true goal comes into view.  Before the St. Mary's crises...</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT</pattern><template>Don't shoot me, please! It's him! It's him!</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU SAYING I'M UNDER SURVEILLANCE  MR  CREEDY</pattern><template>At this time, it would behoove you...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S THAT MEAN</pattern><template>Spare the rod.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LAST YOU KNOW THE TRUTH</pattern><template>You're stunned, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA ASK A QUESTION  DOMINIC</pattern><template>I don't care if you answer me or not.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST FINISHED GOING THROUGH THE FILE    INSPECTOR  YOU BETTER GET BACK HERE   YEAH  OKAY</pattern><template>My God. He's killed them all.</template></category><category><pattern>PROTHERO'S MILITARY RECORD</pattern><template>What do you see?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS NOT FUNNY  GORDON</pattern><template>Yeah, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT THEY CLOSED THIS ALL DOWN</pattern><template>They did.</template></category><category><pattern>VERY GOOD EVENING    LADIES AND GENTLEMEN    LISTEN  WE'VE GOT AN EXTRAORDINARY   SHOW FOR YOU TONIGHT    YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE IT    AS A MATTER OF FACT  I DON'T THINK I DO    WILL YOU PLEASE GIVE   A VERY WARM WELCOME         TO OUR OWN CHANCELLOR ADAM SUTLER     NO WAY</pattern><template>No, it can't be!</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  MR  ETHERIDGE   A RECORDING DEVICE WAS FOUND WIRED INTO THE CENTRAL EMERGENCY BROADCAST SYSTEM</pattern><template>The DCD was Tchaikovsky's  1812 Overture .</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK PEOPLE WILL BUY THIS</pattern><template>Why not?</template></category><category><pattern>COVERT INTEL</pattern><template>Original black baggers, all under Creedy.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYBODY OUT</pattern><template>Dascomb.</template></category><category><pattern>CHANCELLOR SUTLER AGREED  FOR OBVIOUS REASONS  WE HAVE TO KEEP THIS DISCREET</pattern><template>In the wrong light, the loss of the Voice of London...</template></category><category><pattern>PROBLEM IS  I CAN'T FIND ANY OTHER RECORD OF IT</pattern><template>Larkhill? Larkhill? I cannot recall that particular facility, inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FATHER WAS A WRITER</pattern><template>You would have liked him.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SO FUNNY NOW  IS IT  FUNNYMAN</pattern><template>Gotcha.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I FOUND THIS HARD COPY FILED IN THE COLD VAULT</pattern><template>Everything we've got on Larkhill is in there.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT ANY EYES OR EARS ON THIS</pattern><template>No, camcos were cut.</template></category><category><pattern>IN A HURRY  ARE WE</pattern><template>I was just...</template></category><category><pattern>IF MY APPETITES WERE FOR LESS CONVENTIONAL FARE</pattern><template>Unfortunately, a man in my position is expected to entertain...</template></category><category><pattern>I SUSPECT IF THEY DO  A FEW BITS OF ART WILL BE THE LEAST OF MY WORRIES</pattern><template>You mean, after what you've done.</template></category><category><pattern>TONIGHT I GIVE YOU   MY MOST SOLEMN VOW         THAT JUSTICE WILL BE SWIFT         IT WILL BE RIGHTEOUS         AND IT WILL BE WITHOUT MERCY   OH  GOD  NO</pattern><template>At last, we finally meet.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I DO  I DO  I DO</pattern><template>Let me show you the firmness of my beliefs.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS MY GIFT TO YOU  EVEY</pattern><template>Everything that I have: My home, my books, the gallery, this train...</template></category><category><pattern>ROOKWOOD GOES MISSING</pattern><template>Bloody coincidences are making me sick to my stomach.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TIME TO HAVE A LOOK AT YOUR FACE</pattern><template>Take off your mask.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  THERE WAS NO BLOODY DEMOLITION</pattern><template>I saw it, the whole thing.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOOK YOUR BROTHER FROM YOU</pattern><template>They put you in a cell and took everything they could take except your life.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A BASIC PRINCIPLE OF THE UNIVERSE</pattern><template>...that every action will create an equal and opposing reaction.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  FRED</pattern><template>All that been x rayed?</template></category><category><pattern>INDICATING A HIGH PERCENTAGE OF CONVERSATION CONCERNED WITH THE EXPLOSION</pattern><template>Mr. Dascomb ,  what are we doing about that?  We're calling it an emergency demolition.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY I'M NOT LIKE MY PARENTS</pattern><template>I wish I was...</template></category><category><pattern>SICK UNCLE  WHAT YOU THINK ON THAT  WILLY</pattern><template>It's a load of bollocks.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S THE SAME M O  AS BEFORE</pattern><template>But we got an elevator log ID.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S HE DOING IN THE DARK THERE</pattern><template>Creepy Creedy. Not sure I wanna know.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TWO  COVER THESE ELEVATORS</pattern><template>The rest of you follow me.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE CAUGHT  THEY CONFESSED</pattern><template>And they were executed. I know.</template></category><category><pattern>I SUPPOSE</pattern><template>You see, I'm a musician of sorts...</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH I WASN'T AFRAID ALL THE TIME</pattern><template>...but I am.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NO MORE THAT FACE THAN I AM THE MUSCLES BENEATH IT</pattern><template>...or the bones beneath them.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I HAD LEFT YOU THERE  RIGHT NOW YOU'D BE IN ONE OF CREEDY'S INTERROGATION CELLS</pattern><template>They'd imprison you, torture you, and, in all probability, kill you...</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE INTERRUPTING YOUR REGULARLY SCHEDULED   PROGRAM TO BRING YOU THIS TERRIFYING REPORT         OF A TERRORIST TAKEOVER OF JORDAN TOWER   WHICH ENDED ONLY MOMENTS AGO    A PSYCHOTIC TERRORIST    IDENTIFIED ONLY AS THE LETTER V         ATTACKED THE CONTROL BOOTH WITH   HIGH POWERED EXPLOSIVES AND WEAPONS         THAT HE USED AGAINST UNARMED CIVILIANS   IN ORDER TO BROADCAST A MESSAGE OF HATE    WE'VE JUST RECEIVED THIS FOOTAGE   OF A DARING POLICE RAID    STOP  STOP  STAY WHERE YOU ARE    OR WE'LL SHOOT  STAY WHERE YOU ARE    NOW  THIS IS ONLY AN INITIAL REPORT         BUT AT THIS TIME  IT'S BELIEVED   THAT DURING THIS HEROIC RAID         THE TERRORIST WAS SHOT AND KILLED   BOLLOCKS</pattern><template>Again, from what we've been told   by authorities, the danger is now over.   The terrorist is dead.  Right there. What's he thinking?</template></category><category><pattern>THEN EVERYTHING CHANGED</pattern><template>I fell in love with you, Evey...</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME  EVEY</pattern><template>This may be the most important moment of your life. Commit to it.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT DIFFERENT PEOPLE WILL SHAPE  AND THIS CHOICE BELONGS TO THEM</pattern><template>Where are you going?</template></category><category><pattern>HE USED TO SAY ARTISTS USED LIES TO TELL THE TRUTH</pattern><template>...while politicians used them to cover the truth up.</template></category><category><pattern>HER PARENTS WERE POLITICAL ACTIVISTS</pattern><template>They were detained when she was 12.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU MEAN IT</pattern><template>Every word.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THANK YOU  I'M STARVING  ACTUALLY</pattern><template>Have a seat.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCKING HELL</pattern><template>Come on, let's move!</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  DON'T GET ME WRONG  I LOVE IT</pattern><template>A cow getting crucified.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>I swear.</template></category><category><pattern>APPROXIMATELY 10 MILES NORTH OF SALISBURY</pattern><template>Well, there you have it.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT YET YOU'RE NOT  BUT YOU WILL BE</pattern><template>By sunup, if you're not the sorriest piece of ass in all of London...</template></category><category><pattern>HOW YOU CAN BE ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT THINGS THAT HAS HAPPENED TO ME</pattern><template>...and yet I know almost nothing about you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO FILED THAT REPORT   CHIEF INSPECTOR FINCH</pattern><template>Do you have any evidence   to support this conclusion, Mr. Finch?  No, sir. Just a feeling.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE HAS ARRIVED  BUT THERE WAS SOME CONFUSION AT THE AGENCY</pattern><template>They've sent a new girl who, I'm afraid, is a little older than usual.</template></category><category><pattern>IRAQ  KURDISTAN  SYRIA  BEFORE AND AFTER  SUDAN</pattern><template>Busy boy.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS YOUR TITLE  REMEMBER</pattern><template>When we first met, all those years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL IT SAYS IS THAT THERE WAS A DETENTION FACILITY AT LARKHILL</pattern><template>...approximately 10 miles north of Salisbury.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WAIT  IT IS TO MADAME JUSTICE THAT I DEDICATE THIS CONCERTO</pattern><template>...in honor of the holiday she seems to have taken from these parts...</template></category><category><pattern>WE THREW OUT THE CENSOR APPROVED SCRIPT AND SHOT ONE I WROTE THIS MORNING</pattern><template>Oh, my God.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A COPY OF THE KORAN  14TH CENTURY</pattern><template>Are you a Muslim?</template></category><category><pattern>IF THE GOVERNMENT EVER SEARCHED MY HOUSE  YOU WOULD BE THE LEAST OF MY PROBLEMS</pattern><template>You trusted me.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE IT'S THE ONLY WAY YOU'RE EVER GOING TO STOP ME</pattern><template>It is not my sword, Mondego ,  but your past that disarmed you.   May we come up?   You find your own tree.  We got Creepy pinned like a butterfly for weeks.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T RECALL GETTING STOOD UP BY A MORE ATTRACTIVE WOMAN</pattern><template>Mr. Deitrich...</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S    IT'S A SCARLET CARSON</pattern><template>They're believed to be extinct.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE GOVERNMENT'S JOB</pattern><template>On the lighter side of things...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT USUALLY HAPPENS WHEN PEOPLE WITHOUT GUNS</pattern><template>...stand up to people with guns.</template></category><category><pattern>THINGS WILL TURN NASTY</pattern><template>Rioters were arrested in Brixton.  And then Sutler will be forced to do the only thing he knows how to do.</template></category><category><pattern>SIR</pattern><template>Everyone else, let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>AS A RESULT  I'M IN NEED OF SOMEONE WITH SOME THEATRICAL SKILL</pattern><template>I'll do my best.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY</pattern><template>Run every name in that file.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY INFORMATION COULD BE HELPFUL</pattern><template>Of course.</template></category><category><pattern>GORDON  PLEASE</pattern><template>I don't need  mister  to make this body feel any older.</template></category><category><pattern>ARRANGE A DETAIL OF SIX MEN</pattern><template>...and take her out behind the chemical shed and shoot her.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS PAID ALMOST 200 GRAND A MONTH</pattern><template>Now, that is interesting.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  IT AIN'T GOOD</pattern><template>They were interned at Belmarsh.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I MERELY PLAYED MY PART</pattern><template>But tell me, do you enjoy music, Evey?</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYTHING THAT I HAVE: MY HOME  MY BOOKS  THE GALLERY  THIS TRAIN</pattern><template>...I'm leaving to you to do with what you will.</template></category><category><pattern>MEA CULPA</pattern><template>Your Grace, we don't have much time and I have to tell you something.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M USELESS WITHOUT A STUDIO AUDIENCE</pattern><template>I've seen people go to jail for less than that.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IS WHY I WANTED TO ASK  IF THERE IS ANYTHING I CAN DO TO HELP MAKE IT RIGHT</pattern><template>...please let me know.</template></category><category><pattern>I'D ALWAYS KNOWN   WHAT I WANTED TO DO WITH MY LIFE         AND IN 2015 I STARRED IN MY FIRST FILM   THE SALT FLATS</pattern><template>It was the most important role of my life.   Not because of my career...   ...but because that was how I met Ruth.   The first time we kissed...   ...I knew I never wanted to kiss   any other lips but hers again.   We moved to a small flat   in London together.   She grew Scarlet Carsons for me   in our window box...   ...and our place always smelt of roses.   Those were the best years of my life.   But America's war grew worse and worse ,  and eventually came to London.  The bill proposed by the Undersecretary for Defense, Adam Sutler...</template></category><category><pattern>GOTCHA</pattern><template>No, no.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHAT DO WE DO NOW  INSPECTOR</pattern><template>We do what we should have been doing.</template></category><category><pattern>TONIGHT WE MUST REMAIN STEADFAST    WE MUST REMAIN DETERMINED    BUT MOST OF ALL    WE MUST REMAIN UNITED    THOSE CAUGHT TONIGHT   IN VIOLATION OF CURFEW         WILL BE CONSIDERED IN LEAGUE   WITH OUR ENEMY         AND PROSECUTED AS A TERRORIST   WITHOUT LENIENCY OR EXCEPTION   I WANT TO SEE HIS FACE</pattern><template>Tonight I give you   my most solemn vow...   ...that justice will be swift...   ...it will be righteous...   ...and it will be without mercy.  Oh, God. No.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WOULD HAVE LIKED HIM</pattern><template>He used to say artists used lies to tell the truth...</template></category><category><pattern>I MADE A MISTAKE  I SHOULDN'T BE OUT AFTER CURFEW  I KNOW THAT</pattern><template>Maybe you could look after us before getting back to your uncle.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU PROVE ANY OF THIS</pattern><template>Why do you think I'm still alive?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU SO MUCH</pattern><template>It's all right.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE EVEY HAMMOND  AREN'T YOU</pattern><template>Then it's over?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT SURE</pattern><template>She's clearly one of the people in charge at Larkhill.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY SHOULD I TRUST YOU</pattern><template>Because it's the only way you're ever going to stop me.</template></category><category><pattern>V  WAIT</pattern><template>Please, you don't have to do this.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE GONNA NEED BACKUP  BUT KEEP IT MINIMAL</pattern><template>You sure about that, sir?</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU GET TO SWALLOW IT</pattern><template>You're Fingermen.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JAMMED</pattern><template>Break it down.</template></category><category><pattern>DOMINIC</pattern><template>Police! Out of the way!</template></category><category><pattern>FORENSICS JUST WRAPPED</pattern><template>No prints, no hair, no fibers.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S THAT</pattern><template>Don't piss me about. You show me ID, or I'll get Storm Saxon on your ass.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT</pattern><template>I must have been out of my mind.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE JUST RECEIVED YOUR INTERLINK ITINERARY</pattern><template>You should arrive in Perth in time for Mass.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  PLEASE  IT'S JUST    ARE YOU ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Yes, yes, yes, I'm fine.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT ANYONE CAUGHT   WITH ONE OF THOSE MASKS ARRESTED   GIVE ME THE MONEY</pattern><template>Give me the fucking money!</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD BE TERRIBLE MANNERS FOR ME NOT TO TRUST YOU</pattern><template>Oh, my God.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO IS BUT THE FORM FOLLOWING THE FUNCTION OF WHAT</pattern><template>...and what I am is a man in a mask.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I WISH    I WISH I'D BEEN THERE    I WISH I'D HAD THE CHANCE   FOR A FACE TO FACE    JUST ONE CHANCE  THAT'S ALL I'D NEED    THIS SO CALLED V AND HIS ACCOMPLICE    EVEY HAMMOND         NEO DEMAGOGUES    SPOUTING THEIR MESSAGE OF HATE    A DELUSIONAL AND ABERRANT VOICE   DELIVERING A TERRORIST'S ULTIMATUM    AN ULTIMATUM THAT WAS MET   WITH SWIFT AND SURGICALLY PRECISE JUSTICE     NO MERCY</pattern><template>The moral, ladies and gentlemen, is:  Good guys win, bad guys lose...</template></category><category><pattern>STOP IT  GET OFF OF ME</pattern><template>Seems I've captured a dangerous terrorist.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE THIS IS</pattern><template>You know it's underground.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS COOPERATE</pattern><template>Process her.</template></category><category><pattern>THESE DEVICES WERE HOMEMADE WITH OVER THE COUNTER CHEMICALS</pattern><template>...making them very difficult to trace.</template></category><category><pattern>WE FIND HIM</pattern><template>Every day, gentlemen.   Every day that brings us closer   to November...   ...every day that man remains free...   ...is one more failure.   Three hundred and forty seven days ,  gentlemen.   Three hundred and forty seven failures!  Chancellor, we do not have the adequate force...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST TELL US THE IDENTITY OR WHEREABOUTS</pattern><template>...of code name V.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I SUPPOSE I SHOULD THANK YOU</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHERE YOU'LL GO</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN CAREFULLY  CAN YOU HEAR IT</pattern><template>Now the brass.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'LL BE HARD TO INVESTIGATE IF YOU'RE DETAINING ALL MY WITNESSES</pattern><template>The security of information is paramount.</template></category><category><pattern>SEVERAL PROMINENT PARTY MEMBERS HAVE BEEN MURDERED  CHIEF INSPECTOR</pattern><template>This is no ordinary situation and requires more than your ordinary attention.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW DO I KNOW THAT NAME</pattern><template>Shit. He must have had a hidden trip on his file at the Finger.</template></category><category><pattern>THE CORONER</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE ALREADY CALLED THE CHANCELLOR      WE HAVE TO GET CONTROL OF THE SITUATION     WHAT SITUATION</pattern><template>Chancellor Sutler agreed, for obvious reasons, we have to keep this discreet.</template></category><category><pattern>IS IT WRONG TO HOLD ON TO THAT KIND OF HOPE</pattern><template>I have not come for what you hoped to do.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS YOU</pattern><template>The Ghost of Christmas Past.</template></category><category><pattern>I WORRIED ABOUT MYSELF FOR A WHILE</pattern><template>But then, one day, I was at a market...</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE ALSO SHOWING A 12 PERCENT INCREASE</pattern><template>...over last month's positive mention in all four quadrants.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHEN THEY FOUND A KORAN IN HIS HOUSE  THEY HAD HIM EXECUTED</pattern><template>Oh, God.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAPPENED TO HER</pattern><template>Juvenile Reclamation Project...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND  EVEY  I DIDN'T WANT THIS FOR EITHER OF US</pattern><template>...but I couldn't see any other way.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T NEED  MISTER  TO MAKE THIS BODY FEEL ANY OLDER</pattern><template>Gordon...</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT CHIEF INSPECTOR FINCH     IT IS</pattern><template>This is Captain Clark...   ...of the 137th Ward at Southend.     We found him.    Found who?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE CHANGED HER NAME</pattern><template>That's what I'm guessing.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY THERE ARE SEVERAL OF YOUR MEN CLOSE TO SUTLER</pattern><template>...men that can be counted on.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M EVEY</pattern><template>Evey?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S HYSTERICAL</pattern><template>But you'll never get it approved.</template></category><category><pattern>NATIONWIDE WERE DEVASTATED   AS NEWS OF THE MOST POPULAR</pattern><template>Wait. What's this?</template></category><category><pattern>SPREAD OUT</pattern><template>Don't shoot! Please don't shoot!</template></category><category><pattern>I PUT A CALL IN TO THE REGISTRY  BUT I HAVEN'T HEARD BACK</pattern><template>It's late, or early.</template></category><category><pattern>VOIL</pattern><template>In view, a humble vaudevillian veteran...</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS  DON'T YOU</pattern><template>It means that we exercise our own judicial discretion.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  HOW BEST TO PROCURE HER CONFESSION</pattern><template>You little bitch. You fucking little whore!</template></category><category><pattern>PULL OVER HERE</pattern><template>We've searched these tunnels for weeks.</template></category><category><pattern>CAMERAS  WE NEED CAMERAS</pattern><template>How did this happen? Who's to blame?   Certainly there are those   who are more responsible than others.   And they will be held accountable.   But again, truth be told ,  if you're looking for the guilty...   ...you need only look into a mirror.   I know why you did it.   I know you were afraid.   Who wouldn't be? War, terror, disease.   There were a myriad of problems   which conspired...   ...to corrupt your reason   and rob you of your common sense.   Fear got the best of you.   And in your panic, you turned to   the now High Chancellor Adam Sutler.   He promised you order ,  he promised you peace...   ...and all he demanded in return   was your silent, obedient consent.    Inspector, they're almost through.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SPOON FED ME THAT BULLSHIT  AND I ATE IT UP</pattern><template>So, what do we do now, inspector?</template></category><category><pattern>IT MEANS THAT I  LIKE GOD</pattern><template>...do not play with dice and do not believe in coincidence.</template></category><category><pattern>GOVERNMENTS SHOULD BE AFRAID OF THEIR PEOPLE</pattern><template>And you'll make that happen by blowing up a building?</template></category><category><pattern>THE MULTIPLYING VILLAINIES OF NATURE DO SWARM UPON HIM</pattern><template>What the hell?!</template></category><category><pattern>IT CAME AS NO SURPRISE   TO THOSE WHO KNEW HIM         THAT HIS BODY WAS AT HIS OFFICE         WHERE HE OFTEN WORKED LONG HOURS   AFTER EVERYONE ELSE HAD GONE HOME    LEWIS  YOU WILL BE SORELY MISSED   V  YESTERDAY I COULDN'T FIND MY ID</pattern><template>You didn't take it, did you?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO IS SHE</pattern><template>Not sure.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYONE ELSE  LET'S GO</pattern><template>Good God.</template></category><category><pattern>POLICE  OUT OF THE WAY</pattern><template>Get out the way!</template></category><category><pattern>ANCIENT HISTORY  FOR SOME</pattern><template>Not really very good table conversation.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE ACCELERATED MY ORIGINAL PLAN</pattern><template>As a result, I'm in need of someone with some theatrical skill.</template></category><category><pattern>IF I AM SURE OF ANYTHING  INSPECTOR         IT IS THAT THIS GOVERNMENT WILL NOT SURVIVE   IF IT IS TO BE SUBJECT TO YOUR FEELINGS    MR  DASCOMB    WHAT WE NEED RIGHT NOW         IS A CLEAR MESSAGE   TO THE PEOPLE OF THIS COUNTRY    THIS MESSAGE MUST BE READ   IN EVERY NEWSPAPER         HEARD ON EVERY RADIO    SEEN ON EVERY TELEVISION    THIS MESSAGE MUST RESOUND   THROUGHOUT THE ENTIRE INTERLINK    I WANT THIS COUNTRY TO REALIZE   THAT WE STAND ON THE EDGE OF OBLIVION    I WANT EVERY MAN  WOMAN AND CHILD   TO UNDERSTAND HOW CLOSE WE ARE TO CHAOS    I WANT EVERYONE         TO REMEMBER WHY THEY NEED US    IN THE FORMER UNITED STATES  CIVIL WAR   CONTINUES TO DEVASTATE THE MIDWEST    SCIENTISTS ATTRIBUTE THIS WATER SHORTAGE   TO THE LACK OF RAINFALL THE LAST TWO YEARS    MINISTRY OFFICIALS EXPECT   WATER COUPON PRICES TO RISE    POLICE HAVE ARRESTED NINE SUSPECTS     CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS SHIT</pattern><template>Been going on all summer.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DIDN'T YOU COME FORWARD BEFORE</pattern><template>What were you waiting for?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS FOR YOUR GRACE TO DECIDE</pattern><template>Oh, my.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT</pattern><template>Tanks, anti aircraft, infantry.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE COMPLETELY FREE</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN BE PRETTY CERTAIN THAT IF ANYONE DOES SHOW UP</pattern><template>...Creedy'll black bag every one of them.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER WHAT HAPPENED  AFTER WHAT THEY DID</pattern><template>...I thought about killing myself.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T STAY HERE</pattern><template>I know.</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T DO IT AGAIN  I SWEAR  PLEASE</pattern><template>What do you think, lads?</template></category><category><pattern>I HEARD SUTLER'S GOING TO MAKE A PUBLIC STATEMENT TONIGHT</pattern><template>It's nearly time.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS WONDERING IF YOUR OFFER TO HELP WAS STILL STANDING</pattern><template>Of course.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WOULD HAVE SCARED ME BEFORE</pattern><template>...but I suppose I should thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  YOUR GRACE</pattern><template>She has arrived, but there was some confusion at the agency.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  WELL  YOU BETTER COME INSIDE BEFORE SOMEONE SEES YOU</pattern><template>Cheers.</template></category><category><pattern>IT HAPPENED TO ME JUST AS IT HAPPENED TO YOU</pattern><template>Shut up! I don't want to hear your lies!</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD GOD</pattern><template>Hurry up, you lot! Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>STOP  GET YOUR HAND OFF THAT LEVER</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>FREEZE  NOBODY MOVE</pattern><template>If you're wearing a mask, get down on your knees!</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE IN THIS WORLD  IF I WERE TO INVITE WHO I DESIRED</pattern><template>...I would undoubtedly find myself without a home, let alone a television show.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN IT'S REALLY GOING TO HAPPEN  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>It will if you want it to.</template></category><category><pattern>A MAN AFTER MY OWN HEART</pattern><template>He always told the best stories.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE THE CONFESSIONAL GAME</pattern><template>Tell me your sins.</template></category><category><pattern>MY FELLOW ENGLISHMEN         TONIGHT  OUR COUNTRY         THAT WHICH WE STAND FOR         AND ALL THAT WE HOLD DEAR         FACES A GRAVE AND TERRIBLE THREAT   THE AREA'S CLEAN  SIR</pattern><template>This violent and unparalleled assault   to our security...   ...will not go undefended.  Where is he?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT AFTER THEY SHUT IT DOWN  SHE DISAPPEARED FOR TWO YEARS</pattern><template>Till she applied for an overseas visa, which was denied.</template></category><category><pattern>FEAR BECAME THE ULTIMATE TOOL OF THIS GOVERNMENT</pattern><template>Through it, our politician was ultimately appointed...</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE SHOULD NOT BE AFRAID OF THEIR GOVERNMENTS</pattern><template>Governments should be afraid of their people.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK THERE'S A CONNECTION BETWEEN OUR BOY AND LARKHILL</pattern><template>It might explain the connection between him and the Hammond girl.</template></category><category><pattern>GORDON</pattern><template>Quick, Evey, hide!</template></category><category><pattern>I MUST SAY THAT I AM RATHER ASTONISHED BY THE RESPONSE TIME OF LONDON'S FINEST</pattern><template>I hadn't expected you to be quite so Johnny on the spot.</template></category><category><pattern>A MAN DOES NOT WEAR A MASK     WHAT IS HE</pattern><template>A man does not threaten innocent civilians.   He's what every gutless ,  freedom hating terrorist is:   A goddamn coward!  There will be no negotiation.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERY DAY  GENTLEMEN    EVERY DAY THAT BRINGS US CLOSER   TO NOVEMBER         EVERY DAY THAT MAN REMAINS FREE         IS ONE MORE FAILURE    THREE HUNDRED AND FORTY SEVEN DAYS    GENTLEMEN    THREE HUNDRED AND FORTY SEVEN FAILURES   CHANCELLOR  WE DO NOT HAVE THE ADEQUATE FORCE</pattern><template>We are being buried beneath the avalanche   of your inadequacies, Mr. Creedy!  I'll get it.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  PLEASE  HAVE MERCY</pattern><template>Oh, not tonight, Bishop.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP  WHY DO YOU KEEP CALLING ME THAT</pattern><template>That was your title, remember?</template></category><category><pattern>THE HIGHEST PAID PERSON AT THE CAMP WAS A PRIEST</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>AND TO YOU</pattern><template>What was done to me created me.</template></category><category><pattern>REQUESTING ORDERS</pattern><template>What shall we do?</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU LIKE IT</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>AND ARE YOU GOING TO KILL MORE PEOPLE</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS ISN'T A GAME  YOUR GRACE</pattern><template>Someone's coming.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS HAS TO BE THE BLOODY COLDEST   MARCH IN YEARS    KEEP TALKING LIKE THAT    WE'LL LOSE OUR PARTY STATUS      THEY'RE A PACK OF LYING  GREEDY HYPOCRITES      KEEP IT DOWN  WILL YOU   BASED ON RANDOM AUDIO SWEEPS  I'VE PROJECTED THAT RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>...80 percent of the public believe the terrorist is still alive.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IN RECOGNITION OF THE IMPOSTER THAT STANDS IN HER STEAD</pattern><template>Tell me, do you know what day it is, Evey?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WASN'T MUCH LEFT    BUT WHEN I WAS THERE  IT WAS STRANGE   I SUDDENLY HAD THIS FEELING THAT EVERYTHING WAS CONNECTED</pattern><template>Like I could see the whole thing.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS STRANGE TO SUDDENLY SEE YOUR FACE EVERYWHERE</pattern><template>Conceal me what I am, and be my aid...</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>FROM  FAUST   THAT'S ABOUT TRYING TO CHEAT THE DEVIL  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>It is. And speaking of the devil...</template></category><category><pattern>ANYTHING ELSE ON THE PARENTS</pattern><template>Yeah, it ain't good.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  HERE AND THERE</pattern><template>Much of it from the vaults of the Ministry of objectionable Materials.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  FOR YOU  INSPECTOR</pattern><template>I needed you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE MAD</pattern><template>Either that or I wasn't breast fed.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THIS ONE IS FOR YOU</pattern><template>You're going to kill me now?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A LOAD OF BOLLOCKS</pattern><template>I made a mistake. I shouldn't be out after curfew. I know that.</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T HAVE THIS GETTING ANY MORE BOLLIXED UP THAN IT ALREADY IS</pattern><template>V!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SICK  YOU'RE EVIL</pattern><template>You could have ended it.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE A SEAT</pattern><template>It's delicious.</template></category><category><pattern>TO THINK THAT I DOUBTED YOUR LOVELINESS FOR AN INSTANT</pattern><template>Mea culpa, my child.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE FINGERMEN  PAL</pattern><template>Jesus Christ! Mercy!</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S DEAD</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>WHILE YOU SLEPT</pattern><template>Is there any pain?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE BOTH KNOW WHY</pattern><template>After I destroy Parliament...</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE DOES  AND SOMETHING HAPPENS   TO THAT BUILDING         THE ONLY THING THAT WILL CHANGE    THE ONLY DIFFERENCE IT WILL MAKE         IS THAT TOMORROW MORNING    INSTEAD OF A NEWSPAPER         I WILL BE READING   MR  CREEDY'S RESIGNATION   YOU'VE BEEN BUSY</pattern><template>They're very scared right now.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT THE CHOICE TO PULL THIS LEVER IS NOT MINE TO MAKE</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>TO THE NEWLY CREATED POSITION OF HIGH CHANCELLOR</pattern><template>The rest, as they say, is history.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TWO ESPRESSOS AND THREE COFFEES</pattern><template>And Deitrich is ready for his tea.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  DENIS</pattern><template>Has everything been arranged?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DOES THAT MEAN</pattern><template>Terrorist seems to have...</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  A LEAD ON THE GIRL</pattern><template>Look, don't get me wrong, I love it.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS LOOKS SERIOUS</pattern><template>Her parents were political activists.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL CONTACT YOU AGAIN</pattern><template>Till then, cheerio.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD EVENING  LONDON      ALLOW ME FIRST TO APOLOGIZE       THAT'S THE EMERGENCY CHANNEL</pattern><template>I do, like many of you, appreciate   the comforts of the everyday routine...   ...the security of the familiar ,  the tranquility of repetition.  Bloody hell.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE 872 SONGS IN HERE</pattern><template>I've listened to them all, but I've never danced to any of them.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WITH DEVOTION'S VISAGE AND PIOUS ACTION WE DO SUGAR O'ER THE DEVIL HIMSELF</pattern><template>What's that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE BEEN THROUGH YOUR RECORDS</pattern><template>All it says is that there was a detention facility at Larkhill...</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'D FIND HIM SOON</pattern><template>Please.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU HEAR ME</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>JUSTICE</pattern><template>Oh, I see.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PAST</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I ASK WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>There was a fire. A long time ago.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE GUNS</pattern><template>No, you have bullets and the hope that when your guns are empty...</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER WHAT YOU DID  I COULDN'T LET THAT HAPPEN</pattern><template>...so I picked you up and carried you to the only place I knew you'd be safe: Here, to my home.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT QUESTIONING YOUR POWERS OF OBSERVATION</pattern><template>I'm merely remarking upon the paradox of asking a masked man who he is.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM QUITE SURE THEY WILL SAY SO</pattern><template>But to whom, might I ask, am I speaking?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS PERIMETER ONE</pattern><template>We have enemy contact.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THE BAILEY AND MADE A MISTAKE IN THE JORDAN TOWER</pattern><template>I think this should balance it out.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT DIDN'T SEEM RIGHT  KNOWING YOU WROTE IT</pattern><template>I didn't.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE'S COMING</pattern><template>I think he means to kill you.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T    CAN'T BREATHE</pattern><template>Asthma. When I was little...</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE MEANS TO KILL YOU</pattern><template>I'm sorry?</template></category><category><pattern>WITH SO MUCH CHAOS  SOMEONE WILL DO SOMETHING STUPID</pattern><template>And when they do...</template></category><category><pattern>I'M EVEY HAMMOND  I'M</pattern><template>I've been the prisoner of the terrorist V for the past several weeks.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE INVITED HERE TO SUPPER IN THE FIRST PLACE</pattern><template>...if my appetites were for less conventional fare.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IF THEY COME AFTER YOU</pattern><template>I tell you what's gonna happen.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY CHRIST  JESUS</pattern><template>Good evening, Commander Prothero.</template></category><category><pattern>BUSY BOY</pattern><template>But after all that...</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE WRONG LIGHT  THE LOSS OF THE VOICE OF LONDON</pattern><template>...could be devastating to our credibility.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO  HUH</pattern><template>We've swept this place.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU READY FOR IT</pattern><template>Are we ready for it?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE INFORMATION FOR US</pattern><template>No, you already have the information.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>Yes, thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  ON THE EVE OF YOUR REVOLUTION</pattern><template>A revolution without dancing is a revolution not worth having.</template></category><category><pattern>BY SUNUP  IF YOU'RE NOT THE SORRIEST PIECE OF ASS IN ALL OF LONDON</pattern><template>...then you'll certainly be the sorest.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GIVE THEM SOMETHING  ANYTHING</pattern><template>Thank you...</template></category><category><pattern>AND  AS ALWAYS  ENGLAND PREVAILS</pattern><template>Holy Christ! Jesus!</template></category><category><pattern>WITH A YOUNG  UP AND COMING POLITICIAN</pattern><template>He's a deeply religious man and a member of the Conservative Party.</template></category><category><pattern>A SEPARATE REPORT HAS BEEN FILED</pattern><template>...suggesting a train, despite the fact that the tunnels surrounding Parliament...</template></category><category><pattern>NO  YOU WERE RIGHT ABOUT WHAT I AM</pattern><template>I have no tree waiting for me.</template></category><category><pattern>ALTHOUGH THERE'S AN OBVIOUS EXPLANATION</pattern><template>There is?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY SUTLER'S BEEN KEPT UNDERGROUND FOR SECURITY PURPOSES</pattern><template>That's why there are several of your men close to Sutler...</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I CAN SEE THAT</pattern><template>Of course you can.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS A FACE BENEATH THIS MASK</pattern><template>...but it's not me.</template></category><category><pattern>A MAN AS SMART AS YOU HAS PROBABLY CONSIDERED THIS</pattern><template>A man as smart as you probably has a plan.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WERE HERE BEFORE YOU EVEN STARTED</pattern><template>Bad luck, chummy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR POWERS OF OBSERVATION CONTINUE TO SERVE YOU WELL</pattern><template>But wait. It is to Madame Justice that I dedicate this concerto...</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I KILLED HIM</pattern><template>You...</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU LIKE MUSIC  MR  FINCH</pattern><template>That music?</template></category><category><pattern>NO RESPONSE FROM COMMAND</pattern><template>Or from Party Leader Creedy.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH MY HANDS AROUND YOUR NECK</pattern><template>Bollocks.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU KNOW WHY YOU'RE HERE  EVEY HAMMOND</pattern><template>Please.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALSO DOUBLED OUR RANDOM SWEEPS AND ARE MONITORING PHONE SURVEILLANCE</pattern><template>...indicating a high percentage of conversation concerned with the explosion.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU'RE AT THIS AS LONG AS I'VE BEEN  YOU STOP BELIEVING IN COINCIDENCE</pattern><template>May we come up?     You find your own tree.    You find your own tree.</template></category><category><pattern>AND MAYBE THAT'S REALLY WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>But I see this chain of events...</template></category><category><pattern>MARSHAL  HELP CARRY THIS MAN</pattern><template>Sir.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A GAME I'VE NEVER PLAYED</pattern><template>What a delightful mind you have.</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE THE REST OF YOU IS JUST AS INTERESTING</pattern><template>No, please, you have to believe me.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEY  THERE YOU ARE</pattern><template>You are still working for me.</template></category><category><pattern>DASCOMB</pattern><template>Have you any idea how long it would take to rebuild this facility?</template></category><category><pattern>THE CHANCELLOR SUSPECTS THERE MIGHT BE AN INFORMER</pattern><template>Are you saying I'm under surveillance, Mr. Creedy?</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE THE 5TH</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE IS YOUR MOTHER NOW</pattern><template>She's dead.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS A FIRE  A LONG TIME AGO</pattern><template>Ancient history, for some.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TIME</pattern><template>Tell me...</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT</pattern><template>I'm Evey Hammond. I'm...</template></category><category><pattern>TERRIBLE WHAT ST  MARY'S DID TO IRELAND  WASN'T IT</pattern><template>I've been a party member for 27 years.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I DIDN'T KNOW WHERE ELSE TO GO</pattern><template>Yes, well, you better come inside before someone sees you.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  BUT MR  DEITRICH'S DEAD</pattern><template>I thought they'd arrest him...</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR GRACE  WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME AND I HAVE TO TELL YOU SOMETHING</pattern><template>A confession?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE IN THE CELL NEXT TO HER</pattern><template>And that's what this is all about.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT TONIGHT I INTEND TO CALL UPON THE ENTIRE ORCHESTRA FOR THIS EVENT</pattern><template>...and would be honored if you could join me.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE BELIEVED TO BE EXTINCT</pattern><template>He leaves them at the crime scenes.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE</pattern><template>Several prominent party members have been murdered, chief inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T SAY THAT</pattern><template>I told you, only truth.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SAY THE WORD</pattern><template>What do I get out of this deal?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE UNCONSCIOUS AND I HAD TO MAKE A DECISION</pattern><template>If I had left you there, right now you'd be in one of Creedy's interrogation cells.</template></category><category><pattern>A MORE PERFECT STAGE COULD NOT BE ASKED FOR</pattern><template>I don't see any instruments.</template></category><category><pattern>DIE  DIE</pattern><template>Why won't you die?!</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU HAVE NO FEAR ANYMORE</pattern><template>You're completely free.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ISN'T MUCH TIME</pattern><template>I have something I must give you.</template></category><category><pattern>I WON'T TELL ANYONE  I SWEAR</pattern><template>You know you can trust me.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S NOT TRUE</pattern><template>I can't.</template></category><category><pattern>A NOBLE EXAMPLE FOR ALL THOSE WHO LABOR IN THE NAME OF OUR LORD  BUT</pattern><template>Your Grace?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT WAS A FEELING</pattern><template>But I can guess.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M FINE</pattern><template>Thanks to you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHILE A MEMORIAL IS BUILT TO CANONIZE THEIR VICTIMS</pattern><template>But the end result, the true genius of the plan, was the fear.</template></category><category><pattern>I AM V</pattern><template>At last you know the truth.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT SON OF A BITCH SAT THERE</pattern><template>...and spoon fed me that bullshit, and I ate it up!</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS  DELIA</pattern><template>Any leads on finding this guy?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT IS THAT  MR  DASCOMB     SHOULD THE TERRORIST SUCCEED</pattern><template>He won't.  I understand that it is highly unlikely, but if he does...</template></category><category><pattern>I WISH SOMEONE HAD THE BALLS TO TELL THAT BRAT THIS STATION AIN'T HIS PLAYGROUND</pattern><template>What the hell is this?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I'M IN TELEVISION</pattern><template>But why would you keep it?</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN I WAS 9  I PLAYED VIOLA IN  TWELFTH NIGHT   MUM WAS VERY PROUD</pattern><template>Where is your mother now?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WOULD DO WELL  INSPECTOR         TO PUT IT OUT OF YOUR MIND    MAY 23RD    MY FIRST BATCH OF SUBJECTS ARRIVED TODAY         AND I HAVE TO ADMIT   THAT I'M VERY EXCITED    THIS COULD BE THE DAWN OF A NEW AGE    NUCLEAR POWER IS MEANINGLESS         IN A WORLD WHERE A VIRUS   CAN KILL AN ENTIRE POPULATION         AND LEAVE ITS WEALTH INTACT     STAY TOGETHER</pattern><template>Come on, move!</template></category><category><pattern>E VEY  OF COURSE YOU ARE</pattern><template>What does that mean?</template></category><category><pattern>VIOLA</pattern><template>I don't understand.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU FOUND SOMETHING ELSE</pattern><template>In that cell, you found something that mattered more to you than life.</template></category><category><pattern>FREEZE</pattern><template>Get your hands on your head.</template></category><category><pattern>MONDEGO</pattern><template>Oh, God. I hope I didn't wake you.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD YOU LIKE TO</pattern><template>Does it have a happy ending?</template></category><category><pattern>AND YET I KNOW ALMOST NOTHING ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>I don't know where you were born, who your parents were...</template></category><category><pattern>OPPENHEIMER WAS ABLE TO CHANGE MORE THAN THE COURSE OF A WAR</pattern><template>He changed the entire course of human history.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  I DIDN'T SEE YOU</pattern><template>In a hurry, are we?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST SAID YOU KILLED LEWIS PROTHERO</pattern><template>I might have killed the Fingermen that attacked you. I heard no objection.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M A COP  I HAVE TO KNOW</pattern><template>I came when they opened it.</template></category><category><pattern>ON THE LIGHTER SIDE OF THINGS</pattern><template>...seems that the crew responsible for the demolition of the old Bailey...</template></category><category><pattern>I HOPE I DIDN'T PUT YOU OFF YOUR APPETITE</pattern><template>No, please. It's just... Are you all right?</template></category><category><pattern>IN HONOR OF THE HOLIDAY SHE SEEMS TO HAVE TAKEN FROM THESE PARTS</pattern><template>...and in recognition of the imposter that stands in her stead.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE MOST DILIGENT  DENIS</pattern><template>...a noble example for all those who labor in the name of our Lord, but...</template></category><category><pattern>AS ONLY CELLULOID CAN DELIVER</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD HAVE EVER GIVEN ME</pattern><template>V?</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A TERRORIST  YOU CAN'T EXPECT HIM TO ACT LIKE YOU OR ME</pattern><template>Some part of him's human.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WOULD BE HONORED IF YOU COULD JOIN ME</pattern><template>I don't think so.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CALLED IT  EGGIE IN THE BASKET   MY MUM MADE THEM</pattern><template>This is weird.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING BUT YOUR BLOODY KNIVES AND YOUR FANCY KARATE GIMMICKS</pattern><template>We have guns.</template></category><category><pattern>THE RED REPORT IN FRONT OF YOU HAS BEEN VETTED BY SEVERAL DEMOLITION SPECIALISTS</pattern><template>Now, it concludes that...</template></category><category><pattern>READ MY JOURNAL</pattern><template>What they did was only possible because of you.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE BEEN SEALED SHUT</pattern><template>Who filed that report?  Chief Inspector Finch.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE HE WAS RIGHT</pattern><template>About what?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M READY</pattern><template>Look, all they want is one little piece of information.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  THANK YOU</pattern><template>What is this place?</template></category><category><pattern>SHALL ONE DAY VINDICATE THE VIGILANT AND THE VIRTUOUS</pattern><template>Verily, this vichyssoise of verbiage veers most verbose.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THEY FOUND THAT HERE</pattern><template>I told you, you'd be the least of my worries.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  EVEY</pattern><template>You.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WERE YOU WAITING FOR</pattern><template>Well, for you, inspector.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WERE CALM  YOU WERE STILL</pattern><template>Try to feel now what you felt then.</template></category><category><pattern>CHAOS</pattern><template>Mr. Creedy, I am holding you   personally responsible for this situation.   The problem is that he knows us   better than we know ourselves.  That's why I went to Larkhill last night.</template></category><category><pattern>I LEAVE SUCH JUDGMENTS TO YOU  INSPECTOR</pattern><template>Our story begins, as these stories often do...</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN TO ME  YOU BLEEDING SOD  ENGLAND PREVAILS BECAUSE I SAY IT DOES</pattern><template>So does every lazy cunt on this show, and that includes you.</template></category><category><pattern>TO CEASE ANY INVESTIGATION OF MATTERS THAT HAVE LONG SINCE PASSED</pattern><template>...and concentrate on the concerns of our present.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD'VE LEFT ME ALONE</pattern><template>Why didn't you just leave me alone?!</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU  CHANCELLOR</pattern><template>A farewell gift.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT IS THIS PLACE</pattern><template>It's my home.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IDEAS ARE BULLETPROOF</pattern><template>This is perimeter one.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU KNOW HER</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>I FELL IN LOVE WITH YOU  EVEY</pattern><template>...like I no longer believed I could.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU COULD HAVE GIVEN IN  BUT YOU DIDN'T</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A GIFT FOR YOU  EVEY</pattern><template>...but before I give it to you, I'd like to ask you something.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  IT CONCLUDES THAT</pattern><template>...the most logical delivery system for the terrorist to use...</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU  LIKE  A CRAZY PERSON</pattern><template>I am quite sure they will say so.</template></category><category><pattern>CREEDY'LL BLACK BAG EVERY ONE OF THEM</pattern><template>People should not be afraid of their governments.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'VE SEARCHED THESE TUNNELS FOR WEEKS</pattern><template>You think you're gonna find him now?</template></category><category><pattern>THE MASKS WERE INGENIOUS</pattern><template>It was strange to suddenly see your face everywhere.</template></category><category><pattern>AS HEAD OF THE DETENTION PROGRAM AT THAT</pattern><template>Before you go any further, let me remind you things were very chaotic back then.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE BEEN THINKING</pattern><template>There's something I want to ask you...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WAIT TILL COMMERCIALS TO SET THEM OFF  OKAY</pattern><template>I can't believe you watch that shit.</template></category><category><pattern>A MAN AS SMART AS YOU PROBABLY HAS A PLAN</pattern><template>That plan is the reason Sutler no longer trusts you.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S BEAUTIFUL</pattern><template>Where did you get all this stuff?</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE HE CARED MORE ABOUT REVENGE THAN HE DID ABOUT HER</pattern><template>nationwide were devastated   as news of the most popular ...</template></category><category><pattern>BUT TO WHOM  MIGHT I ASK  AM I SPEAKING</pattern><template>I'm Evey.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT TONIGHT    DON'T DO THIS  I BEG OF YOU   WELL  THEN  CHILDREN'S HOUR AT THE ABBEY</pattern><template>Open your mouth   and stick out your tongue.    What the...?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE PLAYING MUSIC</pattern><template>How do you do that?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T LABOR I WAS SPEAKING OF</pattern><template>It was, rather, my final remittance that I was interested in.</template></category><category><pattern>I THOUGHT ABOUT KEEPING THIS</pattern><template>...but it didn't seem right, knowing you wrote it.</template></category><category><pattern>REAL SICK  BAD CASE OF THE BLUES</pattern><template>You can feel them.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WAS HE</pattern><template>He was Edmond Dantes.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE END RESULT  THE TRUE GENIUS OF THE PLAN  WAS THE FEAR</pattern><template>Fear became the ultimate tool of this government.</template></category><category><pattern>I ENJOY THEM AS MUCH AS ANY BLOKE    BUT IN THE SPIRIT OF COMMEMORATION</pattern><template>Who's that, Mum?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE WELCOME TO REVIEW OUR RECORDS</pattern><template>We've been through your records.</template></category><category><pattern>RIOTERS WERE ARRESTED IN BRIXTON   AND THEN SUTLER WILL BE FORCED TO DO THE ONLY THING HE KNOWS HOW TO DO</pattern><template>At which point, all V needs to do is keep his word.</template></category><category><pattern>THE TIME HAS COME FOR ME TO MEET MY MAKER</pattern><template>...and to repay him in kind for all that he's done.</template></category><category><pattern>A YELLOW CODED CURFEW IS NOW IN EFFECT    ANY UNAUTHORIZED PERSONNEL   WILL BE SUBJECT TO ARREST    THIS IS FOR YOUR PROTECTION    A YELLOW CODED CURFEW IS NOW IN EFFECT    ANY UNAUTHORIZED PERSONNEL   WILL BE SUBJECT TO ARREST    THIS IS FOR YOUR PROTECTION     EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Sorry, I didn't see you...</template></category><category><pattern>BLOWING UP A BUILDING CAN CHANGE THE WORLD</pattern><template>I wish I believed that was possible.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT AIN'T THE WORST OF IT</pattern><template>Her brother was at St. Mary's.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  PLEASE DON'T HURT ME</pattern><template>Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>A COW GETTING CRUCIFIED</pattern><template>It's hysterical.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT AS SORRY AS I AM</pattern><template>The truth is, after so many years...</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER THE 5TH  I NO LONGER THINK IT'LL MATTER</pattern><template>You mean a year from now?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'D BE ENOUGH FOR A CLEVER MAN</pattern><template>Are you saying that I have to stay here?</template></category><category><pattern>HEAVENS  NO</pattern><template>Stealing implies ownership.</template></category><category><pattern>ANARCHY IN THE UK</pattern><template>Chaos.</template></category><category><pattern>I DID IT</pattern><template>Freeze!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT AFRAID OF DEATH</pattern><template>You're like me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TORTURED ME</pattern><template>Why?</template></category><category><pattern>MISTAKES LIKE JORDAN TOWER CAN NO LONGER BE TOLERATED</pattern><template>...if, indeed, Jordan Tower was an accident.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NEARLY TIME</pattern><template>The masks were ingenious.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  FATHER LILLIMAN</pattern><template>Lilliman.</template></category><category><pattern>ON YOUR KNEES  ON YOUR KNEES</pattern><template>Please! Please don't hurt me!</template></category><category><pattern>WHEREBY IMPORTANT EVENTS OF THE PAST         USUALLY ASSOCIATED WITH SOMEONE'S DEATH   OR THE END OF SOME AWFUL  BLOODY STRUGGLE         ARE CELEBRATED WITH A NICE HOLIDAY         I THOUGHT WE COULD MARK   THIS NOVEMBER THE 5TH         A DAY THAT IS  SADLY    NO LONGER REMEMBERED         BY TAKING SOME TIME OUT OF OUR DAILY LIVES   TO SIT DOWN AND HAVE A LITTLE CHAT    THERE ARE  OF COURSE    THOSE WHO DO NOT WANT US TO SPEAK   LET ME THINK  LET ME THINK</pattern><template>Even now, orders are being shouted   into telephones...   ...and men with guns   will soon be on their way.    It's Chancellor Sutler.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THAT CELL  YOU FOUND SOMETHING THAT MATTERED MORE TO YOU THAN LIFE</pattern><template>When they threatened to kill you unless you gave what they wanted...</template></category><category><pattern>AND ALL TRAPPED BY IT</pattern><template>So do you know what's gonna happen?</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE MEANTIME  OUR RATINGS WILL GO THROUGH THE ROOF  IT'LL BE FINE  TRUST ME</pattern><template>Gordon?</template></category><category><pattern>THE BUILDING IS A SYMBOL  AS IS THE ACT OF DESTROYING IT</pattern><template>Symbols are given power by people.</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS SO NERVOUS THAT WHEN THE CASHIER ASKED ME FOR MY MONEY  I DROPPED IT</pattern><template>My friend picked it up...</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  LET'S MOVE</pattern><template>You two, cover these elevators.</template></category><category><pattern>GOODBYE</pattern><template>Evey...</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I DON'T UNDERSTAND  WE KNOW IT WAS</pattern><template>They were caught. They confessed.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD</pattern><template>God, I haven't had real butter since I was a little girl.</template></category><category><pattern>BIG DEAL  WE'VE GOT THE MOST WATCHED SHOW ON AIR</pattern><template>Well, you're my agent, that's what I pay you for.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE STUNNED  I KNOW</pattern><template>Hard to believe, isn't it, that beneath this wrinkled, well fed exterior...</template></category><category><pattern>AND HANDED IT TO ME</pattern><template>She looked at me right in the eyes...</template></category><category><pattern>WE DO WHAT WE SHOULD HAVE BEEN DOING</pattern><template>We find him.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO</pattern><template>Do you know why you're here, Evey Hammond?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL SIGNIFICANT WITNESSES HAVE BEEN DETAINED</pattern><template>Good. Mr. Etheridge?  A recording device was found wired into the central emergency broadcast system.</template></category></AIML>