<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>— THURSD… FRID… “YALLA  YALLA  YALLA ” (LET’S GO ) “YALLA  YALLA  YALLA ”  …ATTACK AGAINST WESTERNERS AND FOREIGNERS    WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE BREAK UP OF CASUALTIES    YOU CAN SEE THAT NON MUSLIMS WERE KILLED  AND SO WERE AMERICANS…  YOU DON’T WORRY ABOUT THE SAUDIS  THEY’LL TAKE CARE OF BUSINESS</pattern><template>Yeah, now.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYA  DO YOU WANNA BRIEF ‘EM</pattern><template>There are two narratives, about the location of Osama bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YEAH</pattern><template>I’m about to go look the president in the eye.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A SHOOTER</pattern><template>We’re blocked.</template></category><category><pattern>WE TALKED ABOUT BURROWING A PINHOLE CAMERA  BUT THERE’S A… HIGH RISK OF DISCOVERY</pattern><template>We found a safe house, but we can’t get a vantage point to fire a telescope over the balcony wall.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DO REALIZE THIS IS NOT A NORMAL PRISON  YOU DETERMINE HOW YOU’RE TREATED AND YOUR LIFE IS GONNA BE VERY UNCOMFORTABLE  UNTIL… YOU GIVE ME THE INFORMATION I NEED</pattern><template>Where exactly is Abu Ahmed living at the moment?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  BUT HE’S  UH  HE’S DEAD  SO DOESN’T THAT MAKE HIM A LITTLE LESS INTERESTING TO YOU</pattern><template>He may not be. We now know Abu Ahmed is one of eight brothers.  All the brothers in the family look alike. Three of them went to Afghanistan  Isn’t it possible that when   the three eldest brothers grew beards in Afghanistan, they started to look alike?  I think the one calling himself Abu Ahmed is still alive.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE HOW THIS WORKS</pattern><template>You don’t mind if my female colleague here checks out your junk, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUY WITH THE PHONE IN THE WHITE CAR</pattern><template>You see him?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE’S NOBODY ELSE HIDDEN AWAY ON SOME OTHER FLOOR</pattern><template>There is just us.</template></category><category><pattern>I  UM  DIDN’T THINK THIS DAY COULD GET ANY WORSE… BUT  UH… BAD NEWS FROM SAUDI INTELLIGENCE  THE  UM… COURIER GUY  ABU AHMED  IS DEAD</pattern><template>It’s a detainee video.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S DEAD    IN AFGHANISTAN  2001  I BURIED HIM WITH MY OWN HANDS    HE’S DEAD  IN AFGHANISTAN  2001…   AND WHERE WAS THIS    KABUL   NO  I DON’T BELIEVE THIS</pattern><template>I don’t believe this.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  MAYA</pattern><template>I always liked this lead.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T HAVE HIS REAL NAME  YOU DON’T HAVE A CLUE OF WHERE HE IS</pattern><template>Yes, but we know that he’s important.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  YOU GOT ME</pattern><template>You did, you got me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PMA  IT’S THE PAKISTANI MILITARY ACADEMY</pattern><template>It’s their West Point.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE THING YOU CAN COUNT ON IN LIFE IS THAT EVERYONE WANTS MONEY</pattern><template>You’re assuming that al Qaeda members are motivated by financial rewards.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY IMMINENT THREATS IN HERE</pattern><template>Oh, we’ve one on the consulate, the Marriott, it’s low security, um, and they’ve got Maj Khan talking about our gas stations in the US.</template></category><category><pattern>I TELL YOU WHAT  MAN  IT’S GOOD TO BE BACK IN KUWAIT</pattern><template>It’s good to see you again.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DOESN’T BELIEVE IN MY LEAD EITHER</pattern><template>It’s a good thing, because the fact that Faraj withheld on Abu Ahmed is very revealing.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE GOT YOU THERE  DUDE</pattern><template>I swear to you both, I don’t know his family name.</template></category><category><pattern>BY LOCATING THE COURIER  WE’VE LOCATED BIN LADEN</pattern><template>That’s really the intel.</template></category><category><pattern>UM  SHE’S BEEN HAVING A GREAT TIME SINCE SHE GOT IN  ISN’T THAT RIGHT</pattern><template>Good. How do you like Pakistan so far?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOO OO OO</pattern><template>— Well done, Patrick.</template></category><category><pattern>DONE</pattern><template>I tell you what, man, it’s good to be back in Kuwait.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HASN’T SLEPT IN  HE’S CLUELESS</pattern><template>You don’t remember, do you?</template></category><category><pattern>— THANK YOU</pattern><template>Moving through!</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S NOT GONNA TRAVEL OUT OF AL QAEDA TERRITORY</pattern><template>— And you’re not going to him.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO CHANGE</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE GO</pattern><template>This box here. This box sucks.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT A V10 LAMBORGHINI</pattern><template>How’s that for friendship?</template></category><category><pattern>AND ABU AHMED</pattern><template>Who’s Abu Ahmed? I’ve heard of the other guys.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  WELL  SO THE JORDS SAY</pattern><template>— Yeah, you’re right.</template></category><category><pattern>10 PERCENT CHANCE HE’S ONE OF THE RELATIVES OF THE BROTHERS</pattern><template>Basically, we agree with you.</template></category><category><pattern>— OKAY</pattern><template>Okay, you can leave it paused for now, but we’re gonna play through that— Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU GOT POPPED… WITH 150 KILOGRAMS OF HIGH EXPLOSIVES IN YOUR HOUSE</pattern><template>And then you dare question me?</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE ON STRIKE  THEY CAN’T BE — THAT MANY OF ‘EM  RIGHT</pattern><template>— Collect all media!</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY  I THOUGHT YOU SHOULD KNOW ABOUT IT</pattern><template>I just wanna say, I’ve heard a lot about you.</template></category><category><pattern>VIDEO CAMERAS  WHERE—WHERE WAS IT FOUND</pattern><template>Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF YOU WERE TO SAY  “HE’S RETIRED ” I’D SAY  “WHERE’S THE SWIMMING POOL ” WHERE’S THE GOLD CAGE WITH THE FALCONS</pattern><template>And why does he send his courier to the two cities in Pakistan, we most associate with al Qaeda, that have nothing particularly to do with heroin production.</template></category><category><pattern>BACK IT UP</pattern><template>Back it up… main gate.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU LIE TO ME  I’M GONNA HURT YOU  NOW  NOW  LOOK AT ME</pattern><template>Look at me, Ammar!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS MAY BE GOING OVERBOARD  BUT I BAKED HIM A CAKE</pattern><template>Muslims don’t celebrate with cake.  Don’t be so literal, everyone likes cake  It’s not too late for you to come, you know, it’ll be fun.  No, I don’t want to be a straphanger.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THAT’S HAIDER  ROOMI ROAD  ZAHID  NOGAZA  TAIMUR</pattern><template>He made a call from Hapur Street. That’s the Spice District.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE EXPLORED THE POSSIBILITY  OF DIGGING TUNNELS  OF SENDING HOT AIR BALLOONS  OF REROUTING SUPPLY C 130S TO TAKE A PEEK  BUT THAT MIGHT BE TOO ALERTING</pattern><template>We’ve looked for ways of collecting available DNA from his trash, you know, looking for his toothbrush, but they burn the trash.</template></category><category><pattern>MEN DON’T MESS WITH THE WASH</pattern><template>Okay, now watch, it takes her about four seconds to move from there, to the front door, so she’s on the older side.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW COME YOU ONLY CALL ME WHEN YOU NEED HELP</pattern><template>But when I need something, you are too busy to pick up the phone.</template></category><category><pattern>— I THINK SHE’S FUCKING SMART</pattern><template>We’re all smart, Jeremy.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK HE’S TELLING THE TRUTH</pattern><template>Twenty detainees recognized that photo of Abu Ahmed.</template></category><category><pattern>— ROGER THAT</pattern><template>— Uh, Lauren, I know you wanna get some questions in there, but give Balawi a little time.</template></category><category><pattern>— WE CANNOT LET THIS BE A WIN–WIN FOR AQ THE WAY YOU DO THIS  IS LOOK AHEAD</pattern><template>London, Heathrow, mass casualties.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THEY DON’T MOVE  SHOOT THEM</pattern><template>He’s still on?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  NO  IT’S GREAT TO SPEAK TO YOU TOO I’M—I’M AMAZED THAT YOU’RE STILL HERE</pattern><template>Well, I—I can do, um… Let me have a look, um… Why don’t we say 1:30.</template></category><category><pattern>— AND DO YOU KNOW WHY WE DID THAT</pattern><template>I don’t think I can answer that question, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHY DOES HE SEND HIS COURIER TO THE TWO CITIES IN PAKISTAN  WE MOST ASSOCIATE WITH AL QAEDA  THAT HAVE NOTHING PARTICULARLY TO DO WITH HEROIN PRODUCTION</pattern><template>The president is a thoughtful, analytical guy. He needs proof.</template></category><category><pattern>BE CONCISE  THE DIRECTOR’S IN THE LOOP… AND I WOULDN’T BE SURPRISED… IF HE DOESN’T UPDATE THE PRESIDENT</pattern><template>Yeah, I’m on it.</template></category><category><pattern>WAZIR BAGH ROAD — 5</pattern><template>Nishtarabad — 5.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE LOST POWER</pattern><template>Go to lock out.  Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>PROTECT THE HOMELAND</pattern><template>Bin Laden is the one who keeps telling them to attack the homeland.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THIS IS FROM A FEW MINUTES AGO  OKAY</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE WAS THE LAST TIME YOU SAW BIN LADEN  HUH</pattern><template>You know when you lie to me, I hurt you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE HAVE TO TALK TO HIM AND FIND OUT</pattern><template>The key is to meet him, so we can figure out for ourselves what he can actually do.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S OKAY</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I HAVE TIME  YOU DON’T</pattern><template>I have other things to do but you don’t.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE GONNA NEED AT LEAST TEN MINUTES  SIR</pattern><template>Echo Zero–Five, you have four Mikes.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S CLEAR</pattern><template>How’d it go the other night?</template></category><category><pattern>— OR IT’S CONFIRMATION BIAS</pattern><template>Mmm… We’re just worried about you, okay? Is that okay to say?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS GUY’S A FREELANCER WORKING OFF THE FUCKING INTERNET</pattern><template>No one’s even talked to bin Laden in four years. He’s out of the game.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  I’M FINE  I’M JUST… YOU KNOW  I’VE SEEN TOO MANY GUYS NAKED</pattern><template>It’s gonna be over a fucking hundred at this point.</template></category><category><pattern>I TELL YOU  BUDDY</pattern><template>Her confidence is the one thing that’s keeping me from getting ass raped in some Pakistani prison.</template></category><category><pattern>TOO MUCH UPDRAFT  NOW  HURRY UP</pattern><template>We’ve lost power.</template></category><category><pattern>— BUT IT DOES NOT SCREAM BIN LADEN</pattern><template>— You get the point?</template></category><category><pattern>— EXCEPT IF IT WAS TUPAC THERE… — THIS IS WORTH 5 MILLION BUCKS</pattern><template>You know we gonna have to chase it down.</template></category><category><pattern>— TWELVE YEARS</pattern><template>— I was recruited out of high school.</template></category><category><pattern>GO</pattern><template>Come on, over here!</template></category><category><pattern>— OKAY  HEADING EAST</pattern><template>Fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE’S NO PATTERN</pattern><template>Sometimes, he calls every two weeks, sometimes, every three.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT STILL WOULDN’T WORK</pattern><template>— Why?</template></category><category><pattern>I’M GONNA BE HONEST WITH YOU  BRO</pattern><template>I’m cool with it.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WERE ALWAYS TOGETHER</pattern><template>What did he do for Faraj?</template></category><category><pattern>— SLOW DOWN</pattern><template>— Video cameras?</template></category><category><pattern>DON’T THEY GET GROCERIES</pattern><template>The unidentified third male does not get groceries.</template></category><category><pattern>PLUS  I THINK IT’S A GOOD THING HE LIED</pattern><template>No, not at the expense of protecting the homeland, you can’t… Wait a minute. Why is it a good thing?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  JUST SO YOU KNOW  IT’S GONNA TAKE A WHILE</pattern><template>He has to learn how helpless he is.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS DECISION IS NOT GOING— IT’S HER AGAINST THE WORLD</pattern><template>Oh, yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>— FIFTY BUCKS</pattern><template>Fifty bucks.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT MAKES YOU SAY THAT</pattern><template>He brought me many messages from the “Sheik”.</template></category><category><pattern>PAPERBOY</pattern><template>A disgrace to humanity. You and your uncle murdered 3,000 innocent people.</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL DEFEND IT</pattern><template>Done.</template></category><category><pattern>FINE</pattern><template>Facilitators come and go.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN I’M GONNA KILL BIN LADEN</pattern><template>Right.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  BREAKING OFF</pattern><template>The guy you’ve been looking for, geolocated, on his cell phone, in his white car.</template></category><category><pattern>15… 20… HE’S MOVING FAST  HE’S IN A VEHICLE</pattern><template>Weaker now, he shifted. Go back to 5.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU EVEN REALIZE WHAT YOU JUST DID</pattern><template>Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>DUDE  YOU SHIT YOUR PANTS</pattern><template>You stay here, I’ll be back.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES  I WOULDN’T EVEN SEE HIM</pattern><template>He would just tell me, where to leave the messages.</template></category><category><pattern>ABU AHMED AL KUWAITI</pattern><template>Abu Ahmed means “father of Ahmed”, it’s a kunya.</template></category><category><pattern>’CAUSE THE TRUTH IS  WE’VE BEEN ON THIS OP BEFORE</pattern><template>It was ‘07, and it wasn’t bin Laden, and we lost a couple of guys.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THEY’RE PROBABLY BETWEEN 7 AND 9</pattern><template>— Boys, definitely.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  WE’VE ONE ON THE CONSULATE  THE MARRIOTT  IT’S LOW SECURITY  UM  AND THEY’VE GOT MAJ KHAN TALKING ABOUT OUR GAS STATIONS IN THE US</pattern><template>And that’s a conversation?</template></category><category><pattern>APPRECIATE IT</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  FINE  95 PERCENT ‘CAUSE I KNOW CERTAINTY FREAKS YOU GUYS OUT  BUT IT’S A HUNDRED</pattern><template>They’re all cowed.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU WILL NEVER FIND HIM</pattern><template>— Why is that?</template></category><category><pattern>UH  IT’S OKAY</pattern><template>— How long have you worked for the CIA?</template></category><category><pattern>TALL  LONG WHITE BEARD</pattern><template>Thin. He uses a cane.</template></category><category><pattern>SAYEED</pattern><template>— Who is it?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT ONE  WE’RE INTERNAL ON THE SOUTH SIDE   THIS IS A NEGATIVE BREACH</pattern><template>Roger, ready to make our entry out here.</template></category><category><pattern>WE PULLED THE CELL TOWER NEARBY</pattern><template>And I’m also going to give up hope that he might ever get in that white SUV, and… drive around a bit and we could see him.</template></category><category><pattern>— SUNDAY</pattern><template>— Almost.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STAY HERE  I’LL BE BACK</pattern><template>Your friend is an animal.</template></category><category><pattern>— IN THE BOX YOU GO</pattern><template>— Sunday!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS GUY YOU ARE OBSESSED WITH</pattern><template>What’s his name again?</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP</pattern><template>Humam Khalil al Balawi.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAID WHITES FACES DON’T BELONG HERE</pattern><template>If they don’t move, shoot them.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW WE FIND HIM AGAIN  AND… BOY  DOES HE HAVE A REALLY NICE HOUSE</pattern><template>— Is that it?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE WE GONNA BOARD THESE WINDOWS UP OR WHAT</pattern><template>Just off the plane from Washington… Rocking your best suit for your first interrogation, and you get this guy.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M GONNA SMOKE EVERYBODY INVOLVED IN THIS OP</pattern><template>And then I’m gonna kill bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE’S NO WORKING GROUP COMING TO THE RESCUE</pattern><template>There’s nobody else hidden away on some other floor.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAS TO LEARN HOW HELPLESS HE IS</pattern><template>Come on, let’s get a coffee.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY STUCK IN SOME CHECKPOINT  SOMEWHERE</pattern><template>You two hooked up yet?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT</pattern><template>I wanna make something absolutely clear.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’LL NOTICE THESE STEALTH PANELS  SIMILAR TO WHAT WE USE ON THE B 2</pattern><template>The rotors have been muffled with decibel killers.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GROUND BRANCH GUYS ARE DRAGGING THEIR HEELS    THERE’S NO TEAM DEPLOYED RIGHT NOW   FUCK</pattern><template>He hasn’t said anything incriminating,   but he’s at the Rawal call center in Rawalpindi.  Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST DON’T GET THE RHYTHMS OF POLITICS</pattern><template>Oh, you think this is political?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS MOSTLY WITH ABU FARAJ</pattern><template>They were always together.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ALL COME AT THIS  THROUGH THE FILTER OF OUR OWN PAST EXPERIENCES</pattern><template>Now I remember Iraq WMD, very clearly. I fronted that.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S A GOOD THING  BECAUSE THE FACT THAT FARAJ WITHHELD ON ABU AHMED IS VERY REVEALING</pattern><template>The only other thing Faraj lied about, was the location of bin Laden himself.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK YOU</pattern><template>I want the e mails of the rest of the Saudi group.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE BASING THIS MOSTLY ON DETAINEE REPORTING  AND I SPENT A BUNCH OF TIME IN THOSE ROOMS  I’D SAY IT’S A SOFT 60  SIR</pattern><template>I’m virtually certain there’s some high value target there, I’m just not sure it’s bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>— FROM YOU</pattern><template>— You think so?</template></category><category><pattern>— FUCK</pattern><template>— Go.</template></category><category><pattern>SUNDAY  THIS SUNDAY OR NEXT SUNDAY</pattern><template>Where?</template></category><category><pattern>HE REALLY ASKED FOR A DIALYSIS MACHINE</pattern><template>Maybe we can fill the damn thing with poison.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS MOTHER LIVES HERE</pattern><template>I just need her phone number.</template></category><category><pattern>LET’S GO</pattern><template>Right now, all this is about, simply, is you coming to terms with your situation.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU WANNA TAKE A RUN AT HIM</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WORKS FOR BIN LADEN</pattern><template>The guys that talk about ops on the phone don’t get that job.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK</pattern><template>We got a signal on Tipu Road for ten minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>“WHAT THEY SAY IS TRUE  THE SHAOLIN AND THE WU TANG COULD BE DANGEROUS ” WHAT DO YOU LIKE TO BE CALLED</pattern><template>“Faraj”, “Fareej”, “Buzzie”?</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU OKAY</pattern><template>— Yeah, I’m fine, I’m just… You know, I’ve seen too many guys naked.</template></category><category><pattern>UM  I DID SEE HIM  ONCE  ABOUT A YEAR AGO  IN KARACHI</pattern><template>He read us all a letter from the “Sheik”.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT YOU</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR ONE THING  IT’S DANGEROUS</pattern><template>For another, the area is too congested for us to be effective, without some predictive intelligence.</template></category><category><pattern>I SHOT THE THIRD FLOOR GUY</pattern><template>Why’ncha get to work? Grab a bag.</template></category><category><pattern>THIRTY SECONDS TO FIRST TURN   HEY  JUSTIN  WHAT’RE YOU LISTENING TO</pattern><template>— Tony Robbins.</template></category><category><pattern>CIGARETTE</pattern><template>It said, “Continue the jihad.” “The work will go on for a hundred years.”  You and I are gonna talk about some of the guys at the training camps, yeah?   Okay.   Some of these brothers have done some bad things.   What I wanna do is, I wanna separate them from the people like you.   Definitely, yeah.   All right, a guy called Abu Ahmed, from Kuwait.   Yes, I remember him. The nice guy.   How close was he? What was his relationship to the leadership?   I don’t know.   Did he eat with you guys?   Did he eat with the good guys, or did he eat with the leadership?   I don’t know, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME HUMMUS  TABBOULEH  DON’T KNOW WHAT THAT IS  SOME FIGS  YOU EARNED IT</pattern><template>So uh you flew via Amman to Kabul, yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT A FUCKING MESS</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>— IS THAT HIM</pattern><template>— Could be.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’VE GOT ONE MIKE TO BLOW THAT DOWNED HELO   — YOU ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>FAILED BREACH  FAILED BREACH</pattern><template>Back it up.</template></category><category><pattern>WE THOUGHT ABOUT SENDING A GUY WITH A BUCKET  TO PULL A SAMPLE FROM THE SEWER  TO ANALYZE HIS FECAL MATTER</pattern><template>What was wrong with that, exactly?</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S GONNA WITHHOLD OPERATIONAL DETAILS ON THE KSM NETWORK AND PROBABLY BIN LADEN</pattern><template>But he’s been in complete isolation.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT ME  AMMAR</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S THE BEST MAN FOR IT</pattern><template>Uh, yeah, the London station’s already asking if he’s contacting anybody in the UK.</template></category><category><pattern>JORDANIANS ARE BEING REALLY HELPFUL WITH AMMAR’S TRANSIT PAPERS</pattern><template>Any imminent threats in here?</template></category><category><pattern>MUKHTAR</pattern><template>— How did you know that?</template></category><category><pattern>﻿1  UNITED 1523  DID YOU HEAR YOUR COMPANY  DID YOU HEAR…   …COUPLE OF MINUTES AGO  SCREAMING    WE DID HEAR THAT  UH  YELLING TOO    YES I DID  797  AND  UH  WE COULDN’T TELL WHAT IT WAS EITHER    …TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT’S GOING ON… UNITED 93  CLEVELAND    AMERICAN AIRLINES EMERGENCY LINE  PLEASE STATE YOUR EMERGENCY    THE FLIGHT ATTENDANT IS ADVISING OUR REPS THAT THE PILOT…   EVERYONE’S BEEN STABBED AND UM  I THINK THERE’S MACE   …THAT WE CAN’T BREATHE  I DONT KNOW I THINK WE’RE GETTING HIJACKED   HIJACKED AIRCRAFT HEADED TOWARDS NEW YORK    IS THIS REAL WORLD OR EXERCISE    NO  THIS IS NOT AN EXERCISE    CAN ANYBODY GET UP TO THE COCKPIT    WHAT’S GOING ON  BETTY  BETTY  TALK TO ME    A PLANE’S CRASHED INTO THE WORLD TRADE CENTER…   I THINK WE MIGHT HAVE LOST HER    HEY  MA  SURE THAT YOU’VE HEARD…   THAT A PLANE CRASHED INTO WORLD TRADE CENTER ONE    BABY  YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME CAREFULLY    I’M ON A PLANE THAT’S BEEN HIJACKED    I HOPE TO BE ABLE TO SEE YOUR FACE AGAIN  BABY    I LOVE YOU  GOODBYE    …OF ANOTHER INCOMING PLANE  WE MAY HAVE TO TAKE COVER    ARE THEY GONNA BE ABLE TO GET SOMEBODY UP HERE    OF COURSE  MA’AM  WE’RE COMING UP TO YOU    WELL  THERE’S NO ONE HERE YET AND THE FLOOR IS COMPLETELY ENGULFED   WE’RE ON THE FLOOR AND WE CAN’T BREATHE    HOLD FOR ONE SECOND  PLEASE I’M GONNA DIE  AREN’T I    — NO  NO  NO  NO  NO  NO</pattern><template>— I think I’m gonna die.   Ma’am, ma’am, now, I’m gonna die.   Look, stay calm, stay calm, stay calm, stay calm.   Please, God…   You’re doing a good job, ma’am, you’re doing a good job.   No, it’s so hot, I’m burning up.   …fine, they’re gonna come get you.   Can anyone hear me?   Oh, my God…  I own you, Ammar.</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>I’m glad you said that.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DID A RED TEAM ON YOUR ANALYSIS</pattern><template>According to them, this behavior could belong to someone other than al Qaeda.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT I DON’T KNOW WHERE HE IS NOW</pattern><template>Sometimes, I wouldn’t even see him.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE LOCATED AN INDIVIDUAL  WE BELIEVE  BASED ON DETAINEE REPORTING  IS BIN LADEN’S COURIER</pattern><template>He’s living in a house, in Abbottabad, Pakistan.</template></category><category><pattern>I SWEAR TO YOU BOTH  I DON’T KNOW HIS FAMILY NAME</pattern><template>I would have never asked him something like that. It’s not how my uncle worked.</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL TAKE THAT  THANK YOU VERY MUCH</pattern><template>— Take that too.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THERE’S SOME FAMOUS “BALUCHI” GUY  WORKING FOR YOU AND BIN LADEN  THAT I’VE NEVER EVEN HEARD OF</pattern><template>— Why should you have heard of him?</template></category><category><pattern>LOCKED GATE BLOCKING THE STAIRS</pattern><template>Breacher up.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S RIGHT THERE IN THE INNER CIRCLE</pattern><template>I don’t buy it. Didn’t you tell me yourself, nobody turns on al Qaeda?</template></category><category><pattern>GO AHEAD AND STAND DOWN   COPY THAT</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I’VE DONE NOTHING ELSE</pattern><template>Well, you certainly have a flair for it.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S YOUR MONEY MAKER RIGHT THERE</pattern><template>And this is the guy that’s KSM’s nephew.</template></category><category><pattern>— TALK TO THE KID</pattern><template>Ladi!</template></category><category><pattern>HARD LANDING    PRINCE FIVE–ONE IS DOWN    BLACK HAWK DOWN IN THE ANIMAL PEN   THIS WAY</pattern><template>This mission is still a “go”, I repeat, we are a “go”.   Alpha Team is in the animal pen, making entry for AC1.  No ropes, wheels down.</template></category><category><pattern>DETAINEE’S READY FOR YOU</pattern><template>Come on. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS ONE OF TEN NAMES ON A WATCH LIST SENT TO US BY THE MOROCCANS AFTER 9/11</pattern><template>Ibrahim Sayeed.</template></category><category><pattern>MEANWHILE  OUR CHIEF FOREIGN CORRESPONDENT  RICHARD ENGEL CONFIRMS   THE CIA’S TOP SPY IN PAKISTAN HAS BEEN PULLED OUT OF THERE    HE’S BEEN RECEIVING DEATH THREATS  AFTER BEING NAMED PUBLICLY IN A LAWSUIT    BY THE FAMILY OF A VICTIM OF A US DRONE ATTACK    RICHARD ENGEL QUOTES A SENIOR INTELLIGENCE OFFICIAL AS SAYING    THE OFFICER IS RETURNING TO THE US  AFTER THE DECISION WAS MADE THAT   TERRORIST THREATS AGAINST HIM  IN PAKISTAN  WERE OF SUCH A SERIOUS NATURE    IT WOULD NOT BE SMART NOT TO ACT   ISI FUCKED YOU</pattern><template>I’m so sorry, Joseph.</template></category><category><pattern>BECAUSE WE’RE FRIENDS</pattern><template>You’re saying we are friend.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN SEE THEIR HEIGHT RELATIVE TO THIS  THESE ARE COWS</pattern><template>So, they’re probably between 7 and 9.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  REAL TRADECRAFT</pattern><template>The only people we’ve seen behave in this way, are other top level al Qaeda operatives.</template></category><category><pattern>— HOW</pattern><template>Oh, you have to be really careful with people in KSM’s circle, they’re devious.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT NARRATIVE IS PRE 9/11 UNDERSTANDING OF UBL</pattern><template>The second narrative, is that he’s living in a city.</template></category><category><pattern>A FUCKING “YES” OR A “NO”</pattern><template>We don’t deal in certainty, we deal in probability.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  DAN</pattern><template>Look, Maya, you gotta be real careful with the detainees now.</template></category><category><pattern>IN RAWALPINDI  HAIDER ROAD</pattern><template>Roomi Road.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE US OPTIONS</pattern><template>Technically, these don’t exist.</template></category><category><pattern>“FARAJ”  “FAREEJ”  “BUZZIE”</pattern><template>C’mon, dude, what do you like? You like a bit of, uh… You guys like a bit of Bob Marley, with the Reggae?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT ORDER OKAY  OR D—DO YOU WANNA INTRODUCE EVERYONE</pattern><template>I’ll introduce you, you introduce your team.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  WHICH DAY IS IT</pattern><template>Partial information… You gonna go in the box, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>MM HM</pattern><template>And they went north, I think, to Kunar.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S HIM</pattern><template>He was one of ten names on a watch list sent to us by the Moroccans after 9/11.</template></category><category><pattern>USAMAH… USAMAH… USAMAH… DOWN</pattern><template>Got a possible jackpot.</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL INTRODUCE YOU  YOU INTRODUCE YOUR TEAM</pattern><template>— He knows this is a high level meeting.</template></category><category><pattern>— WELL DONE  PATRICK</pattern><template>— Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>HER CONFIDENCE</pattern><template>That’s the kinda concrete data point I’m looking for.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE FUCKING OUT OF YOUR MIND</pattern><template>I need four techs and a safe house in Rawalpindi… Four techs and a safe house in Peshawar.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  LOOK HOW RUN DOWN YOU ARE</pattern><template>Where’s Jack?</template></category><category><pattern>— WE GONNA SEARCH HIM WHEN HE GETS HERE — SURE</pattern><template>Okay, let’s go.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  PROCEDURES ONLY WORK IF WE FOLLOW THEM EVERY TIME</pattern><template>This is different. I’m sorry, I can’t explain, but it’s for a good cause.</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>Alpha–Three…  This is Echo Eleven, we’re at primary set point, prepping to breach.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW IS THE FOOD DOWN HERE ANYWAY</pattern><template>Uh, it’s okay.</template></category><category><pattern>BILL  SHE’S GOOD TO GO  I’LL GET HER THE RIGHT ONE TOMORROW</pattern><template>Was I lying or what?</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S TOO DANGEROUS</pattern><template>— Yup.</template></category><category><pattern>ECHO ZERO–FIVE  YOU HAVE FOUR MIKES</pattern><template>This is a gold mine, I need more time than that.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  YOU’RE RIGHT</pattern><template>We can’t rely on this or the Jords.</template></category><category><pattern>NO VEST</pattern><template>All clear.</template></category><category><pattern>BEFORE YOU WENT BACK TO PESH</pattern><template>After 9/11, we had to choose.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOLD YOU BEFORE  I WON’T TALK TO YOU</pattern><template>Have it your way. Let’s go.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I WANT TO FOCUS ON IS THE SAUDI GROUP</pattern><template>That, there, is Hazem al Kashmiri.</template></category><category><pattern>HER CONFIDENCE IS THE ONE THING THAT’S KEEPING ME FROM GETTING ASS RAPED IN SOME PAKISTANI PRISON</pattern><template>I’m gonna be honest with you, bro.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT SENATORS JUMPING OUT OF OUR ASSES</pattern><template>And the director is very concerned.</template></category><category><pattern>MIGHT WANNA PUT THIS ON</pattern><template>You’re not wearing one?</template></category><category><pattern>C’MON OUT</pattern><template>“Erfa Edak!” (Hands up!) Get down!</template></category><category><pattern>SAYEED FAMILY CALL IN PROGRESS  BUT YOU’RE NOT GONNA LIKE THIS</pattern><template>The ground branch guys are dragging their heels,   there’s no team deployed right now.  Fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>OBVIOUSLY  THIS ASSUMES HE DOESN’T CHANGE VEHICLES</pattern><template>— Morning.</template></category><category><pattern>TECHNICALLY  THESE DON’T EXIST</pattern><template>I actually tried to kill this program a couple of times.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S HIS NAME AGAIN</pattern><template>Abu Ahmed al Kuwaiti is the nom de guerre.</template></category><category><pattern>COUNTRIES WANTING TO HELP OUT</pattern><template>We got a million tips, and… you know, things got lost in the shuffle.</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL GO TO WASHINGTON  DO THE DANCE  SEE HOW THAT ENVIRONMENT WORKS</pattern><template>You should come with me.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  HE KNOWS</pattern><template>— How?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY KILLED MY MONKEYS</pattern><template>Some bullshit about escaping, you fucking believe that?</template></category><category><pattern>— ABU AHMED    ABU AHMED    ABU AHMED   DIRECTEMENT POUR BEN LADEN</pattern><template>On peut pas savoir qui travaille directement pour Ben Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>GO  GO  GO</pattern><template>This is Echo Zero–Nine, we have unknowns gathering in the southwest rooftops.</template></category><category><pattern>SERIOUSLY  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Don’t you thank me until you hear what I want for it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WORKS FOR ZAWAHIRI</pattern><template>He’s in charge of military tactics.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Go, go, go!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  AL QAEDA NEEDS DOCTORS  AND THEY ARE SHORT STAFFED  AND… THAT COULD EXPLAIN HIS RISE</pattern><template>In six months to a year, if he doesn’t fuck up, he could be called in to treat bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD JOB</pattern><template>— Slow down.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THEY’RE USING YOU GUYS  AS CANARIES  IN A THEORY THAT IF BIN LADEN ISN’T THERE  YOU CAN SNEAK AWAY  — AND NO ONE WILL BE THE WISER</pattern><template>— Hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT ATIYAH ABDUL RAHMAN</pattern><template>He works for Zawahiri.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY OTHER THING FARAJ LIED ABOUT  WAS THE LOCATION OF BIN LADEN HIMSELF</pattern><template>That means Faraj thinks Abu Ahmed’s just as important to protect as bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD YOU PICKED UP INSTEAD OF KILLING YOU  BECAUSE YOU’RE NOT A VIOLENT MAN  AND YOU DON’T DESERVE TO DIE</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS  IT’S NOT ON YOU</pattern><template>Oh, and who said that, huh? Zayid? Fuck him. This is on me. Ammar is on me, — No, no, no. Now, you had what, days?</template></category><category><pattern>ABRAR</pattern><template>Abrar… Abrar!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT ANY FRIENDS AT ALL</pattern><template>That’s Jack.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN HE NEEDS FRESH AIR  HE PACES AROUND  BENEATH A GRAPE ARBOR</pattern><template>But the leaves are so thick, they obscure our satellite views.</template></category><category><pattern>MUSLIMS DON’T CELEBRATE WITH CAKE   DON’T BE SO LITERAL  EVERYONE LIKES CAKE  IT’S NOT TOO LATE FOR YOU TO COME  YOU KNOW  IT’LL BE FUN   NO  I DON’T WANT TO BE A STRAPHANGER</pattern><template>It’s your show. You were the first to see the potential in this.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  SLIDE RIGHT  SLIDE RIGHT</pattern><template>Too much updraft! Now, hurry up!</template></category><category><pattern>THE HOUSE SCREAMS SECURITY</pattern><template>It screams someone who wants privacy; it even screams bad guy.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE</pattern><template>You can help yourself by being truthful.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT PEOPLE DIDN’T BELIEVE IN THIS LEAD ENOUGH TO DROP A BOMB</pattern><template>So, they’re using you guys, as canaries, in a theory that if bin Laden isn’t there, you can sneak away, — and no one will be the wiser.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY I JUST GOT HERE</pattern><template>What are you going to do?</template></category><category><pattern>SOME GUY IN GITMO WHO’S ALL LAWYERED UP</pattern><template>He’ll just tell his lawyer to warn bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S THE ONLY NAME THEY GAVE ME</pattern><template>You can sit wherever you want, you’re the only one on the manifest.</template></category><category><pattern>— WA ALAYKUM SALAM</pattern><template>— Thank you very much for this.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT’S THAT UP THERE</pattern><template>— Uh, those are kids, they’re shuffling around, sword fighting or something, with sticks.</template></category><category><pattern>ABBOTTABAD IS INTERESTING BECAUSE WE KNOW FROM DETAINEE REPORTING THAT ABU FARAJ STAYED THERE  BRIEFLY  IN 2003 THE GOOD NEWS IS HE’S DRIVING A WHITE SUV</pattern><template>SUVs are actually pretty rare in Pakistan.</template></category><category><pattern>EVERYONE  AGENT MAYA  MAYA  EVERYONE</pattern><template>Please don’t ask her how it’s going with Ammar, ’cause she’s not gonna fucking tell you.</template></category><category><pattern>HE MAY WELL EVEN BE DEAD  HE MIGHT AS WELL BE FUCKING DEAD</pattern><template>But you know what you’re doing?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT THE FUCK HAVE WE DONE ABOUT IT  HUH</pattern><template>What have we done?</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU GUYS EVER AGREE ON ANYTHING</pattern><template>— Well, I agree with Mike.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT DOES THIS BALUCHI GUY LOOK LIKE</pattern><template>Tall. Long white beard.</template></category><category><pattern>— THEY’RE NOT ALWAYS THIS INTENSE</pattern><template>— I’m fine.</template></category><category><pattern>— “ALLAH HU AKBAR ” — GET YOUR HAND OUT OF YOUR POC… — “ALLAH HU AKB—”  THE CIA SAYS  SEVEN OF IT’S EMPLOYEES WERE KILLED    AND SIX OTHERS WOUNDED  IN A SUICIDE BOMBING IN A BASE IN AFGHANISTAN    IT WAS ONE OF THE DEADLIEST ATTACKS IN CIA HISTORY    THE ASSOCIATED PRESS HAS LEARNED THAT…   THE CHIEF OF THE CIA’S POST IN THE PROVINCE  IS AMONG THE VICTIMS    FORMER OFFICIALS SAY  SHE WAS THE MOTHER OF THREE    THE TALIBAN CLAIMED RESPOSIBILITY FOR THE BOMBING…  — YOU OKAY</pattern><template>— Mhm.</template></category><category><pattern>KASHMIR IS INTERESTING BECAUSE IT’S A WAY STATION FOR THE TRIBALS</pattern><template>Abbottabad is interesting because we know from detainee reporting that Abu Faraj stayed there, briefly, in 2003 The good news is he’s driving a white SUV.</template></category><category><pattern>ME  AND SOME OTHER GUYS WHO WERE HANGING AROUND AT THAT TIME</pattern><template>You know, I can always go and eat with some other dude, hang you back up to the ceiling.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  GO AHEAD</pattern><template>So a little context here, if you take a right, out of Islamabad, drive about forty five minutes north, you’ll find yourself here in Abbottabad.</template></category><category><pattern>HE MADE THIS VIDEO TO PROVE HIS BONA FIDES</pattern><template>Shut up.</template></category><category><pattern>— HUH</pattern><template>— Noori Hasan.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  THAT’S PRE 9/11 BEHAVIOR</pattern><template>We have no reason to believe he’s changed security tactics.</template></category><category><pattern>I ALWAYS LIKED THIS LEAD</pattern><template>Sorry I just got here.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S GONNA BE OVER A FUCKING HUNDRED AT THIS POINT</pattern><template>I need to go and do something normal for a while.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S JACK</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  SO  UBL  YOU GOT—YOU GOT AN INTEL SOURCE ON THE GROUND</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>BEN ON VA EN PARLER UN P’TIT PEU ALORS  HEIN</pattern><template>Tu vas m’en parler?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS BOX HERE  THIS BOX SUCKS</pattern><template>And I’m gonna put you in it.</template></category><category><pattern>HUH  MAYBE A CONVERTIBLE</pattern><template>Get a little wind in the hair?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HE’S EITHER GONNA KEEP WITHHOLDING OR HE’S GONNA DIE FROM THE PRESSSURE YOU’RE PUTTING ON HIM</pattern><template>Hey, you wanna take a run at him?</template></category><category><pattern>HE IS HIS MOST TRUSTED COURIER</pattern><template>What makes you say that?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S SUPPOSED TO BE HIS ROYAL GUARD</pattern><template>No, that’s pre 9/11 behavior.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT… TARGETS</pattern><template>Do your fuckin’ jobs, bring me people to kill.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT BUYS A NEW LIFE</pattern><template>Do you think he might be exaggerating his access?</template></category><category><pattern>HE HASN’T SAID ANYTHING INCRIMINATING    BUT HE’S AT THE RAWAL CALL CENTER IN RAWALPINDI   HEY</pattern><template>Why haven’t you deployed a team to stay in Rawalpindi?</template></category><category><pattern>NEGATIVE  THIS IS ECHO ZERO–ONE  I’M…  INTERNAL ON THE CORRIDOR</pattern><template>I’ll let you guys in.   Roger that.  Shut that fucking kid up, please.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU WANT TO KNOW</pattern><template>I’m gonna ask you a series of questions, based on your knowledge of al Qaeda, and your position as key financier for the organization.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TWO HOOKED UP YET</pattern><template>Hello, I work with him. I’m not that girl that fucks. It’s unbecoming.</template></category><category><pattern>CORRECT  YOU’RE ASSUMING THAT  UH  GREED WON’T OVERRIDE IDEOLOGY IN SOME OF THE WEAKER MEMBERS</pattern><template>Money for walk ins worked great in the Cold War, I’ll give you that.</template></category><category><pattern>ROGER  READY TO MAKE OUR ENTRY OUT HERE</pattern><template>Yeah, roger that, we’re coming to meet you.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S GOTTA HAVE THAT  GIVEN THE FAMILY TIES</pattern><template>He’s tight with his uncle. He’s got his prints all over 9/11 money.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED A PICKET LINE ALONG THE GT HIGHWAY  AND MEN SPACED AT INTERVALS — ALONG THE ROAD  AND AT EVERY EXIT</pattern><template>— Maya, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE DIRECTOR IS VERY CONCERNED</pattern><template>They will not stop until they have a body.</template></category><category><pattern>WE SCAN FOR HEAT SIGNATURES</pattern><template>But we can’t validate if it’s a man or a woman up there.</template></category><category><pattern>LAHORE STREET  WHICH IS ALSO IN PESH — 30 MINUTES</pattern><template>Wazir Bagh Road — 5.</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  FUCKING SHIT</pattern><template>Usamah… Usamah… Usamah… Down.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO</pattern><template>When was the last time you saw him?</template></category><category><pattern>TU VAS M’EN PARLER</pattern><template>How’s the needle in the haystack?</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN YOU DARE QUESTION ME</pattern><template>Come on, man, I’m fucking with you.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  AND WHO SAID THAT  HUH  ZAYID  FUCK HIM  THIS IS ON ME  AMMAR IS ON ME  — NO  NO  NO  NOW  YOU HAD WHAT  DAYS</pattern><template>— and it’s on her. And, we do not, — Brief custody, unresponsive ally?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I’VE JUST LEARNED FROM MY PREDECESSOR  THAT LIFE IS BETTER WHEN I DON’T DISAGREE WITH YOU</pattern><template>Our current hypothesis is that he lives somewhere along the highway, in one of the towns, or a medium sized city called Abbottabad, or up near Kashmir.</template></category><category><pattern>GO BACK</pattern><template>No vest.</template></category><category><pattern>HOPE  YEAH</pattern><template>You give up your hope, right now.</template></category><category><pattern>A DISGRACE TO HUMANITY  YOU AND YOUR UNCLE MURDERED 3 000 INNOCENT PEOPLE</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SOUND JUST LIKE BRADLEY</pattern><template>He doesn’t believe in my lead either.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M BAD FUCKIN’ NEWS</pattern><template>I’m not your friend.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN I COULDN’T FIND HIM  HE ALWAYS CONTACTED ME OUT OF THE BLUE</pattern><template>He’s one of “the disappeared ones”.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  AMMAR  IS IT SUNDAY OR MONDAY</pattern><template>Partial information will be treated as a lie. Come on, let’s go.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT’S ASKING TOO MUCH TO GET A VOICE CONFIRMATION WITH HIM ON THE PHONE</pattern><template>They don’t make telephone calls from the compound.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID THE UK BOMBINGS  RIGHT</pattern><template>Well, you’re the second “Number 3” I’ve captured. I got KSM.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT HE’S SURROUNDED BY A LARGE CONTINGENT OF LOYAL FIGHTERS</pattern><template>But that narrative is pre 9/11 understanding of UBL.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE DID YOU LAST SEE HIM  AND WHERE IS HE NOW</pattern><template>— You will never find him.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE WHAT</pattern><template>I’ll go to Washington, do the dance, see how that environment works.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THAT’S GOOD  THANK YOU</pattern><template>I’ll take that. Thank you very much.</template></category><category><pattern>— LOOK  I DON’T HAVE THE PERSONNEL</pattern><template>— That’s bullshit, man.</template></category><category><pattern>ABRAR… ABRAR</pattern><template>It’s okay.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  YOU CAN LEAVE IT PAUSED FOR NOW  BUT WE’RE GONNA PLAY THROUGH THAT— HEY</pattern><template>— Maya, come see.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  EAT UP  MAN</pattern><template>Some hummus, tabbouleh, don’t know what that is, some figs. You earned it.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU’RE WELCOME</pattern><template>Appreciate it.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST… GIVE ME A NAME</pattern><template>I don’t know!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST NEED THEM TO GO AWAY FOR A MINUTE</pattern><template>You can search him as soon as he gets here.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW LONG DO YOU NEED FOR SSE</pattern><template>We’re gonna need at least ten minutes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>MM–HM</pattern><template>Come on, eat up, man.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  DON’T NEED HIM  SORRY  THE DIAMOND SIGHTING IS BULLSHIT</pattern><template>Uh, see if the Paks will send someone to talk to the farmer. Anything else?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THAT DIDN’T WORK OUT</pattern><template>We thought about sending a guy with a bucket, to pull a sample from the sewer, to analyze his fecal matter.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE SPENDING BILLIONS OF DOLLARS</pattern><template>People are dying!</template></category><category><pattern>— TUESDAY</pattern><template>— Huh? There we go.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT  THERE  IS HAZEM AL KASHMIRI</pattern><template>And I know this dude is up to some serious shit.</template></category><category><pattern>FOURTEEN MINUTES TO INTERCEPT</pattern><template>Any station, this is Red Zero–Two, we need a body bag.  This is Echo Zero–Nine, stand by.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO’S IN THE SAUDI GROUP</pattern><template>And what’s the target?</template></category><category><pattern>ROOMI ROAD</pattern><template>He went to the Convoy Road, which is near the hospital, all right?</template></category><category><pattern>21 DAYS</pattern><template>It’s been 21 days since we found the house, nothing’s happened.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUY NEVER STAYS ON THE PHONE LONG ENOUGH</pattern><template>— You haven’t tried.</template></category><category><pattern>— GET YOUR HAND OUT OF YOUR POCKET</pattern><template>— Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS I LYING OR WHAT</pattern><template>Uh, Maya, this is Joseph Bradley, our illustrious station chief.</template></category><category><pattern>UM  I THINK HE’LL GIVE UP THE SAUDIS  BUT HEATHROW’S GONNA BE TOUGH</pattern><template>Anyway, uh… anything from last night?</template></category><category><pattern>— DOWN  DOWN  DOWN  DOWN… — “YALLA  YALLA ” COME ON</pattern><template>Throw your hands in the air!</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S YOU AND ME  BRO</pattern><template>I want you to understand that I know you… that I’ve been studying and following you for a very long time.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  A LITTLE FOOLING AROUND WOULDN’T HURT YOU</pattern><template>Hmph… — So, no boyfriend?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK DO YOU THINK IS GOING ON  AMMAR</pattern><template>Walid has already told me that you know, hmm?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LET’S GO TALK TO THE BOSS</pattern><template>Oh, you, uh, you should sit back there.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO WISH TO BE TORTURED AGAIN</pattern><template>Ask me a question, I will answer it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT ZIPLOC BAGS AND SHARPIES  USE THEM</pattern><template>Come on, mark all media!</template></category><category><pattern>STATE YOUR REQUEST</pattern><template>Move heaven and earth… and bring me this fucking Sayeed family’s phone number.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT A POSSIBLE JACKPOT</pattern><template>— Roger that, possible jackpot.  — Shit.</template></category><category><pattern>GO TO LOCK OUT   HEY</pattern><template>Hard landing!   Prince Five–One is down.   Black Hawk down in the animal pen.  This way!</template></category><category><pattern>— I THINK I’M GONNA DIE    MA’AM  MA’AM  NOW  I’M GONNA DIE    LOOK  STAY CALM  STAY CALM  STAY CALM  STAY CALM    PLEASE  GOD…   YOU’RE DOING A GOOD JOB  MA’AM  YOU’RE DOING A GOOD JOB    NO  IT’S SO HOT  I’M BURNING UP    …FINE  THEY’RE GONNA COME GET YOU    CAN ANYONE HEAR ME    OH  MY GOD…  I OWN YOU  AMMAR</pattern><template>You belong to me.</template></category><category><pattern>DID YOU REALLY THINK… THAT WHEN WE GOT YOU  “I WOULD GET A NICE FUCKING GUY”</pattern><template>You’re a mid level guy. You’re a garbageman in the corporation!</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IN THE END  EVERYBODY BREAKS  BRO  THAT’S BIOLOGY</pattern><template>Can you open the trunk, ma’am?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T BUY IT  DIDN’T YOU TELL ME YOURSELF  NOBODY TURNS ON AL QAEDA</pattern><template>The Jordans have worked him for a year, dinners, money. They convinced him… it’s his patriotic duty to turn on al Qaeda, and get rich doing it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN</pattern><template>It’s tautology.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S STILL ON</pattern><template>— He’s east of us, try the market.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S A LUCKY SHOT</pattern><template>— Fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  SIR</pattern><template>Good job.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL STATIONS  THIS IS WHIPLASH</pattern><template>Go ahead and stand down.  Copy that.</template></category><category><pattern>— YES  SIR</pattern><template>We got Ziploc bags and Sharpies, use them.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS RED ZERO–TWO    GERONIMO    FOR GOD AND COUNTRY    GERONIMO   ALL STATIONS  TARGET SECURE  TARGET SECURE</pattern><template>Roger, copy that, target secure.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU STEP OFF THIS MAT  I HURT YOU</pattern><template>If you lie to me, I’m gonna hurt you! Now! Now, look at me!</template></category><category><pattern>— AS SALAM ALAYKUM</pattern><template>— Wa alaykum salam.</template></category><category><pattern>POOR FUCKER HAD TO GET OUT OF BED</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>— SINCE WHEN  NO</pattern><template>You know, I was meaning to tell you, I’m getting outta here.</template></category><category><pattern>HE CARRIED MESSAGES FROM ABU FARAJ TO BIN LADEN  FROM BIN LADEN BACK TO ABU FARAJ</pattern><template>We need to ask him something to see if he’s telling the truth.</template></category><category><pattern>— COME ON  LET’S GO  COME ON</pattern><template>— Hang on… — Sunday.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BLAST LEFT A CRATER  10 METERS OR 30 FEET WIDE  IN FRONT OF THE HOTEL    POLICE TELL CNN  THE DRIVER OF THE TRUCK BOMB TRIED TO TALK HIS WAY PASS   THE HOTEL’S STEEL SECURITY GATE  WHEN ARMED GUARDS SAID NO    POLICE SAID THE DRIVER DETONATED MORE THAN 2 000 POUNDS OF EXPLOSIVES    THE MARRIOTT  ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR DESTINATIONS FOR LOCALS AND WESTERNERS   IN ISLAMABAD  NOW DESTROYED   THE JORDS HAVE A MOLE</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN’T MATTER</pattern><template>You’re on a list.</template></category><category><pattern>— HOW’S YOUR FLIGHT</pattern><template>— Fine.</template></category><category><pattern>PREFERABLY  SOMETHING THAT LEADS TO A STRIKE</pattern><template>This is what remains of the No. 10 bus,   which was travelling through Tavistock Square, near Euston station.   There’d been explosions near Liverpool Street and Edgware Road stations too.   Dozens of the survivors were critically injured,   but many of the wounded were also keen to share their stories.   We just pulled out of Edgware Road,   and next thing I know, is a loud, um, large flash of light.   Uh, I felt a burning sensation on my hands, put my hands up to my face…   Uh, I was on the floor by that point…   Yeah, I can’t recall anything prior to that anymore. Any noise, any bang…   Normal life in one of the busiest parts of the capital has now been suspended.   Just a few yards down the road here, they continue to care for the injured.   And all around, groups of Londoners are standing on corners, asking themselves,   “What has happened here, and who could possibly have done this?”  Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>KILO–RED FORTY SIX INBOUND FOR LZ IN THIRTY SECONDS  OUT    CHOPPER FOUR–SIX  WE WERE DEMOING FIVE–ONE    CHOPPER FOUR–SIX  WAVE OFF    FOUR–SIX  WAVE OFF  WAVE OFF   UP</pattern><template>Whoo oo oo!</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOU AGREE WITH ME NOW  THIS IS IMPORTANT</pattern><template>No, I’ve just learned from my predecessor, that life is better when I don’t disagree with you.</template></category><category><pattern>ASK ME A QUESTION  I WILL ANSWER IT</pattern><template>What can you tell me about Atiyah Abdul Rahman?</template></category><category><pattern>SO UH YOU FLEW VIA AMMAN TO KABUL  YEAH</pattern><template>Hang out with your uncle.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WELL  YOU CAN UP RES THIS IMAGE</pattern><template>Even more?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  I JUST GOTTA GET HIS ASS DOWN HERE</pattern><template>Why are there gate guards there?</template></category><category><pattern>— IS THAT IT</pattern><template>— Pretty much.</template></category><category><pattern>— FRIDAY</pattern><template>— Come on, let’s go! Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>A HUNDRED PERCENT HE’S THERE</pattern><template>Okay, fine, 95 percent ‘cause I know certainty freaks you guys out, but it’s a hundred.</template></category><category><pattern>GREAT</pattern><template>And Lahore reporting, ISI was painfully slow last night, again.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M NOT YOUR FRIEND</pattern><template>Not gonna help you.</template></category><category><pattern>— MORNING  HAMAD</pattern><template>“Yalla, yalla…” Any American in Pakistan is a target.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  NOW</pattern><template>You warned them, they didn’t take you seriously.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN KSM WAS CAPTURED  HE WENT TO WORK FOR ABU FARAJ</pattern><template>Primarily as a courier, from Faraj to bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>A MONTH AGO  IN KARACHI</pattern><template>But I don’t know where he is now.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONLY PEOPLE WE’VE SEEN BEHAVE IN THIS WAY  ARE OTHER TOP LEVEL AL QAEDA OPERATIVES</pattern><template>We did a red team on your analysis.</template></category><category><pattern>— “ALLAH HU AKBAR ” (GOD IS GREAT) — HEY</pattern><template>— Get your hand out of your pocket — Do it now!</template></category><category><pattern>PATRICK  BE HONEST WITH ME</pattern><template>You really believe this story?</template></category><category><pattern>— MAYA</pattern><template>— Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I’M ON IT</pattern><template>Now, I just gotta get his ass down here.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY YOU GOT</pattern><template>Patrick, be honest with me.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  15… 20… 30… 40… 50… WE’RE WITHIN TEN METERS OF IT</pattern><template>Back to 40.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN YOU BEAT ME WHEN MY HANDS ARE TIED</pattern><template>So I won’t talk to you.</template></category><category><pattern>EXECUTE</pattern><template>Go, go!</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY WENT NORTH  I THINK  TO KUNAR</pattern><template>What’s his family name?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  LET’S GO</pattern><template>Bring him up.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW IT’S A MOSTLY MIDDLE CLASS COMMUNITY  SOME EX MILITARY</pattern><template>Not particularly interesting to us.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE SOCIALIZING  BE SOCIAL</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I KNOW ABU AHMED IS YOUR BABY  BUT IT IS TIME TO CUT THE UMBILICAL CORD — NO  IT’S NOT</pattern><template>— So Faraj went south on you, it happens, there are still cells in London and Spain, who are planning the next round of attacks.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WAS A LOT OF WHITE NOISE AFTER 9/11</pattern><template>Countries wanting to help out.</template></category><category><pattern>— CAN’T OR WON’T</pattern><template>— He’s not gonna travel. Security risk.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T THINK SHE’S A LITTLE YOUNG FOR THE HARD STUFF</pattern><template>— Washington says she’s a killer.</template></category><category><pattern>IJLISOO ” (GO SIT ) — “MA’LAYSH  MA’LAYSH ” (DON’T WORRY) — DOWN  SIT DOWN</pattern><template>— Echo Eleven on perimeter.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT I’D LIKE TO KNOW  NO FUCKING BULLSHIT  IS WHERE EVERYONE STANDS ON THIS THING</pattern><template>Now, very simply, is he there, or is he not fucking there?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S THAT</pattern><template>Okay, I’m saying that’s Bushra, the brother’s wife.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE DON’T ASK HER HOW IT’S GOING WITH AMMAR  ’CAUSE SHE’S NOT GONNA FUCKING TELL YOU</pattern><template>Ammar is withholding.</template></category><category><pattern>WE WANTED TO KILL AMERICANS</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S A NICE CHOICE  MY FRIEND</pattern><template>Speed yellow, go big or go home, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>IF IT WASN’T FOR HIM  AL QAEDA WOULD STILL BE FOCUSED ON OVERSEAS TARGETS</pattern><template>If you really wanna protect the homeland, you need to get bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  UH  I GOT AN E MAIL FROM YOU TO HIM  WITH ALL YOUR COMMS FOR YEARS  BRO</pattern><template>Who, um… Who else is in your Saudi group?</template></category><category><pattern>15 PERCENT CHANCE HE’S A KUWAITI ARMS SMUGGLER</pattern><template>10 percent chance he’s one of the relatives of the brothers.</template></category><category><pattern>— SO YOU FOUND TWO MALES  THREE FEMALES</pattern><template>— That’s correct.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THE UK  HE’S GOT A CLEAN PASSPORT</pattern><template>He’s not gonna travel out of al Qaeda territory.</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT OF MY FRIENDS HAVE DIED  TRYING TO DO THIS</pattern><template>I believe I was spared, so I could finish the job.</template></category><category><pattern>TALK TO ME</pattern><template>No fucking way we can blow this thing.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS MUST BE ABU AHMED</pattern><template>Doesn’t matter. God, I wish I had that five years ago.</template></category><category><pattern>— “AHAD ” (SUNDAY) SUNDAY  WHERE  WHOA… SUNDAY  WHERE</pattern><template>Sunday. This Sunday or next Sunday?</template></category><category><pattern>SIR  THE AGENCY EXPERT GAVE VISUAL CONFIRMATION</pattern><template>Yes, sir, the girl. Hundred percent. Thank you, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW CAN I REMEMBER</pattern><template>After we kept you awake for 96 hours you… gave us the names of some of your brothers, and you helped save the lives of a lot of innocent people.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU CHOSE TO FIGHT  YEAH</pattern><template>We wanted to kill Americans.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I KNOW THIS DUDE IS UP TO SOME SERIOUS SHIT</pattern><template>What I want from you is his Saudi e mail.</template></category><category><pattern>BACK IT UP  BACK UP</pattern><template>Hey, back it up.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  BUD</pattern><template>Yeah. I forgot, were we supposed to crash that helo?</template></category><category><pattern>THREE MINUTES  STAND BY FOR DOORS OPEN    TWO MINUTES    SHOULD BE COMING UP JUST OFF OUR NOSE  ELEVEN O’CLOCK    EYES ON TARGET   STAY TIGHT</pattern><template>Three seconds.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER TORA BORA  I WENT BACK TO PESH  AS YOU KNOW</pattern><template>Mm hm.</template></category><category><pattern>SO THEY’RE GONNA ASK  IF BIN LADEN IS AT THE END OF THIS RAINBOW… IS THE PAK MILITARY WITH HIM</pattern><template>The question isn’t: Are the Paks protecting bin Laden?</template></category><category><pattern>TOTALLY UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>Bin Laden uses a courier, to interact with the outside world.</template></category><category><pattern>THE QUESTION ISN’T: ARE THE PAKS PROTECTING BIN LADEN</pattern><template>The question is: Would he allow himself to be protected by the Paks?</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S UP AT 5 AGAIN</pattern><template>15… 20… He’s moving fast, he’s in a vehicle.</template></category><category><pattern>— A’IGHT</pattern><template>Ladi!</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS THIS “ABU” IS ACTUALLY A COVER STORY AND HE’S REALLY A FUCKING UNICORN</pattern><template>But the withholding doesn’t reveal what you want it to, does it?</template></category><category><pattern>STAY WITH THESE KIDS  AND DON’T LET THEM IN THAT BACKROOM</pattern><template>— Good?</template></category><category><pattern>GO AHEAD  YOU GUYS</pattern><template>I gotta say, your job… — Hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHO DO YOU THINK</pattern><template>Guy’s a terrorist.</template></category><category><pattern>— HANG ON… — SUNDAY</pattern><template>— Monday.</template></category><category><pattern>— TONY ROBBINS</pattern><template>— Tony Robbins, really?</template></category><category><pattern>Q–ROD IS INBOUND  EIGHT MILES OUT   PAK AIR FORCE IS RESPONDING</pattern><template>Fourteen minutes to intercept.</template></category><category><pattern>ABU AHMED MEANS “FATHER OF AHMED”  IT’S A KUNYA</pattern><template>Ammar, I know the difference between a war name and an Arabic name.</template></category><category><pattern>— MM–MM</pattern><template>You got any friends at all?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WE CAN’T VALIDATE IF IT’S A MAN OR A WOMAN UP THERE</pattern><template>We talked about burrowing a pinhole camera, but there’s a… high risk of discovery.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT THE CARS  HE’S IN A VEHICLE</pattern><template>The guy with the phone in the white car.</template></category><category><pattern>— NO</pattern><template>Okay, so how do you know it’s bin Laden?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS WRONG WITH THAT  THAT  UH… THE SAMPLE WOULD BE TOO DILUTED</pattern><template>And it’s asking too much to get a voice confirmation with him on the phone?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO’S ABU AHMED  I’VE HEARD OF THE OTHER GUYS</pattern><template>He was a computer guy with us at the time.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED A FAVOR</pattern><template>Why I should help you?</template></category><category><pattern>GET A LOOK IN THE MAIN HOUSE</pattern><template>It would probably be discovered.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I’M GONNA PUT YOU IN IT</pattern><template>When is the attack?</template></category><category><pattern>THE KEY IS TO MEET HIM  SO WE CAN FIGURE OUT FOR OURSELVES WHAT HE CAN ACTUALLY DO</pattern><template>He really asked for a dialysis machine?</template></category><category><pattern>THREE SECONDS</pattern><template>Hey! Slide right! Slide right!</template></category><category><pattern>— UH  LAUREN  I KNOW YOU WANNA GET SOME QUESTIONS IN THERE  BUT GIVE BALAWI A LITTLE TIME</pattern><template>After John speaks, we’ll cover the basics, have his birthday cake, then we’ll get into the nitty–gritty.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU THINK SO</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE HIM</pattern><template>— Is that him?</template></category><category><pattern>— HMM</pattern><template>But bin Laden, is there.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’LL KEEP UP ON THE SURVEILLANCE AS BEST WE CAN</pattern><template>The high res version, can you get closer than that?</template></category><category><pattern>SO A LITTLE CONTEXT HERE  IF YOU TAKE A RIGHT  OUT OF ISLAMABAD  DRIVE ABOUT FORTY FIVE MINUTES NORTH  YOU’LL FIND YOURSELF HERE IN ABBOTTABAD</pattern><template>Now it’s a mostly middle class community, some ex military.</template></category><category><pattern>— I AM CALM</pattern><template>State your request.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  HOW DO YOU LIKE PAKISTAN SO FAR</pattern><template>It’s kinda fucked up.</template></category><category><pattern>— NOORI HASAN</pattern><template>— Yo, she says it’s not him.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S GOT ‘EM IN HIS HEAD  HE NEEDS TO DISCLOSE ‘EM</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>WE FOUND A SAFE HOUSE  BUT WE CAN’T GET A VANTAGE POINT TO FIRE A TELESCOPE OVER THE BALCONY WALL</pattern><template>We have explored the possibility, of digging tunnels, of sending hot air balloons, of rerouting supply C 130s to take a peek, but that might be too alerting.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LET’S PUT SOME RUNS ON THE BOARD AGAINST FARAJ  OKAY</pattern><template>Talk to the case officers who didn’t see fit to make it today, and “thank” them.</template></category><category><pattern>NEVER</pattern><template>Let’s go.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MUCH LATITUDE DOES HE GET TO PICK TARGETS</pattern><template>Um, I think he’ll give up the Saudis, but Heathrow’s gonna be tough.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T THINK WE’LL GET AN APPROVAL</pattern><template>This decision is not going— It’s her against the world.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN SEARCH HIM AS SOON AS HE GETS HERE</pattern><template>All stations, this is Whiplash.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MUST BE PRETTY FUCKED UP FOR YOU GUYS AFTER 9/11</pattern><template>And what did you do, um, what did you do after the invasion?</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S YOUR SHOW  YOU WERE THE FIRST TO SEE THE POTENTIAL IN THIS</pattern><template>Oh, come on, we’ve got lots of wine.  Cool, bring me back a bottle.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  IT’S NOT LIKE HE’S SAYING  “HEY  MOM  IT’S ME  THE TERRORIST ” YEAH  I KNOW  BUT  LOOK  OVER THE COURSE OF TWO MONTHS  HE’S CALLED FROM SIX DIFFERENT PAYPHONES FROM TWO DIFFERENT CITIES  NEVER USING THE SAME PHONE TWICE</pattern><template>And when his mother asked him where he was, he lied.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE BLOCKED</pattern><template>Let me talk to them.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHERE’RE YOU GONNA GET THAT</pattern><template>— From you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>He made this video to prove his bona fides.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WENT TO THE CONVOY ROAD  WHICH IS NEAR THE HOSPITAL  ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>So that’s Haider, Roomi Road, Zahid, NoGaza, Taimur.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S NOT ALL YOU DON’T KNOW</pattern><template>You don’t have his real name, you don’t have a clue of where he is.</template></category><category><pattern>HI  I PAINSTAKINGLY COMBED THROUGH EVERYTHING IN THE SYSTEM AND FOUND THIS</pattern><template>It’s him.</template></category><category><pattern>HUH  IT’S BEEN A WHILE</pattern><template>I need a favor.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE US A MINUTE  THANK YOU</pattern><template>That’s a nice choice, my friend.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW  VERY SIMPLY  IS HE THERE  OR IS HE NOT FUCKING THERE</pattern><template>We all come at this, through the filter of our own past experiences.</template></category><category><pattern>HE DOESN’T KNOW WE’VE FAILED</pattern><template>We could tell him anything.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  HOLD ON  HE GOES TO A BIG FEAST IN BANGKOK  ABOUT A YEAR AGO</pattern><template>Guest of honor: Osama bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  IF THERE ARE THREE FEMALES  THERE OUGHT TO BE THREE MALES</pattern><template>Observant Muslim women live with their parents, over their husbands.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE’S YOUR KILLER  WOLF  YOU PUT HER ON THE FIELD</pattern><template>Come on, “Bismillah ar Rahman ar Raheem” (In the name of God, most Gracious, most Merciful) Allah rewards those that strive and fight, over those that sit behind a desk.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ABOUT CAMP CHAPMAN… AFGHANISTAN  THAT CAN BE SAFE TERRITORY</pattern><template>This may be going overboard, but I baked him a cake.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU KNOW WHAT YOU’RE DOING</pattern><template>You’re chasing a ghost while the whole fucking network grows all around you.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  AGREE  I SPOKE TO THE CHIEF ABOUT THAT  ANYTHING ON BIN LADEN</pattern><template>Uh, farmer on the Afghan border near Tora Bora… reports a diamond shaped pattern in the hills, tall male in the center of the diamond, flanked by four guards, consistent with UBL’s movements.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  SOMEBODY MIGHT DIE  AT SOME POINT  IN PAKISTAN</pattern><template>We got a deal?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  HERE WE GO</pattern><template>Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR JIHAD IS OVER</pattern><template>Get him up.</template></category><category><pattern>GET DOWN</pattern><template>Ladi!</template></category><category><pattern>NOW I REMEMBER IRAQ WMD  VERY CLEARLY  I FRONTED THAT</pattern><template>And I can tell you the case for that, was much stronger than this case.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  FUCKING CHECKPOINTS</pattern><template>— Maya?</template></category><category><pattern>OK  THEN WE’RE ALL GOOD</pattern><template>We’ve just crossed the border, now entering Pakistan.  Pakistani comms, no chatter.</template></category><category><pattern>IBRAHIM</pattern><template>C’mon out!</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  NOT ONE SINGLE DETAINEE HAS SAID THAT HE’S BEEN LOCATED WITH THE BIG GUY  JUST THAT HE DELIVERS MESSAGES  AM I WRONG</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>— CDS  DVDS</pattern><template>— Who’s got a Sharpie?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANNA MAKE SOMETHING ABSOLUTELY CLEAR</pattern><template>If you thought there was some… secret cell somewhere, working al Qaeda, well, I want you to know that you’re wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE WILL BE NO REPERCUSSIONS IN KUWAIT</pattern><template>I mean, somebody might die, at some point, in Pakistan.</template></category><category><pattern>AMMAR  BRO  I KNOW THAT YOU KNOW THIS DUDE</pattern><template>Just give me his e mail, and I will—I will give you a blanket.</template></category><category><pattern>2ND FLOOR  OPPOSITE  DOWN ON THE RIGHT</pattern><template>3rd Floor, ladies’ underwear.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE JUST CROSSED THE BORDER  NOW ENTERING PAKISTAN   PAKISTANI COMMS  NO CHATTER</pattern><template>Three minutes, stand by for doors open.   Two minutes.   Should be coming up just off our nose, eleven o’clock.   Eyes on target.  Stay tight.</template></category><category><pattern>ALPHA–THREE…  THIS IS ECHO ELEVEN  WE’RE AT PRIMARY SET POINT  PREPPING TO BREACH</pattern><template>Wait one, we’re internal on the south side.  This is a negative breach.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHEN YOU LIE TO ME  I HURT YOU</pattern><template>This is what defeat looks like, bro.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHEN HIS MOTHER ASKED HIM WHERE HE WAS  HE LIED</pattern><template>He said that he was in a place in the country with bad cell reception, implying he was in the Tribals. When, in fact, he was in a market in Peshawar.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO</pattern><template>I’m gonna smoke everybody involved in this op.</template></category><category><pattern>CHILDREN’S CRUSADE  HUH</pattern><template>They wanna put the next generation on the field.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LET’S JUST  UH… LET’S TAKE IT EASY TODAY  HUH</pattern><template>You hungry?</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK   — FIFTY BUCKS</pattern><template>— Fifty bucks.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN’T KNOW WHO THE GUYS WERE</pattern><template>When you lie to me, I hurt you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO HERE’S BEEN IN A HELO CRASH BEFORE</pattern><template>OK, then we’re all good.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T GET IT</pattern><template>He’s driving in circles.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S IN CHARGE OF MILITARY TACTICS</pattern><template>In what context have you ever heard the name Abu Ahmed?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT</pattern><template>What else have you done for us?</template></category><category><pattern>PRETTY GOOD  HUH</pattern><template>Richard Reid.</template></category><category><pattern>MY GUESS IS THAT HE LIVES CLOSE TO WHERE HE’S MAKING THE CALLS</pattern><template>And it makes sense he’d be living in Rawalpindi, because there’s an Al Jazeera office there.</template></category><category><pattern>LET’S GO  NOW</pattern><template>You’ve got one Mike to blow that downed helo.  — You all right?</template></category><category><pattern>IBRAHIM SAYEED</pattern><template>They told us to watch out for him. Apparently, they think his whole family and extended family is bad, and has ties to KSM.</template></category><category><pattern>THROW YOUR HANDS IN THE AIR</pattern><template>— “Yalla! Yalla!” — Down! Down! Down! Down!</template></category><category><pattern>HE’LL MEET US IN MAIDAN SHAR WITH THE TRIBALS</pattern><template>He knows you’re white, we’d get kidnapped there.</template></category><category><pattern>— AND YOU’RE NOT GOING TO HIM</pattern><template>— I’m not, believe me.</template></category><category><pattern>I CHASED YOU IN LAHORE</pattern><template>I had you picked up instead of killing you, because you’re not a violent man, and you don’t deserve to die.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I’M RESPONSIBLE FOR EVERYBODY’S SAFETY  OKAY  IT’S NOT JUST ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>I just need them to go away for a minute.</template></category><category><pattern>— NOBODY SAW IT  MOST LIKELY</pattern><template>There was a lot of white noise after 9/11.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THIS TAKING PLACE INSIDE OUR MAIN BUILDING</pattern><template>Right, and, uh, Lauren, Washington will want real time updates, so please, stay on top of that.</template></category><category><pattern>GRAB ME THE BUCKET</pattern><template>— Huh?</template></category><category><pattern>I CONCUR  60 PERCENT</pattern><template>I’m at 80 percent, their OPSEC is what convinces me.</template></category><category><pattern>— ANYONE COULD BE CALLING HOME</pattern><template>— I know.</template></category><category><pattern>KHALID… KHALID… ECHO ZERO–TWO  MOVING TO DECK 3</pattern><template>Clear!</template></category><category><pattern>HUH</pattern><template>No?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HE’S BEEN IN THE FILES THIS  WHOLE TIME  THE FAMILY’S NAME IS SAYEED</pattern><template>Okay, but he’s, uh, he’s dead, so doesn’t that make him a little less interesting to you?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT AN UNLOCKED DOOR</pattern><template>Abrar!</template></category><category><pattern>ABU AHMED AL KUWAITI IS THE NOM DE GUERRE</pattern><template>His true name, we think, is Ibrahim Sayeed.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE A DRUG DEALER</pattern><template>You know we lost the ability to prove them when we lost the Detainee Program.</template></category><category><pattern>— I KNOW</pattern><template>I mean, it’s not like he’s saying, “Hey, Mom, it’s me, the terrorist.” Yeah, I know. But, look, over the course of two months, He’s called from six different payphones from two different cities, never using the same phone twice.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT</pattern><template>— “Ahad.” (Sunday) Sunday, where? Whoa… Sunday, where?</template></category><category><pattern>GO  GO</pattern><template>This is Echo Zero–Five moving to level 2.</template></category><category><pattern>I’LL LET YOU GUYS IN    ROGER THAT   SHUT THAT FUCKING KID UP  PLEASE</pattern><template>Talk to me.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WORKS FOR FARAJ AND BIN LADEN</pattern><template>He is his most trusted courier.</template></category><category><pattern>GOT SOME LIBYAN MUSIC YOU LIKE</pattern><template>You did the UK bombings, right?</template></category><category><pattern>— GET YOUR HAND OUT OF YOUR POCKET — DO IT NOW</pattern><template>— “Allah hu Akbar.” — Get your hand out of your poc… — “Allah hu Akb—”  The CIA says, seven of it’s employees were killed,   and six others wounded, in a suicide bombing in a base in Afghanistan.   It was one of the deadliest attacks in CIA history.   The Associated Press has learned that…   the chief of the CIA’s post in the province, is among the victims.   Former officials say, she was the mother of three.   The Taliban claimed resposibility for the bombing…  — You okay?</template></category><category><pattern>BASICALLY  WE HAD A GUY WHO ROLLED WITH AL QAEDA  AND DID SERVICES FOR HIM</pattern><template>— Mm–hm.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE ARE FAILING</pattern><template>We’re spending billions of dollars.</template></category><category><pattern>— UH  THOSE ARE KIDS  THEY’RE SHUFFLING AROUND  SWORD FIGHTING OR SOMETHING  WITH STICKS</pattern><template>You can see their height relative to this. These are cows.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU WANT THE WATER AGAIN</pattern><template>Or do you want something else?</template></category><category><pattern>— ALL RIGHT  FAIR ENOUGH</pattern><template>How about a V10 Lamborghini?</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A DEAL</pattern><template>Hey, Jack.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WOULD JUST TELL ME  WHERE TO LEAVE THE MESSAGES</pattern><template>You’re not being fulsome in your replies You cannot force me to tell you something I don’t know.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE ALL COWED</pattern><template>— What do you think of the girl?</template></category><category><pattern>— “YALLA  YALLA ” — DOWN  DOWN  DOWN  DOWN</pattern><template>Down!</template></category><category><pattern>— FINE</pattern><template>Um, she’s been having a great time since she got in, isn’t that right?</template></category><category><pattern>GET A LITTLE WIND IN THE HAIR</pattern><template>Huh? Put the top down?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WE LOST THE ABILITY TO PROVE THEM WHEN WE LOST THE DETAINEE PROGRAM</pattern><template>Who the hell am I supposed to ask? Huh?</template></category><category><pattern>NISHTARABAD — 5</pattern><template>Phandu Road — 5 minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>BIN LADEN IS THE ONE WHO KEEPS TELLING THEM TO ATTACK THE HOMELAND</pattern><template>If it wasn’t for him, al Qaeda would still be focused on overseas targets.</template></category><category><pattern>HE JUST TOLD ME THE NAMES OF ALL OF ABU FARAJ’S CHILDREN</pattern><template>I think he’s telling the truth.</template></category><category><pattern>RED FIVE–TWO  INBOUND FOR LZ   WHERE DO YOU NEED THE BAG</pattern><template>Third deck.  Here!</template></category><category><pattern>AND THIS IS THE GUY THAT’S KSM’S NEPHEW</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>GO BACK  THEY WILL KILL YOU</pattern><template>They will kill you!</template></category><category><pattern>COPY</pattern><template>Copy that.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  CAN’T YOU PUT A CAMERA SOMEWHERE</pattern><template>In these trees here, maybe?</template></category><category><pattern>THIN  HE USES A CANE</pattern><template>Kinda like Gandalf.</template></category><category><pattern>NAME… NAME… LADI… — WE’RE MEETING DOWN</pattern><template>— A’ight.</template></category><category><pattern>SO REMEMBER  WE’VE GOT TWO MALES  TWO FEMALES AND SEVEN KIDS</pattern><template>What’s that?</template></category><category><pattern>— NOBODY TALKS TO HIM</pattern><template>— Roger that.</template></category><category><pattern>KICK BACK  TAKE IT EASY AFTER YOU’VE BLOWN SOME SHIT UP</pattern><template>Huh?</template></category><category><pattern>MAY I JOIN YOU</pattern><template>How is the food down here anyway?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE CHASING A GHOST WHILE THE WHOLE FUCKING NETWORK GROWS ALL AROUND YOU</pattern><template>You just want me to nail some low level molar–cracker–doler, so you can check that box on your resume that says, while you were in Pakistan, you got a real terrorist.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PAKS HAVE SCRAMBLED THE F–16S   FOUR MINUTES</pattern><template>Red Five–Two, inbound for LZ.  Where do you need the bag?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO UNDERSTAND THAT I KNOW YOU… THAT I’VE BEEN STUDYING AND FOLLOWING YOU FOR A VERY LONG TIME</pattern><template>That I could’ve had you killed in Karachi, but I didn’t.</template></category><category><pattern>— WASHINGTON SAYS SHE’S A KILLER</pattern><template>— Hmm.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN I BE HONEST WITH YOU</pattern><template>I’m bad fuckin’ news.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WE GONNA HAVE TO CHASE IT DOWN</pattern><template>He’s like, “Hey, that’s me, man. No job too small.” That’s why I have a gift for you, my friend.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY HAVE SLAUGHTERED OUR FORWARD–DEPLOYED</pattern><template>And what the fuck have we done about it, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>IT’D BE CONVENIENT FOR HIM TO DROP THE TAPES OFF  IF HE’S MESSENGERING  EITHER FROM BIN LADEN  OR TO AN INTERMEDIARY</pattern><template>So, when he wants to make a call, he leaves the house, walks a few blocks, then switches on the phone.</template></category><category><pattern>— AND WHAT’S HIS ISSUE</pattern><template>He’s being a dick.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PRESIDENT IS A THOUGHTFUL  ANALYTICAL GUY  HE NEEDS PROOF</pattern><template>Go ahead, you guys.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>Look, I know Abu Ahmed is your baby, but it is time to cut the umbilical cord — No, it’s not.</template></category><category><pattern>— MUKHTAR    “MUKHTAR”… “POTATO”…   YOU SAY  “PO–TAH–TO”; I SAY  “FUCKING KSM”; YOU SAY  “MUKHTAR”  OKAY    NOW  AFTER MUKHTAR WAS CAPTURED  WHAT DID ABU AHMED DO    ABU AHMED  I BELIEVE… I BELIEVE  HE WENT TO WORK FOR THE “SHEIK”    IS THAT HIM    — SAY IT</pattern><template>— Abu Ahmed.   — Say it again.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  LIFE ISN’T ALWAYS FAIR  MY FRIEND</pattern><template>Did you really think… that when we got you, “I would get a nice fucking guy”?</template></category><category><pattern>“ERFA EDAK ” (HANDS UP ) GET DOWN</pattern><template>— Down, down, down, down… — “Yalla! Yalla!” Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER WE KEPT YOU AWAKE FOR 96 HOURS YOU… GAVE US THE NAMES OF SOME OF YOUR BROTHERS  AND YOU HELPED SAVE THE LIVES OF A LOT OF INNOCENT PEOPLE</pattern><template>Which is a smart thing to do when you’re starting to think for yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  THIS THIRD MALE THAT YOU’VE IDENTIFIED AS POSSIBLY BEING BIN LADEN  DO I GIVE UP ALL HOPE OF EVER SEEING A PHOTOGRAPH OF HIM</pattern><template>Hope? Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  DOES BIN LADEN INVITE HIM INTO THE LIVING ROOM  AND HAND HIM A LETTER DIRECTLY  OR IS ABU JUST THE LAST GUY IN A LONG LINE OF COURIERS  AND THAT’S WHY EVERYBODY KNOWS HIM</pattern><template>That’s not all you don’t know.</template></category><category><pattern>WE JUST HAVEN’T TESTED WITH PEOPLE IN THEM YET</pattern><template>You’ll notice these stealth panels, similar to what we use on the B 2.</template></category><category><pattern>THE WINDOWS ARE BLACKED OUT</pattern><template>There’s even a 7–foot privacy wall here, so, even if we got up high, we couldn’t get a vantage point.</template></category><category><pattern>— HEY</pattern><template>— “Allah hu Akbar.” (God is Great) — Hey!</template></category><category><pattern>TARGET SECURE  COMMENCE SSE   PREP FOR SSE RIGHT NOW  BOOKS  DVDS  CDS… EVERY FUCKING HARD DRIVE</pattern><template>Do not leave a hard drive!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST NEED HER PHONE NUMBER</pattern><template>There will be no repercussions in Kuwait?</template></category><category><pattern>— I’M FINE</pattern><template>Well, just so you know, it’s gonna take a while.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU THOUGHT THERE WAS SOME… SECRET CELL SOMEWHERE  WORKING AL QAEDA  WELL  I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT YOU’RE WRONG</pattern><template>This is it.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’D BE THE FIRST SUCCESSFUL DRUG DEALER NEVER TO HAVE DEALT DRUGS</pattern><template>He has no internet access to the house; he makes no phone calls either in or out Who’s he selling to? Who’s he buying from? How’s he making his money?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BOSS  I GOT A GUY  FOR 5 000 BUCKS  HE CAN SET UP A TAXI STAND  AND SNOOP AROUND A BIT</pattern><template>No, don’t need him. Sorry, the diamond sighting is bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  LET’S GET A COFFEE</pattern><template>No, we should go back in.</template></category><category><pattern>THEN HE WENT TO UMAR ROAD FOR 5 MINUTES  NOGAZA ROAD  DARYA ABAD  THAT’S IN THE UMAR ROAD AREA</pattern><template>In Rawalpindi, Haider Road.</template></category><category><pattern>FIFTY BUCKS</pattern><template>It’s a lucky shot.</template></category><category><pattern>— TAKE THAT TOO</pattern><template>— You got it “ch”.</template></category><category><pattern>WE LOST HIM  NO SIGNAL</pattern><template>Heading south.</template></category><category><pattern>FRID… — AMMAR  WHICH DAY</pattern><template>— Thursd… Frid… “Yalla! Yalla! Yalla!” (Let’s go!) “Yalla! Yalla! Yalla!”  …attack against westerners and foreigners.   When you look at the break up of casualties,   you can see that non muslims were killed, and so were Americans…  You don’t worry about the Saudis, they’ll take care of business.</template></category><category><pattern>OR DO YOU WANT SOMETHING ELSE</pattern><template>— Water?</template></category><category><pattern>FOUR MAX</pattern><template>— Where’re you gonna get that?</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>If you’re right, the whole world’s gonna want in on this.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  YOU GOTTA STICK TO YOUR GUNS NOW</pattern><template>Okay. No, it’s great to speak to you too I’m—I’m amazed that you’re still here.</template></category><category><pattern>FARAJ IS COMPLETELY DENYING KNOWING ABU AHMED</pattern><template>That’s using every measure we have.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  I’VE GOT A MEETING WITH ISI IN TWENTY MINUTES</pattern><template>They’re slow rolling us on Lahore, you might wanna bitch about that.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  BE MY NUMBER TWO  YOU’RE LOOKING A LITTLE STRUNG OUT YOURSELF</pattern><template>I’m not gonna find Abu Ahmed from DC.</template></category><category><pattern>— GO</pattern><template>Copy.</template></category><category><pattern>I BELIEVE I WAS SPARED  SO I COULD FINISH THE JOB</pattern><template>It is in surveillance video and pictures like this of the explosive laden vehicle   just moments before it was parked, that police hope to find the man,   who wanted so badly last night, to leave a body count in Times Square.   There are some people around the world, that find our freedom so threatening,   that they’re willing to kill themselves and others,   to prevent us from enjoying it, but we’re not gonna let that happen…  Hey, I really need to talk to you about beefing up our surveillance operation on the caller.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT PARTICULARLY INTERESTING TO US</pattern><template>Except we did find this compound, which is unique.</template></category><category><pattern>FACILITATORS COME AND GO</pattern><template>One thing you can count on in life is that everyone wants money.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  IT’S NO SHAME IF YOU WANNA WATCH FROM THE MONITOR</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>THE QUESTION IS: WOULD HE ALLOW HIMSELF TO BE PROTECTED BY THE PAKS</pattern><template>I mean, why would he trust them? He tried to kill Musharraf.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  MAYA  THIS IS JOSEPH BRADLEY  OUR ILLUSTRIOUS STATION CHIEF</pattern><template>Joe and I did Iraq together.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME TALK TO THEM</pattern><template>They said whites faces don’t belong here.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S DRIVING IN CIRCLES</pattern><template>— No change?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT YOU DO HAVE DEEP TIES TO AL QAEDA I WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT  BEFORE YOU GET SENT TO YOUR NEXT LOCATION  WHICH MIGHT BE ISRAEL</pattern><template>However, depending on how candid you are here today, I may be able to keep you in Pakistan.</template></category><category><pattern>— HOW LONG HAVE YOU WORKED FOR THE CIA</pattern><template>— Twelve years.</template></category><category><pattern>— MHM</pattern><template>I, um, didn’t think this day could get any worse… But, uh… bad news from Saudi intelligence. The, um… courier guy, Abu Ahmed, is dead.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN HE ARRIVES  LET ME SET THE TONE  AND THEN I’LL FLIP IT TO YOU  AND YOU CAN TALK ABOUT ASSET PROTECTION</pattern><template>— Roger that.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DID GIVE A 40 PERCENT CHANCE THAT THE UNIDENTIFIED THIRD MAN… IS A SENIOR AL QAEDA OPERATIVE</pattern><template>But they also said there’s a 35 percent chance he’s a Saudi drug dealer.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE WE CAN FILL THE DAMN THING WITH POISON</pattern><template>The meeting with Balawi is off. He can’t come to Islamabad.</template></category><category><pattern>— HUH  THERE WE GO</pattern><template>— Friday!</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE GOTTA EVALUATE HIM FACE TO FACE</pattern><template>He may not be that smart, he may be full of shit.</template></category><category><pattern>AS IT IS  MY GUYS DON’T GET ANY SLEEP  TRACKING THE THREATS WITHIN PAKISTAN</pattern><template>Right, I understand.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  AND  UH  LAUREN  WASHINGTON WILL WANT REAL TIME UPDATES  SO PLEASE  STAY ON TOP OF THAT</pattern><template>Be concise, the director’s in the loop… and I wouldn’t be surprised… if he doesn’t update the president.</template></category><category><pattern>THE PLAN IS STILL ACTIVE</pattern><template>Ammar doesn’t have a clue about what happened.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE YOU’D LET ME BUY YOU A KEBAB SOMETIME</pattern><template>Don’t eat out.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S THIS  THIS CLUSTER OF BUILDINGS DOWN HERE</pattern><template>The PMA. It’s the Pakistani Military Academy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’VE INSPIRED ME TO COME TO PAKISTAN</pattern><template>Maybe you’d let me buy you a kebab sometime.</template></category><category><pattern>BIG TIME  I WANNA TALK TO ALL OF YOU ABOUT IT</pattern><template>Who here’s been in a helo crash before?</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU CAN’T PROVE IT’S BIN LADEN  AT LEAST PROVE IT’S NOT SOMEONE ELSE</pattern><template>Like a drug dealer.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT THE E MAILS OF THE REST OF THE SAUDI GROUP</pattern><template>Give me one e mail and I will stop this.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S USING EVERY MEASURE WE HAVE</pattern><template>Well, he’s either gonna keep withholding or he’s gonna die from the presssure you’re putting on him.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S NICE  REALLY NICE</pattern><template>What are you thinking?</template></category><category><pattern>STILL ON TOWER THREE</pattern><template>5… Signal getting stronger, 10… 15… Keep going.</template></category><category><pattern>— ECHO ELEVEN ON PERIMETER</pattern><template>— Ready to breach at P2.</template></category><category><pattern>CLEAR</pattern><template>Yalla! Yalla!</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WILL KILL YOU</pattern><template>Go back!</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S TAUTOLOGY</pattern><template>Listen, not one single detainee has said that he’s been located with the big guy, just that he delivers messages, am I wrong?</template></category><category><pattern>— PRETTY MUCH</pattern><template>All right, let’s go talk to the boss.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU  OF ALL PEOPLE  SHOULD KNOW THAT ONCE YOU’RE ON THEIR LIST… YOU NEVER GET OFF</pattern><template>Next time, there may not be bulletproof glass to save you.</template></category><category><pattern>AT THAT MOMENT  WITH 25 MILL ON THE TABLE  I THINK HE GIVES UP THE BIG MAN</pattern><template>And if he doesn’t, we kill him.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE ME ONE E MAIL AND I WILL STOP THIS</pattern><template>Who’s in the Saudi group?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE NOT BEING FULSOME IN YOUR REPLIES YOU CANNOT FORCE ME TO TELL YOU SOMETHING I DON’T KNOW</pattern><template>You do realize this is not a normal prison? You determine how you’re treated And your life is gonna be very uncomfortable, until… you give me the information I need!</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST WANNA SAY  I’VE HEARD A LOT ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>You’ve inspired me to come to Pakistan.</template></category><category><pattern>25 MILLION DOLLARS</pattern><template>That buys a new life.</template></category><category><pattern>IF THIS WAS POLITICAL  WE’D BE HAVING THIS CONVERSATION IN OCTOBER  WHEN THERE’S AN ELECTION BUMP</pattern><template>This is pure risk, based on deductive reasoning, inference, supposition, and the only human reporting you have is six years old, from detainees, who were questioned under duress.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON’T KNOW WHAT WE DON’T KNOW</pattern><template>What the fuck is that supposed to mean?</template></category><category><pattern>UH  FARMER ON THE AFGHAN BORDER NEAR TORA BORA… REPORTS A DIAMOND SHAPED PATTERN IN THE HILLS  TALL MALE IN THE CENTER OF THE DIAMOND  FLANKED BY FOUR GUARDS  CONSISTENT WITH UBL’S MOVEMENTS</pattern><template>That’s supposed to be his Royal Guard.</template></category><category><pattern>TWENTY DETAINEES RECOGNIZED THAT PHOTO OF ABU AHMED</pattern><template>They say he’s part of an inner circle of guys that was hanging out in Afghanistan pre 9/11.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE WITHHOLDING DOESN’T REVEAL WHAT YOU WANT IT TO  DOES IT</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT PART CONVINCED YOU</pattern><template>Her confidence.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  YOU HAVEN’T EATEN IN 18 HOURS  WE NEED TO KEEP YOUR ENERGY UP</pattern><template>You hungry?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT’S THE TARGET</pattern><template>Where was the last time you saw bin Laden?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT SHOULD I RESPECT YOU  HUH</pattern><template>— Why?</template></category><category><pattern>TO CLEAN THAT AUDIO AS WELL  JUST TAKE THE LOW ONE OUT</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>HE MAY NOT BE  WE NOW KNOW ABU AHMED IS ONE OF EIGHT BROTHERS   ALL THE BROTHERS IN THE FAMILY LOOK ALIKE  THREE OF THEM WENT TO AFGHANISTAN  ISN’T IT POSSIBLE THAT WHEN   THE THREE ELDEST BROTHERS GREW BEARDS IN AFGHANISTAN  THEY STARTED TO LOOK ALIKE   I THINK THE ONE CALLING HIMSELF ABU AHMED IS STILL ALIVE</pattern><template>The picture we’ve been using is wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  LOOK  THIS IS A CLOTHESLINE RIGHT HERE FOR LAUNDRY</pattern><template>Men don’t mess with the wash.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S BEING A DICK</pattern><template>If he’s trying to outsmart you, why don’t you tell him about your PhD?</template></category><category><pattern>ABU AHMED IS TOO SMART TO TIP HIS HAND  BY TALKING ABOUT OPS ON THE PHONE</pattern><template>He works for bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M THE MOTHERFUCKER THAT FOUND THIS PLACE  SIR</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>PUT SOME WATER IN IT</pattern><template>Come on, let’s go!</template></category><category><pattern>— IT’S OKAY</pattern><template>Do you even realize what you just did?</template></category><category><pattern>DON’T EAT OUT</pattern><template>It’s too dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR</pattern><template>One moment, please.</template></category><category><pattern>— GENTLEMEN  WATCH YOUR BACKS</pattern><template>— Slow down.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT IS A FASCINATING QUESTION</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>PEOPLE ARE DYING</pattern><template>We are still no closer to defeating our enemy.</template></category><category><pattern>GOD–FUCKING–DAMNIT  CAN YOU POP IT MANUALLY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SAID  “CONTINUE THE JIHAD ” “THE WORK WILL GO ON FOR A HUNDRED YEARS ”  YOU AND I ARE GONNA TALK ABOUT SOME OF THE GUYS AT THE TRAINING CAMPS  YEAH    OKAY    SOME OF THESE BROTHERS HAVE DONE SOME BAD THINGS    WHAT I WANNA DO IS  I WANNA SEPARATE THEM FROM THE PEOPLE LIKE YOU    DEFINITELY  YEAH    ALL RIGHT  A GUY CALLED ABU AHMED  FROM KUWAIT    YES  I REMEMBER HIM  THE NICE GUY    HOW CLOSE WAS HE  WHAT WAS HIS RELATIONSHIP TO THE LEADERSHIP    I DON’T KNOW    DID HE EAT WITH YOU GUYS    DID HE EAT WITH THE GOOD GUYS  OR DID HE EAT WITH THE LEADERSHIP    I DON’T KNOW  SIR</pattern><template>I have no idea about it.   That’s something you don’t need an idea about.   When you met Khalid Sheikh Mohammed, was this one of the facilitators?   Is this Abu Ahmed?   — KSM, your boss.</template></category><category><pattern>HUMAN ERROR</pattern><template>Anyway, I thought you should know about it.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHO ARE YOU</pattern><template>I’m the motherfucker that found this place, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE NOT WEARING ONE</pattern><template>Is he ever getting out?</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S BEEN 21 DAYS SINCE WE FOUND THE HOUSE  NOTHING’S HAPPENED</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THE UNIDENTIFIED THIRD MALE DOES NOT GET GROCERIES</pattern><template>He does not leave the compound; he does not present himself for photographs.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE TRUTH IS  YOU DON’T UNDERSTAND PAKISTAN  AND YOU DON’T KNOW AL QAEDA</pattern><template>Either give me the team I need, to follow this lead, or that other thing you’re gonna have on your resume, is being the first station chief to be called before Congressional Committee, for subverting the efforts to capture or kill bin Laden!</template></category><category><pattern>GENERAL</pattern><template>Excuse me.</template></category><category><pattern>WE INVADED AFGHANISTAN  THAT’S A REASON</pattern><template>Hey, boss. I got a guy, for 5,000 bucks, he can set up a taxi stand, and snoop around a bit.</template></category><category><pattern>BRING HIM UP</pattern><template>Here we go!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD LISTEN TO IT</pattern><template>I got plans for after this.</template></category><category><pattern>HAKIM  GET HIM BACK  OR I’LL START SMOKIN’ ‘EM</pattern><template>Wait, wait, wait.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS COULD CRACK OPEN THE FACILITATOR MAYA’S BEEN LOOKING FOR  BY GIVING US A PHONE NUMBER</pattern><template>She’s your killer, Wolf, you put her on the field.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE SAYING WE ARE FRIEND</pattern><template>How come you only call me when you need help?</template></category><category><pattern>ECHO TEAM IS AWAY  PRINCE FIVE–TWO EXITING ALPHA–OSCAR   THREE… TWO… ONE… EXECUTE</pattern><template>Ibrahim!</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE WAS DRIVING A SEDAN OR A COMPACT  WE’D BE FUCKED</pattern><template>Obviously, this assumes he doesn’t change vehicles.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE’S EVEN A 7–FOOT PRIVACY WALL HERE  SO  EVEN IF WE GOT UP HIGH  WE COULDN’T GET A VANTAGE POINT</pattern><template>I mean it’s— it’s a fortress.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU AGENCY GUYS ARE TWISTED</pattern><template>Detainee’s ready for you.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT I COULD’VE HAD YOU KILLED IN KARACHI  BUT I DIDN’T</pattern><template>I let you live, so that you and I could talk.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  OVER HERE</pattern><template>The blast left a crater, 10 meters or 30 feet wide, in front of the hotel.   Police tell CNN, the driver of the truck bomb tried to talk his way pass   the hotel’s steel security gate. When armed guards said no,   police said the driver detonated more than 2,000 pounds of explosives.   The Marriott, one of the most popular destinations for locals and westerners   in Islamabad, now destroyed.  The Jords have a mole.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU JUST WANT ME TO NAIL SOME LOW LEVEL MOLAR–CRACKER–DOLER  SO YOU CAN CHECK THAT BOX ON YOUR RESUME THAT SAYS  WHILE YOU WERE IN PAKISTAN  YOU GOT A REAL TERRORIST</pattern><template>But the truth is, you don’t understand Pakistan, and you don’t know al Qaeda!</template></category><category><pattern>— ROGER THAT  POSSIBLE JACKPOT   — SHIT</pattern><template>It’s okay.</template></category><category><pattern>— WELL  I AGREE WITH MIKE</pattern><template>We’re basing this mostly on detainee reporting, and I spent a bunch of time in those rooms. I’d say it’s a soft 60, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>FIGHT TO PROTECT OUR TURF OR RUN</pattern><template>And you chose to fight, yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH</pattern><template>That’s the only name they gave me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE WAS THE LAST TIME YOU SAW BIN LADEN</pattern><template>Where was the last time you saw bin Laden, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>— SIR</pattern><template>All right, go ahead.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE JUST FUCKIN’ AROUND  ’CAUSE YOU SEE I’M UP BY TWO GAMES</pattern><template>How many you got?</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE LOOKED FOR WAYS OF COLLECTING AVAILABLE DNA FROM HIS TRASH  YOU KNOW  LOOKING FOR HIS TOOTHBRUSH  BUT THEY BURN THE TRASH</pattern><template>We started a vaccination program, sent a doctor to the house, see if he could pull blood.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  MAN  I’M FUCKING WITH YOU</pattern><template>No, I don’t want to talk about 9/11 yet.</template></category><category><pattern>— HELLO</pattern><template>— Sir.</template></category><category><pattern>ROGER  COPY THAT  TARGET SECURE</pattern><template>Target secure. Commence SSE.  Prep for SSE right now. Books, DVDs, CDs… Every fucking hard drive!</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S LIVING IN A HOUSE  IN ABBOTTABAD  PAKISTAN</pattern><template>And we assess, that one of the other occupants of the house, is UBL.</template></category><category><pattern>— YEAH  BUT THAT’S WHY YOU SHOULD FORWARD DEPLOY  SO YOU CAN SHORTEN THE RESPONSE TIME</pattern><template>— It still wouldn’t work.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU REALLY WANNA PROTECT THE HOMELAND  YOU NEED TO GET BIN LADEN</pattern><template>This guy never met bin Laden!</template></category><category><pattern>HE MADE A CALL FROM HAPUR STREET  THAT’S THE SPICE DISTRICT</pattern><template>Lahore Street, which is also in Pesh — 30 minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>THE POLITICAL MOVE HERE IS TO TELL YOU TO GO FUCK YOURSELF  AND REMIND YOU  THAT I WAS IN THE ROOM  WHEN YOUR OLD BOSS PITCHED WMD IRAQ</pattern><template>At least, there, you guys brought photographs.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S FEMALE NUMBER THREE</pattern><template>— So you found two males, three females.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SCREAMS SOMEONE WHO WANTS PRIVACY; IT EVEN SCREAMS BAD GUY</pattern><template>— But it does not scream bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HUNGRY</pattern><template>A lot of brothers told us, Abu Ahmed was Bin Laden’s courier, and that he worked very closely with you.</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE WE’RE JUST KEEPING IT FROM THEM</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>HAMZA RABIA</pattern><template>Khabab al Masri.</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT’S BULLSHIT  MAN</pattern><template>— Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>HE MAY NOT BE THAT SMART  HE MAY BE FULL OF SHIT</pattern><template>But we have to talk to him and find out.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU THINK HE MIGHT BE EXAGGERATING HIS ACCESS</pattern><template>Possibly.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S OF HIS OLDER BROTHER  HABIB  HE’S THE ONE THAT’S DEAD</pattern><template>Okay, and what are you basing this on?</template></category><category><pattern>SUVS ARE ACTUALLY PRETTY RARE IN PAKISTAN</pattern><template>If he was driving a sedan or a compact, we’d be fucked.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’VE KILLED HIM</pattern><template>— Let’s go.</template></category><category><pattern>AMMAR DOESN’T HAVE A CLUE ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>— Oh, he knows.</template></category><category><pattern>ECHO ZERO–FIVE  IF YOU’RE NOT AT THE LZ AT 4 MIKES  I’M GONNA LEAVE YOUR ASS BEHIND</pattern><template>The Paks have scrambled the F–16s.  Four minutes!</template></category><category><pattern>YES  BUT WE KNOW THAT HE’S IMPORTANT</pattern><template>The fact that everybody’s heard of Abu Ahmed, but nobody will tell me where he is, suggests that.</template></category><category><pattern>HMM</pattern><template>The risk of potentially letting bin Laden slip through your fingers.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ELSE HAVE YOU DONE FOR US</pattern><template>Besides bin Laden?</template></category><category><pattern>WE THINK THERE’S A THIRD FAMILY  LIVING IN THE HOUSE</pattern><template>So, this third male that you’ve identified as possibly being bin Laden, do I give up all hope of ever seeing a photograph of him?</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  WHY WOULD HE TRUST THEM  HE TRIED TO KILL MUSHARRAF</pattern><template>— Hello.</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED TO GO AND DO SOMETHING NORMAL FOR A WHILE</pattern><template>Like what?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  POLITICS ARE CHANGING  AND YOU DON’T WANNA BE THE LAST ONE HOLDING A DOG COLLAR  WHEN THE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE COMES</pattern><template>— I know.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON’T KNOW IF HE REALLY KNEW FARAJ</pattern><template>He just told me the names of all of Abu Faraj’s children.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DETERMINE HOW I TREAT YOU</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT  I WILL DO   NOT TO GET TECHNICAL  BUT THIS GUY IS ACTUALLY THE FIRST BIG BREAK WE’VE HAD SINCE 9/11</pattern><template>To big breaks, and the little people that make ‘em happen.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  WHAT’S UP</pattern><template>I shot the third floor guy.</template></category><category><pattern>HAZEM WAS A FRIEND OF RAMZI YOUSEF</pattern><template>You guys met in Iran back in the nineties.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF HE DOESN’T  WE KILL HIM</pattern><template>— John.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’LL JUST TELL HIS LAWYER TO WARN BIN LADEN</pattern><template>You’ll think of something.</template></category><category><pattern>PARTIAL INFORMATION IS TREATED AS A LIE  LET’S GO</pattern><template>— Saturday!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  ROGER THAT  WE’RE COMING TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>Stay with these kids, and don’t let them in that backroom.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WANNA PUT THE NEXT GENERATION ON THE FIELD</pattern><template>Listen, I’ve got a meeting with ISI in twenty minutes.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS ECHO ELEVEN   WE’RE GONNA BREACH THE MAIN GATE</pattern><template>Negative, this is Echo Zero–One, I’m…  internal on the corridor.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK ME DEAD</pattern><template>It’s nice, really nice.</template></category><category><pattern>BREACHER</pattern><template>Echo Team is away, Prince Five–Two exiting Alpha–Oscar.  Three… Two… One… Execute!</template></category><category><pattern>— WE LOST HIM FOR SEVEN YEARS</pattern><template>Now we find him again, and… boy, does he have a really nice house.</template></category><category><pattern>— ABU AHMED    — SAY IT AGAIN</pattern><template>— Abu Ahmed.   Abu Ahmed!   Abu Ahmed.  directement pour Ben Laden?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  SHORT TERM MEMORY LOSS IS A SIDE EFFECT OF SLEEP DEPRIVATION  SO IT SHOULD COME BACK TO YOU</pattern><template>I don’t know.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  COME ON</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M NOT SAYING WE’RE GONNA DO IT  BUT THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO KNOW  IF WE WERE GONNA ACT  HOW WOULD WE DO IT</pattern><template>Give us options.</template></category><category><pattern>HANG OUT WITH YOUR UNCLE</pattern><template>Mukhtar.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  SO TELL ME HOW I’M DOING SO FAR</pattern><template>Basically, we had a guy who rolled with al Qaeda, and did services for him.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS IN SURVEILLANCE VIDEO AND PICTURES LIKE THIS OF THE EXPLOSIVE LADEN VEHICLE   JUST MOMENTS BEFORE IT WAS PARKED  THAT POLICE HOPE TO FIND THE MAN    WHO WANTED SO BADLY LAST NIGHT  TO LEAVE A BODY COUNT IN TIMES SQUARE    THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE AROUND THE WORLD  THAT FIND OUR FREEDOM SO THREATENING    THAT THEY’RE WILLING TO KILL THEMSELVES AND OTHERS    TO PREVENT US FROM ENJOYING IT  BUT WE’RE NOT GONNA LET THAT HAPPEN…  HEY  I REALLY NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT BEEFING UP OUR SURVEILLANCE OPERATION ON THE CALLER</pattern><template>We don’t have a surveillance operation on the caller.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT  I UNDERSTAND</pattern><template>But, you know, I don’t really care if your guys get sleep or not.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T THINK I CAN ANSWER THAT QUESTION  SIR</pattern><template>I don’t think I’m allowed to… answer.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY ATTACKED US</pattern><template>On land, in ‘98, by sea in 2000, and from the air in 2001 They murdered 3,000 of our citizens, in cold blood.</template></category><category><pattern>— I DON’T THINK WE ARE FRIENDS</pattern><template>— All right, fair enough.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY ARE THERE GATE GUARDS THERE</pattern><template>We talked about this, no one is supposed to be there when my source arrives.</template></category><category><pattern>MONEY FOR WALK INS WORKED GREAT IN THE COLD WAR  I’LL GIVE YOU THAT</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE NO REASON TO BELIEVE HE’S CHANGED SECURITY TACTICS</pattern><template>We invaded Afghanistan, that’s a reason.</template></category><category><pattern>— HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT</pattern><template>— I told you, man, I know you.</template></category><category><pattern>PARTIAL INFORMATION… YOU GONNA GO IN THE BOX  HUH</pattern><template>Partial information is treated as a lie! Let’s go!</template></category><category><pattern>AMMAR IS WITHHOLDING</pattern><template>Washington assesses Abu Faraj as officially the new “Number 3”.</template></category><category><pattern>OUR CURRENT HYPOTHESIS IS THAT HE LIVES SOMEWHERE ALONG THE HIGHWAY  IN ONE OF THE TOWNS  OR A MEDIUM SIZED CITY CALLED ABBOTTABAD  OR UP NEAR KASHMIR</pattern><template>Kashmir is interesting because it’s a way station for the Tribals.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A DOG COLLAR</pattern><template>— No!</template></category><category><pattern>— I GOT HER</pattern><template>“Taht, taht, taht…” (Under) Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>GET HIM UP</pattern><template>Try to understand the concept here.</template></category><category><pattern>— OOH  IS THIS A BALBONI</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS ECHO ZERO–FIVE MOVING TO LEVEL 2</pattern><template>Hakim, get those guys back.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M SORRY  WHO’S THE “WE” IN THAT SENTENCE</pattern><template>Me, and some other guys who were hanging around at that time.</template></category><category><pattern>— PLEASE</pattern><template>Just… give me a name.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S OKAY</pattern><template>Get down.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MAN  I WAS THINKING ABOUT HIM</pattern><template>The guy gets a bomb in a shoe on a plane. Un fucking believable.</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT NOW  ALL THIS IS ABOUT  SIMPLY  IS YOU COMING TO TERMS WITH YOUR SITUATION</pattern><template>It’s you and me, bro.</template></category><category><pattern>IF HE’S TRYING TO OUTSMART YOU  WHY DON’T YOU TELL HIM ABOUT YOUR PHD</pattern><template>Yeah. No, but I am gonna have to turn up the heat on this asshole.</template></category><category><pattern>WE TRIED TO GET INTO TORA BORA  BUT THE BOMBING WAS TOO HIGH  WE COULDN’T CROSS</pattern><template>I’m sorry, who’s the “we” in that sentence?</template></category><category><pattern>AND IT MAKES SENSE HE’D BE LIVING IN RAWALPINDI  BECAUSE THERE’S AN AL JAZEERA OFFICE THERE</pattern><template>It’d be convenient for him to drop the tapes off, if he’s messengering, either from Bin Laden, or to an intermediary.</template></category><category><pattern>— MAYA  I KNOW</pattern><template>So, you agree with me now, this is important.</template></category><category><pattern>FLIGHT MANIFESTS</pattern><template>It must be pretty fucked up for you guys after 9/11.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST OFF THE PLANE FROM WASHINGTON… ROCKING YOUR BEST SUIT FOR YOUR FIRST INTERROGATION  AND YOU GET THIS GUY</pattern><template>— They’re not always this intense.</template></category><category><pattern>QATAR BASE SIX HAVE A BEAD ON THE ARABS THAT ESCAPED  THEY’RE MEETING WITH ISI THIS AFTERNOON  HOPEFULLY SET UP A RAID DOWN THERE</pattern><template>Great.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVING THROUGH</pattern><template>All right, listen up, gentlemen. Read the signs.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  CAN YOU JUST HOLD THE LINE  PLEASE</pattern><template>I need a picket line along the GT Highway, and men spaced at intervals — along the road, and at every exit.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DID  YOU GOT ME</pattern><template>Flight manifests.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW’S THE NEEDLE IN THE HAYSTACK</pattern><template>Fine.</template></category><category><pattern>COULD WE DO IT SOMEWHERE ELSE  GERMANY</pattern><template>In the UK? He’s got a clean passport.</template></category><category><pattern>— GOT HIM</pattern><template>Okay, breaking off.</template></category><category><pattern>I BELIEVE YOU  I DO  I BELIEVE YOU</pattern><template>It’s good, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S REALLY THE INTEL</pattern><template>That’s it?</template></category><category><pattern>I WANTED TO DROP A BOMB</pattern><template>But people didn’t believe in this lead enough to drop a bomb.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  IT CAN HIDE</pattern><template>So, uh, e—excuse me, but what do we—what do we need this for in—in Libya. I mean, Gaddafi’s anti air is virtually non existent.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCEPT WE DID FIND THIS COMPOUND  WHICH IS UNIQUE</pattern><template>We got a 16–foot wall around the entire perimeter.</template></category><category><pattern>— OH  YEAH</pattern><template>— I popped him from outside.</template></category><category><pattern>— IS HE SUPPOSED TO LIMP LIKE THAT</pattern><template>— Get your hand out of your pocket.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOUR FUCKIN’ JOBS  BRING ME PEOPLE TO KILL</pattern><template>Hi, I painstakingly combed through everything in the system and found this.</template></category><category><pattern>DEAL</pattern><template>Don’t you wanna see whats in the folder?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS GUY NEVER MET BIN LADEN</pattern><template>This guy’s a freelancer working off the fucking internet.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I FUCKING SMOKED ABRAR… AND HIS WIFE</pattern><template>She still alive?</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’VE GONE THROUGH  UH  AN INITIAL ROUND OF TESTING  AND THEY HAVE EXCELLENT RADAR DEFEAT</pattern><template>We just haven’t tested with people in them yet.</template></category><category><pattern>— BOYS  DEFINITELY</pattern><template>— Wow, your female’s moving fast.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT ME</pattern><template>You don’t look at me when I talk to you, I hurt you!</template></category><category><pattern>— VIDEO CAMERAS</pattern><template>Video cameras, where—where was it found?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DID HE DO FOR FARAJ</pattern><template>He carried messages from Abu Faraj to bin Laden, from bin Laden back to Abu Faraj.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I WAS MEANING TO TELL YOU  I’M GETTING OUTTA HERE</pattern><template>— You okay?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS GOOD  I MEAN THE LOCAL COPS NEED A LITTLE TACTICAL HELP  BUT… HE’S TIER FUCKING ONE  BABY</pattern><template>That’s your money maker right there.</template></category><category><pattern>— YUP</pattern><template>— Dan, Debbie found Abu Ahmed.</template></category><category><pattern>THIRD DECK   HERE</pattern><template>Hey.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN’T RUN A GLOBAL NETWORK OF INTERCONNECTED CELLS FROM A CAVE</pattern><template>We’ve located an individual, we believe, based on detainee reporting, is bin Laden’s courier.</template></category><category><pattern>THE RISK OF POTENTIALLY LETTING BIN LADEN SLIP THROUGH YOUR FINGERS</pattern><template>That is a fascinating question.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE IN LUCK  I GOT YOU A ONE–ON–ONE WITH FARAJ</pattern><template>Seriously? Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>ANYWAY  UH… ANYTHING FROM LAST NIGHT</pattern><template>Qatar Base Six have a bead on the Arabs that escaped, they’re meeting with ISI this afternoon, hopefully set up a raid down there.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUY YOU’VE BEEN LOOKING FOR  GEOLOCATED  ON HIS CELL PHONE  IN HIS WHITE CAR</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>OR MAYBE HE JUST DOESN’T LIKE HIS MUM</pattern><template>Look, if he talks about an operation or… refers to anything remotely fishy, I’ll get on him.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHY IS THAT</pattern><template>Even I couldn’t find him. He always contacted me out of the blue.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE IT YOUR WAY  LET’S GO</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DON’T MAKE TELEPHONE CALLS FROM THE COMPOUND</pattern><template>We pulled the cell tower nearby.</template></category><category><pattern>PRIMARILY AS A COURIER  FROM FARAJ TO BIN LADEN</pattern><template>That’s good, but you still don’t have— Yeah, but we don’t know if Abu’s on the outside of the network.</template></category><category><pattern>WE COULD TELL HIM ANYTHING</pattern><template>What? Bluff him?</template></category><category><pattern>I NEED FOUR TECHS AND A SAFE HOUSE IN RAWALPINDI… FOUR TECHS AND A SAFE HOUSE IN PESHAWAR</pattern><template>Either send them out, or send me back to DC, and explain to the director why you didn’t.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU GOT HIM</pattern><template>— Got him.</template></category><category><pattern>LADI</pattern><template>Hey, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE STILL NO CLOSER TO DEFEATING OUR ENEMY</pattern><template>They attacked us!</template></category><category><pattern>— HANG ON</pattern><template>You determine how I treat you.</template></category><category><pattern>— S… — WHAT</pattern><template>— What?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE THE HARD DRIVES GO</pattern><template>— Guys, marker on tables!</template></category><category><pattern>— LOOK AT THE CARS</pattern><template>Look at the cars, he’s in a vehicle.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T LOOK AT ME WHEN I TALK TO YOU  I HURT YOU</pattern><template>You step off this mat, I hurt you!</template></category><category><pattern>NO  GOOD</pattern><template>Dude, you shit your pants?</template></category><category><pattern>— HE’S HERE SOMEWHERE</pattern><template>— Look at the cars.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I WANT FROM YOU IS HIS SAUDI E MAIL</pattern><template>Ammar, bro, I know that you know this dude.</template></category><category><pattern>— COULD BE</pattern><template>— You got him?</template></category><category><pattern>GET IT UP</pattern><template>All right, let’s move it out.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  YOU’RE RIGHT  I AGREE WITH EVERYTHING YOU JUST SAID</pattern><template>What I meant was, a man in your position… How do you evaluate the risk of not doing something?</template></category><category><pattern>— AL BALUCHI  MY COURIER FOR THE “SHEIK”</pattern><template>Okay, so you’re telling me, all the other brothers are wrong.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU BELONG TO ME</pattern><template>Look at me.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY I SHOULD HELP YOU</pattern><template>Because we’re friends.</template></category><category><pattern>LET’S GO  BUDDY</pattern><template>Echo Zero–Five, this is Red Zero–Two.</template></category><category><pattern>— COLLECT ALL MEDIA</pattern><template>— CDs, DVDs?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I THINK THE MONEY IS PERSUASIVE</pattern><template>25 million dollars?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE MY DOG  I GOTTA WALK YOU</pattern><template>What the fuck do you think is going on, Ammar?</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN YOU LIE TO ME  I HURT YOU</pattern><template>Please.</template></category><category><pattern>AND EVERY TIME HIS PHONE RINGS  THIS PHONE WILL RING</pattern><template>Did I hook you up? Did I?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHAT DEFEAT LOOKS LIKE  BRO</pattern><template>Your jihad is over.</template></category><category><pattern>YES  SIR  THE GIRL  HUNDRED PERCENT  THANK YOU  SIR</pattern><template>— Are you Maya?</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU SAW HIM</pattern><template>A month ago, in Karachi.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW</pattern><template>My uncle told me he worked for bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>C’MON  DUDE  WHAT DO YOU LIKE  YOU LIKE A BIT OF  UH… YOU GUYS LIKE A BIT OF BOB MARLEY  WITH THE REGGAE</pattern><template>Kick back, take it easy after you’ve blown some shit up?</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS PICKED UP FOR FAKE PAPERS AND A DOCTORED EXIT VISA LEAVING AFGHANISTAN  TRAVELING THROUGH MOROCCO  EN ROUTE TO KUWAIT  ABU AHMED AL KUWAITI</pattern><template>This must be Abu Ahmed.</template></category><category><pattern>ECHO ZERO–FIVE  THIS IS RED ZERO–TWO</pattern><template>How long do you need for SSE?</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO KEEP CANVASSING THE NEIGHBORHOOD UNTIL WE FIND HIM</pattern><template>We got a shooter.</template></category><category><pattern>“YALLA  YALLA  IJLISOO</pattern><template>Ijlisoo!” (Go sit!) — “Ma’laysh, ma’laysh.” (Don’t worry) — Down! Sit down!</template></category><category><pattern>PARTIAL INFORMATION WILL BE TREATED AS A LIE  COME ON  LET’S GO</pattern><template>Come on, which day is it?</template></category><category><pattern>DID I TELL YOU THIS  THAT  UH  THIS DUDE IN MALAYSIA  HE TELLS A MALAYSIAN STATION THAT HIS NEPHEW — WORKS WITH A GUY  WHO KNOWS A GUY… — AWW  HERE WE GO</pattern><template>No, hold on. He goes to a big feast in Bangkok, about a year ago.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS WHAT REMAINS OF THE NO  10 BUS    WHICH WAS TRAVELLING THROUGH TAVISTOCK SQUARE  NEAR EUSTON STATION    THERE’D BEEN EXPLOSIONS NEAR LIVERPOOL STREET AND EDGWARE ROAD STATIONS TOO    DOZENS OF THE SURVIVORS WERE CRITICALLY INJURED    BUT MANY OF THE WOUNDED WERE ALSO KEEN TO SHARE THEIR STORIES    WE JUST PULLED OUT OF EDGWARE ROAD    AND NEXT THING I KNOW  IS A LOUD  UM  LARGE FLASH OF LIGHT    UH  I FELT A BURNING SENSATION ON MY HANDS  PUT MY HANDS UP TO MY FACE…   UH  I WAS ON THE FLOOR BY THAT POINT…   YEAH  I CAN’T RECALL ANYTHING PRIOR TO THAT ANYMORE  ANY NOISE  ANY BANG…   NORMAL LIFE IN ONE OF THE BUSIEST PARTS OF THE CAPITAL HAS NOW BEEN SUSPENDED    JUST A FEW YARDS DOWN THE ROAD HERE  THEY CONTINUE TO CARE FOR THE INJURED    AND ALL AROUND  GROUPS OF LONDONERS ARE STANDING ON CORNERS  ASKING THEMSELVES    “WHAT HAS HAPPENED HERE  AND WHO COULD POSSIBLY HAVE DONE THIS ”  COME ON</pattern><template>You too, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>— MORNING</pattern><template>— Morning, Hamad.</template></category><category><pattern>HIS TRUE NAME  WE THINK  IS IBRAHIM SAYEED</pattern><template>Family lives in Kuwait. We’ve been listening in on their calls.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR FRIEND IS AN ANIMAL</pattern><template>Please, help me.</template></category><category><pattern>I RAN IT</pattern><template>I’ll defend it.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU THINKING</pattern><template>Huh? Maybe a convertible?</template></category><category><pattern>DETAINEES CAN WITHHOLD HIS LOCATION FOR ANY NUMBER OF REASONS</pattern><template>Perhaps they don’t know.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR ANOTHER  THE AREA IS TOO CONGESTED FOR US TO BE EFFECTIVE  WITHOUT SOME PREDICTIVE INTELLIGENCE</pattern><template>— Yeah, but that’s why you should forward deploy, so you can shorten the response time.</template></category><category><pattern>THE DETAINEE PROGRAM IS NOW FLYPAPER</pattern><template>We got Senators jumping out of our asses.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M AT 80 PERCENT  THEIR OPSEC IS WHAT CONVINCES ME</pattern><template>— You guys ever agree on anything?</template></category><category><pattern>GUY’S A TERRORIST</pattern><template>His mother lives here.</template></category><category><pattern>IS HE EVER GETTING OUT</pattern><template>Never.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE SLOW ROLLING US ON LAHORE  YOU MIGHT WANNA BITCH ABOUT THAT</pattern><template>Did I tell you this? That, uh, this dude in Malaysia, he tells a Malaysian station that his nephew — works with a guy, who knows a guy… — Aww, here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GUYS MET IN IRAN BACK IN THE NINETIES</pattern><template>I don’t know!</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT  WAIT</pattern><template>Go back! They will kill you!</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN IT’S— IT’S A FORTRESS</pattern><template>Well, can’t you put a camera somewhere?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  MARK ALL MEDIA</pattern><template>— Gentlemen, watch your backs.</template></category><category><pattern>— UH HUH</pattern><template>— Good.</template></category><category><pattern>— DAN  DEBBIE FOUND ABU AHMED</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>BACK TO 40</pattern><template>— He’s here somewhere.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A SIGNAL ON TIPU ROAD FOR TEN MINUTES</pattern><template>Then he went to Umar Road for 5 minutes, NoGaza Road, Darya Abad, that’s in the Umar Road area.</template></category><category><pattern>LONDON  HEATHROW  MASS CASUALTIES</pattern><template>The plan is still active.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO THE HELL AM I SUPPOSED TO ASK  HUH</pattern><template>Some guy in Gitmo who’s all lawyered up?</template></category><category><pattern>HE DOES NOT LEAVE THE COMPOUND; HE DOES NOT PRESENT HIMSELF FOR PHOTOGRAPHS</pattern><template>When he needs fresh air, he paces around, beneath a grape arbor.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M GONNA ASK YOU A SERIES OF QUESTIONS  BASED ON YOUR KNOWLEDGE OF AL QAEDA  AND YOUR POSITION AS KEY FINANCIER FOR THE ORGANIZATION</pattern><template>I have dealt with the horrors.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU HAVE TO BE REALLY CAREFUL WITH PEOPLE IN KSM’S CIRCLE  THEY’RE DEVIOUS</pattern><template>He’s not gonna talk about attacks in the homeland.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY WILL NOT STOP UNTIL THEY HAVE A BODY</pattern><template>I ran it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND YOU’RE GONNA KILL HIM FOR ME</pattern><template>They’re nervous downtown.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M GONNA BREAK YOU</pattern><template>Any questions?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOO  COME ON</pattern><template>You agency guys are twisted.</template></category><category><pattern>THE SECOND NARRATIVE  IS THAT HE’S LIVING IN A CITY</pattern><template>Living in a city with multiple points of egress and entry, Access to communications, so that he can keep in touch with the organization.</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAS NO INTERNET ACCESS TO THE HOUSE; HE MAKES NO PHONE CALLS EITHER IN OR OUT WHO’S HE SELLING TO  WHO’S HE BUYING FROM  HOW’S HE MAKING HIS MONEY</pattern><template>And if you were to say, “He’s retired,” I’d say, “Where’s the swimming pool?” Where’s the gold cage with the falcons?</template></category><category><pattern>THIRD FLOOR  NORTHEAST CORNER</pattern><template>You don’t think she’s a little young for the hard stuff?</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  WHOA  HOW DO YOU KNOW THE GENDER</pattern><template>Well, look, this is a clothesline right here for laundry.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>This is Red Zero–Two.   Geronimo.   For God and country.   Geronimo.  All stations, target secure, target secure.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU TOO  SIR</pattern><template>— How’s your flight?</template></category><category><pattern>ANY STATION  THIS IS RED ZERO–TWO  WE NEED A BODY BAG   THIS IS ECHO ZERO–NINE  STAND BY</pattern><template>Hakim, I got this. Get it to him.</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST HANDED OUT SOME CASH FOR THEM</pattern><template>I didn’t know who the guys were.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NOT AT THE EXPENSE OF PROTECTING THE HOMELAND  YOU CAN’T… WAIT A MINUTE  WHY IS IT A GOOD THING</pattern><template>You sound just like Bradley.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY</pattern><template>Get it up.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING</pattern><template>I’ve done nothing else.</template></category><category><pattern>JOE AND I DID IRAQ TOGETHER</pattern><template>— It’s nice to meet you.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  THIS IS A LITTLE BIT OF A CLUSTER FUCK  ISN’T IT</pattern><template>I’d like to know what Maya thinks.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY DON’T NECESSARILY KNOW I’M CIA</pattern><template>Doesn’t matter.</template></category><category><pattern>— LET’S GO</pattern><template>— I got her.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I MEANT WAS  A MAN IN YOUR POSITION… HOW DO YOU EVALUATE THE RISK OF NOT DOING SOMETHING</pattern><template>Hmm?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  OH  WHOA  WHOA  WHOA</pattern><template>I want you to understand that I know you I’ve been following you, and studying you, for a long time.</template></category><category><pattern>— THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR THIS</pattern><template>— You’re welcome.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT WHEN I NEED SOMETHING  YOU ARE TOO BUSY TO PICK UP THE PHONE</pattern><template>— I don’t think we are friends.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WE HAVE TO GET A LOOK INTO THE HOUSE  DON’T WE</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHO IS IT</pattern><template>— Who do you think?</template></category><category><pattern>NOT GONNA HELP YOU</pattern><template>I’m gonna break you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF YOU DID FIND HIM  YOU DON’T KNOW THAT HE’D BE WITH BIN LADEN</pattern><template>We don’t know what we don’t know.</template></category><category><pattern>EITHER GIVE ME THE TEAM I NEED  TO FOLLOW THIS LEAD  OR THAT OTHER THING YOU’RE GONNA HAVE ON YOUR RESUME  IS BEING THE FIRST STATION CHIEF TO BE CALLED BEFORE CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEE  FOR SUBVERTING THE EFFORTS TO CAPTURE OR KILL BIN LADEN</pattern><template>You’re fucking out of your mind.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS DIFFERENT  I’M SORRY  I CAN’T EXPLAIN  BUT IT’S FOR A GOOD CAUSE</pattern><template>Look, I’m responsible for everybody’s safety, okay. It’s not just about you.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE ON A LIST</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE BEGINNING TO THINK IT’S NOT INCOMPETENCE</pattern><template>Okay, agree. I spoke to the chief about that. Anything on bin Laden?</template></category><category><pattern>EITHER SEND THEM OUT  OR SEND ME BACK TO DC  AND EXPLAIN TO THE DIRECTOR WHY YOU DIDN’T</pattern><template>I’ve been looking for you.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE</pattern><template>Detainees can withhold his location for any number of reasons.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW HIM  DON’T YOU</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT FAMILY TIES  FINANCIAL NETWORKS MEDIA SOURCES  DISGRUNTLED EMPLOYEES  IMMINENT THREATS  HOMELAND PLOTS  FOREIGN SALES  HEALTH STATUS  FINANCIAL RESOURCES  TRADECRAFT  RECRUITING TACTICS  ANYTHING ELSE</pattern><template>— No, I think that covers it.</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT OF BROTHERS TOLD US  ABU AHMED WAS BIN LADEN’S COURIER  AND THAT HE WORKED VERY CLOSELY WITH YOU</pattern><template>You are thinking of Abu Khaled.</template></category><category><pattern>— MM–HM</pattern><template>— We lost him for seven years.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S THEIR WEST POINT</pattern><template>And how close is that to the house?</template></category><category><pattern>QUITE FRANKLY  I DIDN’T EVEN WANNA USE YOU GUYS</pattern><template>With your dip and your velcro and all your gear bullshit.</template></category><category><pattern>— I’M NOT  BELIEVE ME</pattern><template>We’re stuck.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  “BISMILLAH AR RAHMAN AR RAHEEM” (IN THE NAME OF GOD  MOST GRACIOUS  MOST MERCIFUL) ALLAH REWARDS THOSE THAT STRIVE AND FIGHT  OVER THOSE THAT SIT BEHIND A DESK</pattern><template>As you know, Abu Ghraib and Gitmo fucked us.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE NO INTERCEPTS ABOUT ABU AHMED DYING   WE JUST HAVE A DETAINEE  WHO SAID HE BURIED A GUY  WHO LOOKED LIKE ABU AHMED</pattern><template>But if someone as important as Abu Ahmed had died, they’d be talking about it online,  in chatrooms all over the place.   Plus, the detainee said that Habib died in 2001.  We know Abu Ahmed was alive then, trying to get into Tora Bora with Ammar.</template></category><category><pattern>I’D LIKE TO KNOW WHAT MAYA THINKS</pattern><template>We’re all incorporating her assessment into ours.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  I WORK WITH HIM  I’M NOT THAT GIRL THAT FUCKS  IT’S UNBECOMING</pattern><template>So, a little fooling around wouldn’t hurt you.</template></category><category><pattern>20… 15… 10… SIGNAL’S GETTING WEAKER</pattern><template>We lost him, no signal.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GRAND TRUNK ROAD — 45 SECONDS</pattern><template>There’s no pattern.</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN’T MATTER  GOD  I WISH I HAD THAT FIVE YEARS AGO</pattern><template>— How come I never saw it before?</template></category><category><pattern>TOUT CE QUE JE SAIS  C’EST QU’IL FAIT PARTIE DU GROUPE</pattern><template>Tu connais d’autres gens qui portaient des messages pour Ben Laden?</template></category><category><pattern>SHE STILL ALIVE</pattern><template>— She’s gonna bleed out.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’LL THINK OF SOMETHING</pattern><template>He’d be the first successful drug dealer never to have dealt drugs.</template></category><category><pattern>TO BIG BREAKS  AND THE LITTLE PEOPLE THAT MAKE ‘EM HAPPEN</pattern><template>So far, everything he’s said, we’ve cross checked, and it’s proved legit.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  IF HE TALKS ABOUT AN OPERATION OR… REFERS TO ANYTHING REMOTELY FISHY  I’LL GET ON HIM</pattern><template>— Okay?</template></category><category><pattern>BIN LADEN USES A COURIER  TO INTERACT WITH THE OUTSIDE WORLD</pattern><template>By locating the courier, we’ve located bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>IF YOU’RE RIGHT  THE WHOLE WORLD’S GONNA WANT IN ON THIS</pattern><template>So, you gotta stick to your guns now.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN  NO OFFENSE  NO OFFENSE  I KNOW  BUT  OSAMA BIN LADEN</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IF SOMEONE AS IMPORTANT AS ABU AHMED HAD DIED  THEY’D BE TALKING ABOUT IT ONLINE   IN CHATROOMS ALL OVER THE PLACE    PLUS  THE DETAINEE SAID THAT HABIB DIED IN 2001   WE KNOW ABU AHMED WAS ALIVE THEN  TRYING TO GET INTO TORA BORA WITH AMMAR</pattern><template>That means it’s probably one of the other brothers  that’s dead.  — In other words, you want it to be true — Yes, I fucking want it to be true!</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  NO  NOT OKAY  LOOK</pattern><template>Abu Ahmed is too smart to tip his hand, by talking about ops on the phone.</template></category><category><pattern>OBSERVANT MUSLIM WOMEN LIVE WITH THEIR PARENTS  OVER THEIR HUSBANDS</pattern><template>We think there’s a third family, living in the house.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT THE WHOLE PLANE TO YOURSELF</pattern><template>Where do you wanna go?</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S CLOSE BY HERE  SOMEWHERE</pattern><template>I don’t get it.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE STUCK</pattern><template>What about Camp Chapman… Afghanistan? That can be safe territory.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SO YOU’RE TELLING ME  ALL THE OTHER BROTHERS ARE WRONG</pattern><template>And there’s some famous “Baluchi” guy, working for you and bin Laden, that I’ve never even heard of.</template></category><category><pattern>POSSIBLY</pattern><template>But, al Qaeda needs doctors, and they are short staffed, and… that could explain his rise.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE’S EVEN TALKED TO BIN LADEN IN FOUR YEARS  HE’S OUT OF THE GAME</pattern><template>He may well even be dead. He might as well be fucking dead.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>All right, I wanna know more about who’s inside this house by the end of the week Sir.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WOULD PROBABLY BE DISCOVERED</pattern><template>Well, we have to get a look into the house, don’t we?</template></category><category><pattern>— WHY SHOULD YOU HAVE HEARD OF HIM</pattern><template>— What does this Baluchi guy look like?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE TWO NARRATIVES  ABOUT THE LOCATION OF OSAMA BIN LADEN</pattern><template>The one that you’re most familiar with, is that UBL is hiding in a cave in the tribal areas.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GIVE UP YOUR HOPE  RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>We scan for heat signatures.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN MORE</pattern><template>Okay, that’s good. Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>SOME BULLSHIT ABOUT ESCAPING  YOU FUCKING BELIEVE THAT</pattern><template>Sorry, Dan.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A 16–FOOT WALL AROUND THE ENTIRE PERIMETER</pattern><template>The windows are blacked out.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW LET’S HOPE HE COMES BACK AROUND</pattern><template>Okay, 15… 20… 30… 40… 50… We’re within ten meters of it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND LAHORE REPORTING  ISI WAS PAINFULLY SLOW LAST NIGHT  AGAIN</pattern><template>They’re beginning to think it’s not incompetence.</template></category><category><pattern>4 221 FEET  IT’S CLOSER TO EIGHT–TENTHS OF A MILE</pattern><template>But who are you?</template></category><category><pattern>ON PEUT PAS SAVOIR QUI TRAVAILLE DIRECTEMENT POUR BEN LADEN</pattern><template>Tout ce que je sais, c’est qu’il fait partie du groupe.</template></category><category><pattern>THE MEETING WITH BALAWI IS OFF  HE CAN’T COME TO ISLAMABAD</pattern><template>— Can’t or won’t?</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE ALL SMART  JEREMY</pattern><template>May I join you?</template></category><category><pattern>THE FACT THAT EVERYBODY’S HEARD OF ABU AHMED  BUT NOBODY WILL TELL ME WHERE HE IS  SUGGESTS THAT</pattern><template>Maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M GLAD YOU SAID THAT</pattern><template>Okay, uh, I got an e mail from you to him, with all your comms for years, bro.</template></category><category><pattern>— AND IT’S ON HER  AND  WE DO NOT  — BRIEF CUSTODY  UNRESPONSIVE ALLY</pattern><template>— we cannot let this be a win–win for AQ The way you do this, is look ahead.</template></category><category><pattern>HE NEEDS TO GIVE UP THE SAUDI GROUP NOW</pattern><template>He’s gotta have that, given the family ties.</template></category><category><pattern>NEXT TIME  THERE MAY NOT BE BULLETPROOF GLASS TO SAVE YOU</pattern><template>We’ll keep up on the surveillance as best we can.</template></category><category><pattern>KINDA LIKE GANDALF</pattern><template>Who?</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LET’S BE SERIOUS NOW</pattern><template>Yeah don’t fuck around on this one, dude.</template></category><category><pattern>5… SIGNAL GETTING STRONGER  10… 15… KEEP GOING</pattern><template>20… 15… 10… Signal’s getting weaker.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT HAVE WE DONE</pattern><template>We have twenty leadership names.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS JUST US</pattern><template>And we are failing!</template></category><category><pattern>— WATER</pattern><template>— Please.</template></category><category><pattern>DID I HOOK YOU UP  DID I</pattern><template>My guess is that he lives close to where he’s making the calls.</template></category><category><pattern>MOVE HEAVEN AND EARTH… AND BRING ME THIS FUCKING SAYEED FAMILY’S PHONE NUMBER</pattern><template>Okay, I’ll go and talk to the Wolf.  — As salam alaykum. (Peace be unto you) — Wa alaykum salam. (And unto you peace) I need a couple of hundred thousand bucks.</template></category><category><pattern>FOOD IN HERE SUCKS  SO I BROUGHT YOU SOME OF THIS</pattern><template>Pretty good, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S SLOWER THAN A BLACK HAWK  LACKS THE OFFENSE AND THE STABILITY</pattern><template>But, it can hide.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S A DETAINEE VIDEO</pattern><template>He’s dead.   In Afghanistan, 2001, I buried him with my own hands.   He’s dead. In Afghanistan, 2001…   And where was this?   Kabul.  No, I don’t believe this.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN’T PREDICT WHEN HE’S GONNA MAKE ANOTHER CALL  ‘CAUSE THE GUY’S ERRATIC</pattern><template>Meanwhile, our chief foreign correspondent, Richard Engel confirms   the CIA’s top spy in Pakistan has been pulled out of there.   He’s been receiving death threats, after being named publicly in a lawsuit,   by the family of a victim of a US drone attack.   Richard Engel quotes a senior intelligence official as saying,   the officer is returning to the US, after the decision was made that   terrorist threats against him, in Pakistan, were of such a serious nature,   it would not be smart not to act.  ISI fucked you.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NO IDEA ABOUT IT    THAT’S SOMETHING YOU DON’T NEED AN IDEA ABOUT    WHEN YOU MET KHALID SHEIKH MOHAMMED  WAS THIS ONE OF THE FACILITATORS    IS THIS ABU AHMED    — KSM  YOUR BOSS</pattern><template>— Mukhtar.   “Mukhtar”… “Potato”…   You say, “Po–tah–to”; I say, “Fucking KSM”; you say, “Mukhtar”, okay?   Now, after Mukhtar was captured, what did Abu Ahmed do?   Abu Ahmed. I believe… I believe, he went to work for the “Sheik”.   Is that him?   — Say it.</template></category><category><pattern>— HE’S EAST OF US  TRY THE MARKET</pattern><template>— Okay, heading east.</template></category><category><pattern>WE STARTED A VACCINATION PROGRAM  SENT A DOCTOR TO THE HOUSE  SEE IF HE COULD PULL BLOOD</pattern><template>But that didn’t work out.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT  BLUFF HIM</pattern><template>He hasn’t slept in. He’s clueless.</template></category><category><pattern>— IT’S NICE TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>— You too, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>— GOOD</pattern><template>— Yeah, bud.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S GONNA HAPPEN   — WHEN</pattern><template>— Tonight.</template></category><category><pattern>— HE KNOWS THIS IS A HIGH LEVEL MEETING</pattern><template>— Quick question.</template></category><category><pattern>WE NEED TO ASK HIM SOMETHING TO SEE IF HE’S TELLING THE TRUTH</pattern><template>We don’t know if he really knew Faraj.</template></category><category><pattern>AMMAR  I KNOW THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A WAR NAME AND AN ARABIC NAME</pattern><template>She got you there, dude.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  MAYA  YOU GOTTA BE REAL CAREFUL WITH THE DETAINEES NOW</pattern><template>Okay, politics are changing, and you don’t wanna be the last one holding a dog collar, when the Oversight Committee comes.</template></category><category><pattern>BREACHER UP</pattern><template>Back it up, back up.</template></category><category><pattern>HE BROUGHT ME MANY MESSAGES FROM THE “SHEIK”</pattern><template>Where did you last see him, and where is he now?</template></category><category><pattern>MMM… WE’RE JUST WORRIED ABOUT YOU  OKAY  IS THAT OKAY TO SAY</pattern><template>I mean, look how run down you are.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO DID HE WORK FOR</pattern><template>He was mostly with Abu Faraj.</template></category><category><pattern>— WOW  YOUR FEMALE’S MOVING FAST</pattern><template>Okay, that’s what I wanted to show you. Can we pause this please?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T REMEMBER  DO YOU</pattern><template>Well, short term memory loss is a side effect of sleep deprivation, so it should come back to you.</template></category><category><pattern>WASHINGTON ASSESSES ABU FARAJ AS OFFICIALLY THE NEW “NUMBER 3”</pattern><template>He’s the best man for it.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I’M ALSO GOING TO GIVE UP HOPE THAT HE MIGHT EVER GET IN THAT WHITE SUV  AND… DRIVE AROUND A BIT AND WE COULD SEE HIM</pattern><template>Don’t they get groceries?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THE LEAVES ARE SO THICK  THEY OBSCURE OUR SATELLITE VIEWS</pattern><template>This is a professional attempt to avoid detection.</template></category><category><pattern>WASN’T IT… LIKE  EIGHT BROTHERS AND A MILLION COUSINS THAT WE KNOW ABOUT</pattern><template>— Anyone could be calling home.</template></category><category><pattern>A LETTER</pattern><template>What’d it say?</template></category><category><pattern>— SO FARAJ WENT SOUTH ON YOU  IT HAPPENS  THERE ARE STILL CELLS IN LONDON AND SPAIN  WHO ARE PLANNING THE NEXT ROUND OF ATTACKS</pattern><template>I could work on it at the same time.</template></category><category><pattern>— HE’S THE KEY TO BIN LADEN</pattern><template>I don’t fucking care about bin Laden, I care about the next attack.</template></category><category><pattern>DOES IT MATTER WHAT FARAJ THINKS ABOUT HEATHROW</pattern><template>How much latitude does he get to pick targets?</template></category><category><pattern>TRY TO UNDERSTAND THE CONCEPT HERE</pattern><template>Okay, I have time. You don’t.</template></category><category><pattern>“YALLA  YALLA…” ANY AMERICAN IN PAKISTAN IS A TARGET</pattern><template>They don’t necessarily know I’m CIA.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUYS THAT TALK ABOUT OPS ON THE PHONE DON’T GET THAT JOB</pattern><template>A lot of my friends have died, trying to do this.</template></category><category><pattern>— READY TO BREACH AT P2</pattern><template>Fire in the hole.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S TIGHT WITH HIS UNCLE  HE’S GOT HIS PRINTS ALL OVER 9/11 MONEY</pattern><template>He’s got ‘em in his head, he needs to disclose ‘em.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY  HE’S BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU</pattern><template>Yesterday, your caller bought himself a cell phone.</template></category><category><pattern>— YO  SHE SAYS IT’S NOT HIM</pattern><template>— Talk to the kid.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I’M SAYING THAT’S BUSHRA  THE BROTHER’S WIFE</pattern><template>Whoa, whoa, how do you know the gender?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  NOW WATCH  IT TAKES HER ABOUT FOUR SECONDS TO MOVE FROM THERE  TO THE FRONT DOOR  SO SHE’S ON THE OLDER SIDE</pattern><template>— What’s that up there?</template></category><category><pattern>LET’S GO  GUYS</pattern><template>Hey, what’s up?</template></category><category><pattern>HEADING SOUTH</pattern><template>He’s up at 5 again.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’—IT’S COOL THAT YOU’RE STRONG  I RESPECT IT  I DO</pattern><template>But in the end, everybody breaks, bro. That’s biology.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S NOT GONNA TALK ABOUT ATTACKS IN THE HOMELAND</pattern><template>He’s gonna withhold operational details on the KSM network and probably bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>HONESTLY  THERE’S 600 QUESTIONS IN THERE  I’D DO HEATHROW  THE SAUDIS</pattern><template>Does it matter what Faraj thinks about Heathrow?</template></category><category><pattern>— DUDE</pattern><template>— It’s okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WE CAN’T RELY ON THIS OR THE JORDS</pattern><template>We’ve gotta evaluate him face to face.</template></category><category><pattern>— C’MON  GRAB THE BUCKET</pattern><template>Put some water in it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE GONNA START WORKING ON THE AMERICAN AL QAEDA CELLS</pattern><template>Protect the homeland.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH DAY</pattern><template>Frid… — Ammar, which day?</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S GOOD  HUH</pattern><template>Do you want the water again?</template></category><category><pattern>NICE JOB</pattern><template>Where the hard drives go?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  LET’S GO</pattern><template>— Is he supposed to limp like that?</template></category><category><pattern>— ALMOST</pattern><template>Monday!</template></category><category><pattern>SO I WON’T TALK TO YOU</pattern><template>Well, life isn’t always fair, my friend.</template></category><category><pattern>HUH  PUT THE TOP DOWN</pattern><template>I think I will choose this one.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT THEY ALSO SAID THERE’S A 35 PERCENT CHANCE HE’S A SAUDI DRUG DEALER</pattern><template>15 percent chance he’s a Kuwaiti arms smuggler.</template></category><category><pattern>— SORRY</pattern><template>— No.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  I WANNA KNOW MORE ABOUT WHO’S INSIDE THIS HOUSE BY THE END OF THE WEEK SIR</pattern><template>Motherfucker.</template></category><category><pattern>HOWEVER  DEPENDING ON HOW CANDID YOU ARE HERE TODAY  I MAY BE ABLE TO KEEP YOU IN PAKISTAN</pattern><template>What do you want to know?</template></category><category><pattern>MY UNCLE TOLD ME HE WORKED FOR BIN LADEN</pattern><template>Um, I did see him, once, about a year ago, in Karachi.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  HE’S COMING</pattern><template>— We gonna search him when he gets here — Sure.</template></category><category><pattern>YALLA  YALLA</pattern><template>Hakim, get him back, or I’ll start smokin’ ‘em.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON’T HAVE A SURVEILLANCE OPERATION ON THE CALLER</pattern><template>Someone just tried to blow up Times Square and you’re talking to me about some facilitator, who some detainee, seven years ago, said, — might have been working with al Qaeda?</template></category><category><pattern>AND WATCH YOUR BACK WHEN YOU GET BACK TO PAKISTAN  EVERYONE KNOWS YOU THERE NOW</pattern><template>Sorry. Fucking checkpoints.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  BACK IT UP</pattern><template>Watch out.</template></category><category><pattern>— TONY ROBBINS  REALLY</pattern><template>You should listen to it.</template></category><category><pattern>COPY THAT</pattern><template>Thirty seconds to first turn.  Hey, Justin, what’re you listening to?</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAYS IT LOOKS LIKE ABU AHMED</pattern><template>Who did he work for?</template></category><category><pattern>— HOW COME I NEVER SAW IT BEFORE</pattern><template>— Nobody saw it, most likely.</template></category><category><pattern>— AND YOU’RE A MONEYMAN</pattern><template>Paperboy.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN SIT WHEREVER YOU WANT  YOU’RE THE ONLY ONE ON THE MANIFEST</pattern><template>You must be pretty important.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST  THERE  YOU GUYS BROUGHT PHOTOGRAPHS</pattern><template>You know, you’re right, I agree with everything you just said.</template></category><category><pattern>HE SAID THAT HE WAS IN A PLACE IN THE COUNTRY WITH BAD CELL RECEPTION  IMPLYING HE WAS IN THE TRIBALS  WHEN  IN FACT  HE WAS IN A MARKET IN PESHAWAR</pattern><template>I’m sorry but that’s not normal guy behavior, that’s tradecraft.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS WRONG WITH THAT  EXACTLY</pattern><template>What was wrong with that? That, uh… The sample would be too diluted.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  YEAH  THE LONDON STATION’S ALREADY ASKING IF HE’S CONTACTING ANYBODY IN THE UK</pattern><template>Like we’re just keeping it from them?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WARNED THEM  THEY DIDN’T TAKE YOU SERIOUSLY</pattern><template>This is what happens. It’s not on you.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHO</pattern><template>— Al Baluchi, my courier for the “Sheik”.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T BELIEVE THIS</pattern><template>Sorry, Maya.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOTTA SAY  YOUR JOB… — HMM</pattern><template>— Huh.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU HAVEN’T TRIED</pattern><template>— Look, I don’t have the personnel.</template></category><category><pattern>— I POPPED HIM FROM OUTSIDE</pattern><template>Oh, I fucking smoked Abrar… and his wife.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  COME ON  WE’VE GOT LOTS OF WINE   COOL  BRING ME BACK A BOTTLE</pattern><template>That, I will do.  Not to get technical, but this guy is actually the first big break we’ve had since 9/11.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS IT</pattern><template>There’s no working group coming to the rescue.</template></category><category><pattern>BACK IT UP… MAIN GATE</pattern><template>We got an unlocked door.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHY</pattern><template>The guy never stays on the phone long enough.</template></category><category><pattern>I ACTUALLY TRIED TO KILL THIS PROGRAM A COUPLE OF TIMES</pattern><template>They’ve gone through, uh, an initial round of testing, and they have excellent radar defeat.</template></category><category><pattern>TORA BORA  YEAH</pattern><template>— Uh huh.</template></category><category><pattern>HAKIM  GET THOSE GUYS BACK</pattern><template>Khalid… Khalid… Echo Zero–Two, moving to deck 3.</template></category><category><pattern>EXCUSE ME</pattern><template>Uh, so, UBL, you got—you got an intel source on the ground?</template></category><category><pattern>— WHO’S GOT A SHARPIE</pattern><template>— Right here.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE OTHER THINGS TO DO BUT YOU DON’T</pattern><template>It’—it’s cool that you’re strong. I respect it, I do.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK I WILL CHOOSE THIS ONE</pattern><template>Give us a minute? Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>IN WHAT CONTEXT HAVE YOU EVER HEARD THE NAME ABU AHMED</pattern><template>He works for Faraj and bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>LADI… LADI</pattern><template>Name… name… Ladi… — We’re meeting down.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S NOT THE SAME LADY</pattern><template>That’s female number three.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’S HIS FAMILY NAME</pattern><template>Abu Ahmed al Kuwaiti.</template></category><category><pattern>TU CONNAIS D’AUTRES GENS QUI PORTAIENT DES MESSAGES POUR BEN LADEN</pattern><template>Ben on va en parler un p’tit peu alors. Hein.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE EXACTLY IS ABU AHMED LIVING AT THE MOMENT</pattern><template>Faraj is completely denying knowing Abu Ahmed.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  SO HOW DO YOU KNOW IT’S BIN LADEN</pattern><template>’Cause the truth is, we’ve been on this op before.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE DEALT WITH THE HORRORS</pattern><template>I have no wish to be tortured again.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES  HE CALLS EVERY TWO WEEKS  SOMETIMES  EVERY THREE</pattern><template>There’s no consistency.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’RE ALL INCORPORATING HER ASSESSMENT INTO OURS</pattern><template>A hundred percent he’s there.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO TAKE CARE OF ALL THIS BEFORE YOUR FAVORITE SUBJECT</pattern><template>Deal.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT’D IT SAY</pattern><template>Cigarette?</template></category><category><pattern>WHY HAVEN’T YOU DEPLOYED A TEAM TO STAY IN RAWALPINDI</pattern><template>For one thing, it’s dangerous.</template></category><category><pattern>— I WAS RECRUITED OUT OF HIGH SCHOOL</pattern><template>— And do you know why we did that?</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON’T DEAL IN CERTAINTY  WE DEAL IN PROBABILITY</pattern><template>And I’d say there’s a 60 percent probability he’s there.</template></category><category><pattern>MORNING  GEORGE</pattern><template>21 days.</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH IS A SMART THING TO DO WHEN YOU’RE STARTING TO THINK FOR YOURSELF</pattern><template>Mm–hm.</template></category><category><pattern>BESIDES BIN LADEN</pattern><template>Nothing.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN HELP YOURSELF BY BEING TRUTHFUL</pattern><template>This is a dog collar.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  HELP ME</pattern><template>Please.</template></category><category><pattern>TALK TO THE CASE OFFICERS WHO DIDN’T SEE FIT TO MAKE IT TODAY  AND “THANK” THEM</pattern><template>Tora Bora, yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT CONFIRMS MY LEAD</pattern><template>— Or it’s confirmation bias.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS A COMPUTER GUY WITH US AT THE TIME</pattern><template>After Tora Bora, I went back to Pesh, as you know.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIGHT HAVE SPOOKED HIM ALREADY</pattern><template>Well, procedures only work if we follow them every time.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S IT</pattern><template>Quite frankly, I didn’t even wanna use you guys.</template></category><category><pattern>HUMAM KHALIL AL BALAWI</pattern><template>He’s a Jordanian doctor.</template></category><category><pattern>— GUYS  MARKER ON TABLES</pattern><template>— Yes, sir.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE’S JACK</pattern><template>Probably stuck in some checkpoint, somewhere.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYA  IT’S STEVE   — SWING BY  I WANNA SHOW YOU SOMETHING</pattern><template>— Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY SAY HE’S PART OF AN INNER CIRCLE OF GUYS THAT WAS HANGING OUT IN AFGHANISTAN PRE 9/11</pattern><template>A lot of them say that after 9/11, he went to work for KSM.</template></category><category><pattern>— I TOLD YOU  MAN  I KNOW YOU</pattern><template>All right, you got me.</template></category><category><pattern>HE KNOWS YOU’RE WHITE  WE’D GET KIDNAPPED THERE</pattern><template>Could we do it somewhere else? Germany?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T THINK I’M ALLOWED TO… ANSWER</pattern><template>All right.</template></category><category><pattern>I LET YOU LIVE  SO THAT YOU AND I COULD TALK</pattern><template>Then you beat me when my hands are tied.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  UH  E—EXCUSE ME  BUT WHAT DO WE—WHAT DO WE NEED THIS FOR IN—IN LIBYA  I MEAN  GADDAFI’S ANTI AIR IS VIRTUALLY NON EXISTENT</pattern><template>Maya, do you wanna brief ‘em?</template></category><category><pattern>HOW’D IT GO THE OTHER NIGHT</pattern><template>It was good. I mean the local cops need a little tactical help, but… he’s tier fucking one, baby.</template></category><category><pattern>AS YOU KNOW  ABU GHRAIB AND GITMO FUCKED US</pattern><template>The Detainee Program is now flypaper.</template></category><category><pattern>I WOULD HAVE NEVER ASKED HIM SOMETHING LIKE THAT  IT’S NOT HOW MY UNCLE WORKED</pattern><template>I know.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THAT YOU KNOW HIM</pattern><template>I told you before, I won’t talk to you.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY’NCHA GET TO WORK  GRAB A BAG</pattern><template>Q–Rod is inbound, eight miles out.  Pak Air Force is responding.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S GOOD  BUT YOU STILL DON’T HAVE— YEAH  BUT WE DON’T KNOW IF ABU’S ON THE OUTSIDE OF THE NETWORK</pattern><template>A series of cut outs and dead drops, or if he has a direct connection to bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>— WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE GIRL</pattern><template>— I think she’s fucking smart.</template></category><category><pattern>— SATURDAY</pattern><template>— In the box you go!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE THINKING OF ABU KHALED</pattern><template>— Who?</template></category><category><pattern>THE PICTURE WE’VE BEEN USING IS WRONG</pattern><template>It’s of his older brother, Habib. He’s the one that’s dead.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ONE THAT YOU’RE MOST FAMILIAR WITH  IS THAT UBL IS HIDING IN A CAVE IN THE TRIBAL AREAS</pattern><template>That he’s surrounded by a large contingent of loyal fighters.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S KINDA FUCKED UP</pattern><template>You volunteered for this, didn’t you?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  I FORGOT  WERE WE SUPPOSED TO CRASH THAT HELO</pattern><template>Ibrahim tried to shoot through the door.</template></category><category><pattern>— SHE’S GONNA BLEED OUT</pattern><template>— What a fucking mess.</template></category><category><pattern>ANY QUESTIONS</pattern><template>No?</template></category><category><pattern>WALID HAS ALREADY TOLD ME THAT YOU KNOW  HMM</pattern><template>Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>HMPH… — SO  NO BOYFRIEND</pattern><template>— Mm–mm.</template></category><category><pattern>DON’T YOU THANK ME UNTIL YOU HEAR WHAT I WANT FOR IT</pattern><template>I want you to take care of all this before your favorite subject.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  I CAN ALWAYS GO AND EAT WITH SOME OTHER DUDE  HANG YOU BACK UP TO THE CEILING</pattern><template>Hamza Rabia.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL CLEAR</pattern><template>Whoa, fucking shit.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THAT’S A CONVERSATION</pattern><template>Honestly, there’s 600 questions in there. I’d do Heathrow, the Saudis.</template></category><category><pattern>I’VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU</pattern><template>But more importantly, he’s been looking for you.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LISTEN UP  GENTLEMEN  READ THE SIGNS</pattern><template>1st Floor! Hard drives, files, anything!</template></category><category><pattern>— RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>— Good job, man.</template></category><category><pattern>IN THESE TREES HERE  MAYBE</pattern><template>Get a look in the main house?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT  YOU KNOW  I DON’T REALLY CARE IF YOUR GUYS GET SLEEP OR NOT</pattern><template>This guy you are obsessed with.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M NOT GONNA FIND ABU AHMED FROM DC</pattern><template>They killed my monkeys.</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT PLANS FOR AFTER THIS</pattern><template>Big time. I wanna talk to all of you about it.</template></category><category><pattern>— QUICK QUESTION</pattern><template>All this taking place inside our main building?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T FUCKING CARE ABOUT BIN LADEN  I CARE ABOUT THE NEXT ATTACK</pattern><template>You’re gonna start working on the American al Qaeda cells.</template></category><category><pattern>3RD FLOOR  LADIES’ UNDERWEAR</pattern><template>We’re on strike, they can’t be — that many of ‘em, right?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A PROFESSIONAL ATTEMPT TO AVOID DETECTION</pattern><template>Okay? Real tradecraft.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT LEAVE A HARD DRIVE</pattern><template>Hey, open that for me.</template></category><category><pattern>WEAKER NOW  HE SHIFTED  GO BACK TO 5</pattern><template>He’s close by here, somewhere.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN</pattern><template>Huh? It’s been a while.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE’S NO CONSISTENCY</pattern><template>I can’t predict when he’s gonna make another call, ‘cause the guy’s erratic.</template></category><category><pattern>— ARE YOU MAYA</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M COOL WITH IT</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>— GOOD JOB  MAN</pattern><template>Nice job.</template></category><category><pattern>PHANDU ROAD — 5 MINUTES</pattern><template>The Grand Trunk Road — 45 seconds.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I—I CAN DO  UM… LET ME HAVE A LOOK  UM… WHY DON’T WE SAY 1:30</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY TOLD US TO WATCH OUT FOR HIM  APPARENTLY  THEY THINK HIS WHOLE FAMILY AND EXTENDED FAMILY IS BAD  AND HAS TIES TO KSM</pattern><template>He was picked up for fake papers and a doctored exit visa leaving Afghanistan, traveling through Morocco, en route to Kuwait. Abu Ahmed al Kuwaiti.</template></category><category><pattern>— MAYA  COME SEE</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE ASSUMING THAT AL QAEDA MEMBERS ARE MOTIVATED BY FINANCIAL REWARDS</pattern><template>They’re radicals.</template></category><category><pattern>MONDAY</pattern><template>— Tuesday!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS ECHO ZERO–NINE  WE HAVE UNKNOWNS GATHERING IN THE SOUTHWEST ROOFTOPS</pattern><template>Locked gate blocking the stairs.</template></category><category><pattern>— THAT’S CORRECT</pattern><template>So, if there are three females, there ought to be three males.</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A GOLD MINE  I NEED MORE TIME THAN THAT</pattern><template>Echo Zero–Five, if you’re not at the LZ at 4 Mikes, I’m gonna leave your ass behind.</template></category><category><pattern>IN SIX MONTHS TO A YEAR  IF HE DOESN’T FUCK UP  HE COULD BE CALLED IN TO TREAT BIN LADEN</pattern><template>At that moment, with 25 mill on the table, I think he gives up the big man.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE JUST TRIED TO BLOW UP TIMES SQUARE AND YOU’RE TALKING TO ME ABOUT SOME FACILITATOR  WHO SOME DETAINEE  SEVEN YEARS AGO  SAID  — MIGHT HAVE BEEN WORKING WITH AL QAEDA</pattern><template>— He’s the key to bin Laden.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SHOULD COME WITH ME</pattern><template>Yeah, be my number two. You’re looking a little strung out yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL RIGHT  LET’S MOVE IT OUT</pattern><template>Let’s go! Now!</template></category><category><pattern>ACCORDING TO THEM  THIS BEHAVIOR COULD BELONG TO SOMEONE OTHER THAN AL QAEDA</pattern><template>They did give a 40 percent chance that the unidentified third man… is a senior al Qaeda operative.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO  UM… WHO ELSE IS IN YOUR SAUDI GROUP</pattern><template>I just handed out some cash for them.</template></category><category><pattern>GUEST OF HONOR: OSAMA BIN LADEN</pattern><template>— Except if it was Tupac there… — This is worth 5 million bucks.</template></category><category><pattern>WE’VE ONLY ELIMINATED FOUR OF THEM</pattern><template>I want… targets.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WE SHOULD GO BACK IN</pattern><template>You know, it’s no shame if you wanna watch from the monitor.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU’RE THE SECOND “NUMBER 3” I’VE CAPTURED  I GOT KSM</pattern><template>Can I be honest with you?</template></category><category><pattern>ON LAND  IN ‘98  BY SEA IN 2000  AND FROM THE AIR IN 2001 THEY MURDERED 3 000 OF OUR CITIZENS  IN COLD BLOOD</pattern><template>And they have slaughtered our forward–deployed!</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS PURE RISK  BASED ON DEDUCTIVE REASONING  INFERENCE  SUPPOSITION  AND THE ONLY HUMAN REPORTING YOU HAVE IS SIX YEARS OLD  FROM DETAINEES  WHO WERE QUESTIONED UNDER DURESS</pattern><template>The political move here is to tell you to go fuck yourself, and remind you, that I was in the room, when your old boss pitched WMD Iraq.</template></category><category><pattern>AND HOW CLOSE IS THAT TO THE HOUSE</pattern><template>About a mile.</template></category><category><pattern>A SERIES OF CUT OUTS AND DEAD DROPS  OR IF HE HAS A DIRECT CONNECTION TO BIN LADEN</pattern><template>I mean, does bin Laden invite him into the living room, and hand him a letter directly, or is Abu just the last guy in a long line of couriers, and that’s why everybody knows him.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU  UH  YOU SHOULD SIT BACK THERE</pattern><template>— Sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I’D SAY THERE’S A 60 PERCENT PROBABILITY HE’S THERE</pattern><template>I concur, 60 percent.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN IS THE ATTACK</pattern><template>— S… — What?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST BE PRETTY IMPORTANT</pattern><template>You got the whole plane to yourself.</template></category><category><pattern>“TAHT  TAHT  TAHT…” (UNDER) HEY</pattern><template>“Yalla! Yalla! Ijlisoo!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU’RE A MID LEVEL GUY  YOU’RE A GARBAGEMAN IN THE CORPORATION</pattern><template>What should I respect you, huh?</template></category><category><pattern>— NO  I THINK THAT COVERS IT</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>WE GOT A MILLION TIPS  AND… YOU KNOW  THINGS GOT LOST IN THE SHUFFLE</pattern><template>Human error.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  I’LL GO AND TALK TO THE WOLF   — AS SALAM ALAYKUM  (PEACE BE UNTO YOU) — WA ALAYKUM SALAM  (AND UNTO YOU PEACE) I NEED A COUPLE OF HUNDRED THOUSAND BUCKS</pattern><template>Four max.</template></category><category><pattern>PRAYER ROOM’S CLEAR</pattern><template>Breacher!</template></category><category><pattern>— TONIGHT</pattern><template>Good luck.  — Fifty bucks?</template></category><category><pattern>AND I CAN TELL YOU THE CASE FOR THAT  WAS MUCH STRONGER THAN THIS CASE</pattern><template>A fucking “yes” or a “no”.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU VOLUNTEERED FOR THIS  DIDN’T YOU</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>MOTHERFUCKER</pattern><template>Good.</template></category><category><pattern>DOWN</pattern><template>You’ve killed him!</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER 9/11  WE HAD TO CHOOSE</pattern><template>Fight to protect our turf or run.</template></category><category><pattern>CAN YOU OPEN THE TRUNK  MA’AM</pattern><template>It’s clear.</template></category><category><pattern>HAKIM  I GOT THIS  GET IT TO HIM</pattern><template>Let’s go, buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  OPEN THAT FOR ME</pattern><template>Let’s go, guys.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU GOT IT “CH”</pattern><template>.. to clean that audio as well, just take the low one out.</template></category><category><pattern>IT’S STILL GOOD WORK  LET ME KNOW WHEN YOU’VE GOT SOME ACTUAL INTELLIGENCE</pattern><template>Preferably, something that leads to a strike.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW’S THAT FOR FRIENDSHIP</pattern><template>Poor fucker had to get out of bed.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YOU THINK THIS IS POLITICAL</pattern><template>If this was political, we’d be having this conversation in October, when there’s an election bump.</template></category><category><pattern>RICHARD REID</pattern><template>Oh, man, I was thinking about him.</template></category><category><pattern>IBRAHIM TRIED TO SHOOT THROUGH THE DOOR</pattern><template>— Oh, yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT A MILE</pattern><template>4,221 feet. It’s closer to eight–tenths of a mile.</template></category><category><pattern>A LOT OF THEM SAY THAT AFTER 9/11  HE WENT TO WORK FOR KSM</pattern><template>When KSM was captured, he went to work for Abu Faraj.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  JACK</pattern><template>Sayeed family call in progress, but you’re not gonna like this.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  GIVE IT TO ME</pattern><template>Hazem was a friend of Ramzi Yousef.</template></category><category><pattern>UH  SEE IF THE PAKS WILL SEND SOMEONE TO TALK TO THE FARMER  ANYTHING ELSE</pattern><template>No?</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S A JORDANIAN DOCTOR</pattern><template>He’s right there in the inner circle.</template></category><category><pattern>WE TALKED ABOUT THIS  NO ONE IS SUPPOSED TO BE THERE WHEN MY SOURCE ARRIVES</pattern><template>You might have spooked him already.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MEANS IT’S PROBABLY ONE OF THE OTHER BROTHERS  THAT’S DEAD   — IN OTHER WORDS  YOU WANT IT TO BE TRUE — YES  I FUCKING WANT IT TO BE TRUE</pattern><template>Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, calm down.  — Calm down.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE NERVOUS DOWNTOWN</pattern><template>I don’t think we’ll get an approval.</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S ONE OF “THE DISAPPEARED ONES”</pattern><template>You’re in luck, I got you a one–on–one with Faraj.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE ASSESS  THAT ONE OF THE OTHER OCCUPANTS OF THE HOUSE  IS UBL</pattern><template>General.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT’S THE KINDA CONCRETE DATA POINT I’M LOOKING FOR</pattern><template>I tell you, buddy.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON’T KNOW</pattern><template>How can I remember?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE YOUR NAME… ON A $5 000 TRANSFER VIA WESTERN UNION TO A 9/11 HIJACKER</pattern><template>And you got popped… with 150 kilograms of high explosives in your house!</template></category><category><pattern>SO FAR  EVERYTHING HE’S SAID  WE’VE CROSS CHECKED  AND IT’S PROVED LEGIT</pattern><template>And I think the money is persuasive.</template></category><category><pattern>KHABAB AL MASRI</pattern><template>And Abu Ahmed.</template></category><category><pattern>NICE CHOICE</pattern><template>Sayeed.</template></category><category><pattern>NO FUCKING WAY WE CAN BLOW THIS THING</pattern><template>God–fucking–damnit, can you pop it manually?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  NO  BUT I AM GONNA HAVE TO TURN UP THE HEAT ON THIS ASSHOLE</pattern><template>He needs to give up the Saudi group now.</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH OUT</pattern><template>Execute.</template></category><category><pattern>PERHAPS THEY DON’T KNOW</pattern><template>Perhaps this “Abu” is actually a cover story and he’s really a fucking unicorn.</template></category><category><pattern>— JOHN</pattern><template>— Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY’RE RADICALS</pattern><template>Correct. You’re assuming that, uh, greed won’t override ideology in some of the weaker members.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  THAT’S WHAT I WANTED TO SHOW YOU  CAN WE PAUSE THIS PLEASE</pattern><template>That’s not the same lady.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYA  I WANTED YOU TO HEAR IT FIRST   YOU KNOW THAT THING WE TALKED ABOUT</pattern><template>It’s gonna happen.  — When?</template></category><category><pattern>1ST FLOOR  HARD DRIVES  FILES  ANYTHING</pattern><template>2nd Floor! Opposite, down on the right!</template></category><category><pattern>WHOA  WHOA  WHOA  WHOA  WHOA  CALM DOWN   — CALM DOWN</pattern><template>— I am calm.</template></category><category><pattern>— SHH… THURSD… AMMAR  WHICH DAY IS IT</pattern><template>Which day?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT HE’S BEEN IN COMPLETE ISOLATION</pattern><template>He doesn’t know we’ve failed.</template></category><category><pattern>…AND  UH  I’VE SAID REPEATEDLY  THAT AMERICA DOESN’T TORTURE    AND I’M GONNA MAKE SURE THAT WE DON’T TORTURE  THOSE ARE PART AND PARCEL OF…   AN—AN EFFORT TO REGAIN  UH  AMERICA’S MORAL STATURE IN THE WORLD    CAN YOU GIVE US SOME SENSE OF WHEN YOU MIGHT START…  HE… WANTS US TO GO TO HIM</pattern><template>He’ll meet us in Maidan Shar with the Tribals.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRE IN THE HOLE</pattern><template>Failed breach, failed breach.</template></category><category><pattern>YESTERDAY  YOUR CALLER BOUGHT HIMSELF A CELL PHONE</pattern><template>And every time his phone rings, this phone will ring.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULD WORK ON IT AT THE SAME TIME</pattern><template>Plus, I think it’s a good thing he lied.</template></category><category><pattern>— HE’S NOT GONNA TRAVEL  SECURITY RISK</pattern><template>…and, uh, I’ve said repeatedly, that America doesn’t torture.   And I’m gonna make sure that we don’t torture. Those are part and parcel of…   an—an effort to regain, uh, America’s moral stature in the world.   Can you give us some sense of when you might start…  He… wants us to go to him.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU REALLY BELIEVE THIS STORY</pattern><template>I mean, no offense, no offense, I know, but, Osama bin Laden?</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I DON’T WANT TO TALK ABOUT 9/11 YET</pattern><template>What I want to focus on is the Saudi group.</template></category><category><pattern>THE GUY GETS A BOMB IN A SHOE ON A PLANE  UN FUCKING BELIEVABLE</pattern><template>You know him, don’t you?</template></category><category><pattern>HE’S LIKE  “HEY  THAT’S ME  MAN  NO JOB TOO SMALL ” THAT’S WHY I HAVE A GIFT FOR YOU  MY FRIEND</pattern><template>Everyone, Agent Maya. Maya, everyone.</template></category><category><pattern>WE HAVE TWENTY LEADERSHIP NAMES</pattern><template>We’ve only eliminated four of them.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HIGH RES VERSION  CAN YOU GET CLOSER THAN THAT</pattern><template>Yeah, well, you can up res this image.</template></category><category><pattern>— MONDAY</pattern><template>— Shh… Thursd… Ammar, which day is it?</template></category><category><pattern>THE ROTORS HAVE BEEN MUFFLED WITH DECIBEL KILLERS</pattern><template>It’s slower than a Black Hawk, lacks the offense and the stability.</template></category><category><pattern>HE READ US ALL A LETTER FROM THE “SHEIK”</pattern><template>A letter?</template></category><category><pattern>DON’T YOU WANNA SEE WHATS IN THE FOLDER</pattern><template>You want family ties, financial networks media sources, disgruntled employees, imminent threats, homeland plots, foreign sales, health status, financial resources, tradecraft, recruiting tactics, anything else?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON’T MIND IF MY FEMALE COLLEAGUE HERE CHECKS OUT YOUR JUNK  DO YOU</pattern><template>No? Good.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M SO SORRY  JOSEPH</pattern><template>Still on tower three.</template></category><category><pattern>I WANT YOU TO UNDERSTAND THAT I KNOW YOU I’VE BEEN FOLLOWING YOU  AND STUDYING YOU  FOR A LONG TIME</pattern><template>I chased you in Lahore.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WHAT DID YOU DO  UM  WHAT DID YOU DO AFTER THE INVASION</pattern><template>Before you went back to Pesh?</template></category><category><pattern>I WILL GIVE YOU A BLANKET AND SOME SOLID FOOD</pattern><template>I know that you know him.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT BIN LADEN  IS THERE</pattern><template>And you’re gonna kill him for me.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE MOMENT  PLEASE</pattern><template>Sir, the agency expert gave visual confirmation.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M ABOUT TO GO LOOK THE PRESIDENT IN THE EYE</pattern><template>And what I’d like to know, no fucking bullshit, is where everyone stands on this thing.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  AND WHAT ARE YOU BASING THIS ON</pattern><template>We have no intercepts about Abu Ahmed dying.  We just have a detainee, who said he buried a guy, who looked like Abu Ahmed.</template></category><category><pattern>THE JORDANS HAVE WORKED HIM FOR A YEAR  DINNERS  MONEY  THEY CONVINCED HIM… IT’S HIS PATRIOTIC DUTY TO TURN ON AL QAEDA  AND GET RICH DOING IT</pattern><template>— Yeah, well, so the Jords say.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  YOU CERTAINLY HAVE A FLAIR FOR IT</pattern><template>No?</template></category><category><pattern>BASICALLY  WE AGREE WITH YOU</pattern><template>The house screams security.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M VIRTUALLY CERTAIN THERE’S SOME HIGH VALUE TARGET THERE  I’M JUST NOT SURE IT’S BIN LADEN</pattern><template>Well, this is a little bit of a cluster fuck, isn’t it?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT MEANS FARAJ THINKS ABU AHMED’S JUST AS IMPORTANT TO PROTECT AS BIN LADEN</pattern><template>— That confirms my lead.</template></category><category><pattern>I’M SORRY BUT THAT’S NOT NORMAL GUY BEHAVIOR  THAT’S TRADECRAFT</pattern><template>Or maybe he just doesn’t like his Mum.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHEN HE WANTS TO MAKE A CALL  HE LEAVES THE HOUSE  WALKS A FEW BLOCKS  THEN SWITCHES ON THE PHONE</pattern><template>We need to keep canvassing the neighborhood until we find him.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST GIVE ME HIS E MAIL  AND I WILL—I WILL GIVE YOU A BLANKET</pattern><template>I will give you a blanket and some solid food.</template></category><category><pattern>FAMILY LIVES IN KUWAIT  WE’VE BEEN LISTENING IN ON THEIR CALLS</pattern><template>Wasn’t it… like, eight brothers and a million cousins that we know about?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS MISSION IS STILL A “GO”  I REPEAT  WE ARE A “GO”    ALPHA TEAM IS IN THE ANIMAL PEN  MAKING ENTRY FOR AC1   NO ROPES  WHEELS DOWN</pattern><template>Prayer room’s clear.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH DON’T FUCK AROUND ON THIS ONE  DUDE</pattern><template>You’re just fuckin’ around, ’cause you see I’m up by two games.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS ‘07  AND IT WASN’T BIN LADEN  AND WE LOST A COUPLE OF GUYS</pattern><template>Totally understand.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD</pattern><template>Morning, George.</template></category><category><pattern>AFTER JOHN SPEAKS  WE’LL COVER THE BASICS  HAVE HIS BIRTHDAY CAKE  THEN WE’LL GET INTO THE NITTY–GRITTY</pattern><template>Is that order okay? Or d—do you wanna introduce everyone?</template></category><category><pattern>SPEED YELLOW  GO BIG OR GO HOME  HUH</pattern><template>Nice choice.</template></category><category><pattern>WITH YOUR DIP AND YOUR VELCRO AND ALL YOUR GEAR BULLSHIT</pattern><template>I wanted to drop a bomb.</template></category><category><pattern>LIVING IN A CITY WITH MULTIPLE POINTS OF EGRESS AND ENTRY  ACCESS TO COMMUNICATIONS  SO THAT HE CAN KEEP IN TOUCH WITH THE ORGANIZATION</pattern><template>You can’t run a global network of interconnected cells from a cave.</template></category><category><pattern>— YOU GET THE POINT</pattern><template>If you can’t prove it’s bin Laden, at least prove it’s not someone else.</template></category></AIML>