<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><AIML><category><pattern>SHE KINDA GOES FOR  LIKE  BAD BOYS</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>MOUNTAIN DEW</pattern><template>Yeah, Code Red. And here is some Gold Grams.</template></category><category><pattern>THE BEST THING IS NO MORE FLUSHING  EPIC</pattern><template>And worst thing?</template></category><category><pattern>WHO CARES</pattern><template>The best thing is no more flushing, epic.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I  THINK I PULLED SOMETHING</pattern><template>You think there's two of us smart enough to come home with a car like that?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS SO SURREAL  I MEAN  YOU PROBABLY GET THIS ALL THE TIME WELL  MAYBE NOT LATELY  BUT I'M SUCH A HUGE FAN OF YOURS</pattern><template>I've seen everyone of your movies a million times.</template></category><category><pattern>RULE NO  22  / I    WHEN IN DOUBT  KNOW YOUR WAY OUT   / I    THEY'RE SISTERS</pattern><template>The little one's been bit, and, you know, try not to freak her out.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HESITATED</pattern><template>Would it be better to be smart, or lucky?</template></category><category><pattern>LOSING BOB</pattern><template>That's his puppy.</template></category><category><pattern>OH GOD</pattern><template>Words cannot express..</template></category><category><pattern>COME GET A PIECE OF TALLAHASSEE</pattern><template>Anybody hungry?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST HUMOR HIM  TRUST ME</pattern><template>Hold on.</template></category><category><pattern>DIBS ON THE BED</pattern><template>Too soft for me anyway.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL GET HIM</pattern><template>Watch this.</template></category><category><pattern>LADIES AND GENTLEMEN  WELCOME TO LA MENZION DE MURRAY</pattern><template>Oh, Bill Murray   God, no way.</template></category><category><pattern>FAKE</pattern><template>First kiss.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK</pattern><template>We better start working on our apology.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU COMING</pattern><template>Yes.. Yeah, one second.</template></category><category><pattern>LITTLE ROCK COME HERE</pattern><template>Why do I get stuck with her?</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T SWING  DON'T SWING</pattern><template>Swing!</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN DO WHAT YOU WANT WITH A MAN  BUT DO NOT FUCK WITH HIS CADILLAC</pattern><template>Hey there's a nice minivan.</template></category><category><pattern>HOLD ON</pattern><template>Who wants to go first?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S ADORABLE</pattern><template>I'm just saying we should find a place to crash.</template></category><category><pattern>FUCK ME</pattern><template>I know Let me be the mature one.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  HOW WAS IT</pattern><template>He's a zombie   That's a tough break.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST KISS</pattern><template>Scotty Lynch   Did you guys.. use tongue?</template></category><category><pattern>WHICH REMINDS ME  I NEVER HAD HEADACHES LIKE THIS 'TIL YOUR ASS CAME ON BOARD</pattern><template>I mean do what you want with a man, but do not fuck with his Cadillac.</template></category><category><pattern>BYE HOPE YOU MAKE YOUR FLIGHT</pattern><template>I know it's around here somewhere, she's on a plane, that's the beauty of it.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  / I    LOOK AT THIS FUCKING CLOWN   / I    OF COURSE  IT HAD TO BE A CLOWN   / I    NO  IT HAD TO BE A CLOWN   / I    AND IT HAD TO BE WICHITA FOR ME TO FINALLY UNDERSTAND  / I    THAT SOME RULES ARE MADE TO BE BROKEN   / I    TIME TO NUT UP OR SHUT UP   / I    FUCK THIS CLOWN   / I    THANKS</pattern><template>Wichita   Christa.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW LET ME BE THE MATURE ONE</pattern><template>So Where are you guys headed.</template></category><category><pattern>I COULD TELL SHE KNEW WHAT I WAS FEELING   / I    WE ARE ALL ORPHANS IN ZOMBIELAND   / I  I KNOW THIS PACIFIC PLAYLAND THING IS NUTS  BUT  IT'S BEEN SO LONG SINCE SHE GOT TO BE A KID</pattern><template>It's tough growing up in Zombieland.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S HIS PUPPY</pattern><template>I tell you, I never thought I could love anything like Bob The day he was born I just lost my mind.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH PROBLEMS</pattern><template>Oh, they stole my Hummer ,  We have trust issues .</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR</pattern><template>It's your gal.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT AS FUN AS I REMEMBER</pattern><template>Shoot the control box.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT FACE  THAT'S ME REALIZING THAT THOSE SMART GIRLS  / I    IN THAT BIG BLACK TRUCK   / I    AND THAT BIG GUY IN THAT SNAKESKIN JACKET  / I    THEY WERE THE CLOSEST TO SOMETHING I HAD ALWAYS WANTED  BUT NEVER REALLY HAD   / I    A FAMILY   / I    I TRUSTED THEM AND THEY TRUSTED ME   / I    RULE NO  32 ENJOY THE LITTLE THINGS  / I    TALLAHASSEE GOT HIS TWINKIE  / I    AND EVEN THOUGH LIFE WILL NEVER BE SIMPLE OR INNOCENT AGAIN   / I    AS HE SAVORED THAT SPONGY YELLOW LOG OF CREAM   / I    WE HAD HOPE  WE HAD EACH OTHER   / I    AND WITHOUT OTHER PEOPLE  YOU MIGHT SWELL BE A ZOMBIE   / I    THANK YOU SO MUCH   YOU HAD US GOING</pattern><template>So until next time remember:  / i    Cardio, seat belts  / i    and this really has nothing to do with anything, but a little sunscreen never hurt anybody.  / i</template></category><category><pattern>FINALLY HE GOT TO FIRST BASE</pattern><template>Not bad for that scrawny little spit fuck.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY NOBODY</pattern><template>Look!</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS ENGAGED ONCE  BUT I'M SINGLE NOW</pattern><template>Bye Hope you make your flight.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S EASY</pattern><template>Losing Bob.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU DOING</pattern><template>Look, stay back 406, ok? I don't wanna hurt you, but..</template></category><category><pattern>TALLAHASSEE FIRMLY BELIEVES THAT YOU HAVE TO BLOW OFF STEAM IN ZOMBIELAND   / I    OR ELSE YOU LOSE WHAT'S LEFT OF YOUR MIND   / I    WELL  IF IT MAKES HIM HAPPY AND KEEPS HIM FROM USING THAT CROWBAR ON ME   / I    THEN I SAY  HEY  GO WASTE SHIT    / I    I WANT MY CADDIE BACK</pattern><template>Stupid little bitches.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE WE GO</pattern><template>Wichita! Little Rock!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  A FORMER GREENSKEEPER ABOUT TO BECOME THE MASTER CHAMPION     THAT'S WHY WE DO IT</pattern><template>I love you Bill, I love you.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH ZOMBIES HEAD IS THE CAP</pattern><template>Wait are you one of these guys that tries to, like, wonder if everybody else has a story?</template></category><category><pattern>RIGHT TWO GRAVES  ONE FOR THE BIG CHICK  ONE FOR THE LITTLE CHICK</pattern><template>You are scary happy.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  NO  I DON'T</pattern><template>Yeah I shave every mooring but sometimes   Since this is a freeway. You can get it up to 65, but you don't wanna go more than 75.</template></category><category><pattern>IZ WAS GIRLS CHOICE</pattern><template>Those bitches!</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF YOU GOT IT  SUGARLESS GUM</pattern><template>What the fuck..</template></category><category><pattern>HERE HERE YOU GO</pattern><template>Mountain Dew?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHERE I'M HEADED AMIGO</pattern><template>Whatever.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEN I THOUGHT  LIKE  MAYBE HE WAS RUNNING FROM SOMEONE  OR AFTER THEM</pattern><template>The last time I saw him he was still out there going crazy.</template></category><category><pattern>TOTALLY ZOMBIE FREE</pattern><template>Only place west of Waco.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THEY STOLE MY HUMMER    WE HAVE TRUST ISSUES</pattern><template>Now get over it, okay, we can't just fucking drive down the road playing I spy, or some shit for two hours, like four normal ass Americans?</template></category><category><pattern>AND INSTEAD  THIS</pattern><template>I mean it makes you..</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE YOU YOU SPONGY YELLOW DELICIOUS BASTARDS</pattern><template>Where are you?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK SO</pattern><template>I mean you got the guts of a guppy, but I could hit that.</template></category><category><pattern>COLUMBUS</pattern><template>Tallahassee.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE  I TOLD YOU WE SHOULD'VE GONE TO RUSSEL CROWE'S  NO ONE LISTENS TO ME</pattern><template>Hello, inside voices, okay?</template></category><category><pattern>BUT</pattern><template>Zombie kill of the week.. no sir.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY</pattern><template>I didn't realize it was..</template></category><category><pattern>SCOTTY LYNCH   DID YOU GUYS   USE TONGUE</pattern><template>Maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>FRESH</pattern><template>Well this Twinkie thing, it ain't over yet.</template></category><category><pattern>HELP ME WITH THE BOOTS</pattern><template>Ok, I'll get 'em myself.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD I AM SO FUCKING SORRY</pattern><template>You see, you just can't trust anyone.  / i    the first time I let a girl into my life and she tries to eat me.  / i  Listen to me, 406 if you're in there, you're just sick, ok?</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT FUCKING WICHITA</pattern><template>Wish granted. She spent the last 24 hours fucking us both.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOKS LIKE THEY HOOFED IT</pattern><template>Probably headed west.</template></category><category><pattern>I KIND OF PICTURED TOM CRUISE LIVING SOMEWHERE NICER</pattern><template>B..lister compared to who I got in mind folks.</template></category><category><pattern>SO COLUMBUS IS THE SCARED ONE</pattern><template>Yeah, he's like a little bunny.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR</pattern><template>Nothing I just.. I have this list.</template></category><category><pattern>IT AIN'T BOB MARLEY</pattern><template>This place is incredible.</template></category><category><pattern>HERE'S THE DEAL  COLUMBUS</pattern><template>I'm not easy to get along with and I'm sensing you're a bit of a bitch, So I give this relationship to.. about Texarkana.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  IT'S WORSE</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT EASY TO GET ALONG WITH AND I'M SENSING YOU'RE A BIT OF A BITCH  SO I GIVE THIS RELATIONSHIP TO   ABOUT TEXARKANA</pattern><template>Really? Yeah. Well take me as far as Texarkana.</template></category><category><pattern>LIGHT 'EM UP MURRAY</pattern><template>See you on the other side Pete.</template></category><category><pattern>AND LORD WILLIN'  A GD TWINKIE</pattern><template>Gotta enjoy the little things.</template></category><category><pattern>SO DO YOU NEVER STRAP IN OR JUST  WHEN ON ROAD TRIPS</pattern><template>It's just, you know, there's zombies everywhere. I think the least of my worries is..</template></category><category><pattern>I REALLY  REALLY WANNA IMPRESS WICHITA   / I    BUT IT WOULD BE A DIRECT VIOLATION OF RULE 17  MAYBE THE MOST IMPORTANT OF ALL   / I    DON'T BE HERO   / I    WHY DON'T YOU TAKE THIS ONE</pattern><template>Don't mind if I do.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE OKAY</pattern><template>The hell I am.</template></category><category><pattern>GO</pattern><template>Not as fun as I remember.</template></category><category><pattern>MY MAMA ALWAYS TOLD ME  SOMEDAY I'LL BE GOOD AT SOMETHING</pattern><template>Who'd have guessed that something'd be zombie killin'.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THIS IS SO EXCITING  YOU'RE ABOUT TO LEARN WHO YOU'RE GONNA CALL</pattern><template>Ghostbusters.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SURE   YOU GET 45% POWER</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T LET THEM CATCH YOU WITH YOUR PANTS DOWN  RULE NO  3:  / I    BEWARE OF BATHROOMS   / I    AS ZOMBIES BEGAN TO OUTNUMBER HUMANS   / I    THAT'S WHEN YOU HAD TO CUT ALL EMOTIONAL TIES   / I    IF THE GIRLS IN YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD ARE NOW FUCKED UP LITTLE MONSTERS    / I    WELL MAYBE IT'S TIME TO STOP DRIVING CARPOOL    / I    YOU HAD TO FOCUS ON YOUR OWN SURVIVAL   / I    WHICH LEADS TO RULE NO  4   / I    PRETTY BASIC:  / I    FASTEN YOUR SEAT BELTS   / I    IT'S GONNA BE A BUMPY RIDE   / I    THAT GUY DOWN THERE IS ME   / I    I'M IN GARLIND  TEXAS  AND IT MAY LOOK LIKE ZOMBIES DESTROYED IT  BUT THAT'S ACTUALLY JUST GARLIND   / I</pattern><template>Months since patient zero took  / i    a bite of a contaminated burger at a Gas 'N Gulp.  / i    Just two months and i might be the last non cannibal freak in the country.  / i    I may seem like an unlikely survivor with all my phobias and irritable bowel syndrome.  / i    But I had the advantage of never having any friends or any close family.  / i    I survive, because I play it safe and follow the rules.  / i    My rules.  / i  Rule No. 1 Cardio Shit Rule No. 1 Cardio Of course Rule No. 4 Seatbelts Motherfucker Rule No. 2 Double tap   On the bright side, I found a place to go number two.  / i    Another rule to surviving Zombieland: Travel light.  / i    And I don't mean just luggage.  / i    I've always been kind of a loner.  / i    I avoided people like they were zombies even before they were zombies.  / i    Now that they are all zombies,  / i    I kind of miss people.  / i    So I'm on my from my college dorm in Austin, Texas to Columbus, Ohio.  / i    Where I'm hoping my parents are still alive.  / i    Even though we were never really close.  / i    It would just be nice to see a familiar face,  / i    or any face, that hasn't blood dripping from it's lips and flesh between it's teeth.  / i  Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>BUMMER</pattern><template>Now step away from the vehicle.</template></category><category><pattern>IT IS PRETTY CATCHY</pattern><template>Help me with the boots, come on.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  TALLAHASSE  YOU WANNA STICK TOGETHER</pattern><template>At least for a while?</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE YOUR TIME</pattern><template>You know they say  He who seeks revenge should remember to dig two graves .</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW IT'S AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE  SHE'S ON A PLANE  THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF IT</pattern><template>Let me call you back.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'LL SEE</pattern><template>Hey, here's a big BM.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T EVEN TELL YOU THE WORST PART</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>WOW  THESE FELLAS REALLY LET THEMSELVES GO</pattern><template>And they're so fat.</template></category><category><pattern>RULE 2 DOUBLE STRIKE   THAT WAS MY FIRST BRUSH WITH THE PLAGUE OF THE 21ST CENTURY  / I    REMEMBER MAD COW DISEASE   / I    WELL  MAD COW BECAME MAD PERSON BECAME MAD ZOMBIE   / I    IT'S A FAST ACTING VIRUS THAT LEFT YOU WITH A SWOLLEN BRAIN  A RAGING FEVER THAT MADE YOU HATEFUL  VIOLENT   / I</pattern><template>and gave you a really, really bad case of the munchies.  / i    Alright, you steer, I'll push.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT THE FUCK</pattern><template>Wait, why are you guys doing this?</template></category><category><pattern>SO DO YOU HAVE ANY REGRETS</pattern><template>Garfield , maybe.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU EVER READ THAT BOOK  SHE'S JUST NOT THAT INTO YOU</pattern><template>You can't make yourself too available.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL DO IT</pattern><template>I love you.</template></category><category><pattern>OW  THAT'S STILL TENDER</pattern><template>You think you might pull through?</template></category><category><pattern>OH YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT HOME</pattern><template>For me home, was a puppy named Buck, cutest dog ever.</template></category><category><pattern>SIX PEOPLE LEFT IN THE WORLD  ONE OF THEM IS BILL FUCKING MURRAY</pattern><template>I know that's not your middle name. I've been watching you since i was like.. since I could masturbate, not that they're connected.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY BUT WHAT THE HELL ARE WE DOING</pattern><template>Just humor him, trust me.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST PLAYED NINE HOLES AT THE RIVIERA  JUST WALKED ON  NOBODY THERE</pattern><template>Goddamn it, Bill fucking Murray.</template></category><category><pattern>HONK IT</pattern><template>Oh, there's your sister, that's my gun.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  ROB CURTIS IS GEARING UP FOR FRIDAY</pattern><template>Who cares.</template></category><category><pattern>AND SHE KNOWS  WE'RE JUST LOOKING FOR A WAY OUT</pattern><template>No, no, no, she's just a little girl.</template></category><category><pattern>40  60  80  400  THAT'S IT  THAT'S THE WHOLE REGISTER</pattern><template>You made someone very happy.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I WAS WALKING HOME FROM THE BAR  TALKING ON MY PHONE  AND THEN   HE JUST CAME SPRINTING TOWARDS ME</pattern><template>I mean not running, sprinting.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE GONNA RISK OUR LIVES FOR A TWINKIE</pattern><template>There is a box of Twinkies in that grocery store, not just any box of Twinkies, The last box of Twinkies that anyone will enjoy in the whole universe.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN YOU GOT THE GUTS OF A GUPPY  BUT I COULD HIT THAT</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>ON BEHALF OF ALL THE EIGHT GRADE GIRLS  I WOULD LIKE YOU TO MAKE IT UP TO YOU</pattern><template>Relax, Scotty's old news.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THOSE VIOLENT VIDEO GAMES</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE A LITTLE HUNCH</pattern><template>Where are you you spongy yellow delicious bastards?</template></category><category><pattern>IT 1997   GOR GORGEOUS    I NEVER TOOK FRENCH</pattern><template>Gorgeus day what the hell?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY TALLAHASSEE  WICHITA WHY DON'T YOU TAKE THAT WAY</pattern><template>Little Rock come here.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE  YOU CAN TAKE THAT TRUCK</pattern><template>Well, I, hope you find whoever it is you're looking for.</template></category><category><pattern>AVOID THE VANITY MIRROR</pattern><template>Relax ok, I just passed for a zombie.</template></category><category><pattern>THE POINT IS  I'M HERE FOR YOU</pattern><template>Ok?</template></category><category><pattern>WICHITA   CHRISTA</pattern><template>Ok, we should probably head out, now.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON</pattern><template>On the count of three.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I WILL NOT STAND FOR THIS  YOU KNOW WHAT</pattern><template>On behalf of all the eight grade girls, I would like you to make it up to you.</template></category><category><pattern>GIVE HIM THE GUN</pattern><template>Wait, wait..</template></category><category><pattern>JUST  JUST GIVE ME YOUR NUMBER</pattern><template>I'll find it.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S COLOGNE</pattern><template>I'm thinking:  Lanco Magnifique    Why don't you speak up, they might've missed it in Santa fe.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR THE FIRST TIME IN A LONG TIME   / I    WE WERE HAVING FUN   / I    SO EVEN THOUGH IT RAN COUNTER TO OUR SURVIVAL STRATEGIES   / I    WE DECIDED TO STAY TOGETHER AS FAR AS PACIFIC PLAYLAND   / I    YOU KNOW I THINK SLEEP DEPRIVATION IS LIKE THE NUMBER ONE HEALTH PROBLEM IN AMERICA</pattern><template>No, I think it moth be number two.</template></category><category><pattern>SHUT UP</pattern><template>No, no, I was headed east, she west.</template></category><category><pattern>B  LISTER COMPARED TO WHO I GOT IN MIND FOLKS</pattern><template>We are going to the Tipi Top of the A list.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY</pattern><template>He had my personality, my laugh, my appetite,   Laugh? And that's when it hit me. i felt so ashamed that it had taken me this long.  / i    Me with the best card in the business to realize I wasn't the only one running from something.  / i</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE RIGHT  THAT'S THE WORST PART</pattern><template>Sorry, I'm just so scared.</template></category><category><pattern>BILL MURRAY  YOU'RE A ZOMBIE</pattern><template>You're not a zombie, you're talking.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN NOT RUNNING  SPRINTING</pattern><template>And then I thought, like, maybe he was running from someone, or after them.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  TALLAHASSEE AND COLUMBUS ARE BOTH</pattern><template>East.</template></category><category><pattern>EAST</pattern><template>So?</template></category><category><pattern>35 FEET LONG  WEIGHING APPROXIMATELY 600 POUNDS     THAT'S A BIG TWINKIE    YOUR SISTER'S SINGLE  RIGHT  THERE'S NOTHING LONG DISTANCE OR ANYTHING</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'M NOT GOING TO PLAY WITH YOU AT PACIFIC PLAYLAND</pattern><template>Don't worry he grows on you.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW STEP AWAY FROM THE VEHICLE</pattern><template>You get to ride shotgun   I kinda like this girl.  / i    She's not your typical hot, stuck up bitch.  / i    Even before Zombieland, Wichita was running the table on guys like us.  / i    What are you looking for?</template></category><category><pattern>OK  I'LL GET 'EM MYSELF</pattern><template>Bill Murray, you're a zombie?</template></category><category><pattern>NICE</pattern><template>Doesn't that feel good.</template></category><category><pattern>TIME TO NUT UP OR SHUT UP</pattern><template>Holy shit.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  OK   STOP</pattern><template>What are you doing?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEONE'S EAR IS IN DANGER OF HAVING HAIR BRUSHED OVER IT  / I    I'LL CATCH UP</pattern><template>Rule No. 22  / i    When in doubt, know your way out.  / i    They're sisters.</template></category><category><pattern>NO ONE BACK THERE WITH MY DUFFEL BAG</pattern><template>What's your name?</template></category><category><pattern>CAUSE I GOT NOTHING ELSE TO DO</pattern><template>I was engaged once, but I'm single now.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SUITS MY LIFESTYLE  YOU KNOW I LIKE TO GET OUT AND DO STUFF</pattern><template>Just played nine holes at the Riviera, just walked on, nobody there.</template></category><category><pattern>DO YOU THINK YOU CAN  MAYBE  JUST PICK OUT THE BUCKSHOT AND JUST KIND OF EAT AROUND IT</pattern><template>No!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  HURRY</pattern><template>Get in!</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE NO PENGUINS ON THE NORTH POLE</pattern><template>You wanna feel how hard I can punch?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE CLOWNS WITH RED NOSES  OR LIKE THE RAGS THEY USE TO WIPE DOWN TABLES WHEN YOU FINISH EATING  LIKE A CHAIN RESTAURANT</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE YOU</pattern><template>False advertising!</template></category><category><pattern>HAD MY FIRST SCHOOL DANCE</pattern><template>I was Sadie Hawkins..</template></category><category><pattern>WE ARE GOING TO THE TIPI TOP OF THE A LIST</pattern><template>Who?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS NEVER A VERY GOOD PRACTICAL JOKER</pattern><template>So do you have any regrets?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WEREN'T STORMING' THE TRENCHES BEFORE I CAME ALONG</pattern><template>That's why I don't let people close, you only get burned.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL I COULD THINK OF WAS  WHAT ARE THE ODDS     / I    ANOTHER MARRIAGEABLE WOMAN TO BRING HOME TO THE FOLKS   / I    COME QUICK</pattern><template>Someone's ear is in danger of having hair brushed over it  / i    I'll catch up.</template></category><category><pattern>THE ZIPLOCK BAG KEEP'S 'EM CRISP</pattern><template>So.. tell me what happened?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S LIKE THE RIGHT IND OF SCARED  THAT'S REASONABLE SCARED  YOU KNOW I GET SCARED FOR THINGS THAT LIKE  DON'T MAKE SENSE AT ALL</pattern><template>like clowns with red noses, or like the rags they use to wipe down tables when you finish eating, like a chain restaurant.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD LUCK NOW PETUNIA</pattern><template>Ok, let me begin my three part apology by saying that I think you're a wonderful human with great potential..</template></category><category><pattern>IT DOESN'T SEEM TO END</pattern><template>Hey come here.</template></category><category><pattern>TALLAHASSEE NICE OVER HERE</pattern><template>Come on, come on you ugly bastards.</template></category><category><pattern>FYI: I BEAT WHOLESALE ASS FOR A LOT LESS THAN THAT</pattern><template>I'm sure   You get 45% power.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S OKAY  IT'S OKAY  I GOT HIM</pattern><template>Is that how you say hello where you come from?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TOO SOON</pattern><template>Do you think you can, maybe, just pick out the Buckshot and just kind of eat around it?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU OWE ME</pattern><template>You're incredible.</template></category><category><pattern>PACIFIC PLAY LAND    THE AMUSEMENT PARK</pattern><template>Wait, outside LA?</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  WHY DON'T WE JUST FORGET ABOUT THOSE GIRLS AND HEAD HOME</pattern><template>Oh you wanna talk about home.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WE TOOK SHELTER IN THE BACK OF THE TRUCK</pattern><template>Was full of undelivered packages.</template></category><category><pattern>NO TWINKIES</pattern><template>Shit Bob.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  WHATEVER YOU HAVE WAITIN' FOR YOU IN COLUMBUS  I'LL PROMISE IT AIN'T ANY PRETTIER THAN OUR FRIEND HERE ENJOYING HER MAN WHICH</pattern><template>Tallahassee had a sick sense of humor when it came to zombies  / i    zombies aren't the most lovable creatures, but he really hated them.  / I    In fact the only thing he was more obsessed with, than killing zombies,  / i    was finding a Twinkie.  / i    Something about a Twinkie reminded him of a time not so long ago  / i    When things were simple and not so fucking psychotic.  / i    It was like if he got a taste of that comforting childhood treat,  / i    the world would become innocent again and everything would return to normal.  / i    Pretty prospecting.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS  I'VE BEEN LOOKING ALL OVER FOR IT</pattern><template>Your ring?</template></category><category><pattern>YES</pattern><template>Oh Free parking, which coincidentally is the best thing about Zombieland.</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT BOB</pattern><template>See? I told you we should've gone to Russel Crowe's. No one listens to me.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LAST TIME I SAW HIM HE WAS STILL OUT THERE GOING CRAZY</pattern><template>Drugs maybe..</template></category><category><pattern>OH  ANACONDA</pattern><template>First tattoo, a purpoise.</template></category><category><pattern>IT MAKES YOU SICK</pattern><template>Kind'a makes you sad, it makes you, makes you think if you could go back, to the way things were right now, you know, you'd be out in the back yard, you know, try to catch fireflies.</template></category><category><pattern>AND GAVE YOU A REALLY  REALLY BAD CASE OF THE MUNCHIES   / I    ALRIGHT  YOU STEER  I'LL PUSH</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>WORDS CANNOT EXPRESS</pattern><template>It's too soon.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  I  HOPE YOU FIND WHOEVER IT IS YOU'RE LOOKING FOR</pattern><template>And don't let go, once you do.</template></category><category><pattern>WILLIE NELSON</pattern><template>Yeah, no, I don't.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I DON'T THINK SHE HAS LONG</pattern><template>I know, I know.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THEY SAY  HE WHO SEEKS REVENGE SHOULD REMEMBER TO DIG TWO GRAVES</pattern><template>Right two graves. One for the big chick, one for the little chick.</template></category><category><pattern>SHIT  I'M OUT OF SHELLS</pattern><template>Here we go.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT GREAT AT FAREWELLS SO   THAT'LL DO PIG</pattern><template>That's the worst goodbye I have ever heard and you stole it from a movie.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T CROSS THE STREAMS</pattern><template>35 feet long, weighing approximately 600 pounds     That's a big Twinkie    Your sister's single, right? There's nothing long distance or anything.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I'VE ACTUALLY BEEN MEANING TO ASK YOU  DID YOU HEAR ANYTHING ABOUT COLUMBUS  OHIO</pattern><template>You've heard of the quiet game?</template></category><category><pattern>OPEN SESAME</pattern><template>This is the problem with getting attached to someone.  / i    When they leave you just feel lost.  / i    Having Tallahassee around didn't comfort me, it just made me feel more alone.  / i    Hey, you weren't exactly gonna score anyway.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  IF WERE BEING BACK I'M ABOUT   I JUST TAKE THE BROWNS TO THE SUPERBOWL</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS GUY HAS A DIRECT LINE TO MY FUNNY BONE  I MEAN EVERY</pattern><template>Boy, who's Bill Murray?</template></category><category><pattern>HEY COME HERE</pattern><template>He has his own movie theatre?</template></category><category><pattern>I MADE A PROMISE WE ALREADY SAID GOODBYE  BUT WE DIDN'T HAVE A GUN</pattern><template>We don't know that there's definitely no cure, right, I mean..</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  HERE'S A BIG BM</pattern><template>It ain't Bob Marley.</template></category><category><pattern>PROBABLY HEADED WEST</pattern><template>Just drive slow, keep your eyes peeled.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WASN'T JUST BECAUSE I HAD NOWHERE ELSE TO GO   / I    IT WAS CAUSE IN THAT MOMENT IT BECAME CLEAR   / I    WHEREVER THIS GIRL WAS  / I     THAT'S WHERE I WANTED TO BE    / I    MAN WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO PULL OVER SOON</pattern><template>I'm feeling cooped up.</template></category><category><pattern>SHOOT THE CONTROL BOX</pattern><template>Columbus.</template></category><category><pattern>BUDDY OF MINE  MAKE UP GUY  SHOWED HOW TO DO THIS</pattern><template>Corn starch, you know some berries, a little liquish for the ladies.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST FOR A WHILE</pattern><template>Here's the deal, Columbus.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE THE ONE THAT GAVE HER THE GUN</pattern><template>Those guys were dumb.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE COLUMBUS</pattern><template>I'm sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  SHIT</pattern><template>Oh my God I am so fucking sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT SAY S H O W E R  OKAY</pattern><template>Let's just get where we're going.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT A ZOMBIE  YOU'RE TALKING</pattern><template>You're okay.</template></category><category><pattern>TOMORROW MAYBE  SKINNY DIPPING IN THE YELLOWSTONE RIVER  SWING FROM THE CHANDELIERS IN THE PLAYBOY MANSION  BUT TODAY  A VORTEX SIX FUCKING LITER V8  A BOX FULL OF</pattern><template>and Lord willin', a GD Twinkie.</template></category><category><pattern>AT LEAST UNTIL WE KNOW WE ARE ALONE</pattern><template>Hey Tallahassee, Wichita why don't you take that way.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  ONE FOR ME  ONE AND DONE  I ALWAYS SAY   I SAID THAT ONCE</pattern><template>You know, Tallahassee and Columbus are both..</template></category><category><pattern>NO</pattern><template>That face. That's me realizing that those smart girls  / i    in that big black truck   / i    and that big guy in that snakeskin jacket  / i    they were the closest to something i had always wanted, but never really had.  / i    A family.  / i    I trusted them and they trusted me.  / i    Rule No. 32 Enjoy the little things  / i    Tallahassee got his Twinkie  / i    and even though life will never be simple or innocent again,  / i    as he savored that spongy yellow log of cream,  / i    we had hope, we had each other.  / i    And without other people, you might swell be a zombie.  / i    Thank you so much   You had us going.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU THINK WE'RE DOING IN THE 90210 SALLY</pattern><template>I kind of pictured Tom Cruise living somewhere nicer.</template></category><category><pattern>GORGEUS DAY WHAT THE HELL</pattern><template>It's a 97?</template></category><category><pattern>NUMBER TWO</pattern><template>That's adorable.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  NO  SHE'S JUST A LITTLE GIRL</pattern><template>Don 't talk about me like I'm not here.</template></category><category><pattern>OK</pattern><template>And as long as you're by my side, I am not leaving this apartment   Do you mind if I just close my eyes for a minute?</template></category><category><pattern>RELAX  SCOTTY'S OLD NEWS</pattern><template>I don't even know your name, but this is actually really nice.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  THERE'S YOUR SISTER  THAT'S MY GUN</pattern><template>Hello.</template></category><category><pattern>OH NO</pattern><template>Frightening, as Anaconda Woodshop, which doesn't really count as a class anyway.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  OF COURSE</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MAKE ME DRINK ALONE</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO</pattern><template>Bummer.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU BILL  I LOVE YOU</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW</pattern><template>No, I will not stand for this, you know what?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  STAY BACK 406  OK  I DON'T WANNA HURT YOU  BUT</pattern><template>Oh, shit.</template></category><category><pattern>MEXICO  YOU KNOW WHAT THEY CALL TWINKIES IN MEXICO  LOS SUBMERINOS</pattern><template>That's where I'm headed amigo.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD  GOOD</pattern><template>And if she had, like, a type   if you can have a type   what would that be?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>Look, whatever you have waitin' for you in Columbus, I'll promise it ain't any prettier than our friend here enjoying her man which.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MIGHT WANNA BUCKLE UP  YOU KNOW  FOR SAFETY</pattern><template>I can tell already, you are gonna get on my nerves.</template></category><category><pattern>HE WAS HOMELESS AND   SICK</pattern><template>And I was walking home from the bar  talking on my phone, and then.. he just came sprinting towards me.</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY  RIGHT</pattern><template>So..</template></category><category><pattern>GET IN</pattern><template>Come on, come on!</template></category><category><pattern>LOVE YOU TOO</pattern><template>You need some help?</template></category><category><pattern>OUT WEST WE HEAR IT'S BACK EAST  BACK EAST THEY HEAR IT'S OUT WEST</pattern><template>It's all just nonsense.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T WORRY HE GROWS ON YOU</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK THERE'S TWO OF US SMART ENOUGH TO COME HOME WITH A CAR LIKE THAT</pattern><template>You hesitated.</template></category><category><pattern>ONE  TWO  THREE</pattern><template>Are you okay? Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>MY WHOLE LIFE  ALL I'D EVER WANTED WAS TO FIND A GIRL   / I    AND FALL IN LOVE</pattern><template>Bring her home to meet the folks.  / i    Then again, since my folks are a couple of paranoid shut ins like me,  / i    maybe this girl could bring me home to her folks.  / i    And the I'd finally be a member of a cool functional family.  / i  Please! Anyone home?</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE</pattern><template>At the Hollywood bowl.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S COOL</pattern><template>So Columbus is the scared one?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH</pattern><template>Was that a good year?</template></category><category><pattern>SNOWBALLS</pattern><template>Where's the fucking twinkies?</template></category><category><pattern>COLUMBUS  YOU</pattern><template>Tallahassee.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL GIVE YOU A REWARD   DO NOT BE SILLY</pattern><template>Three thousand dollars.</template></category><category><pattern>SEE YOU ON THE OTHER SIDE PETE</pattern><template>You're so disgusting.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE ARE NO ZOMBIES THERE   YEAH  WE HEARD</pattern><template>You know what, I may not shoot you, but you still royally piss me off.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL THIS TWINKIE THING  IT AIN'T OVER YET</pattern><template>Hey! If were being back I'm about.. I just take the browns to the Superbowl.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW HONK YOUR HORN</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>DOESN'T THAT FEEL GOOD</pattern><template>Sometimes Tallahassee's right. You gotta enjoy the little things.  / i    Even if that means destroying a whole lot of little things.  / i    What smells like perfume?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS SADIE HAWKINS</pattern><template>girls choice.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH THAT'S TRUE</pattern><template>..seat belts.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S WORTH MORE THAN MY CAR</pattern><template>Just, just give me your number.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING AFTER WICHITA</pattern><template>You ever read that book  She's just not that into you ?</template></category><category><pattern>THE LAST TIME YOU WENT TWENTY TOES  THE PERCY IN THE PLAYPEN  WALLPAPERED THE CLOSET  PASSED THE GRAVY  WENT HEELS TO JESUS</pattern><template>Oh, made love.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME SEE</pattern><template>Enough for us to get to California.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU AND ME</pattern><template>You have just survived the zombie apocalypse and drove halfway across the country.</template></category><category><pattern>TAKE AWAY A MAN'S SON  YOU'VE TRULY GIVEN HIM NOTHING LEFT TO LOSE   / I    I HAVEN'T CRIED LIKE THAT SINCE TITANIC</pattern><template>A hint?</template></category><category><pattern>JUST ME</pattern><template>I'm really sorry. She was like a crouching tiger.</template></category><category><pattern>BEVERLY  BEVERLY HILLS   YOU DOG</pattern><template>So, what about you?</template></category><category><pattern>THREE WEEKS AGO  YEAH  IN THE BACK OF AN ABANDONED FEDEX TRUCK</pattern><template>Shut up ....</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GOT TAKEN HOSTAGE BY A TWELVE YEAR OLD</pattern><template>Well, girls mature faster than boys.</template></category><category><pattern>FRIGHTENING  AS ANACONDA WOODSHOP  WHICH DOESN'T REALLY COUNT AS A CLASS ANYWAY</pattern><template>Had my first school dance.</template></category><category><pattern>NO YOU SHOULD ACTUALLY LIMBER UP AS WELL</pattern><template>Especially if we're going down that hill, is very important.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  WELL THEY'RE PLAYING IT IN COLUMBUS  OHIO</pattern><template>It's a total ghost town, burned to the ground.</template></category><category><pattern>BUT IT STILL IS SAD</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>TALLAHASSEE HAD A SICK SENSE OF HUMOR WHEN IT CAME TO ZOMBIES  / I    ZOMBIES AREN'T THE MOST LOVABLE CREATURES  BUT HE REALLY HATED THEM   / I    IN FACT THE ONLY THING HE WAS MORE OBSESSED WITH  THAN KILLING ZOMBIES   / I    WAS FINDING A TWINKIE   / I    SOMETHING ABOUT A TWINKIE REMINDED HIM OF A TIME NOT SO LONG AGO  / I    WHEN THINGS WERE SIMPLE AND NOT SO FUCKING PSYCHOTIC   / I    IT WAS LIKE IF HE GOT A TASTE OF THAT COMFORTING CHILDHOOD TREAT   / I    THE WORLD WOULD BECOME INNOCENT AGAIN AND EVERYTHING WOULD RETURN TO NORMAL   / I    PRETTY PROSPECTING</pattern><template>Jesus Christ!</template></category><category><pattern>MY MIND  IT'S SO FUN  JUST GOOD ENTERTAINMENT FOR THE WHOLE FAMILY</pattern><template>Yeah actually I went there as a kid too. In fact this probably counts as off season.</template></category><category><pattern>SO  WHAT ABOUT YOU</pattern><template>Me?, I..</template></category><category><pattern>IT BECAME QUICKLY APPARENT  HOWEVER  THAT HE DID HAVE ONE WEAKNESS   / I    WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE</pattern><template>We're taking a look, it's a Goddamn Hostess truck.</template></category><category><pattern>NOTHING I JUST   I HAVE THIS LIST</pattern><template>No one back there with my duffel bag.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  ONE SECOND  IT'S A DOUBLE BARREL SO</pattern><template>Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>A HINT</pattern><template>Why don't you exhale slowly, then squeeze the trigger.</template></category><category><pattern>TRUST ME</pattern><template>So he's on one of the serious Tour 'de France bikes, you know with the, like the toeholds, right, and he's peddling,</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  GIRLS MATURE FASTER THAN BOYS</pattern><template>She is way ahead of where I was at that age.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M WIDE AHEAD OF YOU</pattern><template>Time to nut up or shut up.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WAIT</pattern><template>I'll do it.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON</pattern><template>Come get a piece of Tallahassee!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH I'LL START LOOKING FOR IT RIGHT NOW</pattern><template>Cause I got nothing else to do.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN'T MAKE YOURSELF TOO AVAILABLE</pattern><template>I don't care, alright I wanna be with her.</template></category><category><pattern>GARFIELD   MAYBE</pattern><template>I'm sorry, he just gets me.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE SO DISGUSTING</pattern><template>Don't cross the streams.</template></category><category><pattern>WHATEVER</pattern><template>I'm going after Wichita.</template></category><category><pattern>ABOUT Z LAND</pattern><template>You mean other than the fact that I shot Bill Murray?</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU FUCKIN' WITH ME</pattern><template>No You should actually limber up as well.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  I THINK IT MOTH BE NUMBER TWO</pattern><template>Number two..</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  WE WENT THERE AS KIDS</pattern><template>That place totally blows..</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  BETTER YOU MAKE THE MISTAKE OF TRUSTING US  THAN WE MAKE THE MISTAKE OF TRUSTING YOU</pattern><template>Of course the first hot girl in a thousand miles shows up,  / i    makes me feel like an idiot, steals my double barrel / i    and says I'm the one that can't be trusted.  / i    Nice going, genius.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO  I WAS HEADED EAST  SHE WEST</pattern><template>And we took shelter in the back of the truck.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE INCREDIBLE</pattern><template>I know.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  STARTING NOW</pattern><template>Oh, I've actually been meaning to ask you. Did you hear anything about Columbus, Ohio?</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH I SHAVE EVERY MOORING BUT SOMETIMES   SINCE THIS IS A FREEWAY  YOU CAN GET IT UP TO 65  BUT YOU DON'T WANNA GO MORE THAN 75</pattern><template>You don't wanna go more than 20.</template></category><category><pattern>MAYBE</pattern><template>Are you jealous of Scotty Lynch?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW THAT'S NOT YOUR MIDDLE NAME  I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOU SINCE I WAS LIKE   SINCE I COULD MASTURBATE  NOT THAT THEY'RE CONNECTED</pattern><template>You know  A former greenskeeper about to become the master champion.    That's why we do it.</template></category><category><pattern>ACTUALLY I THINK I'M JEALOUS OF YOUR WHOLE 1997</pattern><template>Let's see mine.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANNA FEEL HOW HARD I CAN PUNCH</pattern><template>So what do you think?</template></category><category><pattern>AT THE HOLLYWOOD BOWL</pattern><template>Well, how was it?</template></category><category><pattern>GOTTA ENJOY THE LITTLE THINGS</pattern><template>I hate to give credit to anyone who looks like your Samity Sam,  / i    but I'm writing it down.  / i    Rule No. 32 Enjoy the little things  / i    Going in, it's a trap.</template></category><category><pattern>OH FREE PARKING  WHICH COINCIDENTALLY IS THE BEST THING ABOUT ZOMBIELAND</pattern><template>No, best thing about Z land: No Facebook status updates.</template></category><category><pattern>MY ENGAGEMENT RING</pattern><template>I took it off to pump my gas and I thought I had it in my purse, but it must've fallen out.</template></category><category><pattern>ENOUGH FOR US TO GET TO CALIFORNIA</pattern><template>Someday I want a ring this big.</template></category><category><pattern>TRUST NO ONE  JUST YOU AND ME</pattern><template>Just you and me.</template></category><category><pattern>EVEN THOUGH TEAMING UP WASN'T MY STYLE   / I    I FIGURED I'D BE SAFER WITH TALLAHASSEE   / I    YOU SEE HE WAS IN THE ASS KICKING BUSINESS  AND    / I    BUSINESS IS GOOD</pattern><template>It became quickly apparent, however, that he did have one weakness.  / i    What are we doing here?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS THE PROBLEM WITH GETTING ATTACHED TO SOMEONE   / I    WHEN THEY LEAVE YOU JUST FEEL LOST   / I    HAVING TALLAHASSEE AROUND DIDN'T COMFORT ME  IT JUST MADE ME FEEL MORE ALONE   / I    HEY  YOU WEREN'T EXACTLY GONNA SCORE ANYWAY</pattern><template>You weren't storming' the trenches before I came along.</template></category><category><pattern>I TELL YOU  I NEVER THOUGHT I COULD LOVE ANYTHING LIKE BOB THE DAY HE WAS BORN I JUST LOST MY MIND</pattern><template>Sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN TELL ALREADY  YOU ARE GONNA GET ON MY NERVES</pattern><template>Even though teaming up wasn't my style,  / i    I figured I'd be safer with Tallahassee.  / i    You see he was in the ass kicking business, and..  / I    Business is good.</template></category><category><pattern>COME HERE BIG FELLA  JUST GONNA TAKE A LITTLE OFF THE TOP</pattern><template>Wow, these fellas really let themselves go.</template></category><category><pattern>I MEAN IT MAKES YOU</pattern><template>Hungry.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO</pattern><template>You'll see.</template></category><category><pattern>BOY  WHO'S BILL MURRAY</pattern><template>I have never hit a kid before, but I mean that's like asking who Gandhi is.</template></category><category><pattern>FOR THE LOW PRICE OF 30 BUCKS  SOLD</pattern><template>It's amazing how far you can get with some costume jewelry and a cut throat attitude.  / i    I guess we're just lucky they didn't leave us by the side of the road.  / i    Thank you Wichita, Thanks Little Rock.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEDAY VERY SOON  LIFE'S LITTLE TWINKLE GAGE IS GONNA GO EMPTY</pattern><template>Time to nut up or shut up.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU GET TO RIDE SHOTGUN   I KINDA LIKE THIS GIRL   / I    SHE'S NOT YOUR TYPICAL HOT  STUCK UP BITCH   / I    EVEN BEFORE ZOMBIELAND  WICHITA WAS RUNNING THE TABLE ON GUYS LIKE US   / I    WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR</pattern><template>My engagement ring.</template></category><category><pattern>I EVEN LOVE YOUR DRAMATIC ROLES  EVERYTHING</pattern><template>Six people left in the world, one of them is Bill fucking Murray.</template></category><category><pattern>SWING</pattern><template>Thank you.</template></category><category><pattern>AND WORST THING</pattern><template>About Z land?</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY</pattern><template>I'll at least give you the intentional walk to first.</template></category><category><pattern>GHOSTBUSTERS</pattern><template>It is pretty catchy.</template></category><category><pattern>I SAW THIS CONSTRUCTION WORKER  I SHIT YOU NOT  HE IS ON A STEAM ROLLER AND THE ZOMBIE GOES DOWN IN FRONT OF ME   EVER ROLL A TUBE OF TOOTH PASTE UP FROM THE BOTTOM</pattern><template>Yeah I always roll it up from the bottom.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  I DIDN'T KNOW THAT IT WAS YOU YOU</pattern><template>Are you..What's with the, the get up?</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  WHY ARE YOU GUYS DOING THIS</pattern><template>Well, better you make the mistake of trusting us, than we make the mistake of trusting you.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT HERE</pattern><template>Drive down if I signal.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT'S YOUR NAME</pattern><template>Stop. No names.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY FOR FUCK'S SAKE  ENOUGH ALREADY  WE'RE BEING CHASED BY RAVENOUS FREAKS</pattern><template>We don't have enough problems?</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  DID YOU GUYS HEAR</pattern><template>There are no zombies there   Yeah, we heard.</template></category><category><pattern>IT SEEMS LIKE EVERYONE WHO HAS EVER BEEN IN A MOVIE LIVES ON THIS BLOCK</pattern><template>What exactly do you think we're doing in the 90210 Sally?</template></category><category><pattern>LIKE YOU WOULD EVER USE IT</pattern><template>Don't kill me with my own gun.</template></category><category><pattern>BILL</pattern><template>Yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>ZOMBIE KILL OF THE WEEK   NO SIR</pattern><template>I saw this construction worker, I shit you not, he is on a steam roller and the zombie goes down in front of me.. Ever roll a tube of tooth paste up from the bottom?</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW    AGAIN   SO SOON   WHAT CAN I SAY  I HAVE A CASE OF CHRONIC ANXIETY   / I    I WAS ALWAYS KIND OF PHOBIC   / I    I FOUND LOTS OF THINGS DISTURBING   / I    LIKE UNDERTOW  OR DEPARTMENT STORE SANTAS   / I    BEING ALONE WITH A BABY   / I    BUT THE THING I FEAR MORE THAN ANYTHING  YES  EVEN MORE THAN ZOMBIES   / I    FUCKING CLOWNS   / I    WHEN YOU ARE AFRAID OF EVERYTHING THAT'S OUT THERE   / I    YOU QUIT GOING OUT THERE   / I    WHICH IS WHAT HAPPENED TO ME BEFORE ZOMBIELAND   / I    FRIDAY NIGHT  THIRD STRAIGHT WEEK INDOORS   / I    WORLD OF WARCRAFT   / I     LEANING TOWER OF PIZZA BOXES    / I     CODE RED MOUNTAIN DEW    / I    PRIDE: NOWHERE  DIGNITY: LONG GONE  VIRGINITY: TOTALLY JUSTIFIABLE TO SPECULATE ON   / I    SMOOTH</pattern><template>My whole life, all I'd ever wanted was to find a girl.  / i    And fall in love.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE SCARY HAPPY</pattern><template>Come on, why don't we just forget about those girls and head home.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  LET'S HOPE THEY SHOOT ME</pattern><template>Looks like they hoofed it.</template></category><category><pattern>GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>Oh my God!</template></category><category><pattern>WAS THAT A GOOD YEAR</pattern><template>Oh my God.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST BILL I THINK NOW</pattern><template>Bill?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M FEELING COOPED UP</pattern><template>Wantamiro Wampum, Yeah that'll work.</template></category><category><pattern>NOT BAD FOR THAT SCRAWNY LITTLE SPIT FUCK</pattern><template>I have a little hunch.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE IN THE BACK  AREN'T THEY</pattern><template>Just me.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE IS WAY AHEAD OF WHERE I WAS AT THAT AGE</pattern><template>Twelve's the new twenty. Gun please.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU HAVE JUST SURVIVED THE ZOMBIE APOCALYPSE AND DROVE HALFWAY ACROSS THE COUNTRY</pattern><template>Where are you gonna go?</template></category><category><pattern>OH  NO  NO   HE DID  I'M JUST KIND OF LIKE A SANCHO PANZA CHARACTER</pattern><template>Look, I don't think she has long.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY THERE'S A NICE MINIVAN</pattern><template>Oh, yeah it is nice.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S THE WORST GOODBYE I HAVE EVER HEARD AND YOU STOLE IT FROM A MOVIE</pattern><template>Tell the ladies I said hey.</template></category><category><pattern>MONTHS SINCE PATIENT ZERO TOOK  / I    A BITE OF A CONTAMINATED BURGER AT A GAS 'N GULP   / I    JUST TWO MONTHS AND I MIGHT BE THE LAST NON CANNIBAL FREAK IN THE COUNTRY   / I    I MAY SEEM LIKE AN UNLIKELY SURVIVOR WITH ALL MY PHOBIAS AND IRRITABLE BOWEL SYNDROME   / I    BUT I HAD THE ADVANTAGE OF NEVER HAVING ANY FRIENDS OR ANY CLOSE FAMILY   / I    I SURVIVE  BECAUSE I PLAY IT SAFE AND FOLLOW THE RULES   / I    MY RULES   / I  RULE NO  1 CARDIO SHIT RULE NO  1 CARDIO OF COURSE RULE NO  4 SEATBELTS MOTHERFUCKER RULE NO  2 DOUBLE TAP   ON THE BRIGHT SIDE  I FOUND A PLACE TO GO NUMBER TWO   / I    ANOTHER RULE TO SURVIVING ZOMBIELAND: TRAVEL LIGHT   / I    AND I DON'T MEAN JUST LUGGAGE   / I    I'VE ALWAYS BEEN KIND OF A LONER   / I    I AVOIDED PEOPLE LIKE THEY WERE ZOMBIES EVEN BEFORE THEY WERE ZOMBIES   / I    NOW THAT THEY ARE ALL ZOMBIES   / I    I KIND OF MISS PEOPLE   / I    SO I'M ON MY FROM MY COLLEGE DORM IN AUSTIN  TEXAS TO COLUMBUS  OHIO   / I    WHERE I'M HOPING MY PARENTS ARE STILL ALIVE   / I    EVEN THOUGH WE WERE NEVER REALLY CLOSE   / I    IT WOULD JUST BE NICE TO SEE A FAMILIAR FACE   / I    OR ANY FACE  THAT HASN'T BLOOD DRIPPING FROM IT'S LIPS AND FLESH BETWEEN IT'S TEETH   / I  THANK YOU</pattern><template>What are you looking for?</template></category><category><pattern>GRAB A MAP</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S WHY I DON'T LET PEOPLE CLOSE  YOU ONLY GET BURNED</pattern><template>You don't say.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T CARE  ALRIGHT I WANNA BE WITH HER</pattern><template>Have fun in Mexico.</template></category><category><pattern>DON 'T TALK ABOUT ME LIKE I'M NOT HERE</pattern><template>Alright, sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  MADE LOVE</pattern><template>Well, just, sex.</template></category><category><pattern>NO MY FRIENDS  THIS IS NOW THE UNITED STATES OF ZOMBIELAND   / I    IT'S AMAZING HOW QUICKLY THINGS CAN GO FROM BAD TO TOTAL SHITSTORM   / I    AND WHY AM I ALIVE  WHEN EVERYONE AROUND ME HAS TURNED TO MEAT   / I    IT'S BECAUSE OF MY LIST OF RULES   / I    RULE NO  1 FOR SURVIVING ZOMBIELAND:  / I  CARDIO    / I    WHEN THE VIRUS STRUCK  FOR OBVIOUS REASONS  THE FIRST ONES TO GO WERE THE FATTIES   / I    POOR FAT BASTARD   / I    BUT AS THE INFECTION SPREAD AND THE CHAOS GREW    / I    IT WASN'T ENOUGH TO JUST BE FAST ON YOUR FEET   / I    YOU HAD TO GET A GUN AND LEARN HOW TO USE IT   / I    WHICH LEADS ME TO MY SECOND RULE:  / I    THE DOUBLE TAP   / I    IN THOSE MOMENTS  WHEN YOU'RE NOT SURE THE UNDEAD ARE REALLY DEAD DEAD   / I    DON'T GET ALL STINGY WITH YOU'RE BULLETS   / I    I MEAN  ONE MORE CLEAN SHOT TO THE HEAD  / I    AND THIS LADY COULD HAVE AVOIDED BECOMING A HUMAN HAPPY MEAL   / I    WOULD'VE  COULD'VE  SHOULD'VE   / I    IT WASN'T LONG BEFORE THE ZOMBIES BEGAN TO GET CLEVER   / I    WHEN YOU'RE AT YOUR MOST VULNERABLE   / I    SOMEHOW THEY COULD JUST SMELL IT   / I  CAN'T A GUY TAKE A DUMP HERE IN PEACE</pattern><template>Don't let them catch you with your pants down! Rule No. 3:  / i    Beware of bathrooms.  / i    As zombies began to outnumber humans,  / i    that's when you had to cut all emotional ties.  / i    If the girls in your neighborhood are now fucked up little monsters,   / i    well maybe it's time to stop driving carpool .  / i    You had to focus on your own survival.  / i    Which leads to Rule No. 4,  / i    pretty basic:  / i    Fasten your seat belts,  / i    it's gonna be a bumpy ride.  / i    That guy down there is me.  / i    I'm in Garlind, Texas, and it may look like zombies destroyed it, but that's actually just Garlind.  / i</template></category><category><pattern>OH  YEAH IT IS NICE</pattern><template>That's a beautiful van.</template></category><category><pattern>KEEPS US FROM GETTING TOO FAMILIAR</pattern><template>You must knock over your alcohol with your knife.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THE ZOMBIES HEAD IS  LIKE  CAUGHT IN THE GEAR  YOU KNOW WITH THE HAIR IN THE CHAIN JUST  LIKE  GOING AROUND</pattern><template>Very cool.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A DANGEROUS MAN</pattern><template>You're gonna risk our lives for a Twinkie?</template></category><category><pattern>STUPID LITTLE BITCHES</pattern><template>Oh, I  think I pulled something.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU NEED SOME HELP</pattern><template>Now that you mention it, We'll take your weapons, your car keys, your ammunition.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M THINKING:  LANCO MAGNIFIQUE    WHY DON'T YOU SPEAK UP  THEY MIGHT'VE MISSED IT IN SANTA FE</pattern><template>Oh my God. You're thinking about fucking Wichita.</template></category><category><pattern>WISH GRANTED  SHE SPENT THE LAST 24 HOURS FUCKING US BOTH</pattern><template>Good luck now Petunia.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO AMERICA  / I    I WISH I COULD TELL YOU THAT THIS WAS STILL AMERICA  / I    BUT I'VE COME TO REALIZE THAT YOU CAN'T HAVE A COUNTRY WITHOUT PEOPLE  / I    AND THERE THERE ARE NO PEOPLE HERE   / I  STOP</pattern><template>No my friends, this is now the United States of Zombieland!  / i    It's amazing how quickly things can go from bad to total shitstorm.  / i    And why am I alive, when everyone around me has turned to meat?  / i    It's because of my list of rules.  / i    Rule No. 1 for surviving Zombieland:  / i  Cardio    / i    When the virus struck, for obvious reasons, the first ones to go were the fatties.  / i    Poor fat bastard.  / i    But as the infection spread and the chaos grew,   / i    it wasn't enough to just be fast on your feet.  / i    You had to get a gun and learn how to use it.  / i    Which leads me to my Second Rule:  / i    The double tap.  / i    In those moments, when you're not sure the undead are really dead dead,  / i    don't get all stingy with you're bullets.  / i    I mean, one more clean shot to the head  / i    and this lady could have avoided becoming a human Happy Meal.  / i    Would've, could've, should've.  / i    It wasn't long before the zombies began to get clever.  / i    When you're at your most vulnerable,  / i    somehow they could just smell it.  / i  Can't a guy take a dump here in peace?</template></category><category><pattern>FALSE ADVERTISING</pattern><template>Jesus Christ.</template></category><category><pattern>SHE'S TWELVE</pattern><template>No Twinkies.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M JUST SAYING WE SHOULD FIND A PLACE TO CRASH</pattern><template>Oh, I got an idea.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE MAKING A FORT</pattern><template>That was probably for the best, cause I like you, Columbus, but my sister and I are going to do whatever it takes to survive so..</template></category><category><pattern>NICE TO MEET YOU</pattern><template>Here Here you go.</template></category><category><pattern>DRUGS MAYBE</pattern><template>I didn't even tell you the worst part.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S JUST  YOU KNOW  THERE'S ZOMBIES EVERYWHERE  I THINK THE LEAST OF MY WORRIES IS</pattern><template>Yeah that's true.</template></category><category><pattern>GIRLS CHOICE</pattern><template>What nobody picked you?</template></category><category><pattern>MORE</pattern><template>No. One for me. One and done, I always say.. I said that once.</template></category><category><pattern>TELL THE LADIES I SAID HEY</pattern><template>You know there are pictures of her in someones wallet too.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M SORRY  HE JUST GETS ME</pattern><template>But it still is sad.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  BEST THING ABOUT Z LAND: NO FACEBOOK STATUS UPDATES</pattern><template>You know  Rob Curtis is gearing up for Friday .</template></category><category><pattern>FOR ME HOME  WAS A PUPPY NAMED BUCK  CUTEST DOG EVER</pattern><template>All those fucking zombies.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  LET ME BEGIN MY THREE PART APOLOGY BY SAYING THAT I THINK YOU'RE A WONDERFUL HUMAN WITH GREAT POTENTIAL</pattern><template>Fyi: I beat wholesale ass for a lot less than that.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY  YOU FOUND MY RING</pattern><template>Thanks, I've been looking all over for it.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE NOT GONNA SHOOT THEM  ARE YOU</pattern><template>Unless the shoot me.</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK  I KNOW THAT YOU'RE REALLY SICK  BUT   YOUR SISTER WANTS ME TO</pattern><template>It's not her decision, okay, It's mine.</template></category><category><pattern>JESUS CHRIST</pattern><template>You want a Sno Ball or something?</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHAT DO YOU THINK</pattern><template>Wait, the last time I laid some pipe?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M NOT SURE WHAT'S MORE TRAGIC   / I    THAT MY FAMILY IS GONE   / I    OR THE REALIZATION THAT I HAD NEVER MUCH OF A FAMILY TO BEGIN WITH   / I    EITHER WAY I CAN'T PRETEND THAT WHATEVER I'M LOOKING FOR   / I    I'LL FIND BY GOING HOME   / I    I HAVE NO HOME   / I    WE CAN  GIVE YOU A RIDE</pattern><template>You can go, see for yourself, or settle somewhere new.</template></category><category><pattern>WOULD IT BE BETTER TO BE SMART  OR LUCKY</pattern><template>Look at what we got here.</template></category><category><pattern>SEAT BELTS</pattern><template>Yes but no, she's not. She's only famous when she's Hannah Montana, when she's wearing the wig.</template></category><category><pattern>ONLY PLACE WEST OF WACO</pattern><template>Trust me.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  WE SHOULD PROBABLY HEAD OUT  NOW</pattern><template>Finally he got to first base.</template></category><category><pattern>I'VE SEEN EVERYONE OF YOUR MOVIES A MILLION TIMES</pattern><template>I even love your dramatic roles, everything.</template></category><category><pattern>THE LITTLE ONE'S BEEN BIT  AND  YOU KNOW  TRY NOT TO FREAK HER OUT</pattern><template>Columbus, Wichita, Litle Rock   So you did all this for a Twinkie?</template></category><category><pattern>UP HERE</pattern><template>Oh my God!</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS MY FRIEND'S</pattern><template>I'm gonna send it to her.</template></category><category><pattern>OK  I'M GONNA TEACH YOU A LITTLE SOMETHING ABOUT BILL MURRAY</pattern><template>The king slept right here.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NICE</pattern><template>Smell the finger?</template></category><category><pattern>LOOK AT WHAT WE GOT HERE</pattern><template>Come on.</template></category><category><pattern>ALL THOSE FUCKING ZOMBIES</pattern><template>I lost him.</template></category><category><pattern>THE HELL I AM</pattern><template>I'm sorry, I didn't know that it was you you.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU  THANK YOU</pattern><template>Nice to meet you.</template></category><category><pattern>CORN STARCH  YOU KNOW SOME BERRIES  A LITTLE LIQUISH FOR THE LADIES</pattern><template>It suits my lifestyle. You know I like to get out and do stuff.</template></category><category><pattern>AND THEY'RE SO FAT</pattern><template>I think we should probably just keep going.</template></category><category><pattern>HELLO  INSIDE VOICES  OKAY</pattern><template>At least until we know we are alone.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'S GANDHI</pattern><template>She's twelve.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DON'T YOU EXHALE SLOWLY  THEN SQUEEZE THE TRIGGER</pattern><template>Don't make me drink alone.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOST HIM</pattern><template>There ain't no getting him back, so I am looking for a new home.</template></category><category><pattern>I LIKE SNOWBALLS</pattern><template>I hate coconut, not the taste, the consistency.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A 97</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE A PEPPY LITTLE SPIT FUCK  AREN'T YOU</pattern><template>You might wanna buckle up, you know, for safety.</template></category><category><pattern>HOP IN THE CAR EVEL KNIEVEL  LET'S GO RIDE THE ROLLER COASTER</pattern><template>Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>AND I'M LATE FOR MY FLIGHT</pattern><template>Listen, I'll find your ring and I'll FedEx it to you.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE'S A PLACE THAT IS UNTOUCHED BY ALL THIS CRAP</pattern><template>Back east, yeah?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU THINK YOU MIGHT PULL THROUGH</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TOUGH GROWING UP</pattern><template>There, you can take that truck.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW MANY LEFT</pattern><template>Let me see.</template></category><category><pattern>BRING HER HOME TO MEET THE FOLKS   / I    THEN AGAIN  SINCE MY FOLKS ARE A COUPLE OF PARANOID SHUT INS LIKE ME   / I    MAYBE THIS GIRL COULD BRING ME HOME TO HER FOLKS   / I    AND THE I'D FINALLY BE A MEMBER OF A COOL FUNCTIONAL FAMILY   / I  PLEASE  ANYONE HOME</pattern><template>Please, it's an emergency!</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  CODE RED  AND HERE IS SOME GOLD GRAMS</pattern><template>The Ziplock bag keep's 'em crisp.</template></category><category><pattern>THANKS</pattern><template>Go!</template></category><category><pattern>DRIVE DOWN IF I SIGNAL</pattern><template>You're not gonna shoot them, are you?</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S OKAY  YOU DON'T HAVE TO</pattern><template>Well, where are you headed?</template></category><category><pattern>CLOSE  BUT NO CIGAR   / I    ZOMBIE KILL OF THE WEEK GOES TO SISTER CYNTHIA KNICKERBOCKER   / I    POOR FLAT BASTARD   / I    PERFUME</pattern><template>What?</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE BITCHES</pattern><template>I know.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH ACTUALLY I WENT THERE AS A KID TOO  IN FACT THIS PROBABLY COUNTS AS OFF SEASON</pattern><template>Well, did you guys hear?</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GONNA SEND IT TO HER</pattern><template>Do I get a reward?</template></category><category><pattern>I CAN'T BELIEVE I ALMOST KISSED HIM  WHAT'S OUR RULE</pattern><template>Trust no one, just you and me.</template></category><category><pattern>RELAX OK  I JUST PASSED FOR A ZOMBIE</pattern><template>What I'd give for a show..</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE ARE YOU GONNA GO</pattern><template>I'm going to Pacific Playland. Woo.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S NOT HER DECISION  OKAY  IT'S MINE</pattern><template>I made a promise We already said goodbye, but we didn't have a gun.</template></category><category><pattern>COLUMBUS  WICHITA  LITLE ROCK   SO YOU DID ALL THIS FOR A TWINKIE</pattern><template>Oh, no, no.. he did. I'm just kind of like a Sancho Panza character.</template></category><category><pattern>WHERE'S THE FUCKING TWINKIES</pattern><template>I like snowballs.</template></category><category><pattern>THREE THOUSAND DOLLARS</pattern><template>It's worth more than my car.</template></category><category><pattern>WHEN TALLAHASSEE GOES HULK ON A ZOMBIE   / I    HE SETS THE STANDARD FOR NOT TO BE FUCKED WITH   / I    NO FEAR  NOTHING TO LOSE   / I    WHAT CAN I SAY  IT'S LIKE ART   / I    YOU GOT A PURDY MOUTH</pattern><template>Don't swing! Don't swing!</template></category><category><pattern>SO</pattern><template>This is kind of freeing.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST YOU AND ME</pattern><template>Yeah, you and me.</template></category><category><pattern>THEY'RE UP THERE  THEY'RE OKAY</pattern><template>What are you waiting for?</template></category><category><pattern>NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT  WE'LL TAKE YOUR WEAPONS  YOUR CAR KEYS  YOUR AMMUNITION</pattern><template>And if you got it, sugarless gum.</template></category><category><pattern>LET ME CALL YOU BACK</pattern><template>Hey, you found my ring.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  YOU HEARD THE SAME THING</pattern><template>Out west we hear it's back east, back east they hear it's out west.</template></category><category><pattern>MR  MURRAY</pattern><template>Just Bill I think now.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S TOUGH GROWING UP IN ZOMBIELAND</pattern><template>It's tough growing up.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD</pattern><template>They're up there, they're okay.</template></category><category><pattern>HOW ABOUT WE PLAY THE QUIET GAME</pattern><template>Yeah? Starting now.</template></category><category><pattern>YOUR RING</pattern><template>It was my friend's.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST TATTOO  A PURPOISE</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT</pattern><template>Is that perfume?</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T BELIEVE IN IT  HAVE YOU EVER SEEN A LION LIMBER UP BEFORE IT TAKES DOWN A GAZELLE</pattern><template>Snowballs.</template></category><category><pattern>IS WHAT TRUE</pattern><template>Totally zombie free.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HOW ABOUT A LITTLE WEST COAST HOSPITALITY  CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING  WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE</pattern><template>Smooth, isn't it?</template></category><category><pattern>HURRY  GET UP</pattern><template>Come on, let's go.</template></category><category><pattern>I HATE COCONUT  NOT THE TASTE  THE CONSISTENCY</pattern><template>Fresh.</template></category><category><pattern>GODDAMN IT  BILL FUCKING MURRAY</pattern><template>I had to get that out. I don't mean to gush.</template></category><category><pattern>TWELVE'S THE NEW TWENTY  GUN PLEASE</pattern><template>Like you would ever use it..</template></category><category><pattern>TALLAHASSEE</pattern><template>I think they might actually require our hard assistance this time. Buckle up.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T EVEN KNOW YOUR NAME  BUT THIS IS ACTUALLY REALLY NICE</pattern><template>You know? Between you, me and You're actually kind of cute.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T WANNA GO MORE THAN 20</pattern><template>Do not worry about it. Blind spots, blind spots are for other drivers.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT ARE YOU ONE OF THESE GUYS THAT TRIES TO  LIKE  WONDER IF EVERYBODY ELSE HAS A STORY</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>DO I GET A REWARD</pattern><template>40, 60, 80, 400, That's it. That's the whole register.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH  HE'S LIKE A LITTLE BUNNY</pattern><template>I'll get him.</template></category><category><pattern>UNLESS THE SHOOT ME</pattern><template>Oh, let's hope they shoot me.</template></category><category><pattern>VERY COOL</pattern><template>But..</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  IT'S JUST THAT YOU LOOK REMARKABLY LIKE EDDY VAN HALEN</pattern><template>I Just saw Eddy Van Halen.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU JEALOUS OF SCOTTY LYNCH</pattern><template>Yes, I am.</template></category><category><pattern>WE DON'T KNOW THAT THERE'S DEFINITELY NO CURE  RIGHT  I MEAN</pattern><template>You're just gut less!</template></category><category><pattern>SMOOTH  ISN'T IT</pattern><template>Oh hurry, hurry he's on the ceiling. Come get him. Oh..</template></category><category><pattern>THIS PLACE IS INCREDIBLE</pattern><template>Ladies and Gentlemen, welcome to La Menzion de Murray.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU ARE STARING AT ME  IT'S A HAIRPIECE IT'S A</pattern><template>Sorry, it's just that you look remarkably like Eddy Van Halen.</template></category><category><pattern>IF IT MEANS ANYTHING NOW I AM SO SORRY</pattern><template>It was just instinctive.</template></category><category><pattern>PLEASE  IT'S AN EMERGENCY</pattern><template>I don't usually unlock my door to the sounds of panic,  / i    but my neighbor of 406 is insanely hot.  / i    Okay, Okay.</template></category><category><pattern>YES   YEAH  ONE SECOND</pattern><template>Are you fuckin' with me?</template></category><category><pattern>I HAD TO GET THAT OUT  I DON'T MEAN TO GUSH</pattern><template>This is so surreal, I mean. You probably get this all the time,well, maybe not lately, but I'm such a huge fan of yours.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S JUST GET WHERE WE'RE GOING</pattern><template>So do you think it's true?</template></category><category><pattern>AND IF SHE HAD  LIKE  A TYPE   IF YOU CAN HAVE A TYPE   WHAT WOULD THAT BE</pattern><template>She kinda goes for, like, bad boys.</template></category><category><pattern>HE TRIED TO BITE ME</pattern><template>You are right, that's the worst part.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL FIND IT</pattern><template>Yeah I'll start looking for it right now.</template></category><category><pattern>YES BUT NO  SHE'S NOT  SHE'S ONLY FAMOUS WHEN SHE'S HANNAH MONTANA  WHEN SHE'S WEARING THE WIG</pattern><template>Okay, right.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU OKAY</pattern><template>Ok, ok.. stop..</template></category><category><pattern>ANYBODY HUNGRY</pattern><template>Tallahassee nice over here.</template></category><category><pattern>FIRST ORTHODONTIST  THE BASTARD GAVE ME HEAD GEAR</pattern><template>I got my first B.</template></category><category><pattern>WHY DO I GET STUCK WITH HER</pattern><template>It doesn't seem to end.</template></category><category><pattern>SO WHERE ARE YOU GUYS HEADED</pattern><template>Pacific Play Land    The amusement park?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT NOBODY PICKED YOU</pattern><template>Iz was girls choice.</template></category><category><pattern>3 2 1   YOU GUYS WANT SOME CARAMEL</pattern><template>Yes.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU  WHAT'S WITH THE  THE GET UP</pattern><template>Oh, I do it to blend in, you know zombies don't mess with other zombies.</template></category><category><pattern>WICHITA  LITTLE ROCK</pattern><template>Oh my God  / i    Look at this fucking clown.  / i    Of course, it had to be a clown.  / i    No, it had to be a clown.  / i    And it had to be Wichita for me to finally understand  / i    that some rules are made to be broken.  / i    Time to nut up or shut up.  / i    Fuck this clown.  / i    Thanks.</template></category><category><pattern>STOP  NO NAMES</pattern><template>Keeps us from getting too familiar.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'VE HEARD OF THE QUIET GAME</pattern><template>Sorry.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T WANNA CROSS</pattern><template>Don't cross the streams!</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAD MY PERSONALITY  MY LAUGH  MY APPETITE    LAUGH  AND THAT'S WHEN IT HIT ME  I FELT SO ASHAMED THAT IT HAD TAKEN ME THIS LONG   / I    ME WITH THE BEST CARD IN THE BUSINESS TO REALIZE I WASN'T THE ONLY ONE RUNNING FROM SOMETHING   / I</pattern><template>We made this wallet together out of Duct Tape.</template></category><category><pattern>SO HE'S ON ONE OF THE SERIOUS TOUR 'DE FRANCE BIKES  YOU KNOW WITH THE  LIKE THE TOEHOLDS  RIGHT  AND HE'S PEDDLING</pattern><template>and the zombies head is, like, caught in the gear, you know with the hair in the chain just, like, going around.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK THEY MIGHT ACTUALLY REQUIRE OUR HARD ASSISTANCE THIS TIME  BUCKLE UP</pattern><template>I'm wide ahead of you.</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  OUTSIDE LA</pattern><template>Yeah, we went there as kids.</template></category><category><pattern>DO NOT WORRY ABOUT IT  BLIND SPOTS  BLIND SPOTS ARE FOR OTHER DRIVERS</pattern><template>So do you never strap in or just, when on road trips?</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT HOW YOU SAY HELLO WHERE YOU COME FROM</pattern><template>Oh my God, Oh my God I can't believe I shot Bill Murray.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW A GUY WAY WORSE AT THAT THAN ME</pattern><template>Let's just try to find a car.</template></category><category><pattern>I KNOW  I KNOW</pattern><template>And she knows, we're just looking for a way out.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE</pattern><template>I'm not great at farewells so.. that'll do pig.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M REALLY SORRY  SHE WAS LIKE A CROUCHING TIGER</pattern><template>You got taken hostage by a twelve year old?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MEAN OTHER THAN THE FACT THAT I SHOT BILL MURRAY</pattern><template>That's easy.</template></category><category><pattern>I'LL AT LEAST GIVE YOU THE INTENTIONAL WALK TO FIRST</pattern><template>Hey little help movin' a couch.</template></category><category><pattern>AND AS LONG AS YOU'RE BY MY SIDE  I AM NOT LEAVING THIS APARTMENT   DO YOU MIND IF I JUST CLOSE MY EYES FOR A MINUTE</pattern><template>No, of course..</template></category><category><pattern>SO DO YOU THINK IT'S TRUE</pattern><template>Is what true?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS A GREAT YEAR  ARE YOU KIDDING ME   I SAW MY FIRST R  RATED MOVIE THAT YEAR</pattern><template>Anaconda.</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS JUST INSTINCTIVE</pattern><template>It was my bad.</template></category><category><pattern>I LOVE YOU</pattern><template>Love you too.</template></category><category><pattern>ARE YOU OKAY  COME ON</pattern><template>Hurry, get up.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S ALL JUST NONSENSE</pattern><template>You know, you're like a penguin on the North Pole, hears the South Pole is really nice this time 'a year.</template></category><category><pattern>HAVE FUN IN MEXICO</pattern><template>Come on! Hurry!</template></category><category><pattern>HE'S A ZOMBIE   THAT'S A TOUGH BREAK</pattern><template>So how about a little west coast hospitality. Can I get you something? What would you like?</template></category><category><pattern>OF COURSE THE FIRST HOT GIRL IN A THOUSAND MILES SHOWS UP   / I    MAKES ME FEEL LIKE AN IDIOT  STEALS MY DOUBLE BARREL / I    AND SAYS I'M THE ONE THAT CAN'T BE TRUSTED   / I    NICE GOING  GENIUS</pattern><template>You're the one that gave her the gun.</template></category><category><pattern>SMELL THE FINGER</pattern><template>Thank God for rednecks.</template></category><category><pattern>SORRY  I'M JUST SO SCARED</pattern><template>No, no.. you should be scared. A homeless man just tried to eat you.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE IN HOLLYWOOD  LET'S SLEEP IN STYLE</pattern><template>Grab a map.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT I'D GIVE FOR A SHOW</pattern><template>Do not say s h o w e r, okay.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S SEE MINE</pattern><template>First orthodontist. The bastard gave me head gear.</template></category><category><pattern>THERE AIN'T NO GETTING HIM BACK  SO I AM LOOKING FOR A NEW HOME</pattern><template>Tomorrow maybe, skinny dipping in the Yellowstone River, swing from the chandeliers in the Playboy Mansion, but today, a vortex six fucking liter V8, a box full of ...</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T USUALLY UNLOCK MY DOOR TO THE SOUNDS OF PANIC   / I    BUT MY NEIGHBOR OF 406 IS INSANELY HOT   / I    OKAY  OKAY</pattern><template>Thank you, thank you..</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I DO IT TO BLEND IN  YOU KNOW ZOMBIES DON'T MESS WITH OTHER ZOMBIES</pattern><template>Buddy of mine, make up guy, showed how to do this.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  YOU'RE LIKE A PENGUIN ON THE NORTH POLE  HEARS THE SOUTH POLE IS REALLY NICE THIS TIME 'A YEAR</pattern><template>There are no penguins on the North Pole.</template></category><category><pattern>SO   TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED</pattern><template>He was homeless and.. sick.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T SAY</pattern><template>Mexico, you know what they call Twinkies in Mexico? Los Submerinos.</template></category><category><pattern>LISTEN  I'LL FIND YOUR RING AND I'LL FEDEX IT TO YOU</pattern><template>I'll give you a reward   Do not be silly.</template></category><category><pattern>REALLY  YEAH  WELL TAKE ME AS FAR AS TEXARKANA</pattern><template>You're a peppy little spit fuck, aren't you?</template></category><category><pattern>SOMETIMES TALLAHASSEE'S RIGHT  YOU GOTTA ENJOY THE LITTLE THINGS   / I    EVEN IF THAT MEANS DESTROYING A WHOLE LOT OF LITTLE THINGS   / I    WHAT SMELLS LIKE PERFUME</pattern><template>You don't know who Willie Nelson is?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU CAN GO  SEE FOR YOURSELF  OR SETTLE SOMEWHERE NEW</pattern><template>I could tell she knew what I was feeling.  / i    We are all orphans in Zombieland.  / i  I know this Pacific Playland thing is nuts, but, it's been so long since she got to be a kid.</template></category><category><pattern>LET'S JUST TRY TO FIND A CAR</pattern><template>Which reminds me. I never had headaches like this 'til your ass came on board.</template></category><category><pattern>I DON'T THINK WE'RE GONNA BE ABLE TO STITCH THIS</pattern><template>Ow, that's still tender.</template></category><category><pattern>IS THAT PERFUME</pattern><template>It's cologne.</template></category><category><pattern>HEY LITTLE HELP MOVIN' A COUCH</pattern><template>We're making a fort.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  JUST  SEX</pattern><template>Three weeks ago, yeah. In the back of an abandoned FedEx truck.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH I SEE THAT  A HOSTESS TRUCK  SO WHAT</pattern><template>I could use a Twinkie.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW THERE ARE PICTURES OF HER IN SOMEONES WALLET TOO</pattern><template>Hop in the car Evel Knievel. Let's go ride the roller coaster.</template></category><category><pattern>KIND'A MAKES YOU SAD  IT MAKES YOU  MAKES YOU THINK IF YOU COULD GO BACK  TO THE WAY THINGS WERE RIGHT NOW  YOU KNOW  YOU'D BE OUT IN THE BACK YARD  YOU KNOW  TRY TO CATCH FIREFLIES</pattern><template>And instead, this.</template></category><category><pattern>WE MADE THIS WALLET TOGETHER OUT OF DUCT TAPE</pattern><template>Take away a man's son, you've truly given him nothing left to lose.  / i    I haven't cried like that since Titanic.</template></category><category><pattern>OH  I GOT AN IDEA</pattern><template>We're in Hollywood, let's sleep in style.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU'RE JUST GUT LESS</pattern><template>Give him the gun.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MADE SOMEONE VERY HAPPY</pattern><template>You too.</template></category><category><pattern>HELP ME WITH THE BOOTS  COME ON</pattern><template>Help me with the boots.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T MIND IF I DO</pattern><template>What do you think? Zombie kill of the week?</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS A REALLY BIG TRUCK AND THESE ARE REALLY BIG GUNS</pattern><template>Take your time.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO'D HAVE GUESSED THAT SOMETHING'D BE ZOMBIE KILLIN'</pattern><template>Probably nobody.</template></category><category><pattern>WE'RE TAKING A LOOK  IT'S A GODDAMN HOSTESS TRUCK</pattern><template>Yeah I see that. A Hostess truck. So what?</template></category><category><pattern>I HATE TO GIVE CREDIT TO ANYONE WHO LOOKS LIKE YOUR SAMITY SAM   / I    BUT I'M WRITING IT DOWN   / I    RULE NO  32 ENJOY THE LITTLE THINGS  / I    GOING IN  IT'S A TRAP</pattern><template>Wait here.</template></category><category><pattern>WANTAMIRO WAMPUM  YEAH THAT'LL WORK</pattern><template>Okay but what the hell are we doing?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU SEE  YOU JUST CAN'T TRUST ANYONE   / I    THE FIRST TIME I LET A GIRL INTO MY LIFE AND SHE TRIES TO EAT ME   / I  LISTEN TO ME  406 IF YOU'RE IN THERE  YOU'RE JUST SICK  OK</pattern><template>Rule 2 Double Strike   That was my first brush with the plague of the 21st century  / i    Remember mad cow disease?  / i    Well, mad cow became mad person became mad zombie.  / i    It's a fast acting virus that left you with a swollen brain, a raging fever that made you hateful, violent,  / i</template></category><category><pattern>THIS IS KIND OF FREEING</pattern><template>Yeah.</template></category><category><pattern>ESPECIALLY IF WE'RE GOING DOWN THAT HILL  IS VERY IMPORTANT</pattern><template>I don't believe in it. Have you ever seen a lion limber up before it takes down a gazelle?</template></category><category><pattern>I COULD USE A TWINKIE</pattern><template>Are you coming?</template></category><category><pattern>HUNGRY</pattern><template>I'm worried about you.</template></category><category><pattern>ON THE COUNT OF THREE</pattern><template>One, two, three.</template></category><category><pattern>ANACONDA</pattern><template>Oh, Anaconda.</template></category><category><pattern>TWINKIE  TWINKIE  TWINKIE   OH  OH   BIG HOSS</pattern><template>Come here big fella, just gonna take a little off the top.</template></category><category><pattern>NOW GET OVER IT  OKAY  WE CAN'T JUST FUCKING DRIVE DOWN THE ROAD PLAYING I SPY  OR SOME SHIT FOR TWO HOURS  LIKE FOUR NORMAL ASS AMERICANS</pattern><template>Fuck me!</template></category><category><pattern>THE KING SLEPT RIGHT HERE</pattern><template>Dibs on the bed.</template></category><category><pattern>SOMEDAY I WANT A RING THIS BIG</pattern><template>For the low price of 30 bucks, sold.</template></category><category><pattern>OH MY GOD  OH MY GOD I CAN'T BELIEVE I SHOT BILL MURRAY</pattern><template>Mr. Murray?</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT WAS HER NAME</pattern><template>Beverly, Beverly Hills   You dog.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU TOO</pattern><template>How many left?</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S A TOTAL GHOST TOWN  BURNED TO THE GROUND</pattern><template>You're Columbus.</template></category><category><pattern>WELL  WHERE ARE YOU HEADED</pattern><template>Columbus, you?</template></category><category><pattern>THERE IS A BOX OF TWINKIES IN THAT GROCERY STORE  NOT JUST ANY BOX OF TWINKIES  THE LAST BOX OF TWINKIES THAT ANYONE WILL ENJOY IN THE WHOLE UNIVERSE</pattern><template>Believe it or not, Twinkies have an expiration date.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S AMAZING HOW FAR YOU CAN GET WITH SOME COSTUME JEWELRY AND A CUT THROAT ATTITUDE   / I    I GUESS WE'RE JUST LUCKY THEY DIDN'T LEAVE US BY THE SIDE OF THE ROAD   / I    THANK YOU WICHITA  THANKS LITTLE ROCK</pattern><template>Hey for fuck's sake, enough already, we're being chased by ravenous freaks.</template></category><category><pattern>JUST DRIVE SLOW  KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED</pattern><template>They're in the back, aren't they?</template></category><category><pattern>OKAY</pattern><template>It 1997,  Gor Gorgeous    I never took French.</template></category><category><pattern>WATCH THIS</pattern><template>It's okay, it's okay. I got him.</template></category><category><pattern>WHAT DO YOU THINK  ZOMBIE KILL OF THE WEEK</pattern><template>Close, but no cigar.  / i    Zombie kill of the week goes to sister Cynthia Knickerbocker.  / i    Poor flat bastard.  / i    Perfume?</template></category><category><pattern>I JUST SAW EDDY VAN HALEN</pattern><template>Really?</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW WHAT  I MAY NOT SHOOT YOU  BUT YOU STILL ROYALLY PISS ME OFF</pattern><template>And I'm not going to play with you at Pacific Playland.</template></category><category><pattern>I TOOK IT OFF TO PUMP MY GAS AND I THOUGHT I HAD IT IN MY PURSE  BUT IT MUST'VE FALLEN OUT</pattern><template>And I'm late for my flight..</template></category><category><pattern>I GOT MY FIRST B</pattern><template>Oh no.</template></category><category><pattern>ALRIGHT  SORRY</pattern><template>Look, i know that you're really sick, but   your sister wants me to..</template></category><category><pattern>OH  BILL MURRAY   GOD  NO WAY</pattern><template>This guy has a direct line to my funny bone  I mean every..</template></category><category><pattern>WE BETTER START WORKING ON OUR APOLOGY</pattern><template>Up here!</template></category><category><pattern>YOU WANT A SNO BALL OR SOMETHING</pattern><template>Oh God!</template></category><category><pattern>ME   I</pattern><template>Oh my God.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT PLACE TOTALLY BLOWS</pattern><template>my mind. It's so fun. Just good entertainment for the whole family.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU DON'T KNOW WHO WILLIE NELSON IS</pattern><template>No.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU MUST KNOCK OVER YOUR ALCOHOL WITH YOUR KNIFE</pattern><template>That's okay, you don't have to..</template></category><category><pattern>SET ASIDE THE FEVERISH  HOMELESS CANNIBAL  I'M LIVING THE DREAM   / I    I HAD ALWAYS  MY WHOLE LIFE  WANTED TO BRUSH A GIRLS HAIR OVER HER EAR   / I   GOOD NIGHT</pattern><template>Good night.</template></category><category><pattern>AND DON'T LET GO  ONCE YOU DO</pattern><template>It wasn't just because i had nowhere else to go.  / i    It was cause in that moment it became clear.  / i    Wherever this girl was, / i     that's where i wanted to be.   / i    Man we're gonna have to pull over soon.</template></category><category><pattern>BELIEVE IT OR NOT  TWINKIES HAVE AN EXPIRATION DATE</pattern><template>Someday very soon, life's little twinkle gage is gonna go empty.</template></category><category><pattern>YOU KNOW  BETWEEN YOU  ME AND YOU'RE ACTUALLY KIND OF CUTE</pattern><template>You think so?</template></category><category><pattern>IT WAS MY BAD</pattern><template>I was never a very good practical joker.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  BREAK ANOTHER ONE</pattern><template>Nice!</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  LET'S GO</pattern><template>There!</template></category><category><pattern>HOLY SHIT</pattern><template>Shit, I'm out of shells.</template></category><category><pattern>IT'S YOUR GAL</pattern><template>Come on!</template></category><category><pattern>THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL VAN</pattern><template>Tallahassee firmly believes that you have to blow off steam in Zombieland,  / i    or else you lose what's left of your mind.  / i    Well, if it makes him happy and keeps him from using that crowbar on me,  / i    Then I say  Hey, go waste shit .  / i    I want my Caddie back.</template></category><category><pattern>I DIDN'T REALIZE IT WAS</pattern><template>I'm not sure what's more tragic,  / i    That my family is gone,  / i    or the realization that I had never much of a family to begin with.  / i    Either way I can't pretend that whatever I'm looking for,  / i    I'll find by going home.  / i    I have no home.  / i    We can, give you a ride.</template></category><category><pattern>THOSE GUYS WERE DUMB</pattern><template>Avoid the vanity mirror.</template></category><category><pattern>NO  NO   YOU SHOULD BE SCARED  A HOMELESS MAN JUST TRIED TO EAT YOU</pattern><template>that's like the right ind of scared. That's reasonable scared. You know I get scared for things that like, don't make sense at all.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK YOU</pattern><template>You are staring at me, it's a hairpiece it's a..</template></category><category><pattern>WAIT  THE LAST TIME I LAID SOME PIPE</pattern><template>The last time you went twenty toes, the percy in the playpen, wallpapered the closet, passed the gravy. Went heels to Jesus.</template></category><category><pattern>THANK GOD FOR REDNECKS</pattern><template>This is a really big truck and these are really big guns.</template></category><category><pattern>DON'T KILL ME WITH MY OWN GUN</pattern><template>All those violent video games.</template></category><category><pattern>THAT WAS PROBABLY FOR THE BEST  CAUSE I LIKE YOU  COLUMBUS  BUT MY SISTER AND I ARE GOING TO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES TO SURVIVE SO</pattern><template>I was hoping Wichita was just playing hard to get,  / i    but I realized that she had more trust issues than I did.  / i    When I woke up the next day and she was leaving.  / i    You are like a giant cock blocking robot, developed in a secret fucking government lab.</template></category><category><pattern>OH HURRY  HURRY HE'S ON THE CEILING  COME GET HIM  OH</pattern><template>Light 'em up Murray.</template></category><category><pattern>I'M GOING TO PACIFIC PLAYLAND  WOO</pattern><template>Open Sesame.</template></category><category><pattern>YEAH I ALWAYS ROLL IT UP FROM THE BOTTOM</pattern><template>Yeah Zombies head is the cap.</template></category><category><pattern>COME ON  COME ON YOU UGLY BASTARDS</pattern><template>Holy Shit!</template></category><category><pattern>HE HAS HIS OWN MOVIE THEATRE</pattern><template>Ok, I'm gonna teach you a little something about Bill Murray.</template></category><category><pattern>I HAVE NEVER HIT A KID BEFORE  BUT I MEAN THAT'S LIKE ASKING WHO GANDHI IS</pattern><template>Who's Gandhi?</template></category><category><pattern>YES  I AM</pattern><template>Actually I think I'm jealous of your whole 1997.</template></category><category><pattern>HURRY</pattern><template>It seems like everyone who has ever been in a movie lives on this block.</template></category><category><pattern>TOO SOFT FOR ME ANYWAY</pattern><template>Oh, this is so exciting, you're about to learn who you're gonna call.</template></category><category><pattern>WHO WANTS TO GO FIRST</pattern><template>I really, really wanna impress Wichita,  / i    but it would be a direct violation of Rule 17, maybe the most important of all,  / i    Don't be hero.  / i    Why don't you take this one.</template></category><category><pattern>I THINK WE SHOULD PROBABLY JUST KEEP GOING</pattern><template>All I could think of was  What are the odds? .  / i    Another marriageable woman to bring home to the folks.  / i    Come quick.</template></category><category><pattern>WAS FULL OF UNDELIVERED PACKAGES</pattern><template>What was her name?</template></category><category><pattern>BACK EAST  YEAH</pattern><template>Yeah, you heard the same thing?</template></category><category><pattern>I WAS HOPING WICHITA WAS JUST PLAYING HARD TO GET   / I    BUT I REALIZED THAT SHE HAD MORE TRUST ISSUES THAN I DID   / I    WHEN I WOKE UP THE NEXT DAY AND SHE WAS LEAVING   / I    YOU ARE LIKE A GIANT COCK BLOCKING ROBOT  DEVELOPED IN A SECRET FUCKING GOVERNMENT LAB</pattern><template>I can't believe I almost kissed him. What's our rule?</template></category></AIML>