NARRATOR'. Africa.
This great, sprawling wilderness
is home to some of the planet's rarest
and most fascinating animals.
Some of these species are peaceful
and live closely with one another,
while others are aggressive
and frightening predators
who strike fear into the hearts
of the continent's wildlife.
We're going to follow
some of these incredible animals
and see how they survive
in this sometimes barren
and unforgiving landscape.
We will also witness
the hardships they encounter
and the relationships they build.
Some animals here
have learned to adapt to survive
in strange and unusual ways.
Others have to make great migrations
across the continent
in search of food and water.
Certain species build close
family bonds which last a lifetime,
utilising teamwork
and companionship to survive.
But others survive using aggression,
power and instinct.
Some survive simply
by taking what they can.
This is an ecosystem
of diversity and contrast
which supports
some truly amazing characters.
The challenges which this landscape
presents to some animals
has led to many astonishing
evolutionary adaptations
and highly specialised behaviour.
Land like this, known as savanna,
covers 20% of the globe.
Yet it is a land type
we know surprisingly little about.
Water, the supporter of life
and the habitat for many of Africa's animals.
But possibly the most surprising
thing about Africa
is the incredible struggles
these animals have to endure
to reach water and stay alive.
Dozens of different species
embark on continuous,
arduous journeys around the savanna,
travelling from water source to water source
simply to survive.
Nowhere on the globe is such
a massive journey embarked on
by such a vast amount of animals.
And nowhere on Earth
is the migration more dangerous.
With predators around every corner,
and danger even lurking in the one thing
that keeps them alive,
it is no wonder that so many animals
perish along the way.
To put this great migration into context,
let's look at a typical migration pattern
of the wildebeests over one year.
Travelling great distances
for months on end,
these animals continually circle
the Serengeti National Park.
Moving to and from each water source.
They have to continually keep travelling.
In a way, these animals
act as nature's calendar,
turning up at a different spot each month.
So these wildebeests truly are
nature's greatest travellers.
But when these great travellers
are joined by the zebras,
they become one of the most
impressive sights ever seen in nature.
But along the way the wildebeests pass
different African animals, like the hippos.
Although they may look peaceful,
hippos are one of Africa's most aggressive
and unpredictable animals.
The yawn they often display
is actually a form of intimidation.
Hippos like to group together in pods
which can contain up to 100 hippos.
These pods are usually led
by one dominant male.
A fully grown adult
can weigh up to three tons
and can run up to 18 miles per hour.
An adult hippopotamus can hold its breath
for up to 20 minutes,
swimming or walking along the riverbed
in order to avoid danger.
The name "hippopotamus",
or "hippo" for short,
is derived from
the ancient Greek for "river horse".
Hippos spend a lot of time in the water,
but also can spend months on end
out of the water, in the bush.
After passing most of their day
in or around water,
these hippos will move inland at night
to graze on short grass.
To most animals
this ferociously flowing river
would be incredibly dangerous,
but hippos are completely at home here.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
From water to land
here in Africa we can find some of
the most fascinating animals of our planet,
like the leopard.
Leopards are mysterious
and graceful creatures,
and live most of their lives alone.
She likes to hunt at night to stay hidden
and to avoid the heat of the day.
The leopard stalks her territory
slowly and stealthily,
using her patterned fur for camouflage
so she can get as close
to a prey as possible before pouncing.
Let's follow her for a while as she
searches for her dinner in the undergrowth.
These unsuspecting birds haven't realised
that the leopard is watching them.
She is too tired to hunt them
in the heat of the day.
She prefers to rest.
So, these helmeted guinea fowl
can wander further into the savanna
and pay a visit to the zebra family.
The zebra spends most of her day grazing.
She may look lonely here
but she is in fact part of a big group.
Here are the zebra's family and friends.
They like to stay together
because unlike the crocodile
and the leopard,
they are very vulnerable.
Like many animals living on the savanna,
zebras are very dependent
on water and grass
and spend a lot of their time migrating
to make sure they are always
near a source of quality food.
They're at their happiest when they have
a good place to cool off and have a drink,
but they often forget that crocodiles
are always vigilantly watching them.
Zebras are closely related to horses.
They are large single-hoofed ungulates,
built for speed and long-distance migrations.
Zebras typically stand about
47 to 55 inches at the shoulder.
This black rhino is still roaming
the plains alone, in search of drinking water.
Even though he is well adapted
to dry conditions,
he needs to find some water soon.
His sharp horns may look scary,
but he is in fact an herbivore
grazing on twigs, branches
and other plant life instead of eating meat.
Rhinos are only aggressive
if they are disturbed.
But they have been killed
by humans for centuries
as their horns are very valuable.
This makes them one of
the most endangered species on the planet.
Another herbivore
who calls the savanna home
is the gravity-defying giraffe.
Giraffes are the tallest
living mammals on Earth,
growing to a whopping height of 20 feet.
Although giraffes tend to spend a lot
of their time in groups,
they don't actually have
much of a bond with other giraffes.
Here we see a giraffe
grazing on the leaves of an acacia.
Her neck alone is two metres long
and has evolved over millions of years
so that she can reach
the leaves on the tallest trees.
The giraffe's large, bulging eyes
give it a wide, panoramic field of vision,
making them good at spotting predators.
As well as their incredibly long necks,
giraffes also have tongues
which can grow to 50 centimetres in length.
Like a human's fingerprint,
each giraffe has its own
individual fur pattern.
These complex patterns
give the giraffe camouflage
making them harder for predators to see.
As you can see there is no shortage
of food in this area.
And this is fortunate for her and her family,
because giraffes need to eat a lot
and graze not only on the leaves,
but also twigs
because they contain
more calcium and protein
which giraffes need to
sustain their rate of growth.
She also likes to eat grass, shrubs and fruit.
In all, giraffes are hungry animals,
eating around 34 kilograms
of foliage every day.
Giraffes digest leaves and the other foliage
they eat in a similar way to cows.
They like to chew the food up,
swallow it to help partially digest it
before passing it back into the mouth
for more chewing.
To satisfy their massive appetite,
the family are moving on
to the next set of trees.
But there are more great animals
to explore in Africa.
Here we see a new addition
to an elephant herd.
This young elephant is about two weeks old.
Like zebra foals, baby elephants are able
to stand and walk almost immediately.
This is to give them a better chance
against predators
and because elephants
tend to travel large distances,
so this youngster won't hold
the herd up too much.
The alloparents guide their young charges
to the next watering hole.
Elephants are highly dependent on water
and most of their lives are spent either
at a watering hole, or in search of another.
In addition, elephants cool themselves down
by flapping their ears.
Because it is so hot in the savanna,
elephants have developed large ear surfaces.
Let's join them taking their morning bath.
The long-living elephants have large brains
and are highly intelligent,
hence the expression
"An elephant never forgets".
The lives of male and female elephants
are very different.
The females form strong bonds with
one another and nurture their offspring,
while the males tend to
spend their time independently.
Sometimes they even leave their group
and join another group of elephants.
This elephant has left the water with a nice
coating of mud on her neck.
She knows that mud protects her
from the sun
and also acts as an insect repellent.
As the day wears on,
in the long grass of the savanna
different species move uninterrupted.
Here we see a cheetah,
one of the fastest animals in the world.
Cheetahs can reach speeds
of up to 75 miles per hour.
This cheetah spends most of her day resting
and sheltering from the hot African sun.
But unlike most cats of Africa,
she prefers to hunt in the daytime, too.
As you can see, the cheetah
is an animal built for speed.
She has a long, slender body,
which is extremely light
for an animal of her size.
She also has long legs, a flexible spine
and a very long tail to help her balance
as she is chasing her prey.
Witnessing a sunrise on the savanna
must be one of the most
glorious spectacles on Earth.
As the sunlight creeps
across the grasslands,
we become aware of all the wildlife
awakening to another exciting day.
One animal is always up early,
it's the spotted hyena in the search for food.
Most people think hyenas
are only scavengers,
who feed on the remains of animals
killed by other predators
such as the cheetah or the leopard.
However we have recently found out
that spotted hyenas
actually kill as much as 95%
of the food they eat themselves.
Hyenas can be quite ferocious animals
and have been known to fight off leopards
and sometimes even lionesses
in order to protect their food.
Hyenas have even been known
to attack humans.
- These are spotted hyena.
-(SNARLING)
They are the most sociable
of the hyena species
and also the best hunters.
Spotted hyenas
can weigh up to 75 kilograms,
certainly making them
a force to be reckoned with.
This romantic landscape
appears peaceful and quiet.
But this is deceiving,
because this lioness
is watching out for suitable prey.
What she doesn't know
is that her perfect meal is just over the hill.
These African buffalo are quite slow
and not very intelligent,
meaning they can be easily hunted
by predators like lions.
All the wildlife at this waterhole
are taking advantage of the cooling mud,
oblivious to all the dangers
lurking in the surrounding savanna.
Finally, the lion spots the buffalo
as they move away from the waterhole.
The buffalo slowly proceed on their way,
but one or two of them seem nervous.
They might sense
something is watching them.
African buffalo have what is called
a symbiotic relationship with small birds.
The buffalo offers food for the birds
in the form of bugs,
while receiving a cleaning service.
Suddenly, the lion and her sister
spring into action
and give chase to the large herd of buffalo.
The buffalo could probably
overcome the lions if they would co-operate.
This time, though, they escape.
Lions are very sociable animals
and live together in prides.
Apart from hunting and grooming each other,
they spend a lot of the day resting.
This is mostly to conserve energy
and in order to stay hidden.
Lions grow up together and form
extremely close family and friendship bonds.
(BOTH GROWLING)
Today, the sisters failed to bring
any food back to the pride.
So this lion might have to wait
a long time for his next meal.
But Africa has
more fascinating animals to offer,
like these baboons.
These chacmas baboons like to roam
around the savanna in groups
foraging for food.
With these baboons,
the social standing of a member
plays a large part in foraging decisions.
The most dominant members,
usually alpha males,
lead the rest of group and decide about
where to go in order to find food.
This youngster is enjoying a free ride
on his mother's back.
(SHRIEKING)
Once these baboons arrive at a good site,
they will display
collective foraging behaviour
in order to eat similar amounts
of food as each other.
Chacmas baboons
live in large social groups called troops.
Within a troop, male and female baboons
might form what are
referred to as "friendships".
Let's observe these little baboons
interacting with each other
climbing on an old tree,
like children at a playground.
Blissfully unaware in their innocent play
the monkeys are almost able to forget
that in the savanna there is
always something eerily watching you.
This ominous circling of birds
can mean only one thing.
- There has been a kill.
-(SCREAMING)
These opportunistic scavengers
have swarmed to the site of a kill
to try and steal some free food.
The victim is the African buffalo
which was killed by the hyenas.
This gruesome and bloody sight
is common in the wilds of Africa.
Scavenger birds like the marabou
and vultures congregate
at the top of this tree,
waiting their turn to grab some meat.
These marabou are primarily wading birds,
but are never ones to turn down a free meal.
Scavenging takes far less effort
and expends far less energy,
so most animals will take
the opportunity if it arises.
This hyena tries his best
to fend the vultures off,
knowing they will quickly eat his food.
The vultures are persistent though.
It'll take more than that
to scare them away from a meal.
The vultures' determination
eventually pays off
and while the hyenas are busy tucking in,
the vultures make their move
and swarm on the carcass.
Although the marabous
are taller than the vultures,
they can't match them in terms of
aggression and forcefulness
and are forced to watch from the sidelines.
The savanna is quiet
in the baking afternoon sun.
The wildebeests are still migrating.
These are blue wildebeests
and they are making the long,
exhausting migration
across land during the dry season
in order to find fresh grass for feeding.
During this migration wildebeests can be
very vulnerable to predators
such as leopards, cheetahs, spotted hyenas,
and the wily Nile crocodile.
Wildebeests tend to
group together in large herds
when the chances of being
attacked by a predator are high.
This herd is already spotted
by a leopard high in the trees.
It has noticed that one of the wildebeests
has an injured leg.
This will make it far easier
for her to catch and kill the animal.
Her demeanour changes
almost instantly from that of a lazy cat
to that of a highly motivated
and skilled killer.
She quickly climbs down from her
lookout post and into the undergrowth.
The leopard moves swiftly and efficiently,
treading gently to avoid making noise.
She is keeping a low profile to avoid
any attention from the wildebeests.
The vultures know what is about to happen
and amass in the hope of a free meal.
She makes sure to stay in the long grass,
using her camouflaged fur
to maximum effect.
She pounces instantly and goes straight
for the wildebeest's neck.
Her jaws clamp shut
around the wildebeest's windpipe
in order to suffocate the animal.
The vultures have watched
the entire violent episode
and know that a meal is well on its way.
The leopard finishes the hunt by carrying
the wildebeest into the long grass
to hide it from scavengers
and other predators.
Leopards like to store their kills away
so that they can eat them
over an extended period.
Sometimes they will have
several stored at once
and will feed between them.
Leopards have to make sure
that these carcasses
are extremely well hidden,
or as we've just seen,
there are countless scavengers
in this habitat
hungry and willing
to eat anything they can find.
The elephants have been forced
to move on from the water hole
to the barren and dry plains
in order to graze on grass
and other vegetative matter.
An adult African elephant
eats between 100 and 150 kilograms
of food every day
and spends around three quarters of its time,
day and night, eating.
This one uses her trunk
which is incredibly dexterous
to pull grass from the ground
and into her mouth.
- Elephants' tusks serve multiple purposes.
-(TRUMPETING)
These include digging,
debarking or marking trees,
clearing branches and foliage,
and when these peaceful giants
are forced to fight to protect their family,
the tusks become
a highly dangerous weapon.
Elephants have great control
over their trunks.
This powerful tool also enables the elephant
to breathe when in water,
to produce its well known
loud trumpeting sound
and to have an acute sense of touch.
But the most vital sense for elephants
is their sense of smell.
It is estimated that the elephants
sense of smell
is four times as sensitive as a bloodhound's.
The dry season can be particularly
punishing on the African plains
and many animals die from dehydration
or lack of food.
That's why migration
is their only hope to survive.
The wildebeests have finally
completed their long migration
in search of fresh grazing.
They've found a suitable watering hole
which they can drink from
after the long, dry walk.
The extraordinary, annual great migration
of wildebeests
is one of the
Seven New Wonders of the World.
Nowhere else is a movement of animals
as immense as the wildebeest's journey.
Wildebeests have evolved
so that their migration is timed to coincide
with the annual pattern
of rainfall and grass growth.
This way, wildebeests are staying
close to water supplies at all times.
While the wildebeests
are quenching their thirst,
this zebra is bonding with
the other zebras in her herd.
Alliances are valuable
in this harsh environment.
Because they are regularly thirsty,
zebras simply have no choice
and constantly have to face lurking dangers
such as crocodiles.
This crocodile stays low in the water
so that it isn't seen.
But this time it is spotted by the zebras
and the tribe manage to
escape with their lives.
One of the zebras was just
giving birth to a new life.
Female zebras, or mares, mature more
quickly than their male counterparts.
They are able to reproduce at as early
as three years old,
whilst males are not strong enough
to breed until they are around five or six.
Like horses, zebra foals are able to stand,
and walk slightly
almost immediately after birth.
This is an evolutionary development
to make them less vulnerable to predators.
Foals are born with brown and white stripes,
but these darken as they mature.
The foal is born connected to the placenta,
which the mother sometimes eats
after birth because it is rich in nutrients
and salt which the mother needs
after the strains of labour.
The placenta can also serve
as a nutritious treat for other animals.
These tawny eagles are
the first to notice this discarded organ.
But it's not long before
other birds get in on the act.
This vulture is larger than the eagles
and he always gets first pick
when it comes to food.
(SCREAMING)
Suddenly a feeding frenzy erupts
as more and more birds try and get
a piece of the free lunch on offer.
The eagles, who were first on the scene,
are forced to watch from the sidelines
as the vultures get their fill.
The foal huddles close to her mother.
These desperate, ruthless vultures are her
first experience of life on the African plains.
The zebras stay close to the foal,
instinctively protecting
the newest member of the herd
who will eventually understand her role
in the hierarchy of the local wildlife.
Let's discover what the new foal sees
in her first few moments of life.
Mother and daughter
take their first walk together.
The foal's walking abilities
so early on in life are quite incredible.
The mother takes her daughter
to the watering hole.
She is in desperate need of a drink
after the exhaustive effort of giving birth.
No animal has a more distinctive coat
than the zebra,
no two zebras are exactly alike.
There are a number of different theories
which attempt to explain the reason
for their eye-catching stripy coat.
Because of their uniqueness, stripes may
help zebras recognise one another.
The pattern may also make it difficult
for predators to identify
a single animal from a running herd
and distort distance at midday.
For an even safer journey,
zebras often join large herds of wildebeests.
This giant herd of wildebeests
is thousands strong,
covering the entire plain
as far as the horizon.
The calving season is well
on the way on the savanna.
Many animals now have young offspring.
The wildebeests are again on the move,
looking for the next source of water.
Even when they rest, cheetahs are
always on the lookout for potential prey.
The young cats pant to try and keep cool.
These young cheetahs are still living with,
and learning from, their mothers.
Their mother will bring injured prey
back to her young
to teach them hunting and killing skills
until she thinks they are ready
to brave the world alone.
After about 18 months
the mother will leave the cheetah cubs,
who will form a group known as a sib.
Two years later the female siblings
will leave the group
and the males will remain together,
sometimes throughout adulthood.
It is hard to imagine these furry cubs
will be agile killing machines
just two years from now.
With her young family to feed
she is constantly on the lookout for prey.
She's not, however, sure about
taking on the might of a wildebeest.
Instead, she spots
a Thomson's gazelle with her fawn.
Gazelles are one of
the cheetah's favourite meals.
The cheetah knows
that this encounter may well result in a kill
so she takes her cubs with her
to teach them how it's done.
Gazelles are extremely athletic animals
and can run at speeds up to
62 miles per hour.
This means normally
they have a fair chance against cheetahs
and escape around 50% of the time.
However, a springbok with a fawn
is far more vulnerable as the fawn cannot run
anywhere near as fast as her mother.
The cheetah has seen that the fawn has been
separated from her mother
and so chooses this moment
to launch her rapid attack.
Her incredible speed is clear to see
and she quickly catches up with the gazelle.
The gazelle weaves and dodges,
but the cheetah
is more than equal to the challenge,
using her great balance and reactions
to weave with the gazelle
before finally catching her.
This was barely a challenge for the cheetah,
but animals here will take any food they can.
It will also serve as a
valuable lesson for her cubs.
These growing cheetahs will have to absorb
many lessons from their mother
before trying to bring down
an animal on their own.
Cheetah cubs at this stage in their lives
have almost insatiable appetites
as they need a lot of protein,
fat and calcium to grow.
They have to eat their prey
as quickly as possible,
not because of small scavengers
like vultures and marabou,
but because of other larger predators,
such as lions, who are nearby.
But here they are all together
able to enjoy their family meal in peace.
The mother is careful to ensure
that the young cheetahs
gorge themselves on the prey,
as they may not get another meal
for a very long time.
Africa has more to offer.
Warthogs are also
very common in the Masai Mara.
This warthog is a member of the pig family.
They aren't particularly territorial animals
but instead occupy what is known
as a "home range" which they graze on
in groups called "sounders".
They have the distinctive feeding technique
of kneeling when grazing.
They are herbivores, meaning they feed
mostly on grass,
leaves, roots and other organic matter.
This lioness has spotted
one of the young warthogs
and, like the cheetah,
knows that young animals
are far easier to catch than adults.
This meal won't be enough to feed the pride,
but will boost her energy enough to help her
bring in the next large meal.
Suddenly her hunting instincts
swing into action.
The young Warthog notices the danger
and tries to escape.
His speed is no match for the lioness
and she makes light work of the hog.
Although this is only a small meal,
the other lionesses from her pride
still crowd around for a snack,
but she is in no mood to share.
Out of respect, they leave her
to enjoy her meal in peace.
These male impalas are enjoying
the fresh grass near the water.
The males are distinctive,
because of their large horns.
The females identified by their lack of horns,
are not far behind,
looking on over the grazing males.
But who are these guys, grazing with them?
Thomson's gazelles, who we've met before,
are sympatric to the impalas.
This means they sometimes
share the same territories
and live together peacefully.
These Thomson's gazelles are rutting,
which is an activity they perform annually
at the end of the rainy season
when they are in peak physical condition.
Males do this to assert their dominance
and to impress females.
There is a third mammal
that lives in our crew.
These are the kongoni.
They are related to both
gazelles and impalas,
who are all part of a species called Bovidae.
Kongoni are quite large mammals
with males weighing around 300 pounds
and females weighing around 260 pounds.
Topi, seen here, are more athletic
than they look
and can reach running speeds
of 50 miles per hour.
Male topi have horns
and the size of their horns helps determine
their social standing within the herd.
Unfortunately, this elegant descendant of
an antelope is threatened with extinction.
We can only hope that this young topi calf
will not fall victim to a cheetah or leopard.
This extraordinary looking animal
is called a common eland
and moves in herds of 10 to 30.
As well as its beautiful distinctive markings,
the eland can make itself stop sweating
in order to conserve water.
This is vital in an environment
where water is so scarce.
It is amazing to think that our group of
Bovidae together with the eland
can find enough nourishment in
the dryness of the savanna to survive.
This lioness, one of the many lionesses
in the pride, doesn't have a mane.
This is an example of sexual dimorphism
and means that it is extremely easy
to tell a male and female lion apart.
But this lioness has always been
the dominant male's favourite.
Lions do not mate
at any particular time of year
as female lions are polyestrous,
meaning they are able to conceive
at any time throughout the year.
These two regularly break away from
the pride and spend time alone.
While the two lions are hiding in the grass,
the hungry marabou and vultures
are circling nearby searching for food.
A gang of hyenas have made another kill,
this time out of the birds' vision.
Spotted hyenas develop sharp teeth
behind their crushing premolars.
This means that they can
hunt and kill live prey
instead of depending on the scavenging
of already dead animals.
By this time the pesky marabous
have found the scent of the kill.
Hyenas are voracious eaters
and their highly specialised jaws
and digestive systems mean that they
can absorb nutrients from skin and bones.
A hyena has the ability to eat almost
every part of a carcass apart from hair,
horns and hooves
and so when a group of hyenas
have finished eating,
there will be almost no trace
left of the carcass.
A couple of greedy marabous
are far easier to scare away than vultures
and this hyena makes light work of it.
Here, adult jackals travel back to
their burrows with their pups.
While raising their pups, jackals live in
disguised burrows of warthogs.
In their safe underground lair,
the jackals sleep sound at night,
protected from predators
such as leopards or cheetahs.
The zebra herd is preparing to migrate.
Several herds have joined together
to make the journey.
This crocodile thinks he has found
a perfect place
where the migrating zebra and wildebeests
will make their crossing.
The zebras have joined the wildebeests
and gather at the water's edge
to make the crossing.
Their instinct is making them reluctant
to venture into the water.
On this occasion, the crocodile
has missed out on the opportunity.
The herd is moving away
from the river for now.
About 110 days have passed
since we saw the two lions alone.
This period of time is about the average
for a lioness pregnancy.
She has now given birth to two new cubs,
the result of her mating.
Lionesses like to give birth in
a secluded area, away from the pride.
Cubs are vulnerable to attack from
jackals, snakes, eagles, leopards
and even other lions.
Lion cubs are born blind, and can't
use their eyes until about a week after birth.
Cubs are essentially helpless
for the first few weeks of their lives,
relying almost completely on
their mothers to keep them alive.
Usually a lioness won't
introduce her cubs to pride life
until they are six to eight weeks old.
This is so she can care for them
in the safety of their hides
without interruption
from other pride members.
Mum is sure to move her cubs between
several different hides every month.
This is to prevent a scent from building up
which could alert potentially
predatory animals to their whereabouts.
She can move her cubs
by picking them up in her mouth.
This may look painful for the cubs,
but they have particularly loose and stretchy
skin on the nape of their necks.
It is in this manner that Mum
moves her cubs between hideouts,
carrying them one by one
from one hideout to another.
It is only after three weeks
that they begin to walk.
This is very different from some of
the species we've seen before
like zebras and elephants,
whose young can walk
almost immediately after birth.
This is because lion cubs are kept
in the relative safety of a hide
for the first few weeks of their lives.
These cubs will have
many challenges ahead of them.
As many as 80% of lion cubs die
before they reach maturity.
It's not only the lioness that has found
a partner and given birth.
The solitary leopard also must
increase the population.
She has chosen a partner
and they make their way into the long grass.
As you can see, there is
a certain level of sexual dimorphism
between male and female leopards,
with the male being
far larger than the female.
Like lions, leopards are
able to mate all year round.
Leopards stay pregnant for between
90 and 105 days,
and like to give birth
in caves or hollow trees.
Leopard pairs stay together for several days
when mating and even hunt together.
While they are alone, they will mate
several times a day.
(CHIRPING)
The herd of wildebeests and
zebra are yet to make their river crossing.
The largest known herd of wildebeests
numbers over one million animals.
In human terms, this is almost
the entire population of Manhattan.
However, the members of our herd
are still amassing at the banks of the river.
After a while, some brave zebras
take their first tentative steps
into the fast-flowing current.
It is immediately apparent
that this river crossing
is going to be incredibly dangerous
for these animals.
Each year, 1.5 million wildebeests
go on a long trek
in search for food and water,
and unfortunately, every year
an estimated 250,000 animals
don't make it to their destination.
So, the chances of being picked off
along the way are very high.
More and more animals
congregate at the river's edge
and the scene grows chaotic.
Although it may look to be completely
disorganised, random and frenetic,
recent research has found that
herds of animals crossing rivers
actually possess "swarm intelligence",
whereby the animals work together
as a group to try and overcome obstacles.
The hurry with which these animals
have crossed the river
has created somewhat of a traffic jam
on the river's far bank.
This means that some of the animals remain
trapped in the river, leaving them vulnerable.
The animals take confidence
from seeing their fellow creatures
successfully cross the river,
and more and more wildebeests
and zebra wade into the water.
However it may not be
as simple for some as it looks.
This massive gathering of animals
has not gone unnoticed by this crocodile.
He and his friends
congregate slightly downstream
waiting for an animal caught in trouble
to come their way.
The river's flow grows increasingly ferocious
and some of the animals are at real risk
of being swept downstream.
Some of the weaker swimmers in the group
begin to struggle
and are dragged
further and further from the far bank,
which they are trying to reach.
The zebra and wildebeests
have to swim extremely hard
to avoid being swept away
by the fast moving water.
Some of the animals,
although physically exhausted,
manage to make it to the other side
by the narrowest of margins.
This animal unfortunately
was not strong enough
and is captured by the crocodiles.
This wildebeest has managed to
successfully cross the river,
but now finds itself stranded
on the ledge of the far bank,
unable to reach the higher ground.
Wildebeests communicate visually, vocally,
and also through the sense of smell.
A male's bellow can be heard
up to 1.5 miles away.
The members of the herd use secretions
in order to guide fellow wildebeests
during their journey.
This way the stragglers further behind
the herd will know which direction to go.
As we can see here, in our herd,
no one animal is left behind.
While some of the last stragglers
continue to complete the crossing
the herd continues its long
and arduous migration across Africa.
The vast variety of life across Africa
is plain to see
for anyone who is lucky enough
to observe it.
From giant water dwellers,
to ferocious cats stalking and hunting
their prey from trees and bushes.
Right through to the simple herbivores,
the motherland of all life is still, as ever,
a metropolis of different species.
Each creature has its own journey
and its own story to tell.
Each animal, no matter
how ferocious or deadly,
will have to battle through
bad times as well as the good.
The ever changing
environment that they live in
can be plentiful and barren, dry and wet,
and these animals must be precise
with all their decisions.
We have taken you
across the African savanna
and showed you some of
the amazing characters who live there.
We have seen their struggles
and how they survive,
how they work together
or how they prefer to live apart.
We have witnessed an annual cycle of birth
and death,
along with daily life on the plains.
But what unites these animals is not merely
a matter of finding food and surviving,
but in the modern age, their great challenge
is that of avoiding extinction.
Let's hope all the animals we have seen
will continue to thrive on the savanna
for a long, long time to come.