THE TRUE STORIES IN THIS FILM
WERE COLLECTED DURING
A LONG PERIOD OF RESEARCH
AND ARE PLAYED
BYACTRESSES AND ACTORS.
THE ORIGINAL TESTIMONIES
WERE NOTALTERED.
So... she was seven.
She had childhood-onset diabetes.
She passed out,
but actually
she went into cardiac arrest.
This daughter was seven
and my younger one was four.
Then it was all over.
l lost my bearings.
My husband, poorthing...
Soon after she died,
he left hisjob.
So our lives stopped.
We had no money.
No money at all.
He started to drink.
He'd come home plastered.
And he wasn't
the typical cliché drunk.
He'd come home mute.
He wouldn't say a word.
So l became
more and more aggressive.
ln a really destructive way.
ln an evil way, you know?
Really bad.
l've always been
very aggressive.
Maybe it was a defense of mine.
So when l bought something,
l'd tell him,
''See, l bought this.
You can't buy that.''
And in the meantime,
he got back his self-esteem.
So when l hurt him,
he hurt me back.
l stood it, he stood it.
l rememberthat one day...
l don't knowwhat l said,
but l said something...
and he pushed me.
He pushed me,
so l pushed him back.
And l said, ''You can't talk
to me like that.''
l was feeling my oats.
He didn't hesitate,
he grabbed me,
he lift me up,
and threwme against the wall.
l hit the wall very hard.
l was bruised all over.
All over.
He left home,
and l went to my brother's house.
This was about 3:00 AM.
And l was crying, crying.
And the next day,
l asked him to leave.
He went to his parents' home
in Santo André.
Two months later,
everything l wanted
to happen before,
happened then.
We had a daughter, Juliana...
He would call
to get news about her.
But he called in a nice way.
''Let's talk.'' You know?
So we started dating.
We dated about
four or five months.
lt was the best time of my life.
And a real mature passion
came out ifthis.
So respectful.
We'd talk about everything,
even about what happened.
We talked about it.
So one day he said,
''l shouldn't have done that,
but you knowhowl am...
l have these outbursts,
l really have a temper,
but you provoked me.''
And l did,
l did provoke him.
What kind ofthings
he belittle about you?
-At that time?
-Yeah.
He belittled everything.
The silliest,
most cliché thing...
For instance...
you cut your hair.
And he doesn't say anything.
lt can't be
that he didn't notice.
Ok, l believe,
he doesn't notice.
Bit it's horrible.
lt's horrible.
Oryou make this big effort
to lose seven pounds. Seven.
lt's real hard
to lose seven pounds.
So you put on tight clothes
to get his attention,
and he doesn't say a word?
He sawit, noticed it,
but didn't say a word.
That pissed me off.
When we got back together,
one day, l asked him,
''Marcos, why haven't you ever
praised me?
How can we have a relationship
ifl don't feel admired by you?
He said, ''l admire you.''
l told him,
''But you have to say it.''
''l do?''
''Of course you do''
And he said, ''So you're
that kind of person...''
Howwas it? He said...
''So you're that kind of person
who always needs a compliment?''
As if needing a compliment
was a bad thing.
That really messed
with my head,
but l mustered the courage
and said,
''Marcos, l need compliments.
l need compliments,
the Yankees fans need compliments,
everyone needs compliments.''
And there is
this otherthing...
l had a problem,
l worked a lot.
l was always a bit negligent
caring forthe kids and the house,
and he took that,
he used that.
Because...
that would be my big flaw.
The impossibility of caring
for my girls,
sitting, playing with them.
This kind of...
maternal thing really.
Actually,
l never had the patience.
l don't have
a lot of patience for that.
l'm not very maternal.
So l'd get home and say,
''l got more money.
l won another case.''
''Your daughter Juliana waited
at school until six o'clock.''
So he kept working
on lowering my self-esteem.
When we got back together...
you knownobody
changes over night.
So what happened?
We could only continue
being the same people
because it was very clear to me
the bad things that he did.
Maybe he does it to this day.
You knowthose women
who love to get beaten?
l began to wonder
ifl was one.
l don't like
getting beat up.
But sometimes
l think it's necessary.
You knowkids who need
a smack to knowtheir limits?
l think it was a bit like that.
And there's something else
l worked on in therapy.
lt's the possibility
of really being a woman.
From the moment l took on
my role as a woman,
my relationship,
and everything else...
My relationship improved.
So you had to be beaten
to take on your role as a woman?
Exactly.
And he took on the man's role
after he hit me.
Because he started bringing
money in, paying the bills.
But when you said
you took on the woman's role,
what exactly is that?
l can't really explain it.
One day my therapist asked me,
''Why did you marry him?''
l told her, ''Fuck,
he's real cute, he's gentle.''
And she asked,
''Why don't you showthat to him?''
So l became a nicer person.
Despite being very aggressive
my whole life,
l found out that
l can be a gentle person.
A very gentle,
caring, and romantic person.
l started to laugh,
l became happier, a fun person.
l mock everything.
So l had this reunion
with my delicacy, you know?
lt was really nice.
When l went to bed,
l started to hug Marcos,
to run my hand over his hair.
lfl noticed he was strange,
was a little down,
l'd say to him,
''What's going on?''
Gently, really gently.
An open attitude.
That was nice.
That changes a lot.
That makes a world of difference.
Of course, all this
had a beginning.
To me it had a very clear start.
My mother was beaten up.
When l was a boy,
l sawmy mother being beat up
by people she had
relationships with.
And a certain person
beat my mother badly.
To the point ofleaving
my mom in the middle ofthe street,
fallen, passed out,
and all that.
Up until l was 15, 16,
l went through this.
l wanted to kill people
who did this to my mother.
l actually picked up a gun
to shoot the guy
who did that to my mother...
who wasn't my father.
My father hit her a fewtimes,
because...
There's nojustification,
but actually my mom
drove my father crazy.
My mom...
my mom humiliated him.
My father was a naval officer
and she'd say, ''You're illiterate.
l'm forced to live in the suburbs,
in this miserable life,
when l wanted to live
in a good neighborhood,
and have a good life.
But you can never give me anything
because you're a crummy NCO,
from a poorfamily,
with no money.''
ln fact, my mother's family
was poortoo.
Because herfather hit her a lot
when she was a girl.
So she rebelled
against the husband
as a way to rebel
against her dad.
Or maybe imitate him.
l mean,
nowl see things like that.
And l myself began to hit girls
l was dating.
Which was one way to redeem
my mom for being beat up.
When l was 18, l remember
l hit my girlfriend.
Kid stuff, jealousy,
lack of respect.
But she also hit me,
jealous of some girl.
She tried to slap me,
but l was quicker
and hit her.
So l got used to hitting her,
l hit her several times.
That's something l regret.
She was a good girl,
a great person.
l started dating this guy
when l was 16.
He was my first boyfriend,
he was 20 years old.
l thought l was
an angel in his life.
The first strange thing
that happened was like this...
We had a group
that used to go out to dance.
l went out one day,
but l said l wouldn't dance.
l went to the bathroom
and there was this guy
from the group.
He asked me to dance
and l said okay.
l danced with the guy.
My boyfriend looked radiant.
We left,
but he didn't say anything.
lt took him 3 months
to mention it.
But every time he mentioned it
we'd argue.
''That day you said
you wouldn't dance, but you did.''
And then the threatening
tone began.
He'd say, ''You think l didn't do
anything to that guy?''
And l wondered ifhe really
did something.
Was he capable
of doing something?
l still believed
he could change.
Then came the time
when l realized
he was never going to change.
So l tried to break up.
l tried, but he started
to threat me even more.
He said he'd kill me,
kill my uncle,
my mother, my whole family.
At first you hear that
and you think,
''l'm going to turn my back
and walk away.
This guy is nuts.
Just let him talk.
But it's not so easy.
Because there was a history.
There was this personality
problem l began to notice.
l didn't knowwhen
he was telling the truth
and when he was threatening me
so l'd be afraid ofhim.
Time went on and l became
addicted to beating people.
The women l dated,
the women l had sex with.
Sometimes, l became violent.
lfthe girl didn't like it,
l'd take a step back.
But if she liked it,
l had no limits.
l could really hurt her.
And this comes from something
that has no explanation.
lt can become an addiction,
a pattern.
No, no, l have two lovely,
marvelous girls.
But unfortunately
l hurt my wife a lot.
After my children were born,
l stopped hitting her.
l mean, l didn't stop
being an aggressive person.
Other kinds
of aggression continued.
But the heavy
boxer type of aggression ended.
This is something
that really stayed with me.
The fact that l hit my wife.
Awoman who only did
good things for me,
who loved me,
and who l loved back.
But l had the nerve to hit her.
That's something l can't forgive,
that has no explanation.
l don't knowif you've gone
through something like that.
lf you haven't, thank God.
But it doesn't depend
on anything out ofthe ordinary.
These things come from
the most trivial human relations.
The desire to hurt.
Everything is an excuse,
There's the need to hurt.
lt's almost physiological.
lt's like our need...
to eat... to shit...
to piss... to fuck...
Get it?
lt's a need to hurt.
But afteryou satisfy
this awful instinct,
you regret it.
And there are people who don't,
which is worse.
Can you excuse me a minute?
Hi, honey. Yeah.
No, l'm doing the interview
l told you.
REENACTMENTOF A SITUATION
THAT OCCURRED DURING THE RESEARCH
She wants to continue
listening to the conversation.
ls that okay?
Sex was something l did
to calm him down.
l didn't want to do it,
l couldn't bear looking at him.
So l kept making up excuses.
One week passed, two,
by the third week,
he wanted to beat me.
So l did it.
But l couldn't let it show
that l didn't want to do it.
He asked if it was
an obligation for me.
''No, why are you saying that?''
He said, ''l can tell
you didn't want it.''
lfl said l did,
he'd get medieval on me.
That was my defense mechanism.
l used to say,
''Today l have to want it.''
Because then he'd be calm
and l could have some peace.
l worked as a dentist
for a long time.
Physically, l have no doubt
women are stronger than men.
Women's resistance to pain
is much greaterthan men's.
Men would piss themselves
to sit on my chair.
Women didn't even blink.
Very fewwomen
ever showed any fear.
Men used to offer me money
to not feel any pain.
Men are really
sons oftheir mothers!
They have to get rid
of this fucking Oedipus,
this dependency,
this umbilical cord.
Men have to emancipate themselves
orthey'll go on making women suffer.
Because usually
the man can't give love.
He doesn't know
howto love back.
He's selfish, you know?
Because the best place is his,
the best food is his,
the TV channel is his,
and that's fucked up.
l say this and it sounds
like l'm this model citizen,
but l'm not. l suffer
from all these things.
l'll need a fewincarnations
to heal this stuff.
There was this situation
around the end of last year,
close to the end.
l called him and asked him
not to come to pick me up,
because my father was coming.
So he asked why.
l told him
my father was coming.
And the threatening tone
started again,
my stomach would be
in knots instantly.
He said he was coming
because l'd done something wrong.
So he came to pick me up
and l couldn't react.
Because l did everything
he told me to.
He said, ''l'm picking you up.''
l said okay.
Because l was very afraid
ofhis reaction.
So l couldn't go against
anything he said.
l got in the car and he said,
''We're going to my house
and you're taking off your clothes
and ifl find any marks
that showyou betrayed me,
you'll regret
having been born.''
He kept saying that
and it got into my head,
because l knew
l hadn't done anything,
but l was thinking,
''My God, something
is going to happen.''
l was sure of it.
he was going to find
some invisible mark.
We got to his house,
and l turned around for him,
he was looking at me and said,
''What is this?''
l said, ''The mark of my bra.''
Then he said, ''Okay.''
As ifl was a piece of meat
on display,
a rotisserie chicken
turning around.
l got dressed, l went home.
He was going to take me, and said,
''l'm not taking you home.
lf you go home, you're going
to see TV and laugh.
So you're coming to my house
and stay there with no TV.''
He took me, shut the door,
turned the TVoff
and we were there
till midnight.
All this because
he didn't want me to laugh.
lt was very crazy,
he couldn't stand me to be happy.
That was his objective.
lt's a fact. One thing
is the psychological,
the other is the physical.
And they mess with you so much
that you actually believe it.
Sometimes l stop
and l think,
''l did something wrong,
l'm the guilty one.''
l've always been very jealous.
My thing isjealousy.
l'm very jealous.
She's here,
on the phone with me.
She lives in Spain
and l live in Brazil.
lt's hard.
Man, this is something
very private.
Forthe love of God.
Not that l'm hiding her
from anyone.
l'm still living
with my ex-wife.
We're actually separated.
Not legally, but we are.
l want the best for my ex
and she wants the best for me.
That to me is a victory.
To be friends,
after we separated.
And why did you want
your girlfriend to hear all this?
Because l'd already had episodes
of violence with her.
For what reason?
The same thing that always
moves me with women.
My insecurity,
excessivejealousy,
a need to punish.
l think this
goes back to my mother,
it's a hard thing to resolve.
You want to know something?
l think my mother deserved
the beating she got from my dad.
Not from the other guy,
but from my dad.
My mother drove
my father crazy.
And he wasn't a guy
to hit women.
She humiliated him,
attacked him physically,
hit him in the face,
broke his comb,
ran it on his face,
stamped on his clothes,
threwthem down in the mud.
There came a moment
when he lost control,
he hit her back.
So he hit her with a...
The guy was a naval officer,
a boxer, fucking strong.
My mom was skinny, 86 pounds.
The first time he hit her,
he broke her denture.
l'll tell you,
it's tragic and it's comic.
lt's comic.
You knowas a filmmaker,
that nothing is so tragic
that isn't also comical.
Now, after so many years,
l can find it funny.
My father broke my mom's
and the maid's dentures.
l mean, it was a lot of damage.
But it was profitable
forthe dentist.
The maid tried to help my mom,
my father hit the maid too.
And also broke her denture.
THE INTERVIEWEE
KEPTTHE CELL PHONE AT HIS EAR
DURING THE WHOLE
RESEARCH INTERVIEW
This movie can turn
into a comedy.
Are you satisfied?
lt was clingy.
From my part it was clingy.
And men, when they get clingy...
l think that was my mistake.
l really fell for her!
l spent 15 days in her home.
l left my wife, my kids,
to be with her.
The mother of my kids said
it was a complicated moment
in our relationship.
Because l've been married
with her for 28 years, man.
l raised five kids with her.
And there are two small ones.
That complicated it even more
to suddenly be living
with the mistress.
So once l was close to Butantã,
going by her house.
Then l called her.
She asked me to bring
something from the market for her.
l went to the market
and bought what she asked.
As l was leaving the market,
l sawthis guy who lived
close to her.
And he came with this boy.
lt was really hot that day.
So l said, ''Hey, Júlio,
don't you want a ride?
Come in
and l'll take you there.''
So l dropped the guy off
and got late at her house.
She blewup, man.
She exploded.
She was with her girl.
She went to the door screaming.
All the houses
are close to each other.
So l kind of pushed her back.
And she called her mother,
this time she did.
She never called.
And she went to the precinct
to make a complaint.
That's when she asked
for a restraining order.
Why didn't she come to me?
Why didn't she tell me
about that restraining order?
lt could have been
just a thing ofthe moment.
But at the time,
l didn't understand that.
l started to drink.
l felt really bad
with the restraining order.
We had another date,
we had ice cream,
me, her, and her little girl.
She has a three-year-old.
Actually,
l'm the girl's godfather.
l baptized her.
Got it?
What was the incident
that made you lose control?
She worked on a Sunday.
No, she worked from Saturday
to Sunday.
She says she did.
She worked,
but she didn't call me.
That made me wonder...
lt began to influence me.
She never stopped
at the pay phone.
Was it so hard to call me?
Even if she had no cell on her.
She could find a pay phone
and say,
''Paulo, l'm doing a night shift.
l'm working all night.''
Was it so hard
for herto call me?
Tell me.
So l became suspicious.
l was very suspicious
from then on.
l had spent
that whole night drinking.
l drank all morning...
Then l got there.
When l got there,
it was normal.
She opened the door,
treated me fine.
Because on other days,
she shut the door,
she wouldn't let me come in.
So when l got there,
l told her,
''Don't tell yourfather
l'm here.''
Then she picked up the phone
and called herfather.
And herfather called the cops.
Howis that for you?
Call the fucking police?
Why didn't he talk to me?
l hadn't killed her.
l wouldn't have done
anything bad with her.
That was when it hit me.
Man, to call the police?
l got her like this
and l hurt her a lot
with a knife.
She survived.
She's back to work.
And l felt very sick.
She sent me away.
l got one ofher clothes
because mine was all bloodied.
l really felt sick.
l fell on the sidewalk.
The sun was boiling hot.
The neighbors came
and threw cold water on me.
Their landlord came
and took me to the hospital.
Ever since we were together,
she said she didn't love me.
But that day there was a moment
when she said, ''l love you.''
l was trying to hit her,
on the bed,
and the little girl showed up.
That's when she managed
to push me with her feet.
She pushed me,
and l stood by the door.
She stood there at the sink.
She said, ''Oh, l love you.
Why are you doing this?''
Man, at that moment, l...
l threweverything up,
l threwthe knife.
l lost it.
l couldn't think of anything.
l was crazy.
lt was an impulse.
My emotions were on fire.
Angertoo.
There are a lot oflaws
to protect women.
l want a law
with my name on it.
Alawto protect men too.
One day, we were with a bunch
of people at a college party.
and when she got to the door,
she didn't want to come in.
l didn't want either.
So she decided to give me
a ride home,
and when she got to my home
l decided to kick it off.
l told her,
''Why don't we try it?''
And she said again that
we were friends and stuff.
And it was funny because
l told her to have a friend's kiss.
This story is great.
And so we kissed.
lt was amazing.
There was an awesome chemistry.
At the time,
my mother was out oftown,
so we locked ourselves in my room
until 4 p.m. the next day.
That year we decided
to spend New Year's together.
But she was going to Búzios,
with her family.
We decided to go as friends.
From the start, they weren't
receptive because of my piercings.
From the start, her family
wasn't very welcoming.
And her parents didn't like
us staying in her room for hours.
And we did.
lmagine the two of us
at her parent's beach house
locked in the room
until 3:30 p.m.
lt was a bit too much.
We were being
a little too obvious.
But come on,
we were too blind.
lt was this fascination,
all this desire.
l've never had that either.
Being so happy
with someone in bed.
With her l discovered
newlevels of orgasm.
You know, female ejaculation,
stuffl'd never experienced.
So it was very strong.
But there was this controversy
in the house...
''Your friend isn't cool.''
So l called my mom
who was in Cabo Frio.
l asked herto come visit me
so people wouldn't think
l had no family.
So she brought me a box of Xanax,
because l had run out.
And this was normal.
For my family, it was fine.
l'd been taking it
since l was 15.
So l left the thing
on the table,
her parents sawit
and were horrified.
They told Júlia, ''See, yourfriend
is crazy, she takes drugs.''
They had a fight
and l was watching it all.
But Júlia told them
l was her girlfriend.
l decided to wait outside
the house.
lt was December 31st,
the rain was pouring,
l went to drink something
at a nearby beach kiosk.
Something awful happenned...
l was at the kiosk,
drinking and talking
with the guy selling drinks.
lt must have been around 6 p.m.
There was no one on the beach.
l was talking to this guy
and l felt the need to go pee.
So l went behind the kiosk.
When l bent down, l sawhim coming
to fuck me from behind.
l pushed the guy and ran off
towards Júlia's house.
But l tripped,
fell down and passed out.
Then came her sister,
who was also very uptight,
l wasn't herfriend or anything.
She came and took me back
to her parents' place,
and you can imagine.
They already had
a lot of prejudice against us,
they sawme in this situation
and it only got worse.
Luckily, l had this old friend
living on the same street.
Julia and her sister took me
to this girl's house.
l spent the night
at my friend's.
But the next day
we packed ourthings,
put it in the car
and went to Rio.
l gained about 90 pounds
during my relationship with her.
That made me very insecure.
l became very jealous,
very possessive.
So l developed a serious
self-esteem problem.
And besides beingjealous
and possessive,
l started cheating on her.
Not because l didn't want
to be with her,
l did,
but l had to boost my ego,
l felt the need
to be wanted.
l wanted to have
hot girls desiring me.
At the time,
it was my solution to...
boost my self-esteem.
That created more stress,
more shouting, more fights.
l cheated on her, felt guilty
and told her about it.
And she lost control,
She started to hit me,
punch me
call me a bitch,
a real shouting.
She realized the drug thing
was getting out of control for us.
We decided to stop
snorting together.
But she did it and l didn't.
We would go out,
at a certain point
she'd leave and l'd stay.
This gap brought on more drugs,
more cheating and stuff.
Once l got home at 6 p.m.
thinking it was 6 a.m.
l got home and she was
out of her mind, desperate,
aggressive, shouting,
''Where were you?!''
l didn't knowwhere l was,
l was totally deranged.
l came in and she was
punching me hard.
l remember l went to bed
and lay down on my stomach,
covered my face and she
jumped on me hitting me.
l just felt the pain...
in my back and my neck.
l felt l deserved those punches,
l felt she was right.
ln that situation, ifl could
l would have helped her.
Then there was...
another situation.
We were going through
a calmer phase.
She decided
to invite some friends
and have a party at home
to showthe apartment.
And that day l woke up sick
with the runs.
But so far, so good.
These were her childhood friends.
But this girl
from college called,
a girl l was sure
was into her.
That was crazy because the girl
never showed any interest...
The girl called Julia
who then invited her over.
l lost control. l felt awful.
l was totally enraged.
''Why did you call this girl
today when l'm feeling sick?''
l picked up a glass
and threwit on the wall.
You're having a party?
Let's see a party
without glasses!''
And l broke
every glass in the house.
Then what happened?
All the girls showed up,
l felt better, we went out,
bought some plastic cups,
had this huge party,
and there is this picture
of me with the girl,
with my arm around her
during the party.
lt was such a crazy moment.
You didn't try to heal yourself
ofthat possessiveness?
She was also possessive.
She was very possessive.
She was less aggressive than me,
but she hit me too,
and she poisoned me
against everyone.
Especially against my mother,
my family.
Because she wanted me
just for her,
that was her way
ofbeing possessive.
lt was a symptom
ofher possessiveness.
She wanted me
all to herself.
We each acted differently.
ln my possessiveness,
l would throwglasses.
She poisoned me against everyone
and l let myselfbe poisoned.
Because when l started
to believe
she was the only one
who really believed in me,
l gave her words
absolute power.
lt was an obsessive,
possessive relationship.
lt's very funny
because the sex,
right until the end,
it solved everything.
And in the middle of everything,
when we had sex,
everything was erased.
lt was like a compensation.
The crazy thing is our sex
also grewmore violent.
We enjoyed hitting each other
during sex,
scratching each other,
burning our backs with wax.
But that was good.
That was pleasure.
Usually when l got nervous,
l broke things.
But l won't say l never hit her,
because l did.
Once l tore her clothes.
Not the ones in the closet,
but those she was wearing.
lt was as ifthis hitting
wasn't important,
because we enjoyed so much
the good moments we still had.
But when you hit in anger,
did you feel like killing?
No, it wasn't like that.
lt wasn't anger.
We didn't want
to kill each other,
it was a feeling
of misunderstanding.
''l want to get along with you,
but you're not understanding
what l'm saying.''
And so we did that
to come closertogether.
Even when we fought,
we thought we'd spend
the rest of our lives together.
We thought we'd go to Barcelona
to get really married.
Till one day she woke up early
and l was screwing someone else
in the living room.
But what really split us up
was this drug thing.
Because she was getting clean
and l got deeper into it.
And l became
more and more promiscuous.
And she became disgusted with this
and we stopped having sex.
That's when our balance stopped.
l wanted to have sex with her,
but she couldn't do it with me.
lt hurt me so much,
l brought someone into our house.
So, of course,
she decided to leave.
She said she wasn't
leaving for good
but we needed
some time apart.
Because we never split up.
That day she said,
''l love you,
we will be together,
l need some time alone.''
So l cut myself all over.
She came help me and l said,
''Go away, l don't need you!''
Then she called me at my mother's,
she talked to me,
said she liked me,
that we would be together,
we'd never be apart...
But we were splitting up.
We didn't want to see it
because it was inconceivable,
so we kept feeding this fantasy
that everything was fine.
Till the day she started
seeing someone else.
That was the end for me.
lt was over.
Of all the relationships l had,
this was the most intense,
and the most pleasurable,
also because l was very young...
When you discover
you love someone,
you feel it's the most
important thing in the world.
That it's never going
to happen again.
And truly, if l'm honest,
l can tell you,
am l better off today?
l am,
but it never happened again.
And when you cut yourself,
what did you feel?
l think it was a lot of things.
l felt guilty because l let
my life come to this point.
l did this to myself.
l ran out of money,
l got addicted,
my family didn't want me,
l had no more friends around
when the relationship ended.
So it was also something
to punish myself.
And l wanted to showJulia,
''See what you did to me.''
lt's one thing
ifl say l'm suffering,
it's another
if you see blood everywhere.
lsn't it?
Also, when you have
something that hurts inside,
you can't put on a Band-Aid,
a salve, get stitches.
There's nothing you can do.
But on the outside you can,
so you...
Do you get it?
lf you see one pain,
it softens the other.
But that's something
l only realized a short while ago.
You tried to manipulate her
by cutting yourself.
Yeah.
l learned to manipulate with her.
She was good at that.
l was 14 then.
l lived at Leme,
l never had a boyfriend
and l met Fernando at a party.
So it started.
Like every relationship
in this town, dancing and stuff.
He was very strong,
a body builder.
At that time, l had
a very repressive upbringing.
l couldn't go to the movies,
go out at night.
Fernando would pick me up
at school, we walked home.
Actually, l learned
howto masturbate thanks to him,
because he taught me
howit was done.
But there was this detail.
There was violence in my house
from my father
towards my brother and l.
One day l was going
to a ballet class with my mom
and this stranger in the street
asked her about my bruises.
She said l had fallen,
got hurt,
but l said my father
had hit me.
l told the truth
to that complete stranger.
And the fact
that l wasn't scared
is what made
my father lose control.
l actually think he...
he loved us a lot,
but that made things worse.
We couldn't separate the love
from the occasional violence.
l think it's hard for a man
to be violent from the start.
Violence is an insidious thing,
it appears little by little
as the man realizes
he has power overthe woman.
Or as he grows so insecure
that he getsjealous
to the point of releasing
this latent violence...
We all have a latent violence.
We're capable of doing
all sorts ofthings,
but we're educated,
civilized,
and we learn to contain
our violence.
And a sick, uncontrolled person
can't control that violence.
Fernando started getting violent
because ofjealousy.
l was a virgin
and l stayed a virgin,
l didn't have sex with him.
But despite being 14,
l was always very big, pretty.
l used to draw
people's attention.
That was a wound in his soul,
he couldn't take it.
When he picked me up at school,
he had a lot of questions,
Where did you go?
With whom?
Anyone talked to you?
Anyone messed with you?
Where are you going?
l began to realize
he wasn't very normal.
But when it becomes
a little too constant
you're already in love.
So you can't tell
where the love ends
and where the violence starts.
lsjealousy a sign oflove
or is it violence?
So when l said
l wasn't going to answer,
he would pinch me,
grab my arm.
When he sawhe was really
hurting me,
he'd apologize
and say he wouldn't do it again.
And l think that
at that time...
l was beautiful, attractive,
and wouldn't put an end to it...
because of my family history.
Because l was used to being
submitted to a relationship
of power and aggression,
and love at the same time.
So l thought it was normal
to a point,
when l was pinched
or slapped.
But when he started to
pull my hair real hard,
and l had hair
down to my waist,
that really started to hurt.
And l thought, ''lfl ever marry
this guy, he'll kill me.''
But l insisted...
because it was good.
lt felt nice.
So you think that violence
was attractive to you,
did you like it a bit?
No, l don't think l thought
violence was attractive, but...
The fact is my father hit me,
so how could l interpret a slap,
a pinch as not liking?
That, for me,
was part oflove.
But l felt angry at myself
for not being able to break up.
Then one day...
One day something happened...
l was at the beach,
l used to surfwith a T-shirt
so not to bruise my belly.
l was at the beach
with some friends.
l went in the water without
my board and swam real far.
There l leaned on a friend's board
talking to him.
Fernando arrived
and they pointed me out.
When he saw
that from the sand,
me talking
with my friend on the board,
he decided
to go into the water.
He swam in my direction
and l swam towards him.
When l got close to him,
l sawhis face
and he looked out of control.
l talked normally with him.
''Hi, honey.''
He looked at me
with great anger
and pulled me under the water.
You know, like kids
do on the beach.
But he held me underthe water.
l tried to surface
and l couldn't.
l tried,
but l couldn't surface.
My feet couldn't touch
the bottom.
l became desperate.
l thought, ''l'm going to die here.''
That was very clear to me.
l was going to die here.
l started to cough up water
and he began to let me go.
So l cried desperately.
lt wasn't a cry of relief.
lt was a cry of desperation.
That was so crazy...
What's the line between
loving someone
and wanting to kill her?
Maybe not wanting to kill,
but ending up killing.
Do you remember Eloá's story.
The guy went to the hospital
and asked how she was.
He shot her
in her head and groins,
then he goes to the hospital
and asks how she is?
l mean, was it premeditated?
Did he want to kill me?
l don't think so,
but something went out of control.
He forgot any kind of limit.
l think that after that
l became a person with...
with such a desire forfreedom.
Because while l lived
with my parents,
l lived in a prison.
l couldn't do anything.
The only thing that saved me
were the books.
l could live other stories,
live other lives...
Actually, l think
the paternal violence was...
When l think of it,
the paternal violence was worse.
There was a true
power struggle there.
lt changed when l decided
l was going to work,
l'd make my own money
and leave their house.
An the violence changed...
when l turned 18.
My father came to slap me
in the face,
but l slapped him
and told him to go fuck himself.
l told him
he was a son of a bitch.
l told him not to hit me,
that l was strong.
lf he hit me,
l'd hit him back.
And he looked very surprised.
He didn't expect that from me.
When l think of it,
violence is a loss of control.
And the person who stays
in this kind of situation
isjust as sick
as the person who hits.
Orthey're masochists.
Because the masochist
doesn't exist.
The sadist and the masochist
depend on each other.
That was my situation,
but l changed in my favor.
My brother always hit his kids
and he thought
it was good for them.
And so did his wife.
They also hit each other
and had a very violent
family situation.
l think violence
is a loss of control.
l sawthat in myself
when l lost control.
l had a son.
l would lose control
and spank him a bit.
But then l thought...
''My God, l'm turning
into my father.
l can't turn into my father.''
So when my son had 3 years old,
l looked at him and said,
''Look, Mommy is never
going to spank you or pinch you.
But l'll give you a time out.''
That was a relief for me.
lt was a huge relief. Huge.
You never had
another violent relationship?
No, never again.
Never again.
Never again, l decided.
l would never let another man
lay a finger on me.
l would never again
date someonejealous,
and l would never
be hit again.
And l neverfound anyone
like that again.
l didn't want to find them,
because there are
lots ofthem out there.
l was really lucky
l didn't die at 16,
but a lot of women
become addicted to that.
So l think l turned
my story around in my favor.
First we need to understand
what it is to love.
lf you told me, ''two people
who depend on one another,''
it'd have been easier
than ''two people in love.''
The love relationship
is a permanent act of piracy,
where you take from the other
what you lack.
lt's combat where
the sweat oflove can be...
the excretion ofhate
one has forthe other,
for not having
all the things the other has.
And since this possession
is precarious,
l love and l am
desperate for love.
That through
a survival instinct,
because my instinct tells me
l need to have a child with her,
because that will beget me
strong children.
Or because l'm incapable
ofliving alone...
Or because ofthe need
to transform the other
into a representation
of my success,
or a public exhibition
of my conquest.
Or yet to have
the beauty, intelligence,
sensitivity, or any other quality
the other has and l need.
We hang onto each other,
deluding we can take
what the other has,
in a vampire like manner.
lt's a cannibalistic thing.
l happened to reach my limit
a fewtimes.
When managing
thejealousy for a woman,
if she's a free spirit,
you'll suffer a lot.
You have no idea.
You have no idea what it's like
to be manipulated.
Your hormones won't leave
you alone.
Your balls are producing spunk
that has to be ejected
and because the warmth
and wetness ofthat cunt
which has a certain smell,
a certain feeling,
makes you feel
like you're invulnerable.
l had a girlfriend...
And l only realized howmuch
l loved her after we broke up.
Then l had lunch with her,
it was awful.
We were trying to have
a hard conversation.
This guy went by,
a good-looking guy l knew.
When he sawme talking
to this beautiful woman,
he looked at me
and kind of greated me.
Moments later l sawwhen
she looked at him thinking,
''l think l'd suck
this guy's dick.''
l sawthat in her.
That left me in a state
l thought l had overcome,
that thing ofthe argument,
the misunderstanding,
the melee combat.
l thought l were Zen
and l could generously allowher
to live without guilt.
''Let's live without guilt.
Me too, for fuck's sake.''
lt was so beautiful.
Remember when we were
at that beach hotel?
After we fucked l looked up
and said, ''Fuck, what happened?
Did the sky change?
Did l turn into Van Gogh?''
There were
such lights and colors.
''What's happening to me?''
And l hear her saying
in my ear,
''This is love.
This is love...''
Then suddenly we stab each other,
metaphorically speaking.
But my words were as a saw,
cutting offlegs, arms,
sticking my pen knife
in herthroat
so it would gush blood
from her neck.
How can you go
from an unbelievable ecstasy
to a situation in which
you are a normal person?
Where does that brainstorm go?
The nerves trembling?
That sense of peace
and completeness.
How can l allowanother person
to come like that
with the woman who gave me
this unbelievable compensation?
How can l accept that?
Because while she says,
''l love you'',
it means ''l love you,
l give you all l am, all l have.''
Then it's taken from you.
How can l go on living
after that?
How can l accept it
without violence?
And this violence of yours
is the manifestation
of yourfear oflosing...
oflosing what makes you happy.
Actually, the fear oflosing
what makes you unhappy.
There is a masochism imbued
in all this violence.
And the question is:
why continue the friction?
Why continue with this
love-hate relationship?
Why think
it's the last person,
when there are
three orfour women
on this street
you can get along with?
Why?
Why this permanent
repeating of a thing
that makes you unhappy,
that brings you anguish?
ln the psychotherapeutic world,
they call this masochism.
But there are other words
to describe this and the best are:
''cowardice to confront
your fragility,''
your fear ofbeing alone.
What about the other side,
women's violence against you?
lt's the female game,
the female silence that despises.
l think women knowhowto hurt
more than men.
Women have a natural gift
for hurting.
Men can hit.
But women are more intelligent,
more subtle than men.
We live in loneliness,
we have to pay a therapist
to talk to someone.
''Doctor, l think l'm queer,
but l'm not sure.''
They talk about everything,
look howmany magazines
there are about that.
All kinds of psychological,
emotional subjects,
all the TV shows they have.
They talk, we live in solitude,
we talk when we drink.
Talk what? With whom?
Who are we going to expose
our machoness to?
The great philosopher oflove
was Nelson Rodrigues...
''Forgive me
for betraying me.''
l think that's the basic phrase
over which all other speculations
about love take place.
You give me a cause,
you create the reason
and you hate yourself for being
the cause of what you destroyed.
But you don't know
if you really wanted to destroy it.
There is a masochism imbedded
in all this violence.
ln my case, whenever
there were fights, jealousy,
the melee combat,
the misunderstanding,
there was always a reason.
But l was always
the one to blame.
ln my last relationship,
for example,
a very complicated relationship.
During a fight, l told her,
''Let's take some time out.''
Overthe phone.
l punished her not talking
to herfor 15 days.
A punishment, ironically.
When l showed up,
she had another guy.
We went to a restaurant, she said,
''Let's get back together?''
l say, ''You're the woman
l love the most,
the woman l want the most.
But today l couldn't fuck you
even with three condoms.
Just to imagine some guy
fucking your asshole
and licking your cunt,
that makes me sick.
Go away. Get out of my life
because it's not going to work.
Love... a lot of love.
No, not love.
A lot of unresolved passion.
She wanted to get back together
during that lunch.
l asked her, ''When you fuck
this guy, what do you think?''
''Ninety percent of the time
l think of you.''
God, that's cruel.
How stupid of me
to have asked.
Her nerve to have answered.
You want to knowhowit was?
lt was with another girlfriend,
it's been a while.
She'd already cheated on me
a fewtimes.
She traveled to New York
for 15 days,
when she comes back,
she gives me the clap.
l went nuts. l broke everything,
the fridge, the TV,
l tore the clothes in the closet.
l hit her real hard.
l hit her with an open hand.
l'd kill her with my fist.
Her eye retina tore off.
l took my pen knife.
Suddenly, when l looked up,
there was blood everywhere.
There was blood
on the ceiling moldings.
When l looked,
my finger was cut, almost cut off.
l went to a friend's house
and she took me to the hospital.
When l came back,
she wasn't there.
l got my .357,
got into my car.
l had an Audi at the time,
and searched for her
in bars, restaurants.
l don't drink, but that night
l had four whiskeys in one bar.
l came back home
and she was there.
l stuck the .357 in her mouth.
l cocked it, put my finger
on the trigger.
lt was like l said,
the blood pulsating in the neck,
the heart, the neck.
l didn't shoot.
l don't knowwhat stopped me.
She left.
lt was like this.
l fell for him
because he was the opposite of me.
l sawin him the chance ofhaving
this experience that wasn't mine,
of wanting this experience.
l was fascinated by all the stories
of the years of repression,
the resistance to the dictatorship.
But it was his story, not mine.
Well, when l met him,
l was married,
l fell in love and in a week
l packed my bags and left.
And l left for life,
because l had a thirst for life,
l wanted to leave that life,
l was opening myself
to a newworld,
l was living a dream with him.
The first big surprise
happened at a barbecue
opening our house
for his friends.
Because this kind of person
has a personality
that starts hampering
everything that is your world,
everything that's good foryou,
restricting your world to his.
So we were there
with his friends,
he had a fewbeers too many
and he had a violence outburst
towards me, out ofthe blue.
l was very surprised
because it was the first time...
lt was my first contact
with that.
But l'm guilty.
You put yourselfin a position
of humiliation and you stay.
l was humiliated several times
in front of other people.
Several times.
There was this time
at home once...
This friend ofhis, Roberto,
they were trying
to set up a company,
this project together,
there was a third person
and it was a dinner.
We were talking,
l don't knowwhat,
and something was said
about this person, a woman,
and l criticized that woman.
That provoked
such a fury against me.
He started to scream,
attacking me,
asking who was l
to criticize that woman?
l was an imbecile,
a little shit,
and all these awful things
against me.
And l don't really remember
what he said to me,
but they were things
to meant to diminish me.
l remember l got up to leave
and he said,
''Yeah, go ahead, leave!''
Did l go? You think?
Not at all.
l went for a walk around the block
because l couldn't leave.
Then l came back,
sat and kept quiet.
Do you knowwhy
you couldn't leave?
l liked him.
l really liked him.
At that time, l think l felt
l couldn't live without him.
That's where the psychological
dependence comes in.
Because he realizes he has
control and domination.
He had control
and domination over me.
And my life became
a living hell.
You have to wonder if what you'll do
will botherthe other,
and awaken the beast
that lurks inside him.
So one day l went to buy aspirin
at the drug store.
l got out ofthe car
and left the door open.
Leaving the door open
created this 24 hour crisis,
the guy just kept
screaming at me.
My life became like that.
You don't knowhow
to avoid the problems.
And you never had the courage
to do anything?
Life was moving on.
Then he started to...
he wouldn't showup
one day, three days...
and you sort of...
Life became...
l moved on with my life.
At that time, l had an affair
with a friend ofhis.
One day l came home
after being with his friend
and l told him
l sawthat friend.
l didn't go into details,
because it was normal,
we would get together,
like friends.
We argued a bit about it
and then we went to bed.
At that time l was
creating a discotheque,
arranging his records
in a super cool shelfl made.
lt was coming out very nice.
And l called him
to the room to come see.
And then he came like a beast,
covering me with blows,
because ofthe story
with the friend.
And he kept hitting me,
pinning me against the floor,
covering me with blows,
l obviously became scared,
l tried to get out of that,
l managed to escape,
and l ran to the door,
in my socks, without shoes,
it was raining like crazy outside.
l run out the door
in the pouring rain like crazy,
afraid that
he might come after me.
And he runs to the door
and yells,
''Run, you little bourgeoisie shit.''
Suddenly all the differences
come up.
''You little bourgeoisie shit.''
and all that.
And the little bourgeoisie shit
sought refuge with her sister.
On that day, he tore my clothes
and burnt them.
Real crazy, right?
This friend of ours set up
this meeting between us
at a public place.
lt was a...
Was it a reconcilement court?
No. lt wasn't a family court.
But it was a public place.
We were there at this restaurant,
everyone there,
and to everyone's surprise
instead of split up,
the idiot here
goes back to the guy.
He took my hand,
looked at me with tears
in his eyes and said,
''This will never happen again.
lt will never happen again.''
This kind of relationship
destroys our self-esteem.
l think it's a process.
l don't knowif the other one
is conscious of what he does,
but he keeps on
crippling your life
and making you believe you're shit,
you don't exist,
your self-esteem doesn't exist.
So you become a non-being
next to this person.
Where's the good side
ofthis story?
The good side ofthe story...
There's something l didn't tell,
l guess l jumped over that part,
l don't knowwhy.
One day, he took me
to a friend's home.
And he introduced me to cocaine,
which wasn't well known
at the time.
l'd never had cocaine.
lt was a marvelous night,
l loved that thing.
lt was something else.
And l was...
He traveled, and
l who had loved that thing,
but had no idea,
decided to call his friend
to buy a rock and surprise him.
When he came back
and sawthat,
he was surprised,
he said, ''Wow" .
He couldn't believe it.
lt wasn't in his universe of
possibilities that l could do that.
And the rock
turned into a party,
because we snorted,
and snorted.
Why did l tell you that?
Oh yeah, because l quickly realized
that if anything happened,
a fight, an argument,
a bad mood,
l would go and buy coke.
l knewthat when we snorted
together, we got along.
And we snorted a lot.
We had huge trips...
Once when we snorted...
Anyway...
Once we had sex
for eight hours straight.
And you'll make me
the classic question.
Doesn't the dick go soft?
lt does,
but that's not a problem.
Because it's all in the head,
the pleasure is in the head.
We had great trips,
amazing moments
made eternal by the coke.
There are times...
when you have
a fraction of clarity.
l think my fraction of clarity
came during a New Year's eve
l spent by myself.
All by myself.
He came the next day,
about six in the morning,
grabbed some coffee,
sat on the bed
and said he didn't come
because he was with another woman
and he was torn between
the other woman and me.
That for me was the end.
So l said, ''Look, l've put up
with everything,
but l'm not putting up
with that.
l want you to leave.
So get yourthings and leave.''
He didn't want to got.
He wanted to live both things
and then decide.
That was the limit of my limit.
l wasn't going to take that.
But then there was...
At the time, there was
another majorfactor.
We already had a son together.
l had a child at a time
when l was addicted.
But l was a normal person,
l worked,
l had a lot of work even.
When l became pregnant,
l stopped snorting,
l manage to stop doing coke.
But then l took it up again
soon after.
My daughter must have been
a fewmonths old.
She was always in her crib.
And there was this night
when we snorted quite a lot.
lt was a party, we snorted a lot,
l did too much and passed out.
l passed out in a strange way.
l couldn't move,
l couldn't see, l couldn't...
But l could hear, and l heard him
calling the emergency.
The ambulance was coming.
We lived in an alley at the time.
lt was hard to get in.
l heard the car,
it was the middle ofthe night,
the ambulance couldn't get in.
They were trying to get closer.
And two thoughts
ran through my head.
''l'm not going to die because
l'm not seeing my life go by.''
And another thing l thought
before passing out was...
''They'll take me
to the hospital,
the ambulance will come
and take me away
and this guy is gonna
forget the baby in the crib.''
That for me was the thing.
When l woke up
and l hadn't died,
l thought, ''Fuck,
there's a baby in the crib.''
And so...
l think that was my salvation.
l think the baby
was my redemption.
The baby was my redemption.
Sorry.
But you've gotten over all this.
Sure, but the memory ofthat,
the panic ofthat moment.
l'm sorry, it got to me.
You never had another
violent relationship?
No, never again.
Not like that.
My life moved on...
l think it led me
to another direction.
We were together
for a long time.
We had two children...
A lot of things happened.
l think that
when a break happens...
lt's very... significant.
lt's something that really
changes your life.
Man, it's been so long.
l didn't think it would affect me.
Sorry.
ls it over?
Subtitles Ripped and Corrected by "NA MORAL"
*** www.makingoff.org ***