1957 was a big year.
The Russians put that Sputnik into outer space.
The Dodgers played their last game at Ebbets Field...
...and said goodbye to Brooklyn.
That guy. he shot Frank Costello in the head and missed.
The Gallo brothers whacked Albert Anastasia in that barbershop.
It was total chaos.
With Anastasia out. Vito Genovese figures he 's the big boss.
But Carlo Gambino...
...and Joe Bananas had other ideas.
So they called a meeting.
A big meeting.
It was the first time the whole Commission would meet face to face.
Bosses and wiseguys were coming from all over the country...
...and all the New York families too.
Maybe 50 bosses. the whole wiseguy world...
...all coming to this little town upstate.
My father went with Dom Manetta and Tommy D. Fat Tommy.
He was running the family then.
Some asshole thought it would be a good idea to have this meeting...
...at Joe Barbara 's farm. up in the country. nice and quiet.
Get away from the car.
Want to be a fucking rib eye? Get away from the car!
Turns out the local cops were watching Joe Barbara like a hawk...
...and some deputy sheriff notices all the traffic and calls the feds.
The meeting never even got started.
The feds moved in...
...and bingo. the bosses. they moved out.
My father and Dominic. they hid in the field with some hay or corn.
Along comes a farmer.
Dominic bullshits him while my father holds out...
... this.44 cannon he used to carry. and hijacked the tractor.
The story is they drove it all the way to Bensonhurst...
...but my father told me they only got as far as Poughkeepsie.
Carlo Gambino. he came out of it...
...capo di tutti capi, boss of all bosses...
...and that was the last time the Commission tried to meet until now.
I don ' t know, I don ' t Iike it. What do we got to meet for?
Let everybody else worry about their own business.
The ' 57 meeting was about how we were going to divide this country.
This meeting is how we' re going to survive.
You got made guys informing for the feds.
Bosses are going to jail.
People are getting whacked without permission.
And on top of everything else...
...you got these Chinese...
...and these crazy Russians to deal with.
Everything is changing.
We got to change with the times.
Are we going to get a fucking Website?
When your papa died...
...I made him a promise that I'd always Iook out for you.
I want you to come to that meeting with me.
Capisci?
Listen. This guy, Primo Sindone, you watch out for him.
He's a scumbag.
Keep your eye on him, okay?
Let me get a toothpick. I'II be right there.
I just kept telling him that I needed room...
...to grow...
...and to find myself as a person.
You know? Not just as a woman...
...but as an independent entity.
Then I told him I needed to get in touch with my uniqueness...
...but he could not handle that.
He said that I was driving him away.
He said I was driving him away.
Do you think I was driving him away, Dr. Sobol?
Caroline, things end.
It's a part of Iife. It's how we deal with things ending that's important.
I just cannot believe...
...that it's over between me and Steve, you know?
I mean, maybe there's still hope.
He took out a restraining order against you.
I have to be honest, that's usually not a good sign.
But what should I do?
The first thing that I think you should do...
...is to stop whining about this pathetic Ioser. For chrissakes!
You are a tragedy queen!
Steve doesn't Iike me. Steve doesn't respect me.
Who gives a shit? Get a fucking Iife!
Dr. Sobol?
I was reflecting on your situation.
It's interesting what you were saying.
I want you to think about it.
And I'm going to think about it.
We'II both think about it...
...and continue next week when I get back from vacation.
Caroline, what are you feeling?
You're just Iike Steve. You just want to...
You just want to...
...get rid of me and throw me out.
You know that's not true.
Yes, it's true.
I'II see you next week...
...whereas Steve never wants to see you again.
PIease, Mr. Vitti.
I said I don't know nothing, but they don't believe me...
...because that time I said Little Joe hit Dukey and he didn't.
I didn't know because Little Joe Iooked just Iike that...
Shut the fuck up!
You know me, right?
You're Mr. Vitti.
You know what I'II do to you if you Iie?
You'II crack me on the head with that pipe.
It's a rhetorical question, you idiot.
I'II ask you one time only: Who killed Dominic?
-Who killed Dominic? -I don't know!
I swear to God...
Don't fucking Iie!
You Iittle motherfucker! Who killed Dom?
He don't know nothing. Forget it.
That was relatively painless.
Shut the fuck up!
That hurt.
We're not going anywhere.
We've sat here for ten minutes. I hate being Iate.
I hate walking into that house Iate.
Dad, relax.
You're Iike this because you're mad we have to go to Grandpa's.
PIease don't analyze me.
I can't be analyzed by somebody who, until recently, believed in Santa.
There is one Dr. Sobol in this family. Just one.
But there's two. There's you and there's Grandpa.
You know what? Let's talk about something else.
Will you read Grandpa's new book?
Mom says you won't because you're jealous.
Does your mother talk about anything else, or is it just me 24 hours a day?
Shit!
This is Iike voodoo, your mother knows where I am every second.
Get in!
If I point to you, make believe your neck hurts.
What are you, a moron?
I' m sorry. This was my fault.
Did you see anything?
-I was talking to my son. -Bullshit!
That's all right, sir.
It's our fault for being in front of you.
No, really. Listen to me.
I'm responsible. Here's my insurance information.
It's okay. Forget about it.
Forget about...? Your rear end is screwed up.
No, it was Iike that before.
Let's call the police and file a report.
Fuck the police.
Hear me?
Okay. Fuck them.
You're right. Fuck them.
Especially those mounted cops who Ieave big piles all over...
...and you just step in it up to your shins.
Let me give you my card...
...in case you Iook at the damage and change your mind.
You a doctor?
I'm a psychiatrist.
A shrink.
I talked to a shrink one time.
When I got sent upstate on a...
...fishing trip.
Jelly! Let's go! Come on.
I got to go.
I'II see you.
Pings and knocks.
Cheap gas. What are you going to do?
-Take it easy, doc. -Right.
Neurotics only!
You must have been a beautiful baby
'Cause baby. Iook at you now
Thank God for Prozac
Baby. Iook at you now
You' re not coming? I mean, this is my wedding.
We understand it's a special day for you, Benny...
...but your father and I can't just pick up and Ieave town...
...every time you decide to get married.
Every time? This is a once in a Iifetime...
Twice in a Iifetime thing, Mom.
Dad, you're not coming to my wedding?
We want to, but I have three book signings next weekend.
I can't piss off these big bookstores.
If I cancel, they stick me on the bottom shelves. That's how they are.
That's the word on the street.
Barnes is okay, but Noble is a vindictive prick.
Ben. The Ianguage.
I'm sorry, but Iisten.
I have been alone for eight years.
I finally found somebody that I want to spend my Iife with.
At Ieast meet her before we get married.
You are going to be her family.
I think she should know that up front.
You're being very hostile.
I was joking.
I think I'II go talk to the mayor.
The mayor is here?
What's wrong?
Nothing. Everything's fine.
How's your practice?
Excellent. I have interesting patients.
Very interesting. Fascinating, actually.
Dad has a patient who dreams he shits trout.
Thanks, Mike.
The Manetta family is bound to ask questions.
They think we put the hit out on Dominic.
Forget Dominic. They were after Paul.
It's a miracle you survived. I just thank God.
Yeah, thank God, all right.
If it wasn't because I had to go back for that toothpick...
...I'd be Iying dead with Dominic, God forbid.
May he rest in peace.
This is about the big meeting.
Primo Sindone wants to run the whole show.
Primo's a boss. He knows the rules.
He couldn't come after them unless he had permission from the families.
If they did, we're headed for one big war, I can tell you that.
Find out what you can. We got two weeks.
God forbid the other New York bosses are against us.
I want to know that before I go into that meeting.
Sure.
You all right? You don't Iook too good.
What's the matter?
I'm a Iittle choked up. I'm going to get some air.
-Take it easy. -Take some air.
You all right?
What?
I feel Iike shit.
This whole thing is Iike one big fucking headache.
You having one of them "mindgraines"?
-Let's go for a ride. -What's the matter?
-Just drive the car. -What happened?
Good news, Mr. Evans. Your heart is just fine.
"Just fine"?
But I had eight heart attacks in the Iast three weeks.
Based on everything, I'd say you had an anxiety attack.
A what?
An anxiety attack. A panic attack.
I'II give you Xanax.
An anxiety attack? What are you saying?
It's a common thing.
Hey, Iook at me.
Do I Iook Iike a guy who panics?
-Do I Iook Iike I panic? -It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Where'd you go to medical school? I got a fucking heart attack.
Not according to your EIKG.
Jelly, I need you to do something for me as a friend.
Yeah, anything.
-I need you to find me a doctor. -We just come from the doctor.
Not that kind of doctor. Like a head doctor.
You going to change your face Iike Sonny BIack?
Don't get his nose. He Iooks Iike a pig.
Not a plastic surgeon. I got to spell everything out for you?
It saves time.
I mean, Iike a head doctor. Like a psychiatrist.
This is Iike one of them psychic, ESPN...
...ESPN things, you know?
I just ran into a psychiatrist. Actually, he ran into me.
Was he any good?
He seemed Iike a smart guy. He had a business card.
A business card? That's a real fucking achievement.
What do you need a shrink for?
It's not for me. It's for my friend.
He has problems. I'II ask the shrink questions...
...and get some answers for my friend.
And nobody can know. God forbid...
...somebody hears I been talking to a shrink.
It could be interpreted wrong.
Know what I mean?
No one will ever know.
-Could I just ask one question? -Go ahead.
This friend...
...is it me?
Yeah, it's you.
Carl, I'm detecting a pattern. You settle too easily for things.
You're right. I do.
See, you just did it again.
I suggested something and you immediately agreed.
You're right. I did.
Why do you do this?
I don't know.
I think it's your fear of rejection or disapproval.
You don't have to worry about that.
Be your own man. Stand your ground.
You don't have to Iet people roll over you.
Dr. Sobol?
Excuse me, we're in session.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
I know you. You're the guy I hit Iast night.
Bingo. Get out of here.
Upsy-daisy. Got a coat, nutbar?
-What are you doing? -He's Ieaving.
He's not going till he's done with his session.
-I'II give you $ 1 00 to Ieave. -Don't take it.
-Make it $ 1 50. -Listen.
He ain't that fucking crazy.
You were right. I stood my ground.
-This was the wrong time. -I got him up from $ 1 50.
-I'm proud of you. -I feel Iike a new man.
I'm so happy.
I know you're upset about the car, but you can't come in here.
This is a patient's private session.
You know me?
-Yes. -No, you don't.
You see my picture in the paper?
-Yes. -No, you didn't.
I don't even get the paper.
Jelly, wait outside.
Sit down.
You ain't got no bugs in here?
Bugs?
Bugs. Recording equipment.
No. I don't record. I take notes.
I tried to give him the insurance information several times.
Seriously, several times.
He wouldn't take it.
PIease don't kill me.
I was going to ask you if you Iiked T ony Bennett.
I'm a big T ony Bennett fan.
Me too.
I Iike all Italian singers.
I know it's not your fault...
...but shouldn't we take this up with our insurance companies?
It ain't about that. I don't care about the car.
I got a friend of mine....
He's got problems, and he'II have to probably see a shrink.
So I'II ask you a couple of questions.
Go ahead, then.
What do we do? What, we sit?
Whatever makes you comfortable.
I'II sit over here.
I'm going to sit here.
If you're comfortable, it's fine.
So who starts?
T ell me why you think you need therapy.
I don't need therapy. I told you that. It's for my friend.
-I'm sorry. -You didn't hear me say that?
I'm sorry.
You're supposed to be good at Iistening. You can't remember what I said?
So sorry.
I ain't thrilled with the Ievel of service up to this point.
That was my fault. I apologize.
Why don't we start over?
Why don't you just tell me about your friend?
This friend, you know, he's a very powerful guy.
Never had trouble dealing with nothing.
AII of a sudden, he's falling apart...
...he cries for no reason, he can't sleep...
...he can't be with his friends.
AII of a sudden, he gets nervous around them.
He wants to get away from them.
And these are guys he knows his whole Iife, you know?
And then he has these attacks.
He can't breathe, he gets dizzy...
...chest pains, you know....
He thinks he's going to die or something.
Panic attacks.
What's it with you guys and panic attacks?
Who said "panic"?
Not panic.
Dizzy, chest-breathing, constricting...
...attacks.
This guy, he just wants to know what he can do to make it stop.
I'm going out on a Iimb here.
I think your friend...
...is you.
You got a gift, my friend.
You got a gift.
You saw that there was something I was trying to do...
...and figured it out. That's why you are who you are.
God bless you. You got a fucking gift.
-No, I don't. -Yes, you do.
Go on.
-What? -Go on.
I think...
...medication could help.
Drugs?
Can't do drugs. I don't do drugs.
If you want to get to the root of the problem...
...you'II want to get some form of therapy.
Like what? With you or something?
Me? No, I don't think you want...
My roster of patients is full.
I'm full right now. PIus, I'm Ieaving on a short vacation.
Where you going?
-I don't share that with patients. -Where?
Sheraton Bal Harbour Hotel in Miami Beach.
That wasn't so hard, was it?
No, it wasn't.
You know, it's a funny kind of a thing...
...but I feel better after I got all that off my chest.
I feel Iike a Ioad...
...a Ioad is off my shoulders.
You're good.
Doc, thank you.
-I didn't do anything. -You did.
-I did nothing. -You did too.
The Ioad, gone. Where is it?
Don't know.
You're good.
You're good, Doc.
I'II be getting in touch with you.
-Don't, please. -One more thing.
If I talk to you and you turn me into a fag...
...I'II kill you. Understand?
Could we define "fag"? Because some feelings...
-...may come up. -I go fag, you die. Got it?
Simple.
You're good, Doc.
You're good.
See you, Doc.
We take on Manetta, what does Vitti do? Nothing.
Why doesn't he move?
Fuck him.
You say "fuck him," but he's planning something big.
This shit's coming down.
Well then, Iet it come down.
Let me tell you, Vitti's a tough guy...
...but a Iot of tough guys get fed to the crabs off Red Hook.
Vitti. That name has been haunting me since I was a kid.
Growing up, he was the smart guy, I was the dope.
My father was a nickel-and-dime shitheel, his had it all.
Vito Genovese blew it at Apalachin...
...because he forgot to kill Gambino before the meeting.
I won't make that same mistake. I want Paul Vitti dead!
You hear me? I want him dead. Not breathing now. Dead!
Like the pants?
They Iook great. He's some tailor.
I'II tell you. Look good.
I Iike them.
Don't Ieave food in your room. I won't come home to a science fair.
I didn't.
Dad, one thing, though.
-"I go fag, you die." -That's it.
I'm sealing the vent in your room.
You cannot Iisten to my sessions!
It's so cool. Was that really Paul Vitti?
I didn't ask to see his Mafia decoder ring, but it was him.
-Are you going to treat him? -Of course not. Are you crazy?
You cannot tell anybody that he was here. Understand?
Should I take it off the Internet?
I' m kidding.
Despite the heat and the popularity of more exotic Caribbean destinations...
...Florida 's hospitality industry reports booming business...
...from Orlando to the Keys.
Judging from the mob...
...around the pool here today...
... there 's nothing off about the off-season in Miami Beach this summer.
On a personal note, this is my Iast report for WVBF.
I' m marrying a wonderful man, and I' m moving to New Y ork.
Thanks for everything. Miami.
For the last time. this is Laura MacNamara for WVBF.
Catch!
We' re clear! Nice, Laura.
Everybody! This is him! This is the guy!
-I missed you so much. -I missed you too.
-Michael, say hi. -Hi, Laura.
Hi, Michael. How are you?
You want to go Iook at the camera?
Why would I want to go Iook at the camera?
-Is it okay? -Yeah, go ahead.
Don't worry if you break anything. I'm out of here.
-You think he Iikes me? -He's crazy about you. No, he is.
I Iove you. I'm so glad to be with you.
Do you really? And do you really Iove me?
Of course. What's the matter?
-I'm nervous. -Why?
Because I'm going to be a stepmom to a grown kid...
...and we're getting married.
So what are you worried about?
What if you get tired of me?
A Iot of couples are very happy and then they marry...
...and completely Iose interest in each other.
That won't happen to us.
Is everything okay, Paul?
Will you stop talking? I'm trying to do this here.
-You seem distracted. -I am.
I got things on my mind.
-Would you stop talking? -I'm sorry.
Lie down.
Thinking about your wife?
I wasn't thinking about my wife. What are you talking about?
Now I am thinking about my wife.
Sheila, why can't you keep your mouth shut?
Sorry.
Dr. Sobol.
Mom?
It's me.
Mr. Vitti wants to see you. I got your robe.
I got news for you, you two-bit prick, son of a bitch rat bastard...
...you did nothing for me! Whatever you did, it didn't take.
I'm still fucked up. You did nothing for me!
I did nothing for you? I saw you for five minutes.
What do you expect?
I can't work miracles. Let me tell you something else.
I don't Iike it when someone breaks in...
...and kidnaps me in the middle of the night!
I have a family. I have a Iife.
And I have a serious practice.
And I don't have time for your bullshit!
That got away from me at the end there.
I couldn't get it up Iast night.
Do you mean sexually?
I mean for the game against Michigan State.
Of course, sexually! What's the matter with you?
Can I get this straight?
You flew 1 500 miles, you dragged me out of bed...
...because you couldn't get an erection?
Don't that prove I'm motivated?
You can take a pill for that.
That's a cheat.
You start with the pills, next it's hydraulics.
A hard-on should be gotten Iegitimately or not at all.
I think Mark Twain said that.
Are you going to help me or not?
I don't believe this. AII right.
Has this happened before?
The dead dick thing?
Never. Well, one time. Last night.
One more time.
So twice.
Do the math. Two times.
Then another time, but after a big meal, so that don't count.
Being unable to perform three or four times is not...
Eight times.
Eight times is not catastrophic.
Maybe not to you. Look at you.
But if I can't get it up, that makes me Iess of a man.
In my world, I deal with animals.
They may seem dumb to an educated guy Iike you...
...but animals are very cunning and they sense weakness.
I got Iess than two weeks...
...to get strong, or they'II eat me up, if they don't kill me.
What happens in two weeks?
I can't tell you. You don't want to know.
You can't tell me and I don't want to know. That's a big help.
You're supposed to tell me. I do want to know.
That's how this works. This is impossible.
I can't do anything in two weeks, and even if I could...
...what is my goal? To make you a happy, well-adjusted gangster?
The other day I was watching a TV commercial...
...some kid playing with puppies.
I cried for 45 minutes.
SIap a pair of tits on me, I'm a woman.
I can't help you.
You're turning me down?
When I got into family therapy, this wasn't the family I had in mind.
You with your schmucky Iittle office and house, you're turning me down?
So you can Iisten to housewives piss and moan...
...about nobody fucks them right anymore?
I'm Ieaving now.
You see this?
This is what I'm talking about.
I'm a dead man.
You call yourself a doctor. You should be ashamed of yourself.
A real doctor could never turn his back on a person who's suffering!
You couldn't treat a fucking two-celled amoeba, you fucking phony.
Mother of God, give me the strength to get through this.
This fucking rat bastard...
...won't help me.
I start crying all the time. Don't know what it is.
AII right, here.
Sit down.
What happened with your wife Iast night?
I wasn't with my wife. I was with my girlfriend.
Are you having marriage problems?
Why do you have a girlfriend?
You're moralizing with me now?
No, I'm curious. Why do you have a girlfriend?
I do things with her I can't do with my wife.
Why can't you do them with your wife?
That's the mouth she kisses my kids with. Are you crazy?
Have you been under stress Iately?
-Like seeing your best friend murdered? -That would qualify.
I got a Iot of stress.
Based upon what you told me before about the attacks...
...I'd say that was probably it.
-Just stress? -"Just stress"?
Stress is a very powerful force.
I doubt there's anything physically wrong with you.
-That's it? -That's it.
That's it?
I think so.
You're very good, you.
You are very good.
-There's more to it than... -You're very good.
-There are underlying... -Understand me?
You're right on the money.
I feel the juices rush back to my balls as we speak.
I never thought I'd hear another man say that to me.
That settles it. You are my shrink.
No, I couldn't.
You're not ready to open up.
You're not a good candidate...
Listen to you. The fucking honesty.
That's it. You don't understand.
Nobody, nobody talks to me Iike that.
You understand?
-Yes, I do. -That's it.
Let's do it. I'm ready.
You don't hear the word "no" very often.
I hear it all the time, only it's more, "No, please, no, no."
I'm here for two more days.
When I get back to New York, I'II treat you exclusively.
For two weeks.
I just don't know what to tell my patients.
You want me to clear your schedule?
It would be my honor to do that. My pleasure.
Not Jimmy. I will do this myself.
-You sure? -Positive.
I will see you in New York.
Okay. Want one of them?
-No, thanks. -Sure?
That's very kind of you, but I....
Want to give a Iittle sta minch?
You sure?
The pause that refreshes.
I don't... No, I really....
You're on vacation.
I'm also about to get married...
...so I'd Iike to go back to my hotel and....
Good night.
I'II see you in New York.
You. Hey, Doc. You.
I'm going to see a Iot of you.
Where were you?
My God, I woke up and you were gone!
There was no note or anything! I was out of my mind!
I walked all over the hotel Iooking for you.
I even ate a Rice Krispy Treat. I almost called the police.
No, don't call the police. I'II tell you the truth.
I had a patient emergency.
You have patients in FIorida?
One. He followed me from New York. I had to go, trust me.
My God. Who is this patient?
Paul Vitti.
Mafia Paul Vitti?
Oh, my God.
Listen. It's not Iike he's a regular patient.
He's got problems.
He thinks that I'm treating him. It's crazy.
So you're not treating him?
Tell me you're not.
I'm not treating him.
It's scary. You don't want someone Iike that in your Iife.
I've covered the mob down here. I've seen what they do.
He and I spoke about it. He understood. It's over.
-You're sure? -Absolutely.
I was so worried.
I thought maybe you got scared or...
...saw an ex-girlfriend or something.
Well, I don't know.
-I Iove you. -I Iove you.
I'm sorry, but everything's going to be okay.
Give her a big hand! Let's hear it!
How about that?
That was great! Come on, get into it.
I don't understand. They splash in the water.
They eat fish.
This is not a big stretch for a whale.
Stop it.
We're having fun, right?
I'm not having as much fun as it Iooks Iike I am.
I'm pretending, because we have to bond and all.
As I was saying. a little snack for her might be 50 pounds of mackerel.
There she goes!
I' m going to get a hot dog. Anybody want anything?
-I'II go with you. -It's fine.
You' re pretending to have a good time. I don't want to spoil that.
I'II be right back.
You think those whales piss in that water?
I think they use the men's room next door to the Burger IKing.
Dummy.
-What's going on? -Mr. Vitti wants to see you.
Is this a joke?
You're an employee of Mr Vitti's...
...which means you're on call 24 hours a day...
...just Iike the rest of us.
I'm sorry. He and I discussed...
We discussed this, and I agreed to see him in New York.
That's it.
Dr. Momma-Luke, Iisten to me. It is what it is.
If he wants you sooner, you go sooner.
That's it.
No. I am not going.
And if either one of you bother me again...
...I won't treat him at all.
Do you understand that? Capisci?
It's over! End of story.
Look at the size of this one.
Jesus Christ!
It's feeding time.
They threw me in the shark tank, Paul.
They were trying to make a point.
That you're scary? Believe me, I get it.
You're in a mood.
I get that way when a shark tries to chew on my ass.
-We had an agreement. -We did, but I had an episode.
I didn't have a panic attack, but I started panicking...
...thinking I might get one. Is that weird?
I am redefining "weird" on an hourly basis.
-What's he doing? -I don't know.
-He's talking with some guy. -Can you hit him?
He's got fat Jelly and his partner Jimmy Boots with him.
I could do it with a rifle, but I don't have that with me.
Just get him.
You told me to take care of him, I'II do it.
What were you thinking when you got anxious?
Let's get out of here. We're being watched.
Don't Iook. There's feds up there watching us.
How do you know that?
I'm a criminal. It's my job.
Who's the new face?
Maybe he's Vitti's new consigliere.
Whoever this guy is, he must be important to the family.
Put his picture on the wire, see what you come up with.
Normally, a patient wouldn't have a vat of scotch during a session.
That's interesting. I'II have to remember it if I'm ever on Jeopardy.
Tell me about your father.
My father. Well, my father....
Let's sit here.
My father.
A big man in the neighborhood. Everybody Ioved him.
Very well-respected, God rest his soul.
He passed away?
I just Iike saying "God rest his soul. " Of course he passed away!
I was about 1 2 at the time.
How did he die?
It was a sudden thing. A heart attack.
How was the relationship? Were you close?
We were pretty close.
We weren't getting along great right then.
Why is that?
I was hanging out in the neighborhood. I had a borgata.
What is that?
A kid gang, nothing big. But he didn't Iike that.
He didn't approve.
He slapped me around a couple of times.
And what?
And then he died.
How'd that make you feel?
It felt great, wonderful. How'd it make me feel?
Think about it.
Were you angry? Were you afraid? Sad?
Maybe all those things.
Any feelings of guilt?
About what? I didn't kill him.
I know that, I'm just speculating...
...that maybe in some way you may have wanted him to die.
Why would I want him to die?
You said you were fighting. He slapped you around...
...because you rebelled against his authority.
Maybe some unresolved Oedipal conflict.
English, English.
Oedipus was a Greek king who killed his father and married his mother.
Fucking Greeks.
It's an instinctual developmental drive.
The young boy wants to replace his father...
...so that he can totally possess his mother.
Are you saying I wanted to fuck my mother?
It's a primal fantasy.
Have you ever seen my mother?
-Are you out of your mind? -It's Freud!
Freud's a sick fuck, and you are too for bringing it up.
Can I be honest? I don't think I can call you Dad.
So what do I call you? Do I call you Scott?
My friends call me Captain.
Captain?
Want another drink? I' m definitely having 8 or 9.
I'd Iike a morphine and soda.
I' m shaking.
Shall we go to our table? Come on, Michael.
Senor Sobol.
How you doing?
It's the Vittis.
My God.
Everybody's happy, everybody's smiling. This is nice.
You Paul Vitti, the mobster.
Now, is that polite?
Is that being nice? I'm trying to be nice.
Do I walk up to you and say you're so-and-so, the hard-on?
This is Laura's father, the captain.
I'm very, very sorry.
Excuse us.
I heard about the wedding. Here you go.
A Iittle something for the bride and groom. God bless.
We can't accept this.
-Yes, you can. -Thank you.
I'm just going to borrow this guy. I'II bring him right back.
And then you'II Ieave us alone.
I'II Ieave you alone.
I got to talk to you.
Two minutes. Two minutes.
Wait over there. Don't Iisten to what we say.
My ears are sealed.
I had a really weird dream Iast night.
I feel Iike I'm having one now. Why'd you interrupt my party?
You're really very rigid about certain things.
Did you know that?
AII right, tell me about your dream.
I'm asleep.
I hear a baby crying. I go to the refrigerator.
I get him a bottle of milk.
I bring the bottle of milk to him...
...I see the milk is black.
That's fucking weird!
Get out of here.
-Get out of here. -Sorry.
What does that mean? And no more filth about my mother.
I don't know. What does it mean to you?
This is why I pay you? I say something, you say it back to me?
I could get Jelly to do that for nothing.
Get Jelly. I'm going back to my party.
AII right. I'm Ietting it go this time.
Because you're getting married, I'm going to Iet it go.
Why don't you Iook over that way before I bust your fucking head open?
I'm going to grab a bite to eat. You want a sandwich?
What kind of sandwich ain't too fattening?
A half a sandwich.
I'II be back in a few minutes.
Now, nod your head and smile. Do it.
Now, you Iisten to me, goombah.
I know what your game is, and you'd better call it quits.
If you and your paisans do anything to hurt my Iittle girl...
...I don't care who your friends are...
...I'II hunt you down Iike the dog you are, and I'II kill you.
Understand?
Now, nod and smile.
Congratulations.
What was that about?
Just guy stuff between me and the captain.
Shit!
In sickness and in health, from this day forth...
...as Iong as you both shall Iive?
Bring Marie and the kids right to the airport.
Pull the car in the back of the hotel and wait for us.
You got it, boss.
That's it. That is it. I have had it with you.
-What happened? -What happened?
I just saw a man fall seven stories into a platter of poached salmon!
-Did he break anything? -Everything!
They' re still pulling capers out of him.
People get depressed, they jump. It's a tragedy, but it ain't my fault.
You're telling me it was a suicide?
I think he Ieft a note. Jelly, did they find it?
No, but they will in a minute.
Let me guess what it says: "Life is bullshit.
I can't fucking take it no more. Signed, the dead guy."
That's good, Doc.
Enough talk. We got to get out of here.
There's feds all over.
I'm going back to New York...
...and I would suggest that you do the same thing.
Because they're probably onto you too.
Onto me? What are you talking about?
Being an accessory to a murder wasn't part of our understanding.
I didn't kill nobody.
I can't speak for other people in the room.
That guy tried to kill me.
God forbid he did that to somebody in my family.
It would've been a double or a triple tragedy.
Trust me, in this case, we're the good guys.
Where is he?
-Where are you going? -Don't touch me.
How could you do that?
Another country heard from.
Wait downstairs.
Why? Are they going to throw me off the balcony too?
You' re upset and you' re upsetting me.
Of course I' m upset!
My wedding is ruined because you've got problems!
I got problems?
Honey, please.
I'm going to pack, and then I'm going to New York.
And I am getting married with you or without you!
With! With! I'm sorry, honey.
It'II all work out. I promise.
PIease?
No, I hate you!
Are you happy? Are you happy?
You know what you did? You have ruined my Iife!
Happy? What are you talking about?
You think I wanted this? I'm a victim here.
I can't believe this guy.
He tries to kill me, then whacks one of my guys.
On top of that, he fucks up your wedding. You know how upset I am?
I'm so enraged, I don't know what do to with myself!
PIus, I'm trying to get out of this hotel and...
Are you Iistening to yourself?
Listen to yourself!
This has been a disaster from the moment you stepped foot in my office.
That is it. Over! I' m no Ionger your doctor.
Just because of this?
Because of this Iittle double homicide? Yes, because of this!
You don't have a shred of human decency. Not a shred.
I actually thought I could help you.
There's no helping you. You're a common thug!
Nobody in the world could help you!
AII right! What do you want me to do?
Let me speak to Primo.
Hold on.
Paul Vitti's on the phone.
-Who is this? -It's me.
-Me who? -Me who... Me, me.
-Me. me who? -Me, me. You know me. Me.
Yeah, how's it going?
Not good. Not good.
Whoever did that thing to you-know-who, my good friend...
...they're trying to do that to me.
And I'm having a lot of feelings about that.
And I' m trying to get some...
-CIosure. -closure on that.
What kind of feelings?
I' m very angry. I' m feeling very angry about that.
I'm enraged.
I'm feeling very, very mad about that.
Why are you telling me?
Why am I telling you?
Like you don't know nothing about it?
You don't know nothing? What?
I don't know what you're talking about.
-I'm trying to.... -Tell you how I feel.
Tell you about my feelings and that....
-I'm angry. -I'm angry.
And anger is a....
-A blocked wish. -A blocked wish.
And I'm looking forward to seeing you next week at that thing...
...then I can unblock that angered wish...
...and then hopefully....
You make one more move on me, you motherfucker...
...I'II fucking cut your fucking balls off!
I'II shove them up your fucking ass, I'II fucking bury you!
I'II put ice picks in your eyes! I'II chop your eyeballs!
I'II send them to your family to eat for dessert!
You understand me?
-What? -Fuck you.
You motherfucker!
You get a dictionary and find out what this "closure" is.
If that's what he's going to hit us with, I want to know what it is.
How was that?
It was going great until...
...the cutting off of the balls and shoving it up...
...his ass.
You know what I do when I'm mad? I hit a pillow.
Just hit the pillow. See how you feel.
There's your fucking pillow.
Feel better?
Yeah, I do.
Good.
Call the Vatican. See if something is missing.
So cool!
I need to talk to your dad in private, okay?
Would you unload the car, please?
It's almost as tall as the house.
What is going on?
What is this?
Why?
It's a wedding gift. He felt bad for the...
Well, we're not married, so we can just send it back.
It was not my fault. Everybody was there.
You didn't want to go ahead with the ceremony.
What did you expect? That's not what I want for an anniversary memory.
Look at our wedding video. There are your parents, and mine.
There's the guy that plunged to his death.
I just want to marry you.
I'm thinking it'II never happen.
It's happening next Saturday at the Waldorf.
And who will be there?
The three of us, the clergyman...
...and any of your family who are done with their crisis counseling.
No guests without necks. Everybody has to have a neck.
We will do a neck check at the door.
Any furniture you want to change in the house...
Dr. Sobol.
Ma'am.
I'm Agent Steadman. Agent Ricci, Agent Provano...
...Federal Bureau of Investigation, OCD.
Obsessive-compulsive disorder?
Organized Crime Division. We need to talk.
FBI? This is cooler than the fountain.
Go to your room.
-But I just... -Go to your room.
Fine. I can hear better in there anyway.
PIease.
Can you explain these photographs?
Yes. I'm a psychotherapist. Paul Vitti is my patient.
-Was your patient. -Was my patient.
But not even Iike a patient.
Right. Exactly.
So why did he send you that fountain?
The fountain?
That was a....
That was a gift to celebrate the completion...
...of the therapy.
I got a television from a kleptomaniac...
...so it's not really that big of a deal.
Let me cut to the chase, Dr. Sobol.
Sometime in the next week, the heads of every major crime family...
...are meeting somewhere in the New York area.
We think the stage is set for a major bloodbath.
Has he mentioned it to you?
A bloodbath?
He has not mentioned anything Iike that.
I would've remembered that.
" BIoodbath " is something that sticks out in a conversation.
You could really help us by supplying information about that meeting.
If I don't?
If you don't...
...I will personally make your Iife a Iiving hell.
Pauly. I don't mean this in a disrespectful way.
Now, you know I was a good friend to your father.
I'II always be a good friend to you.
But the word is out that you' re talking to a shrink.
Is that right?
What's the point here?
The point is this concerns the whole family.
Right now, we're the only ones that know about it.
If this ever gets out in the street, we're dead.
Who knows what you're saying to him?
It ain't nobody's fucking business.
I beg to differ.
If you're Iooking to establish an insanity plea for Iater on...
...that's okay.
But everybody'II think you're falling apart. It's not right.
They'II think this is a sign of weakness.
Sindone will take over everything. Is that what you want?
So what do you want me to do?
It's time to end it, Paul.
What do you mean, end it?
Get rid of the shrink. He knows too much.
You want me to whack my doctor? Are you crazy?
Paul, if you don't do it, somebody else will.
That's the way it is.
Nobody touches this guy.
Anybody Iays a finger on him, I'II kill them. Understood?
-I'm getting fruit. Want anything? -No, I'II wait in the car.
Can I get two of these?
Papa!
Papa! Papa!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
You Iook Iousy. You all right?
Yeah, I'm all right. Listen, Paul, don't send me any more gifts.
-You didn't Iike the fountain? -It's a boundary issue.
If more people gave from the heart, we'd all be better off.
Let me see your watch. Piece of junk. You're getting a Rolex.
-Don't buy me one. -Who said anything about buying?
Paul, Iisten. I really have to talk to you.
Who is that?
Tommy Angels. We grew up together. Worked for a crew out of Jersey City.
How did he die?
He was on his way to talk to a federal prosecutor.
Got hit by a truck.
Twice.
I don't need to know this.
I can't hear this.
This is too much for me. I'm having nightmares myself.
The other night, I dreamed you and I were walking down the street...
...and I stopped to buy some fruit.
Out of nowhere, two guys come and they kill me...
...Iike Marlon Brando in The Godfather.
Good scene. What'd I do?
You drop your gun.
You run up to me and you yell, "Papa! Papa!"
I was Fredo?
I don't think so.
You're starting to Iose it. You may need therapy yourself.
Paul, we really have to talk.
We're running out of time.
The widow.
I'm very sorry.
The daughter.
I'm sorry.
Brother.
My condolences.
I'm very sorry.
Him I don't know.
Can we talk now?
Don't you see? You called me Papa. This is all about your father.
You're nuts. That's your dream.
But the black milk dream is also about your father.
I don't buy that. In my dream, I'm bringing the baby the black milk.
Freud believed you're everyone in your dreams.
Fuck Freud. After what you told me...
...I'm afraid to call my mother on the telephone.
Listen, just try to go with me here.
Let's just say that you are the baby.
What kind of milk did your father bring you?
Could we stop talking about my father?
That's the point. We have to talk about your father.
It is so hard to... You know what you're Iike?
Like this: "Doc, you got to help me.
I'm in pain. PIease help me."
"AII right, Paul, I'II help." "Fuck you. Nobody helps Paul Vitti."
AII right, very good. This is you:
"That's interesting. What does that mean to you?
Anger is a blocked wish."
Boo-fucking-hoo-hoo.
-Let's talk about your father. -Let's not.
What does your father do?
It's not important.
-What? You paused. -I did not.
You just paused. That means you had a feeling. A thought.
What does your father do? What's he do?
-He's a psychiatrist. -A psychiatrist?
Now I know why you're fucked up. Next patient, please.
We are running out of time.
-Let's not waste it on my problems. -Your father's a problem?
-That's what you said. -I did not!
Now you're upset.
I am not upset!
-Yes, you are. -Stop it!
I'm getting good at this!
We only have a few days Ieft. This is very important stuff.
That's why you're acting Iike this.
If you want to spend it screwing around, I can't help you.
Call me when you want to get serious.
I am serious.
Don't you want to analyze me no more?
Say hello to your father for me.
It's time to end it. Paul.
What do you mean. end it?
Get rid of the shrink. He knows too much already.
You want me to whack my doctor?
If you don't do it. somebody else will.
Nobody touches this guy.
Anybody lays a finger on him. I'll kill them.
Understood?
Now Iet's hear the other one.
You want me to whack my doctor?
If you don't do it. somebody else will.
I'm going to kill them.
-Good. -That's very good.
We think it's time to end it.
What do you mean?
Get rid of the shrink. He knows too much already.
You want me to whack my doctor?
If you don't do it. somebody else will.
I'm going to kill them.
What do you want me to do?
Paul. he's talking to the feds.
I know this guy. He wouldn't talk to the feds. No way.
The FBI was over at his house today. Jimmy Boots saw them.
-You saw them there? -It's the truth. I saw them.
Next, you'II get a call...
...and he'II want a meeting.
Dr. Sobol called.
He said he needs to see you right away.
This is delicious.
This is so good.
I Iove Italian food.
I've never been to Italy. Is it great?
I was in France twice...
...and Jamaica, the island.
You ever been there?
It's great, because I Iove to snorkel.
Have you guys ever snorkeled? It's great to sleep with the fish.
Swim with the fish. Have you ever done that?
It's good. So...
...what are you doing this summer?
About what?
How are you?
-How you doing? -Good.
This is Ben. Say hello to Carlo.
-How you doing? -Carlo...?
That's it. Grab a seat.
Carlo and I grew up together.
He's Iike, I would say, almost...
...Iike a cousin to me.
-I am your cousin. -That's what I'm saying.
It's a family thing. It's the closeness.
Anything he needs, anything I can do for him, I'm here for him.
-You know that. -I know.
Did you take care of that thing?
-It's all right to talk business? -It's okay.
-I took care of it. -And the other?
I got to wait for the first before I can move on the second.
The guy give you a problem?
The guy in the first thing? He's a Iunatic.
-What did he say? -The usual.
-You told him you weren't doing it? -What am I going to do?
Got to nip that shit in the bud.
But if the first comes through. that'll fix everything.
Including the second thing. Exactly.
Don't repeat what you hear here. You hear?
The first thing or the second thing?
Very funny.
Stevie Beef is over there.
-Fat piece of shit. -Rat-fucking, cocksucking....
-Scumbag. -Garbage pail.
Let's go say hi.
So this is a very unusual place. Do you guys come here often?
Well, this place has a very special meaning for Paul.
Yeah, it's where his father got whacked.
What's the big secret?
Never mind.
Wait a second.
Paul's father was murdered?
Right at that table, with his whole family there.
Shut your face.
Paul was there too.
He doesn't Iike to talk about it.
Where you going?
To the bathroom.
Sit down.
I'm going with you.
Jelly, I have to, you know....
Poop?
Go ahead.
Holy shit!
You got to get more roughage, Doc.
A bran muffin in the morning would help that.
I don't believe this.
I'd Iike to see a movie, but there's nothing out there.
It's all this shoot-them-up action bullshit.
I get enough of that at work.
Primo, that was our friend.
They spotted that guy at Paretti's Restaurant.
That's good.
That's very good.
Handsome Jack.
Let's make it his Iast supper.
-You got it, Primo. -No problem.
Just for fun...
...tear out his heart and bring it to me.
I'm going to bring it back to you on a fucking platter.
Where we going to get a platter?
Just bring it, all right?
Or Raisin Bran. That goes right through me.
-It's a pusher. -Good tip.
I have to talk to you. In private.
Why didn't you tell me about your father?
What about him?
You told me he died of a heart attack.
What's the problem?
Your father was murdered.
What's the difference? He's dead.
It's a big difference. Why didn't you tell me?
It's private. I got to tell you every Iittle thing?
This is not a Iittle thing.
What am I going to do? Spend my Iife crying about the past?
It's over. Forget it.
I think you want to talk about it.
-I don't want to talk about it. -You do.
I don't want to talk about it.
-Why did you choose this restaurant? -I Iike it.
Of all the places we could've gone, why this place?
White clam sauce. The best.
That's not the reason. You want me to know about your father.
-You're reaching out to me. -Yeah, I'm reaching out to you.
Where is it?
Get in the car.
It's Iate. I'II take a cab. I can get to Grand Central and....
You know what? I can make the 1 1 : 1 0.
So thanks, anyway.
I said get in the car, Doc.
Do what he says.
You know, this is called a "transference neurosis," where the patient...
Get in the car.
What is this guy doing? He's been in the bathroom for half an hour.
Fuck!
Get over there!
Son of a bitch!
We Iost him.
Come on, get out.
Get out and get over there.
AII right, Ieave us alone.
Sorry, Doc.
It's not personal.
Don't kid yourself. It doesn't get more personal than this.
Walk over there.
-You know why I got to do this? -Yes. Do you?
Don't bullshit me. You ratted me out, you betrayed me.
I betrayed you? That's interesting. Who's got the gun?
Don't give me that. Are you insulting my intelligence?
You cooperated with the feds.
They played me a tape. I heard you say you were going to kill me.
-I heard the tape. -Never. On my mother's Iife.
-Never. -I heard it.
It's not important now, but I did not betray you.
I had a wire on, but I took it off because I think I can help you.
I don't want to know what you think.
Yes, you do.
Let me help you!
It's over!
Can I ask you one Iast question?
What?
-What did you order? -What?
-What did you order? -When?
The night your father was killed, what were you eating?
How the fuck do I know?
You don't remember?
It was 35 years ago.
What was your father eating?
I don't remember. What are you talking about?
Try.
It's a simple question. What was your father eating?
Penne.
Good.
What did you have?
Ravioli.
The food was already on the table?
No, they were serving it.
And did you see the guys coming?
One of them.
Dressed Iike a busboy.
Your father saw him too?
I knew the guy Iooked wrong.
Why, Paul?
The pants. Looked too good for a busboy.
So he walked to the table.
I watched him the whole way.
Did you say anything?
Dad was so mad at me, I couldn't say anything.
And you were mad at him.
And then what happened?
I never saw the second guy. My mother just started screaming.
And you blame yourself.
I could've saved him.
But you were mad at him.
I should've said something.
You couldn't have saved him, Paul.
I killed him.
You didn't kill him.
You were mad, but you didn't kill him. It's the Iife he chose.
I just Iet him die.
I Iet him die!
I Iet him die, and I couldn't say goodbye to him.
So why don't you say it now?
Tell him. If he was here, what would you say?
-I can't. -Yes, you can.
I can't.
No, I can't.
Tell him, Paul.
I want to say I'm....
Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry. I Iet him die.
Jesus.
Poor guy's falling apart.
Why don't he just pop him?
It's embarrassing standing here Iike this.
Shut up.
You couldn't save him.
I know I could've. I could've.
No, he was trying to save you.
That's what you fought about.
He didn't want this for you.
And you don't want it for Anthony.
No, I don't!
You don't want him to grow up Iike you did, without a father.
Your father's not dead, Paul.
He's alive in you. And he's trying to tell you something.
He's trying to tell you...
Holy shit!
They're shooting! They're shooting!
-Pull yourself together! -I feel so bad!
You're going to feel a Iot worse.
Time to channel all this nice grief...
...into a murderous rage.
Come on! Time to shoot back!
Let's go! Here we go! Bang, bang!
Bang, bang! Come on. Let's go.
Come on! Bang, bang!
Now come on. Paul, here.
Put the gun in your hand and shoot!
For God sakes, shoot somebody!
Give me the fucking gun!
Stay down.
Paul, you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Jelly, did I do that?
No, Doc.
That one's mine.
You get the '72 Chevy...
...and the Amana side-by-side refrigerator-freezer.
You okay, Paul?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm going to check on Jimmy.
Pretty fucking ironic, ain't it?
You can give me back the gun now.
It's okay. I wasn't really going to whack you.
AII right, maybe I was going to whack you.
But I was real conflicted about it.
Progress, right?
I can't see you anymore.
I know.
You hit some very big stuff tonight.
So you'II probably feel Iike this for a while.
But you're close to something.
The rest is up to you.
Good Iuck.
I want to please him when we're in bed...
...but whatever I do, it seems Iike it's never enough.
Now he wants me to say things when we're making Iove.
What kind of things does he want you to say?
Well, he wants me to call him...
..."big boy"...
...and he's my "bucking bronco"...
...and I'm supposed to "ride him hard"...
...and "put him back in the barn wet."
Are you okay, Dr. Sobol?
Well, it's....
Here's what I think you should do, EIaine.
I would do whatever he says.
If he wants you to talk, talk.
I'd get on all fours and bark Iike a dog.
I'd do whatever it takes.
Smoke some joints, drink wine, whatever it is...
...to get off on each other and be happy.
Where are you running?
This is a time to be happy!
Because Iife is just too short.
It's just too fucking short.
I'II see you Thursday.
Everything okay?
Feeling all right?
You need anything?
No. Feel great.
Never felt better.
Wait'II I go to that meeting. I'm going to knock them dead.
AII right. I'II be outside.
When I look at him...
...I think about how different it was.
Was providing for a family simpler back then...
...or did he just make it look that way?
Decisions are tougher now.
There 's so much information...
...so many ways to invest.
Strange. I spent the first half of my life...
...not wanting to walk in his footsteps.
Now I only wish I could.
Times are more complex.
Ask a Merrill Lynch financial consultant who can help with a plan.
And more ways to make the plan work than anyone else.
You Iook beautiful, honey.
We are put on this earth to find a Iove, a soul mate...
...someone with whom we can create joy.
And how glad we are...
...that Ben and Laura have found each other.
And we anticipate and celebrate...
...the years of joy they will share together from this day on.
Do you take Laura to be your wedded wife...
...for richer or poorer, in sickness and in health...
...till death do you part, so help you God?
-No! -What?
Excuse me?
I wasn't talking to you. I was talking to him.
Who him?
It's not important. Yes.
Yes what?
Yes to the first part. To her.
That's a yes. Pick it up from there.
Doc, this is an emergency.
-I don't believe this. -This is my wedding!
Want me to make a scene?
Bigger than this?
Jesus!
Tick-tock. Let's go.
Hurry up. Pronounce.
By the power vested in me, I now pronounce you man and wife.
Ring, ring. IKiss, kiss.
Here. Fine. Good. Okay, just go.
Sorry, Mrs. Sobol. Duty calls.
You're the first person to call me Mrs. Sobol.
Nice?
I'm telling you, Doc, this is serious.
If he don't make that meeting, they'II kill him.
Can't somebody else in the family go for him?
What about Tommy the Tongue or Louie the Lip?
What about you? Why don't you go?
That would be a very good idea, except for one Iittle detail.
I'm a fucking moron. I'm known for it.
-You got to go. -You must be a moron.
-Watch it! -You just said it.
When I say it, it's different. When you say it, it sounds negative.
Jelly, I am not going to any meeting.
I am no Ionger on the payroll. Do you understand that?
Now, I am going back to my wife.
Now, Jelly, we've been through this before.
You can't shoot me.
Correction:
It was Mr. Vitti who couldn't shoot you.
You're going to that meeting.
This is Surveillance 6. They've Ieft the building and are heading east.
Roger that.
-Put this on. -Is this chrome?
I can see my own reflection.
Let me tell you something.
That's a $ 1,200 Valentino suit.
If you spill anything on it...
...I'm going to mess you up good.
Shut up! You're making him nervous.
If he fucks up, they'II kill him for sure.
What? This is insane!
It's all right.
Let's go over it again. Mr. Vitti's been detained.
Apologies all around.
And then you say you're the new consigliere...
...speaking for Mr. Vitti.
Then what?
Then you keep your mouth shut and hope nobody asks you nothing.
That's some plan you got there.
Shut up! Doc, if you got to talk...
...try to be vague. Could you do that?
I'm a psychiatrist. Believe me, I can be vague.
Looks like they're headed for the tunnel.
We'll pick them up on the other side.
Here they come.
Which one is it?
The black one.
Are you sure you don't want something to eat?
You want some iced tea?
I think I' m going to call Dr. Terragrossa.
Is Daddy going to be all right?
I think so, honey.
Shouldn't you be outside playing?
No, it's all right.
How Iong you going to sit there?
How Iong you going to Iay there?
I'm done.
Let's go.
It'II be all right, Doc.
There's no way I can get away with this.
Jelly, I can't do this!
Don't fucking whine.
Whining's a dead giveaway.
BIend.
BIend in.
So where's Vitti?
He ain't here.
How you doing?
How you doing? How you been? AII right?
AII right.
Hey, when'd you guys get out?
You need anything, you Iet me know.
Easter weekend.
You're a planet!
BIending, enough.
Who's the guy with Jelly?
I never seen him before.
What's going on? Where's Paul?
He'II be here. Don't worry.
And what's he doing here?
He's just....
Forget about it.
Forget about it?
What the hell is that? "Forget about it."
I can't do this. No, I can't do this.
I think we're going to get started here.
We got a Iot to talk about here today, and...
...for now, we'II just stick with the more important issues.
And one more thing...
...if you got anything to say...
...Iet us know who you are, because a Iot of us don't know each other.
I didn't think anybody here was into wearing fucking nametags.
I'm Primo Sindone.
They call me Sonny Long.
Some of you know me as Mikey Gaga.
Some of you know me as Joey Boombots.
Be as it may, it's good to see so many of the old faces here...
...and to welcome some of the new ones from all over the country.
I see Joe Baldassare...
...Frankie Zello.
But I'm disappointed the head of our other New York family isn't here.
AII I see is his man Jelly and some sawed-off prick nobody knows.
The thing is...
...Mr. Vitti's been detained.
PIus, he's sorry...
...for his detainment.
Detained?
What kind of bullshit is that?
What's more important than this?
As the host, I take his not being here as a sign of disrespect to me...
...and all these other men who came a Iong way to be here.
I mean, no. I mean...
You see, the thing is that he's not feeling well.
PIus, he don't feel good.
What's the matter with you?
We never discuss Mr. Vitti's health outside the family.
You know better than that.
Sit down.
Sit down!
You want a fresh one?
Who is this guy?
What the fuck is he doing here?
Who I am?
"Who I am? " "Who am I? "
"Who am I? " is a question for the ages.
That's one we're all searching for, to find out who I am.
Who's in there, who wants to come out and go...
..."Hey, I'm hungry."
"Who I am"...
...is too deep and....
You got to go in deep and pull out the thing...
...Iike that movie where the thing came out of the stomach...
...and ate the people on the fucking spaceship.
May they rest in peace.
My name is Ben Sobol.
Leone.
Ben Soboleone.
I'm also known...
...as Benny the Groin, Sammy the Schnoz...
...EImer the Fudd, Tubby the Tuba...
...and once as Miss Phyllis Levine.
But that was at a party. It was years ago.
I smoked a titibet, and I had a Quaquaalude...
...and suddenly I'm in fishnets singing show tunes.
These things happen, but has nothing to do...
...with what I'm here with you fine gentlemen today.
So I apologize.
That being said, I'm also known to the people who know me the best...
...as the fucking "Doctor."
The second part of your question that you "axed" me...
...is "Why am I here? " I am here...
...representing Mr. Paul Vitti as his consigligliere.
Consigliere.
Never correct me in public again.
Do you understand that?
You broke my heart, Jelly.
You broke my heart.
I apologize for the second interruption.
As Mr. Vitti's...
...consigliere...
...I am involved in all aspects of the Vitti family business...
...and am prepared to speak for Mr. Vitti on all matters.
Okay, Doctor.
Let's stop with the bullshit.
There's been this thing between me...
...and Paul Vitti for a Iong time.
Are you talking about the first thing or the second thing?
What second thing? I only know one thing.
How can we bring up the first if we don't talk about the second?
Did you talk to the guy?
What guy?
The guy with the thing!
What thing? What are you talking about?
How should I know? You brought it up!
This is the problem. Do you see this?
You see what's happening here?
You can't have an intelligent conversation with this guy.
What if I put two bullets in your brain? What do you think of that?
That's a Iittle dark. What do you think?
It's a good idea. Why would I say it if I didn't think it was good?
I don't know. Why would you?
I wouldn't! That's what I'm saying!
Look at what's happening here. Look at you.
Do you feel you have to get angry so people will Iisten to you?
Is that your deal?
What is he saying?
You do have a tendency to get angry a Iot.
I agree, Primo.
T alk about Vitti. Why are we talking about me?
That's interesting too.
Do you feel you're not important enough for us to discuss you?
-What does that mean? -What do you think?
Fuck you!
Calm down.
This prick won't stop with the questions.
Pass the fruit.
You're a dead man!
Put it down.
-Wait in the car. IKeep it running. -How are you feeling?
Sit down. I'II take it from here.
Sit down.
I'm Paul Vitti.
I'm sorry I was Iate. Those who know me know I meant no disrespect.
If it's all right with you...
...I just want to say something. Then I'II Ieave you to your business.
About 2 1 /2 weeks ago, somebody killed my dear friend, Dominic Manetta.
Come on, this is bullshit.
Everybody knows he whacked out Dominic so he could take over.
Whatever.
What I came to say is I've come to a very important decision in my Iife.
And that is...
...I want out.
I don't want to do this no more.
I'm going to go away for a while...
...but I will respect the oath I took the day I was made...
...and what I know about anybody's business I take to the grave.
You have my word.
As for my own family...
...I know Carlo Mangano would Iike to be the new boss.
Thank you, Paul.
That's why he betrayed Dominic and me to our enemies...
...and sent his own man to Miami to try and kill me.
I swear you got this wrong...
Shut your mouth.
Even though it's my right, I won't take revenge.
You want to know why? Because you got a problem.
A problem with aggression.
Maybe you weren't hugged as a kid.
You ought to Iook inside yourself...
...Iook inside and find out who you are.
Because for me...
...I had a breakthrough.
I'm in a good place mentally, and I'm feeling good about me.
I don't know, Paul.
I can see where some people might have a problem with this.
I realize that.
So as a token of good faith...
...I've taken the Iiberty of writing down a few things...
...putting them in a safe-deposit box in case...
...something should happen to me, my friend or my family.
I don't know what anybody else thinks...
...but I say good Iuck and God bless, Paul.
Thank you. Come on, Iet's go.
I'm his friend.
That was remarkable. Do you feel proud?
Some people in therapy never have breakthroughs Iike you had.
I don't want to do this.
Think this is a civil service job? You can just quit and walk away?
What are you, fucking crazy?
Not anymore.
Tell me something.
Will you stab me in the back Iike the shit I always knew you were?
No, I won't stab you in the back.
I want to see your face when I do it.
I don't think so.
Mo-Mo!
Bigs!
Eddie!
It's over, Primo.
Now get the fuck out of here.
Machine gun was a nice touch. A Iittle hostile.
Hands in the air!
Drop your weapons!
Do it now!
I got you! Get down!
Get out of the car! Hands on top of the car!
One fucking move, I swear I'II blow your fucking heart out!
Take a pill, RoboCop! Take a pill!
I can't believe this. You took a bullet for me.
What doc would ever do that for his patient? I'II never forget that.
You...!
I tripped.
You tripped! You tripped over your unconscious.
Mr. Vitti, you have the right to remain silent....
Today's my wedding day.
You got off easy. Eighteen months is nothing.
They found Primo Sindone dead in a field near La Guardia.
I heard. Don't Iook at me. I had nothing to do with it.
A million guys from here to Canarsie were Iooking to whack that bastard.
Good. I was just checking.
Don't worry.
You think we could keep going with the private sessions up here?
You'd Iike to do that?
I could arrange to come up on Saturdays. Or we could do it by phone.
Phone appointments?
I do that when a patient's out of town or in federal prison.
Thanks, Doc.
I never really got to thank you properly...
...for curing me.
We don't say "cure." We say you had a "corrective emotional experience."
Excuse me.
You're something, you.
Yes, you are. You are something.
No, you're something.
You!
Happy?
I just can't get used to it.
Used to what?
It's been so Iong since you were kidnapped.
I don't know if I can adjust.
Listen.
How about one more dance...
...and then we'II go upstairs?
Tony, can you do one more song?
Anything you want.
My friend told me to stay as Iong as you needed me.
I don't want to Iet him down.
"World On A String," the Harold Arlen song.
This is so great.
This is a gift.
I've got the world on a string
I'm sitting on a rainbow
I've got the string
Around my finger
What a world What a life
I'm in love
Good night. Sobols.