The Ring of the Fisherman
which bears the official Papal Sigil.
Must be destroyed immediately following the Pope’s death.
The Papal parchment is then sealed for 9 days of mourning.
A period known as "Sede Vacante"... the time of the Empty Throne.
Over the last several days the Catholic leaders from every corner of the world
have flocked to Rome.
Shocked by the sudden death of this progressive and beloved Pope.
Today in St. Peter's Square
the faithful pray that there is among them another leader who can
reunite their Church
which has been raven by change and dissent in recent years.
As the body of Pontif passes by...
We see prayers being offered by the Preferiti...
favorites among those who are considered to succeed him as the Vicar of Christ.
At the end of the mourning period the Colleague of Cardinals will lock itself
behind the doors of the Sistine Chapel for Conclave.
A process by which they will choose a new leader...
for the world's one billion Catholics
who now find their Church at crossroads...
it's ancient traditions threatened by modern world.
Attention Control booth. Going online on LHC beam event.
We are powering up.
Attention Category 1 personnel.
Interlock areas is now restricted.
You have blocked our access, Philippe.
You are terrified because you gave it your all. The accelerator should never create antimatter.
It's only three cylinders under high security. I only ask you to wait.
Don’t worry.
But listen, even with proper calibration, we might not be prepared.
Are you going to call the director or should I?
Vittoria, Vittoria,
this will not blast us to the other side. So, please.
Powering on RTC magnets.
Ion source age in 4-3-2.
Start the collision sequence.
Vittoria, what did Philippe say?
He did not change his mind.
What do you think?
God help us, if there is a God.
Beam on. Beam stability is good. Take your places people.
Trigger calibrated. Collision is imminent.
Injecting 13 protons per bunch.
Let’s hope the heavy ion guys didn't mess up.
Luminosity monitors operational.
Beam line has no restrictions.
Enable beam captor.
Accelerating the beam.
Stage 1.
Magnets is full field.
Last piece still too high.
Yeah, we got lumonasanity 10 out of 34.
Injecting particle beams.
Turning the LHC.
Capture quickly approaches!
Awaiting completion of resonance.
Particles in transition.
Collision is fixed and running.
LHC injecting protons beam 1.
- Lock the feedback systems.
- Particles at 99% of the speed of light.
Colliding stable beams.
Activating injection kicker.
We have signal on luminosity monitors.
We have events.
Photons are moving.
We have created antimatter.
It seems that we have achieved.
Silvano, we have created it.
We are now in God's hands, Vittoria!
I'm on my way.
Silvano!
Why?
Help!
This swim might...
help your jet lag.
I beg your pardon?
Them bags under your eyes...
Besides it's 5 in the morning
and you are from Vatican.
The crossed keys under Triregnum.
It is the Papal symbol.
Claudio Vicenza, Corpodella Gendarmerie Vaticano.
Vatican police?
I was expecting another letter
to my request to access your archives.
Shouldn't you be in Rome? Kind of busy time for you guys.
In fact, I was in New York...
detailed to the UN.
I received a phone call middle of the night.
"Find Professor Robert Langdon,"
"A matter of great urgency."
They told me to show you this.
The Illuminati? They disappeared hundreds of years ago.
- Did they?
- Look at that again.
It is an ambigram. It is the same image forwards and backwards.
Now that’s common for a symbol like Yin and Yang
or a swastika but...that's a word.
That Illuminati ambigramatic symbol has been considered a myth for 400 years.
Possibly in 16th century some artist created it as a tribute to Galileo’s love of symmetry.
It was only gonna be revealed when the Illuminati had amassed enough power...
to resurface and carry out their final goal.
I wrote a book about it.
Which is why you are here.
The Art of the Illuminati -- By Robert Langdon.
Part 1.
Haven’t been able to finish Part 2 because I’m not allowed access to your archives.
It's remarkable... similar.
Someone is trying to make you believe the llluminatis themselves have returned to Rome.
Right after the death of the Pope...
4 Cardinals were kidnapped from their quarters inside Vatican sometime between
3 and 5 AM this morning.
Shortly afterwards...
that document was sent to the office of the Swiss Guard...
along with the threat...
the Cardinals would be publicly executed 1 per hour beginning at 8 PM tonight
in Rome.
Conclave?
Was to begin today. We postponed the start for a few hours as story of illness.
There are no suspicions... yet.
What do you want from me?
These criminals who sent this ambigram
meant it as a taunt.
A provocation.
But Capitan Olivetti thinks if you can use it to learn their identity
perhaps, we can stop this abomination.
Why me?
Your expertise, your erudition.
Your reciting involvement with certain Church, shall we say... mysteries?
I wasn't under the impression that episode had endeared me to the Vatican.
Oh, it didn’t.
But, it did make you... what’s that word...forma...formi...
Formidable?
A Vatican jet is standing by 20 minutes from here...
Will you come with me?
Professor Langdon
you spent your life searching for symbols like the one you now hold in your hand.
How much longer are we going to pretend you’re not already decided to come?
If Illuminati have returned and are in Rome
we will hunt them down and kill them.
The Illuminati did not become violent until the 17th century.
Their name means "The Enlightened Ones"...
They were physicists, mathematicians, astronomers.
They were concerned...
with a Church and an inaccurate teaching and they were dedicated to scientific truth.
But the Vatican did not like that. So the Church begun to...
How do you say it...?
Oh, hunt them down and killed them.
Drove them down underground
into a secret society.
- Professor Langdon.
- Yes.
Welcome to the Vatican City.
Ernesto Olivetti, Inspector General of Vatican police force.
My pleasure.
This way please.
We'll meet in the headquarters of the Swiss Guard.
- I thought you were Swiss Guard.
- No, uh, the Gendarmaria.
We are responsible for everything inside the Vatican walls.
With the exception of the Security of a... His Holiness
and the Apostolic Palace... That is Swiss Guard.
The Ramon carbieri are here as well
in an advisory capacity.
So jurisdictionally this is.
A god-dammed nightmare.
Oh, yes. Pope Pius the 9th. The Great Castration.
I beg your pardon?
1857, Pope Pius the 9th felt
the male form would inspire lust...
So he took hammer and chisel and...
unmanned hundreds of these statues.
The plaster fig leaves were added later.
Are you anti-catholic Professor Langdon?
No.
I'm anti-vandalism.
I urge you to guard your tone here.
The Swiss Guard is a calling.
Not a profession.
Commander Richter the head of the Guard.
He is a deeply spiritual man.
He was very close to the late Pope. Understood.
Look, I don’t study the symbols because I consider them
unimportant ceremonial traditions that mark our lives.
I just hope I can help.
So do I.
You were my idea.
Wait here. Please.
Commander...Commander Richter.
Dr. Vetra.
I’m Commander Richter. Commentate Principale of the Swiss Guard.
Thank you for coming.
Hello.
Oh, Professor Langdon.
What a relief... The symbolist is here.
This way please, Miss Vetra.
The situation has changed.
We received another threat from the kidnapper.
The canister was stolen from our lab around noon yesterday.
The intruder killed my research partner Silvano Bentivoglio
and mutilated him in order to bypass security.
We use retinal scanners...
They cut out his eye.
Is that your stolen canister Ms. Vetra?
Where is that camera number 86?
It's wireless. It too was stolen, lt could be anywhere inside Vatican walls.
That canister contains extremely combustible substance called antimatter.
We need to relocate it immediately, or evacuate Vatican City.
I am quite familiar with the substances Miss Vetra
I never heard antimatter is used as such.
Well it was never generated in significant quantities before.
It is a way of studying the origins of the universe.
Try to isolate what some people called God 'Particle'.
But there are implications for energy research.
God 'Particle'?
Ah, what we call it isn’t important. lt’s what gives all matter mass.
The thing without which it could not exist.
You are talking about "The Moment of Creation."
Yes, in a way I am.
The antimatter is suspended there,
in an air-tight nanocapacity shell with electromagnets in its head.
But if it were to fall out of suspension and come in contact with the matter,
say bottom of canister...
the 2 opposing forces would annihilate one other violently.
And what might cause it to fall out of suspension?
The battery going dead... Which it will. Just before midnight.
What kind of annihilation, how violent?
A cataclysmic event.
A blinding explosion equivalent to about 5 kilotons.
Vatican City would be consumed by light.
Those are the exact words the kidnappers used.
"We will destroy your 4 pillars."
"We will brand your Preferiti,"
"and sacrifice them on the altars of science."
"Then bring your Church down upon you."
"Vatican will see they will be consumed by light."
"A shining star at the end of the path... of illumination."
It’s the ancient and only one threat.
Destruction of Vatican City through the Light.
The 4 pillars. These are the kidnapped Cardinals.
You didn’t tell me they were Preferiti. The favorites to be named the next Pope.
Play it again.
We will destroy your 4 pillars.
- We will brand your Preferiti...
- Wait. Stop.
Brand them?
That’s another...
Illuminati legend. This one says there's a...
set of 5 brands...
Each one an ambigram. The 1st 4 are the fundamentals of science.
Earth, Air, Fire and Water.
The 5th is a mystery.
Maybe it is this.
They say they will be killed publicly.
Yes.
Revenge.
For "La Purga".
"La Purga"?
Geez, you guys don’t even read your own history, do you?
1668.
The Church kidnapped 4 Illuminati scientists and branded each one of them on the chest...
with a symbol of the cross.
To 'purge' them of their sins and they executed them.
Threw their bodies out on the street...
as warning to others to stop questioning...
the Church ruling on scientific matters.
They radicalized them.
The Purge created a darker more violent Illuminati.
Went bent on... on retribution.
And look how they intend to finally get it... using antimatter.
Technology to destroy the Church. Science to obliterate Religion.
Is there any more?
"... and sacrifice them on the altar of science."
"Then bring your Church down upon you."
"Vatican will see they will be consumed by light."
"A shining star at the end of the path... of Illumination."
I need access to the Vatican archives.
Professor I don’t think this is the appropriate moment.
- Your petition has been denied 7 times.
- No. No. This has nothing to do with my work.
The path of the Illumination.
It is a hidden trail through Rome itself. It leads to the Church of the Illumination.
A place where Illuminati would meet in secret.
If I can find the seal, the sign that marks the beginning of that path,
the 4 churches is maybe along where he intends to murder your Cardinals.
One every hour at 8, 9, 10 and 11. Then the device explodes...
At midnight.
If we can figure out the first Church and get there before he does, maybe we can stop it.
But I can’t find the start of the path till I get into the archives.
Even if I wanted to help you...
access to archives is only by written decree by
the curator of the board of the Vatican Librarians.
Or by Papal mandate.
Yes, as you no doubt you heard Holy Father is dead.
What about il Camerlengo?
The Camerlengo is just a priest here.
The former Pope's Chamberlain.
Doesn't the power of the Holy See rest in him during "Tempo Sede Vacante"?
Fellows... you called me.
His Holiness once told me that the Pope is a man...
torn between real world and the divine.
It seems that the real world is upon us tonight.
I'm familiar with the Illuminati lore and the legend of the brandings.
The Purges are dark stains on this Church history.
I'm not surprised that this ghost has returned to haunt us.
Commandante.
Have you begun a search for this explosive device?
Of course, but it could be anywhere.
Our primary concern at the moment is to safety of the Cardinals.
The Sistine Chapel is a fortress.
As long the Cardinals are in the Conclave your security concerns are at minimum.
- Devote as many.
- Signori...
if you’re about to suggest naked eye search of the entire Vatican city.
I will tell you we do not have the people.
Though I am not His Holiness
when you are addressing me you are addressing this office. Do you understand?
Yes Father.
Good.
Now you said that the image on the screen was illuminated with artificial light.
Might I suggest methodically cutting power to...
various sections of the city.
When an image in screen goes dark you will have more specific idea
of the camera's location.
Dr. Vetra, besides yourself and your research partner
who else knew of this antimatter project?
No one but the research team.
This project was strictly confidential.
But Silvano kept detailed journals. If he told anyone else
about what we were doing he would have made note of it.
Do you have these journals?
I can have them flown here from Geneve in an hour.
Please.
Professor Langdon.
Mr. Langdon.
You are correct that I may grant you access to the archives.
Thank you padre.
I said correct that I may. Not that I will.
Christianity’s most secrets codices are in that archive...
Given your recent entanglement with the Church
there is a question I like to ask you first here in the office of His Holiness.
Do you believe in God, sir?
Father I simply believe that religion...
I didn’t asked you to tell me what man says of God.
I asked if you believe in God.
I am an academic.
My mind tells me that I will never...
understand God.
And your heart?
Tells me I’m not meant to...
Faith is a gift that I have yet to receive.
Be delicate with our treasures.
Archives is this way.
Professor Langdon.
If this path really leads to the Church of the Illumination
that may be where they have hidden the antimatter.
Shining star at the end of the path I thought so too.
Follow the path
and we may find the canister at the end of it.
Can you deactivate the device?
I can change the canister's battery so long as we have more than 5 minutes supply,
That would give us another 24 hours to get it safely back to CERN.
Robert Langdon.
Vittoria Vetra.
Are you really symbolist or was he mocking you?
Both.
- you are physicist?
- bio-danglement physics.
Interconnecting life systems.
Okay.
Your project, was it good to energy research?
Eventually yes.
One peg of antimatter could power the entire city for a month.
Or tonight I guess destroy one.
What are we looking for in archives?
A banned volume by Galileo.
Galileo was an Illuminati?
Yes and Catholic
who thinks Church and science were enemies...
but just a difference in languish telling the same story...
he would like minds to find the Church of the Illumination.
But he could not actually advertise it's location...
So he created a coded path.
Richter has started to turn off power on various grids. It will be back in a minute.
Then some unknown Illuminati master sculpted 4 statues.
Each one a tribute to one of the fundamental elements.
Earth, air, water and fire, and placed the statues out in public, in churches throughout Rome.
Each statue held clue pointing to the next.
At the end of the path was Church of the Illumination...
If you could find that then you could find them.
What makes you think they're going to murder Cardinals in the churches?
The Illuminatti called those 4 churches by the special name "L'altare de la Scienza"...
"Sacrifice them on the altar of science", he said.
Exactly.
Wow...
Look at this.
Excuse me Signori.
Cardinal Strauss have you been informed of the situation?
Yeah.
My belief is we should proceed with the sealing of Conclave.
At this late hour?
That would be highly unorthodox.
And yet with such laws it’s my power. I'm the great elector.
Cruelest honor and a crusader.
I have no personal ambitions Patrick.
Only those out for my Church.
St. Peter's Church
which is taken at it's most vulnerable moment.
And this is not a coincidence.
The Church will not fall in a day.
We must evacuate Vatican City.
That is exactly what they want. Publicity and panic.
No, you must not give them oxygen for the media fire.
But people in St. Peter's Square
care deeply about their Church
as we do.
Their faith will sustain them.
Their Faith will not protect them from an explosion.
We are all bound for heaven eventually are we not?
Spoken like one who has enjoyed the blessings of a long full life.
Patrick.
Do not confuse the power of the office you temporary hold
with your true place!
Intermediate!
You were the favorite of His Holiness.
But His Holiness...
is with his Father now.
I’m sorry. Mea culpa.
Seal the doors.
It's time. Everyone outside.
Fellows, this way please.
Oh. Beautiful.
The chambers are hermetic boxes.
Oxygen is kept to lowest possible levels.
There is a partial vacuum inside, so extensive stays is not recommended.
So don’t panic if you feel like lightheaded at first.
I’ll be just outside the door watching you
Mr. Langdon.
The 2nd Payment Transfer
lsle of Man.
The Conclave will go on without us.
It must now of all times.
May God forgive you for what you've done.
Father, if God have issues...
they won’t be what I've done...
They will be with what I’m about do.
It was confiscated from The Nederlands by the Vatican just after Galileo died.
I petitioned to see it about 10 years ago
every since I realized what... what was in it?
What makes you so sure this thing is there?
The number 503.
I kept seeing it over and over again in Illuminati letters,
Scribbled in the margins...
Some times just signed 503. It is a numeric clue.
But to what?
Well, that’s a meaningful number to the Illuminati.
There's the pentagram. Pythagoras. Dozens of other examples in science.
But what about 3?
It didn’t makes sense, till I thought what if it was roman numerals?
The I I I
The 3.
Galileo’s 3rd text.
Dialogo
Discorso
Diagramma.
Just a few days of this and l could've actually finished my book.
And sold dozen copies of it at the Harvard bookstore.
Diagramma Veritatis.
Diagram of Truth.
I know about the book.
Galileo laid out his theories about the earth revolving around the Sun.
He said that the earth was not the center of some universe heaven up hell below.
As Church said it was.
So they forced him to recant his second book.
But what was this one?
This is how he got the word out.
This is the truth. Not what Vatican forced him to write.
Smuggled out of Rome, printed in Holland on setched papyrus. See?
That way any scientist that was caught with copy could just
throw it in water and Galileo’s heresy would dissolve. Disappear.
Between that and the Vatican burnings...
it’s possible this is the only copy that remains.
And if I am not incorrect...
seniel
is hidden on page number...
5.
Yeah.
Do you need help with the Latin?
Sure.
Movement of the planets, elliptical orbits, idiosyntricity...
Sorry. Don’t think there is anything that could be interpreted as a...
Wait, wait, wait.
Do that again.
What is that?
It is a watermark and there is a line of text.
Go back.
It’s in English.
English? Why English?
English wasn't used in the Vatican.
It was too polluted.
It's free thinking.
It was the language of radicals, like Shakespeare and Chaucer.
Here's another one.
"The path of light is laid a sacred test."
- Would you write this down as I dictate?
- Sorry professor, no time.
Yeah, yeah. What the hell. Yeah.
20 minutes till 8. Where are we heading?
Hold on. Hold on. I'll tell in a minute.
Let me see that page again.
Where did you get that paper?
We borrowed it.
- "From Santi's earthly tomb, the demon's hole..."
- Are you insane?
- "across Rome the mystic elements unfold. The path of light is laid in a sacred test."
- "Let angels guide thee on thy lofty quest."
You removed a document from the Vatican archives?
She did.
"From Santi's earthly tomb..."
- The first marker is at Santis tomb.
- Yeah.
- But, but who is Santi?
- Rafael.
- Raphael? The sculptor?
- Yeah. Santi was his last name.
So that path starts at Rafael's tomb.
Rafael is buried at the Pantheon.
Isn’t the Pantheon a Church?
The oldest catholic Church in Rome.
I just have chosen my best men for this. You better be right.
This is one of the busiest spot in all of Rome. You can never get away with it. It's impossible.
The poem implies.
- the poem?
Unbelievable.
I’m basing this operation on an American interpreter of a 400 year old poem.
Well the information we have clearly refers to Raphael's tomb...
And Raphael's tomb is inside that building.
And because the Vatican destroyed all of the pagan statues in late 1800s...
if this is the first marker, whatever clues that were here to lead us to the next are sure gone by now...
The path is dead. So this is it. Your only chance.
Separate approaches. No closer than 2 blocks and no uniforms in 3 minutes.
I'll need a set of eyes inside!
Excuse me...
Richter, they wear matching black suites and earpieces. They are hardly disguised.
- That’s what I have.
- Wow. Fine I’m going.
You don’t have communication. You can’t carry a Walkie Talkie. It’s too conspicuous.
- Tourists have cell phones don’t they?
- No. No, you can't send her in there alone.
Alright I won't.
Don’t look so anxious. We're supposed to be married.
Well, maybe we are not coming along today. Hmm?
Hold my hand.
- But don’t crush it.
- Sorry, nervous newlywed.
Ooh. Look, honey. The oculus.
That could be the demons hall in the poem.
Why are the tombs at an angle?
They are facing east worshiping the rising sun.
But, this is a Christian Church.
New religions often adopt the existing customs and holidays to make conversion less of a shock.
Like the 25th of December. It's the pagan's celebration of the unconquered sun.
Also makes a handy date for birth of Christ.
Let's check the recesses. I go to the right. I'll meet you in 180 degrees.
Follow me please.
Now, the Pantheon which means temple of the gods
was originally built as a temple to all the gods of ancient Rome
in 27 B.C.
Although the building is usually credited to Agrippa of Damascus...
Robert!
It is the Raphael tomb but it is the wrong one.
What are you talking about?
He was moved here in 1759 a century after the Diagramma was published.
Where was he originally buried?
Genoa I think.
What could posssibly be Santi's earthly tomb?
Damn it! Santi's tomb.
It must mean the Chapel that he built.
He's not buried there but he designed it.
The demons hall.
It’s an undercroft. It’s a crypt.
- Any questions?
- Yes. Yes.
Did Raphael Santi ever design a Chapel with an ossuary anex in an angel figure commissioned by the Catholic Church?
I’m sorry, I can only think of one.
One is good.
- Wrong? What do you mean wrong?
- It's the Chigi Chapel in the Church of Santa Maria del Popolo.
It was once called Capella della Terra,
the Chapel of the earth.
Earth, the first element. That’s it!
- You were certain about the Pantheon.
- We have 4 minutes.
We end this! Let’s go back to Vatican.
Back to the Vatican. But you can’t!
Commandate if you cared all about your Church you listen to me.
My Church?
My Church comforts the sick and dying.
My Church feeds the hungry. What does your Church do, Mr. Langdon?
That’s right, you don’t have one.
Take him if you want. I’m done with him.
Alright this make sense. Look, look right front of the Church.
An obelisk lofty pyramid.
The Egyptian symbol adopted by the Illuminati.
If he's going to kill him he'll do it here.
8 o’clock.
The clock.
Robert.
- Its locked.
- Force the gate.
No. No. Here. It's an Annulus.
- Which one is the Chigi Chapel?
- Must be in one of these areas.
Pyramids in the Catholic Church.
This is it. This is the Chigi Chapel.
The Demons Hall.
But it is askew. Come here.
Give me your flashlight.
What is that?
They are voting for themselves to prevent a majority.
They're waiting for the Preferiti to be rescued.
Perhaps we should as well. Yes?
Not until the smoke is white,
will the Colleague of Cardinals have chosen a new Holy Father.
But now the Vatican seat of ultimate power remains vacant.
Get the body out of there.
Search the rest of the building.
Sir.
Outside a perimeter, Secure but invisible.
No light. No guns. Nobody knows. Understand?
- Yes sir.
- Call in all off-duty.
- Is it Rafael?
- The Chapel is Rafael.
But the sculptures are Bernini.
The unknown Illuminati master.
Bernini?
He worked for the Church.
Almost exclusively.
But the Illuminati were infiltrators.
There wasn’t a powerful organization on earth they didn’t penetrate
including the Vatican by hiding in plain sight.
Habakkuk and the Angel.
It's the prophet that predicted the annihilation of the earth.
"Let angels guide thee on thy lofty quest."
This is the first marker. The path is alive.
Southwest.
It was pointing southwest.
Earth, air, fire, water. We're looking for a Bernini sculpture having something to do with air.
The second Church is somewhere southwest of here.
You are sure this time?
I need a map showing all churches of Rome.
I could use it now!
The purple layers with these black crosses represent the churches.
But nothing intersects the line until it hits...until it hits St. Peter's.
Michelangelo designed St. Peter's. Not Bernini.
Michelangelo designed the Basilica. Bernini designed St. Peter's Square.
The second marker must be a statue in St. Peter's Square.
It's 10 minutes to 9, can't we go any faster?
Not unless you want full attention of the world press.
St. Peter's.
No majority in the first vote, but Cardinal Baggia from Italy is the clear favorite...
Still no new Pope, but Cardinal Guidera from Spain has the best chance...
The more conceivable candidate could be Cardinal Ebner from Germany...
Stem cell research saves lives!
Man is not God!
There, another obelisk.
Check the crowd. It's almost 9. He's got to be here already.
There must be hundreds of statues up there.
None of them are angels. Those are all saints.
How in God’s name could you create a sculpture about air?
Bas relief. Of course.
It’s still a sculpture. Check the ground. Look at the carvings.
Look for another something to do with air.
Vento Ponente. West Wind.
Vittoria. Here it is.
West wind. An angel blowing in 5 streaks of air.
This is it.
He's still alive.
His chest.
They punctured his lungs.
"And you squeezed the life out of a bishop of Rome."
He's actually claiming responsibility for the death of His Holiness.
That’s rediculous. He died of the stroke.
It implies Illuminati murder of him with his medication.
What?
Down here.
"With man's solution we stilled his heart."
"With his own needle did we pierce his unholy vein."
Did the Holy Father take any kind of medication by injection?
Tinzaparin.
He had thrombophlebitis. He took injection every day but no one knew that.
Someone knew.
He had health concern and seizures as well.
But he took steps to make sure he was watched
for safety.
He didn’t want it made public so we have no reason to discuss.
Tinzaparin is lethal in wrong doses.
An overdose could cause massive internal bleeding and brain hemmorhages.
It may look stroke at first but in a few days his body would show signs.
This could easily be examined.
Miss Vetra in case you are not aware of it, Papal autopsy is prohibited by Vatican law.
You are not going to defile His Holiness' body
- just because of these claims.
- Why would they send this letter now?
To cause panic.
The sun will blind at midnight
and neither police or professors can stop it.
He knows I’m here.
Oblivious they're hoping this letter would became public.
We might be wise to preempt their next attempt
by making an announcement of our own.
- To refute this absurd claim.
- That’s out of question.
Cardinal Strauss insist this entire matter kept internal.
He shouldn't be aware of it. He's locked in Conclave.
His final instructions before sealing the doors were very clear.
Cardinal Strauss does not dictate Vatican protocols.
And to say, yet, technically, now that Conclave has begun,
it is privilege and duty to control public announcements.
I've drafted a press release about incident at the piazza
but any other statements specifically prohibited.
For that, Cardinal has asked me to remind you we have a chimney.
Commander Richter... the search for the device.
We've turned the power on and off about 20 percent of the Vatican city.
- Nothing on the video yet.
- We are running out of options.
How long would you need to evacuate everyone?
If I pull all my men from the search for the bomb, 30 minutes.
Mr. Langdon you have been right so far about the path.
It’s now 9:15 how quickly can you find the next Church.
The lines of breath on carving pointed due east directly away from Vatican City.
But there are 5 of them so there's room for error.
About 20 churches intercept those lines.
None of them have names include fire.
So the Bernini sculpture must be inside one of them that does.
I need to get back into archives to find it.
- Would you escort Mr. Langdon?
- Yes Father.
Silvano's journals... the killer's name could be in here.
- Can I stay?
- Please, Fine. Of course.
Professor.
Where you surprised to find those clothes suite you.
It would surprise the hell out of me.
The Vatican expressed its sympathy with the families of the victim.
A tourist from Düsseldorf, whose death is confirmed.
Vatican police have arrested a suspect...
The investigation is completed.
Vatican will permit access to St. Peter's again, with strict security measures.
The Vatican did admit that, where there are crowds, so often follows crime.
We're trying now to get the name of the tourist who was...
But wait...
We're getting word of smoke, smoke from the Sistine Chapel chimney
Apparently theres been a
another vote, the smoke is black.
Once again the Cardinals have failed to reach consensus and the Catholic Church remains without a leader.
What are you looking for?
- Church assets.
- I beg your pardon.
Art work is valuable.
Corporations tend to keep track of their holdings.
The Catholic Church is not a corporation. It's a beacon.
A source of inspiration for one billion lost and frightened souls.
- Sure I get that. It’s also a bank.
Commandate Olivetti said not leave out of site this time.
It wasn’t me. It was her.
The flow in Zone 3 is disabled.
No response on the screen.
Flow in Zone 3 again and continue to Zone 4.
What sort of signs?
I’m sorry.
If the Holy Father was given an overdose of zansiban.
What signs would his body bare?
Bleeding of the oral mucosa.
His tongue.
Post-mortem, the blood congeals, then turns the inside of the mouth black.
Even after 14 days?
It wouldn't show up at least a week after his death.
It’s very important to me.
Yeah I understand.
Will you come with me please?
Signore, would you organize a security team to escort Ms. Vetra and myself down to the crypt?
- Yes, sir.
- We'll leave immediately.
Do you smoke?
A little bit.
You better sit down before you keel over.
What does this say in English?
Ecstasy of Saint Theresa. Right there.
Moved at suggestion of the artist.
Moved to another Church. At the suggestion of Bernini?
I don’t know.
Here. Translate all of this for me.
I’ll buy you a pack of smokes. I’m looking for references to a fire.
- Seraphim, meaning the fiery one.
- Right.
This great golden spear.
A point of fire.
Then "Woman left completely afire."
The ecstasy of Saint Theresa. St. Teresa on fire.
So this sculpture was moved to this Church?
Why'd they shut down the system? They know that we are down here.
If there's no power, there's no oxygen.
- Can we get out the door?
- It's electronic.
Well, that’s disappointing.
- Where are we going?
- To see my father.
I do not understand.
I was in orphan when I was 9 years of age.
A bombing in Ulster, the UVF protesting the visit of a Catholic Archbishop.
The Archbishop felt responsible and he adopted me the following day.
And he adopted me following day.
I was raised by him and by the Church.
He is the wisest man I have ever met.
Even when I was young and stubborn,
I wanted to be ordained...
but I was brought up in Italy, so l also wanted to do my military service.
I wanted to fight...
He told me, "Learn to fly."
So, I joined the Aeronautica Militare. Flew helicopters.
Bringing the wounded back to hospitals. He was a great man.
Your father died?
14 days ago.
- Can you get anything?
- No. The walls are lead-lined. There is no signal.
This way.
If the Holy Father was murdered...
the implication is profound.
Vatican security is impenetrable.
No one from outside could get near him.
It was someone who is inside.
Then we cannot trust no one.
On my screen, no response in Zone 7.
With all these power cuts, the battery will soon be empty...
The device will explode at midnight.
Holy Father...
when I was young you told me the voice in my heart was God's voice...
You said I should follow it no matter how painful...
Forgive me. Please give me strength.
What I do, I do in the name of everything you believe.
Santa Maria del Vittoria. Do you know it?
- Yes I do.
- It's the next Church.
I think someone just tried to kill me.
Professor, I promise you, we had no idea.
- He knows I’m here.
- Yes.
You heard me ask permission. You gave me an escort.
Yes, but we had no idea that portions of our white zones were crosswired with that building.
Commander Richter was extending the search.
If he had known the archives were on that grid
he would never have killed the power.
But there is the other possibility.
Is it conceivable the Illuminati have... infiltrated the Swiss Guard?
Perhaps.
The journals, where are they?
Who took the journals from this desk?
Signore, this is unacceptable...
for a Camerlengo to enter the Chapel once Conclave has begun.
Forgive me, there's been a development.
Signori, please, a moment. Please. Signori.
Our Church is at war.
We are under attack from an old enemy.
The Illuminati.
They have struck us from within.
Murdering our Holy Father...
And threatening us all with destruction at the hands of their new God 'Science'.
They call it retribution. They think they are justified.
Because of the Church attacks on the men of science in the distant past...and it’s true...
Since the days of Galileo this Church has tried to slow the relentless march of progress.
Sometimes with misguided means.
But science and religion are not enemies.
There are simply some things that science is just too young to understand.
So the Church pleads, "Stop."
"Slow down. Think. Wait"
For this they call us backward.
But who is more ignorant? The man who cannot define the lightning...
or the man who does not respect its natural awesome power?
The battle is well on their way Signori.
We must defend ourselves.
But, what if this time, we fight their stealth with openness?
Combat their wicked scheme with simple truth.
And end this brutish battle once and for all...
If the outside world could
see this Church as I do...
looking beyond rituals these walls...
they would see a modern miracle.
A Brotherhood of imperfect simple souls...
who want nothing more than to be voices of compassion...
in a world spinning out of control.
Signori I ask, l pray...
that you break this Conclave.
Open the doors. Evacuate St. Peter's Square.
And tell the world the truth.
Get him down.
There. There, that chain. On that pulley.
This bench. Get this pew off here and make it a ladder.
Vatican Police.
My son. God answers all prayers, but...
Sometimes His answer is no.
Colleague will not break Conclave...
May I suggest that you direct your energies to helping the Swiss Guard find...
this explosive device...
if it exists. And leave
Church leadership...
to it's leaders.
Eminence.
There is a growing fear.
That without the 4 Preferiti it defers much authority for any candidate.
It will be not possible unless...
Speak plainly.
It is our recommendations to ask you to be removed from your post as great elector.
Thereby making you self eligible...
to wear the Ring of the Fisherman.
Well, maybe it is God’s will.
His will be done.
Here! I hear someone. Here!
Remove the lid!
Come on! Come on!
Signore are you okay?
Those journals are private property. I demand that you return them to me.
Material evidence in a Vatican investigation.
I’m an Italian citizen. My rights don’t end because I crossed to the other side.
This is not it. Its not even Rome. It's Vatican.
Country of its own. With its own laws. When those journals pass the border...
they become my property l will give them back to you
when I decide they contain nothing of value to this investigation.
Do you have something to hide Commandante Richter?
Do you Dr. Vetra?
If it were up to me. you wouldn't be this way...
It’s a sin to kill with pain.
It's a sin to kill without reason, Father.
They made me a sinner.
St. Teresa on fire.
Professor Landon?
What direction is that?
West I think.
"Across Rome the mystic elements unfold."
Piazza Barba Rini is here. Saint Theresa is here.
Where is the Santa Maria del Popolo the first altar of science?
- Santa Maria del Popolo?
- Yes.
Here.
Thank you.
St. Peter's is here.
We are here.
A Church with water.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Across Rome.
The poem must mean it literally across Rome.
Prof. Landon, Commander Richter has ordered me to escort you to Vatican immediately.
Piazza Navona. Earth, air, fire, water cross Rome.
Briminis 4 rivers.
Professor Langdon. Commander Richter has ordered me to escort you to the Vatican immediately.
Vatican is about to see the 4th Cardinal that.
Now look.
You can do as they say and force me back to Vatican...
We can all mourn his death together...
or you could show how real cops act...
and take me to piazza divine where we still might able to stop it.
Oh, by all means let’s talk it over.
In 14 minutes he's going to be dead.
Yes Padre.
At 11:15 if the Church is still in peril
give the order to evacuate the Cardinals...
but with dignity. Let them walk out St. Peters Square with heads held high...
I don’t want the last image of the Church to be of frightened old men sneaking out of the back door.
"Where the angels guide thee..."
There it is. There it is.
Professor I know this fountain. There is no angel on it.
The dove...
The angel of peace...
It’s looking in what direction?
East I think.
Professor just wait here...
stay put.
Turn off your engine.
Hey!
Help!
Somebody help!
Help! Somebody.
Where was he hiding you?
The Church of Illumination, where is it?
San Angelo
Castle of the angel.
Sir, there is news about Cardinal Batia.
The Cardinal told Langdon he was being held in castle St. Angelo...
If Langdon’s right, that’s where the bomb is.
- send everyone we can spare.
- And you?
I’m staying here.
Vittoria.
- Are you are alright?
- I’m alright. Yes. What about you?
- I just heard about Olivetti on the radio.
- C’mon I’m okay.
Robert, we can’t trust Richter he took Silvano's journals.
There must be something in there he doesn’t want us to see.
The head of the Swiss Guard.
Castle of St. Angelo is close enough... So the wireless signal from that camera
still reaches Vatican.
The Church of The Illumination is somewhere in here.
Your canister's inside it.
Come with me.
For 400 years Illuminati met under the Church's nose.
Tthe Vatican used it as hideout and prison for their enemies.
If an explosion happens here blast radius takes out Vatican
entire Rome with it.
They are pointing it to the angels. Canister must be down there.
- Where are they going?
- Back to search outer castle.
No. It’s got to be here.
Robert it's dead-end.
No it's not.
See if you can find a flashlight.
All of these stones are rectangular granite.
Except right here. What is this?
It’s a pentagram.
- An eye...
that leads to...
Nowhere.
Robert.
These walls overlap. Passage way is in here.
Here. Give me the flashlight.
It’s a passage way that leads to Vatican.
An ancient escape route.
My God.
Here.
Look.
Final payment in Volkswagen
Key taped driver's side front wheel
Get on the radio. Get the word out.
Conclave remain sealed.
- But Camerlengo gave the order for the evacuation.
- I’m counter-demanding it.
This is it, this is the Church.
The canister should be lit by artificial light.
- It is not here, Robert.
- Shining star at end of the path. It has to be.
It’s not here.
- What does the poem say?
- Nothing.
I think it’s all over. There are
just 4 lines each one describing...
There is a fifth brand. It’s not an ambigram. Just crossed keys.
- symbol for the Vatican.
- No. For the Papacy.
They intend to kill him.
They are going to kill Pope themselves.
There is no Pope.
"Tempo Sede Vacante."
Camerlengo.
Take step back please.
Take the cell from your pocket.
Throw them to the fire.
Murderer.
You know when they call me...
and they call me.
It is so important to them that I know that what they ask...
is the Lord's will,
Or Allah's. Or Yahweh's.
I suppose they are right.
Because if it was not vengeance l wouldn’t exist now would I?
I've had several chances to eliminate you tonight.
You are still alive because you have no weapons.
And they didn’t ask me to kill you.
But, if you pursue me it is another matter.
Be careful.
These are men of God.
We can’t let him go.
Have you come to make me a martyr?
Here, here.
- I need to see the Camerlengo.
- He's not available.
- I demand to see Camerlengo
We'll see about that.
It's a chiusa chiave. It's a one way portal.
The only entrance is on the other side.
Hey!
Open the door!
Camerlengo is in danger!
He's the one. He has a gun.
Illumati!
- you Bastard.
- Illumati!
- Padre.
- Order the evacuation.
We only have 19 minutes.
And get the helicopter for the older Cardinals. Right. Yes, sir.
Robert, the brand symbol could have another meaning.
The keys. Those were upside down.
- St. Peter.
- The first Pope.
He was crucified upside down.
- On Vatican Hill.
- Few hundred feet below us.
Necropolis. City of the Dead...
"Upon this rock, I will build my Church."
"Or bring it down upon itself."
The bomb. It is in St. Peter's tomb.
The grid is still cycling. The power to this section must be down.
It must be here. It must be.
Don’t touch it.
We have 7 minutes.
Robert, hold this.
It's cold down here, isn’t it?
What's wrong?
The cold decreases battery life.
So we may have less than 5 minutes.
So.
If I pull the power with less than 5 minutes...
the residual charge won’t hold the suspension.
We should leave it here and get clear if we can.
At least down here the damage...
- No!
- Father!
We are live here at St. Peter's Square. Where despite a bomb threat...
and orderly evacuation the crowd is actually growing in size...
as we wait for an official announcement from the Vatican spokesmen...
for the exact nature of the threat...
and whether or not they are treating it as credible danger.
This way!
He's got a bomb with him.
A bomb?
Roberto this is an emergency, l'll take her up alone.
He's got clearance.
Oh, my God!
Get down.
Cardinal Strauss...
It was the Camerlengo. He has saved us all.
He has saved the Church and he's still alive.
He is alive.
Praise God. Praise God,
He's alive.
He sacrificed himself for all of us.
You know that worst thing we thought that could happen
was that our work would fall into the hands of the energy companies.
We thought we could change the world...
So naive.
No. Not naive.
Innocent maybe.
But... it's not a crime.
I’m not so sure.
Go back to work.
Change the world.
The Carmelengo's age is
insufficient and he's just a priest.
Signori, you are no doubt aware of the Holy Law of man that he is inelligible for election to the Papacy.
He's not a Cardinal. He's a priest. He is of insufficient age.
Or maybe there is a way we could do to consider possibilities.
I’m sorry, protocols of Conclave are not subject to modification.
I will not call a ballot on this matter.
But Signore, you cannot call a ballot.
Surely you remember. You gave up your post as great elector.
They are singing in at St. Peter's Square. Now, what happened here tonight transcends our laws.
Does it? It is God's will that we give ourselves over to frenzy.
Discard the rules of the Church.
Perhaps we need not discard them.
Signori, I am thinking now of Romano Pontifici Eligendo numero 60...
- Acclamation by Adoration.
- Exactly, Signore. Exactly.
If the Holy Spirit speaks through us...
and we call a man’s name out loud... that is election by adoration.
He's God's choice.
And the candidate need only be an ordained member of the clergy...
present in the Sistine Chapel
at the moment of his election.
- Signor Camerlengo.
- Yes.
The Cardinals asked you to join them in Conclave as soon as possible.
Me?
Yes Padre.
- What are you doing?
- Getting some journals. I want them back.
Richter said,
"His Holiness suffered from seizures. We're taking steps"
"for safety."
"Make sure he is watched." he said.
What if he were trying to give me this key?
That’s the Papal office.
If the Pope was worried about seizures, he must've had Richter install cameras without telling anyone.
To keep an eye on him, for safety.
Maybe it's records.
I read the journals Patrick.
The scientist kept journals. So?
- You figure prominently in them.
- Really?
Devolio wasn’t just a physicist. He was also Catholic priest...
He was deeply conflicted about implication of his work
and need of spiritual guidances...
Like Galileo.
About a month ago, he requested audience with the Pope and you know that.
Because you granted the audience. You were also present during it.
The God 'Particle'. It was to claim an act of creation. Blasphemy.
The arrogance.
The Holy Father
didn’t see it like that.
He urged him to go public...
His Holiness thought that discovery could actually scientifically prove
the existence of a divine power.
And begin to bridge the gap between science and religion...
His work was not religious... It was sacrilegious.
But you, you saw the Pope's position as softening of Church law.
As an old man’s weakness. Your Father's weakness!
- You murdered the Vicar of Christ!
- He raised me to protect this Church.
Even from within.
Then you countered up an old enemy from the past. The Illuminati.
You found the ancient brands in the Papal vaults and put them to use.
To spread fear!
Cardinals are men of belief.
Right now they believe evil is uniting them.
The entire catholic world would be united by this attack.
There is no attack!
You're trying to convince the Cardinals they're in a war.
So they'll choose a warrior to lead them.
We are at war. We are weak when we should be strong.
If science is allowed to claim power of creation...
What is left for God?
- It didn't work Patrick.
- It isn't finished.
Oh, yes it's finished.
It's finished.
I have shown the journals to Father Simeon.
The moment doors to Conclave open he will tell Cardinals what you've done.
I was planning doing this alone.
Put it down.
Perhaps it’s better that you're here.
Put it away.
Help. He's the one. He's got a gun.
Illuminati!
You Bastard!
Padre!
- And get the helicopters for older Cardinals. Right.
I've been summoned by colleague of Cardinals.
Gently. But within our walls.
Father into Thy hands l commit my spirit.
Church sources now confirmed that Camerlengo Father Patrick McKenna...
has died over internal injuries sustained in his heroic fall.
The Catholic Church thanks Camerlengo for his selfless act and demands his immediate canonization.
The Vatican has also confirmed the deaths of three Cardinals and the fire in the Santa Maria della Vittoria.
As we wait appearance of the new Holy Father Cardinal Baggia of Italy...
one of the 4 original Preferiti
who despite terrorist attempts and disruption seems to have been the selected.
In one of the swiftest and smoothest Conclaves in modern Church history.
Professor Langdon. Please.
A token thing from His Holiness...
and from his new Camerlengo.
We are grateful you saved his life.
It’s our understanding that you require this text to complete your scholary work.
We ask only that in your last grand testament...
you ensure
that it finds it's way home.
Of course.
And when you write about us... and you will write about us.
May I ask one thing? Do so gently.
I'll try.
Religion is flawed...
but only because men is all flawed.
Including this one.
He chose the name Luke?
There’s been many Marks and Johns.
Never a Luke.
He said he was doctor.
It's quite a message. Science and faith. All in one.
The world is in need of both.
You'll counsel him wisely.
I'm an old man. I'll counsel him briefly.
Mr. Langdon.
Thanks be to God for sending someone to protect this Church.
I don’t believe he sent me Father.
Oh, my son.
Of course he did.
www.moviesubtitles.org