July eighth, 1979...
all the fathers of Nobel Prize
winners were rounded up...
By United Nations military
units, all right?
...and actually
forced at gunpoint...
to give semen samples
in little plastic jars...
which are now stored below Rockefeller
Center, underneath the ice skating rink.
I wouldn't want to be there
for the thaw. Ha-ha-ha. Yuck.
I mean, it's disgusting!
You know what they put
in the water, don't you?
Fluoride! Yeah, fluoride.
On the pretext that it
strengthens your teeth!
That's ridiculous! You know
what this stuff does to you?
It actually weakens your will...
takes away the capacity for
free and creative thought...
and makes you a slave to the state.
Ever wonder about all these militia groups,
survivalist-type kooks on the right-wing side?
They say that they're defending
the country from the U.N. troops.
These guys yelling so loud, my theory
is... And this is a conspiracy, pal.
They are the U.N. troops.
They're in place!
The infrastructure's ready.
It's a fait accompli.
They'll just take over.
We'll all be toast.
Oswald. Yeah, that's
what I said, Oswald.
He said, "I'm just a patsy."
That means he didn't do it, right?
Armand Hammer goes to the doctor.
The doctor says, "Hey, Armand..."
you've only got 3 minutes to live."
And he says, "Oh, God,
that's terrible news."
Isn't there anything you can do
for me, doc? Three minutes?"
And the doctor says,
"Well, I can boil you an egg."
I guess not. All right.
Do you ever see those
advertisements, like, "Got Milk?"
Hey, Open up! Open it up!
What's going on in there?
Open it up.
Son of a bitch!
"Eat beef"?
That's like saying, "Smoke cigarettes,"
or "Drive cars." I mean, it's real generic.
This guy looks at me and says, "You
think you're living in a free country?"
"You think it's a democracy?
Of course it's not."
Web sites, newsletters,
self-published manifestos.
They think we're kooks.
George Bush knew what he was saying
when he said, "New World Order."
You remember those
three little words?
He was a 33rd degree Mason, you know,
and as ex-director of the CIA...
he knew that saying that would send
conspiratologists everywhere...
spinning, spinning their wheels.
Then they destroy their
own credibility.
Don't get me wrong, sister, I'm sure
your heart's in the right place...
but, you know, somebody's got to lift
the festering scab that is the Vatican.
A chip for identification so they can
track down an animal anywhere he's at.
You'll insert it under the dog's skin
and it's an identification thing.
I mean, it's only a
small logical step...
until they start putting it in us and
our children. Before we know it...
they'll probably come
with the pretext...
Sure. Hey, is that one of the new hundreds
where they changed picture of Ben Franklin?
Look at him. He looks like...
the love child of Fred
Mertz and Rosie O'Donnell.
Yeah, that's him. Get rid of
them as soon as you can, lady.
Look at it. See the metal strip in it?
That's a tracking device.
If you got any more of those at home,
get rid of them. Exchange them.
They'll follow you. They know where
every one of those hundreds is going...
Black helicopters. You heard
about them? The black helicopters?
They're... They're everywhere.
They're on whisper mode. You can't
hear them until they've already gone.
You know?
No. There's nobody there.
Where did...? Where did they...?
Where'd they go? Oh, there
was nobody in here! Nobody.
What am I talking...?
Why is the meter on?
Taxi!
- Where to, pal?
- Luxembourg Towers, on 7th.
Okay.
The sound of love.
Excuse me?
That, what you just did.
- That's love.
- Heh.
"Love is just a way of saying,
"I want to sleep with you."
Admit it. I saw you kiss her.
You love her. This is the
street where love lives.
Love is bullshit.
Love gives you wings.
It makes you fly.
I don't even call it love.
I call it "Geronimo."
- Geronimo?
- Yeah.
Geronimo. See, when
you're in love, you'll...
jump right from the top of the
Empire State and you won't care.
Screaming "Geronimo" the whole
way down. It's great.
Yeah, but then you'll die. You'll squash
yourself. So, what's the point?
Hey, aren't you listening? I'm
telling you, love gives you wings.
She must be some girl.
I love her so bad, I just...
Well, she wrecks me.
I'd die for her.
She feel the same about you?
I don't know.
Uh, I never told her.
Why the hell not?
Uh...
I have some problems.
- You dumb creep!
- Oh, my God!
Stop the cab!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Shut up! Wacko!
- I'm sorry.
Forget the fare.
Love Street.
Yeah, sure, it's possible Lee
Harvey Oswald didn't kill Kennedy.
And frankly,
it's possible Jack Ruby...
didn't kill Oswald. Look at those films,
you see this other guy hanging around.
Are you saying that
Oswald is still alive?
Well, no. Somebody who looked
like Lee Harvey Oswald.
She's singing.
Can't take my eyes off of you
Bingo.
I love you, baby
And if it's quite all right
I need you, baby
Through all the lonely night
I love you, baby
Trust in my when I say
Oh, pretty baby
Don't bring me down, I pray
Pretty baby
Now that I've found you, stay
And let me love you,
baby, let me love you
You're just too good to be true
Can't take my eyes off of you
You'd be like heaven to touch
I wanna hold you so much
Why do you do that?
Why do you push yourself?
And I thank God I'm alive
You're just too good to be true
Can't take my eyes off of you
Whoa!
- Yo, brother!
- What are you doing?
Go ahead, play on.
Hey, what's up?
Ha-ha-ha! Look at him.
Come on, keep up! Keep UP!
- Can you swim, man?
- Ha-ha-ha!
The water main broke all the way
up on 40th Street and 7th Avenue.
- Yeah?
- They say the subway's a damn river.
Strange.
What's up, Jerry?
What are you thinking?
Water mains don't usually
break unless it's wintertime.
The pipes burst open
because it's cold.
And it's only the first of October.
- Reminds me of life in the delta.
- Yeah, Mississippi, all right.
- Mekong, my friend. Mekong.
- Oh.
Hey, Flip, did I ever tell you
that the whole Vietnam War...
was fought over a bet...
that Howard Hughes lost
to Aristotle Onassis?
I heard that. The two of them
used my legs for a wishbone.
Nearly snapped my butt in half.
- Yeah, they owe you.
- No, you owe me!
- Ah. Uh, I'll get you tomorrow.
- All right.
- Peace.
- You too! Take it easy, Flip.
Ho! Ho! All right, all right. Yeah!
Seventy-three, 74...
seventy-five, 76, 77, 78...
seventy-nine, 80, 81.
Okay, right.
Not bad, 1:31.
Good, good. I can do that
a couple more times.
Maybe four times if I have to.
Somebody's growing a garden on
the roof. Ripe for the picking.
Yeah, that's it. Health food.
That's disgusting! What is that?
You really don't need it.
I didn't leave this open.
Somebody's been up here. Oh, I'm
not the only one with a key.
Right where I left you.
Yuck. Return to sender.
Disgusting.
- Jerry, keys.
- What? What?
How come this is safe for me,
but not for the keys?
- Smart girl.
- How's that, Jer?
Justice. She's wearing a blindfold.
- Jerry.
- What?
- You have an appointment?
- Sure, naturally.
- Okay, can you show us a slip?
- I'm not wearing one. Ha-ha-ha!
- Good morning, Claudia.
- Good morning, sir. This is what you wanted.
- And, uh, your coffee's on your desk.
- Okay, thank you.
People, give me this room.
Not you, Miss Sutton. You stay.
This is a request from
you for 18 wiretaps...
on the Ezekiel Walters case, a case
that we are no longer investigating.
I've been doing it
in my spare time.
This is the Justice Department,
not Alice Sutton, P.I.
Walters is sewing a life
sentence on the bank bombing.
Until we get new evidence,
this case is closed.
Do you know what it's like, Mr. Wilson,
to think you know what happened...
but to never be sure?
I've been here 20 years, Alice.
I know what it's like.
Until you've investigated your own
father's murder, you have no idea.
Alice Sutton knows me.
- It will not be a surprise.
- You're making it hard.
Ms. Sutton's psychotic
is here again.
Claudia, I want him out
of here right now.
I have a right!
I am an American citizen!
- And I demand to see Alice Sutton!
- Please, you have to...
Shit.
Man, this guy is a restraining
order waiting to happen.
I... Can I see Alice Sutton?
No, he can't. He has to
have an appointment.
I have a right to be here.
She'll tell you that.
- Get him out of here.
- Thank you.
What? She can't... I haven't
done anything wrong!
Officers! Officers,
I'll take him from here.
I'm Alice Sutton. Sorry.
Hi, Alice.
You need to start
making appointments.
Uh, can I make one now? In a couple
minutes? I can wait if you're busy.
Come around.
- I don't see the connection.
- You don't?
Oh, come on. Six major earthquakes in three
and a half years and the space shuttle...
up in orbit for every one. Don't
you think that's strange?
Testing some top-secret
seismic weapon?
No! No. Not testing. Using.
Nukes are passe. We're...
We're talking weapon of the future.
I don't see what it has
to do with the president.
The president's in Europe...
Hi. Europe at the moment.
And, uh, tomorrow he'll be, uh...
in Turkey, right here
along this fault line.
And they sent up a space
shuttle yesterday.
- Motive?
How about $50 billion?
How's that for a motive?
Oh. Oh, here, let me get that.
The president's cutting funding to NASA,
the milk cow of the aerospace industry.
So you're telling me that NASA's going to
kill the president with an earthquake?
- Do you still ride?
- Not for years.
Why do you keep the picture of you?
Kind of wish you hadn't quit?
- Jerry. The earthquake.
- What? Oh.
Not exactly the kind of thing...
a Secret Service agent can just
throw himself on top of, is it?
- Mr. Wilson needs you in his office.
- Thank you.
Does she always just
burst in like that?
Yes, Jerry, that's her job.
Now I have to go.
My boss is looking to yell at me.
Do you want me to talk to him,
smooth things out for you?
No, I want you to go home or
wherever it is that you go.
And I want you to make an appointment.
You can't just keep bursting in.
No, no. It's just what
they'd be expecting.
- If I make an appointment, they...
- Jerry.
I have a serious job here.
I have a boss I must answer to.
Do you understand that?
I'm sorry. You're right.
- Use your common sense.
- Okay.
Okay, deal. So are
you gonna warn him?
Who?
The president.
I'm not gonna promise you anything.
You think I'm crazy.
She thinks I'm crazy.
No. No, Jerry, I think
you're different.
Well, you know, to be
normal in the real world...
and to, you know, drink
Coca-Cola and eat...
- Jerry.
- Sorry. Eat Kentucky Fried Chicken...
you got to be in a
conspiracy against yourself.
Do you wanna go out sometime?
No.
Okay. Okay. Ahem.
So, what's...? What's
your horse's name?
Johnny Dancer.
You've been in my office a dozen
times, you never asked that before.
Um, I was waiting till
I got to know you better.
- Ahem, uh...
- Ahem.
I'd say eight, actually...
times.
Times I've been here. Eight.
Hey! Hey, pal!
Don't these water mains
usually go in the wintertime?
Hey, pal, all I know is
it's beaucoup overtime.
Yeah.
Feds.
No, not Feds.
These guys got a purpose.
Car has government plates.
Government plates.
There's something
fishy going on here.
Yeah. Yeah. Bet my balls.
Oh, here they come. Camera!
Sir, he's in the building now.
Spooks. I knew it.
Yes, sir.
Surprise must count for something.
You guys are good.
You fellas been
watching me a while?
I've been told I have eyes
in the back of my head...
but I didn't even see you guys
coming, you know? I just...
You must be spooks, huh? Spooks?
CIA spooks, right?
Say something, will you?
I was right.
What was...?
What was I right about?
I wasn't right about... No, I wasn't right.
I was wrong. I was wrong! I was...
You guys are from NASA! That's right!
You're from NASA! No! Come on!
No, not the eyes!
God! Unh!
What?
We've been looking for
you a long time, Jerry.
Do I know you?
Very well.
Jerry...
have you ever...
been in a place from
which hope was gone?
Where all that's left...
is patience?
Now, Jerry...
to whom have you been talking?
I... I... I talk to lots of people.
I drive a cab, you know?
- I meet people all day.
- Who else knows what we know?
What?
What we know, Jerry.
Tell me what! What do we know?
If I know what we know, then
I could tell you what we know...
and if someone else knows, okay?
I mean, it's just...
You got to be more specific.
What...? What is that?
Gravy for the brain.
No! Not gravy!
Please! Please! Please!
Not gravy. No, not gravy!
No! God, no.
Don't do this to me, please!
Now, Jerry...
to whom have you been talking?
No, I've had gravy!
I've had gravy.
- I know you!
- Yes. Now you...
- You know now, Jerry. Now you know.
- Unh!
- I don't know! Help me!
- Who else knows, Jerry?
Who else knows, Jerry?
- Who knows?
- Help me!
What do you know? Who
have you been talking to?
Help! Help!
I know I must share some
of the blame for this.
I wish it didn't
have to be this way.
Jerry, to whom have
you been talking?
Who else knows? Who else knows?
Jerry!
I believe.
I believe! I believe!
Agh!
- Who else knows?
- I don't know.
Who else knows, Jerry?
- Names, Jerry, names!
- I don't know!
- I don't want to dance!
- Who else knows?
To whom have you been talking?
Aah! Aah! Now he knows!
Now he knows!
He's flying! He's flying!
You wouldn't do this
if you knew! Alice!
I want to see Alice Sutton!
There she is.
There she is. Alice! Alice!
I don't know...
Alice, this is it! This is it!
They tried to...
I don't know what they
tried, but I know...
I don't know what I know,
but I know that it's big.
And they just... Will you let me talk?
Look, get back, all right?
- Calm down!
- Cut it out, will you?
Get back. Please, just
give me that gun.
- And roll it over here.
- All right, all right!
- Will you get back? Will you get back? Alice.
- All right.
- I need to talk to you.
- You want to talk to me? Here I am.
- I was... In a wheelchair... No, I was...
- Take it easy. Okay.
- Will you get back!
- Okay.
Alice, I have to tell
you something. I...
Why don't you just take it easy?
Take it real easy with that, okay?
Just take it real easy.
Jerry, you have blood
on your shirt.
Oh.
I bit his nose off!
I bit his nose off! I bit...
- You bit somebody's nose off?
- Agh.
Don't get into this thing where you
make me repeat myself. I hate that.
- Okay. I'm sorry.
- Get back...
you dumb complicit sons of bitches!
You're looking for a man with
no nose, not me! Not me.
- I need to tell you there was...
- Jerry, look at me.
Tank. Fishtank. Goldfish, no.
- And I was in the belly of a whale.
- Just calm down.
No! Wheel...! I was crippled and...
Look at me. I want you to
put the gun down, please.
No, there was a goldfish. There
wasn't any gravy and I...
- Jerry. Jerry.
- I...
I don't know what to...
Just put the gun down.
I'm so... I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Okay? Perfect.
- Agh!
- Hey! Take it easy! Take it easy!
- Unh!
- Jesus. My God, Jerry, you're bleeding.
Call an ambulance.
Call an ambulance!
A piece of a wheelchair
poked through me.
- Christ.
- Back away! Back away!
Put it away!
- Oh, Christ!
- Tell me what happened.
I can't.
I can't remember.
I can't remember them.
I can't remember me.
I... I can remember you.
I remember you.
It's on the tip of my tongue.
I'll remember in the
morning. Remem...
I'm just tired.
I just need some sleep.
Open.
Open, please.
She's for you.
No, nurse. No, don't! Don't!
What is it? What is it?
I told them...
- No, what is it?
- Something to help you sleep.
I don't... Agh! I don't want
to sleep, I want to check out.
Why am I handcuffed to this bed?
I'm not a criminal. Please, help!
Alice, you gotta get me out of here.
They gave me some stuff.
- You're under arrest.
- What?
What's...? What's the charge?
- Jerry, you were there. Figure it out.
- Oh, Jesus.
If you remember who stabbed
you with the wheelchair...
- ...or where it happened, it would help.
- Wheelchair, right.
I was in the... Oh, God, I wish I could
explain it so it all made sense.
- It's all right. Just relax.
- Alice. Alice.
You got to switch the charts.
Switch my charts with that guy's
charts. You gotta switch them.
Don't make me repeat myself. Please,
switch my chart or I'll be dead by morning.
- I swear.
- Relax. Go to sleep. I'll see you tomorrow.
- You want to bet?
- You're just being paranoid.
Only paranoid because
they want me dead.
Please, Alice.
Please, save my life.
Switch... Switch them.
Switch the charts.
Could you open this,
please, ma'am? Ma'am?
- What happened?
- Guy came in with a stab wound...
and died of a heart attack.
Go figure.
- You Miss Sutton?
- Yes.
They want me to bring
you downstairs.
Who does?
The FBI, the CIA. You name the
initials, they're down there.
Any special reason?
They said to bring you and
the body to the basement.
And the body's on its
way, so come with me.
Uh...
I just need one minute, please.
Thank you.
For what?
For switching the charts.
I didn't switch the charts.
No, it's okay. The guy, he traded bullets
with an old man in a liquor store.
He had it coming.
You expect me to believe that
someone came in here last night...
and gave that guy something
that stopped his heart?
You switched the
charts, you tell me.
I've got to go downstairs, now.
- The CIA wants to see your body.
- Really?
I won't be here when you
get back. I'll keep in touch.
You're handcuffed
to the bed, Jerry.
I guess I'll have to chew through my arm.
It's better than hospital food.
Thank you.
You saved my life. Thank you.
Heart attacks happen.
I didn't switch the charts.
Yeah, you did.
You switched them.
You switched the charts.
Let's see here. This is
a grueling experience.
Put that out!
Here's a government man now.
Uh, this is Miss Sutton.
Miss Sutton, Agent Lowry, FBI.
Uh, we're waiting for jurisdictional
problems to be cleared.
- This guy Fletcher's something else.
- Tell me about it.
Police want him for assault.
Secret Service for counterfeiting.
We're tracking him on a
string of bank robberies.
No one knows what the
CIA wants him for.
This guy's a CIA shrink,
he's here to ID Fletcher.
- They knew each other somehow.
- Take off the sheet.
- This isn't him.
- Says "Jerry Fletcher" on the chart.
- Alice.
- Uh...
Uh, Jerry's...
- He's...
- He's what?
He's having a heart attack!
- Where's that goddamn cop?
- Agh! Unh!
Get a crash cart in here, stat!
Dr. Hamilton, Code Blue.
- A dog bit it.
- Excuse me?
You were going to ask about my nose.
Poor animal is slated to be destroyed today.
- And you feel bad for it?
- It's my dog.
Oh, no! I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Nurse. Nurse! Aah!
There he goes!
- Open the goddamn gate!
- No, and you watch your language!
- Hey!
- FBI, lady! Open the damn door!
Hi, Alice.
You never saw me.
Shut up! There he goes!
Lady, open the damn door!
- Open the gate! Will you open it?
- Open it!
You! Get hospital security.
- Block all exits.
- Yes sir. Let's go!
Is this guy a psychiatrist
or a field agent?
You want to put your foot
down and get out of there?
Ugh. Come on, buddy.
Look, if you only knew what
really happened to Serpico...
you'd be helping me out right now.
Get out of there!
Come on, now!
Give me a break. I'm wounded.
Hands behind your back.
Sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Agh! Unh.
He said a dog bit his nose.
Oh. Arf.
Please. You got to help me
out of this, Alice, please.
I can't make any promises.
I'm in a tight spot here.
Please, Alice.
You look really pretty today.
Your eyes look kind
of different. Oh, God.
Please, Alice, make
an exception. Alice?
Alice. Alice. Alice. Alice!
Please. Alice,
are you there? Please!
Come back. Please,
don't leave me here.
Alice. Alice. Alice!
Oh, unh.
Thank you.
There we go.
Have you seen him?
- No. Did you see him?
- No way we can shut a place quick enough.
You have a half-naked man chained
to a bed rail. Just block all the exits.
- That's a good idea.
- Um...
Will you keep me company, please?
- David?
- Uh, Carl.
I'm sorry, Carl. Of course. Dr. Fine.
I want your advice about something.
I had a middle-aged guy,
operating on him, gallstones...
- Do I know you?
- Of course. Dr. Fine, Proctology.
So Jerry thinks that NASA is
plotting to kill the president?
You've already asked me that.
And you have no idea
where Jerry lives?
You've asked me that three times. Why
do you keep making me repeat myself?
All right, here's a fresh one.
Over here.
Why you?
Your colleague, Mr. Wilson, tells me
Jerry won't talk to anyone but you.
That seems, um...
oddly possessive behavior to me.
I'm sorry, what was the question?
Why do you insist on
having me repeat myself?
Why...
you?
I think he has a crush on me.
How charming.
He has great taste.
Now, why him?
Why do you, uh, tolerate
his visits to your office?
About six months ago, I was leaving
work and two guys tried to mug me.
Jerry came out of nowhere and
rescued me. That's how I met him.
He probably is crazy, but there's
something about Jerry that...
just...
I don't know.
I guess I don't have the heart
to tell him to get lost.
I didn't know the CIA
had psychiatrists.
We're very specialized.
May I?
Veritas.
Truth.
What is it they say about truth?
The truth will set you free.
Thank you.
"Catcher in the Rye."
That's the book Chapman had on
him when he shot John Lennon.
I was just thinking that.
Remember the guy that
shot Reagan? John Hinckley?
I read they found a copy of
that book in his apartment.
Weird coincidence, huh?
Thanks for your input, officer.
Unh. Gum...
keys...
and a book.
Hmm.
Car.
Maybe apartment.
But, uh...
this in an odd one.
What do you think?
It's got paint on it.
Safety deposit box key.
I'll take that.
And that.
You're welcome.
Spooks.
So, what do you say we, um...
I don't know, compare
notes on this guy?
"Geronimo"?
- No, don't! Don't!
- Let me have the ticket.
No, I'm here, I'm here,
I'm here! Oh, God.
- There's a "no parking" sign there.
- Yeah, I see it. Yeah, yeah.
- Two cops to give a ticket now? Great.
- These days it takes two cops.
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to frighten you.
Tickets have been coming all day.
Didn't know what to do.
- How'd you know this was my car?
- I didn't. It was a lucky guess.
Look, I feel kind of naked.
Could we get out of here?
- Please don't tell me you're naked.
- It's a figure of speech. Can we go?
- Please. Hurry.
- Yeah, okay.
People are looking
everywhere for the...
What took you so long?
I was here all day.
That's how long it takes to turn a hospital
inside-out. There are people after you.
They'll put me in the same place as
Oswald. Another lunatic acting alone.
Oswald killed the president. Is
that what you're planning to do?
No. Did you call him about
the earthquake thing?
- Warn him?
- I'll do that.
- Can you sit up so I can see you?
- No. No. I don't want them to see me.
- Them who?
- Them back there.
Look. Change lanes.
Watch the rear-view mirror.
It's a fun experiment.
- Did you see it? Wraparound headlights?
- Yeah.
Crown Victoria? FBI.
It's a legitimate tail.
As opposed to?
As opposed to people more
serious about their work.
Can you drive this thing, or do
you just like looking good in it?
I suppose you think
I should speed up...
- ...and try to lose them?
- Yes.
It's what a man would do.
I'm not a man.
I noticed. Hey, what...?
What are you doing?
What are you doing? What?
Oh, man.
Agent Lowry.
It wasn't my idea.
Jonas?
It's his show for now.
Look, you want to get some dinner?
Interagency cooperation and all?
When I'm ready to compare
notes, I'll let you know.
It's your call.
Have a good night.
See? Wasn't that a lot easier than squealing
tires and knocking over trash cans?
Nothing's easy.
- You know that guy they arrested in...
- How long have we known each other?
Six months and 11 days. Um...
Six months and 11 days?
All right, I'll give
you one more hour.
Where to?
Why did we have to go
down to go back up?
Shh, shh, shh.
Because...
Because it's, uh... I don't like to
come and go the same way twice.
I just live in there.
I have to get...
Get... Unh.
Okay.
Here.
- You should have this.
- What is it?
It's my union pin. I figured,
the way you drove...
you should be in the union.
I'd be proud to have you
drive me around in a cab.
Come in, please.
Give me those.
I'll put them up. Unh.
Let me shut the door. Sorry
there's not more room in here.
My keys.
I'll just get the light.
The Jerry Garcia file.
I didn't... Oh, yeah. Yes, I did.
You know why The Grateful
Dead are always on tour?
- No.
- Yeah?
You know why? Because they're all
British agents, intelligence agents.
They're spies.
Jerry Garcia himself has a double-0
rating, just like James Bond.
Jerry Garcia's dead.
That's what they want
you to think. Unh.
Is this supposed to protect
you from aliens or something?
No, it's just a beer bottle.
Follow me.
Come into my humble abode.
Here we go.
Welcome.
Would you like something to drink?
Coffee...
if that's okay.
Oh, no, coffee's our friend.
Coffee's our friend. It's fine.
I keep the beans in the fridge. Keeps
them fresher, makes better coffee.
Old Italian guy, Papa
Leoni told me that.
He's dead now. Nice old guy.
The hell?
"I love the delicate shadow..."
of she...
- "wanting me to be."
- Gah, uh...
Yeah, I can't seem to remember this
combination. Want some juice instead?
Sure.
Oh, you know, if my
universe had a hub...
- This would be it?
- Yeah.
Here.
"In the Irons"?
Yeah, I've been reading
up on it lately. Equitation.
- You know.
- Are these yours?
Yes.
But this, I think this is what's
been causing the problem.
This is the third issue this year.
"Conspiracy Theory." I give
you "Conspiracy Theory."
This is my newsletter.
I think it's got them scared.
You know? I must have hit a nerve
with one of those articles in there.
Otherwise... They're pretty pissed
off about something. That's...
"The Space Shuttle's
Seismic Secret"?
"The Oliver Stone-George Bush
Connection"? Oliver Stone?
Oh, oh yeah. Sure. I mean,
he's their spokesman.
Yeah! You think if anyone had the
information that he's got...
and had a national podium to shout
it from, they'd actually let him do it?
No, it's quite clear that he's a
disinformation junkie for him.
The fact that he's still alive
says it all. He should be dead.
- Can you prove any of this?
- Heh.
No. Absolutely not. A good conspiracy
is, um, an unprovable one.
If you can prove it, they screwed
up somewhere along the line.
- And if that's the case...
- They?
They! Yeah.
- They who?
- They?
They? I... I don't know.
That's why they call them "they."
And "them." You know?
Where does Jonas fit in?
He's one of "they." He's one of them.
He's them. I mean, for sure.
- They. Them.
- Them.
Suppose they have a
secret handshake.
- That's it?
- Ha, ha.
No. How would I know?
I'm not one of them.
I'm just horsing around.
- How many subscribers do you have?
- Well, let's see.
Uh, five.
But I think it's probably got
something to do with the economy.
You think one of them
is not who they seem?
You think it might be one of they?
That could be. Oh! Of course!
- You have a list?
- Huh?
- A subscriber's list?
- Oh!
Yes, right over here.
I thought you meant
some other kind of...
Big Holden Caulfield fan?
No.
Not really.
You just like the story?
- Not especially, no.
- Well, Jerry...
you've got a dozen
copies of this book.
I know.
Yeah, I know. I know, I...
There's more of them in here.
And, uh...
Under the bed too.
I don't know why, but
whenever I see one...
I have to buy it.
And if I don't see one...
well, then I have to find one...
to buy...
so that I can feel normal.
I... I don't know why. Ahem.
Did you ever read it?
Um, yeah, you read this in school.
No one ever gave it to
me to read at school.
That's what they start
when you're young.
When you're little, at school, they
Baden-Powell all the boys and...
and they Betty Crocker
all the girls.
Then they air condition you.
And they put you in an Easy Bake
Oven and you can't breathe anymore.
Oh, Jesus.
You must think I'm crazy, huh?
Yeah, right.
Four, twenty-three...
twelve.
That's, uh...
That's the combination of the coffee.
Do you still want some?
Ugh, you idiot.
We're made. Gas them.
Go! Tear gas!
Don't breathe! Don't breathe!
- Delta team, are you secure?
- Delta team, secure.
- Ready?
- Take it down!
Concussion grenade. Clear!
- Get on the bed! Stay down!
- Aah!
Unh! Move it! Come on! Come on.
- What are you doing? Oh, God.
- Get down. There's a ladder.
- Are you coming?
- I'm right behind you.
- Close your eyes.
- Aah! What are you doing?
I'm torching my hub!
What is that?
Uh, that was here when I moved in.
- What are you doing?
- Always be prepared.
Get out now! Go, go, go!
The fire's two flights
up on the left.
Excuse me. Excuse me!
Clear a path.
- Was that who I think it was?
- Yup.
- Has this ever happened before?
- No.
- No, but I've been practicing. Let's go.
- Jerry!
- What?
- Who are you?
I'm just a guy trying
to put out a fire.
Come on, let's go.
See this aluminum-looking
stuff? It's fire wall.
It's amazing. The guy designed this
place so it could be an incinerator...
but it leaves the rest of
the building untouched.
Dr. Jonas. Dr. Jonas!
Something else here you should see.
I want to hear more.
Let's go. Wrap it up. Let's go.
Do you mind?
In one hour, I want to
know what she eats...
where she sleeps, the name of her
kindergarten teacher. Everything.
- See? Home, safe and sound.
- No, it only looks safe.
- You can't stay here.
- They're not after me!
Don't turn the lights on.
Look, I can stay here with you,
I can sleep on your couch.
- Don't turn the lights on.
- No. You're going, okay?
- I don't want to go.
- No. You're going!
I want to ask you something.
Ask me to stay. I could
sleep in the bathtub.
- Jerry, no! Shut up.
- You shouldn't be here alone.
- Get down.
- Jerry, I...
What are you doing now?
You don't want to be seen here.
Always make sure these are shut.
Please, just be still, be quiet.
Listen to me, okay?
I think we can make
some progress...
if you just answer one
question to my satisfaction.
I'll try.
It's about the painting on
the wall in your apartment.
I didn't mean for you to see that.
That's like looking in someone's diary...
- and taking it all out of context, you know.
- Okay. Okay.
That's fair. It's just that...
well, Jerry, it was so big and you obviously
put a lot of time into it and you seem to...
know me so well.
How is that possible?
So, what's the question?
This is you and your dad. He was...
murdered, wasn't he? He was
that judge. I read in the paper.
Did they ever find out, you know...
how, who did it?
You don't mind me asking you?
I mean, it's...
You're changing the subject.
He's why you punish
yourself, isn't it?
Jerry, please, don't start.
You get on the treadmill, and
turn your back to that picture...
like you're running away from him.
You punish yourself. Sometimes
you sing along to the music...
but most of the time,
you punish yourself. Wow.
I don't know where you get the
energy after a full day's work.
- You run like a maniac. I wondered why.
- What are you talking about? Music?
What are you talking about, huh?
Are you watching me?
What do you do? Sit in your car?
Are you waiting in an
alleyway? Every day?
- It's not like...
- What is it? Tell me what it is!
- You don't ride your horse...
- Do not change the subject!
Get out of my house. Now!
I will give you $100 to
get out of my house.
I don't need any money.
I got plenty for a rainy day.
Oh, yeah? Well guess what?
- It's pouring out.
- All right, you're tired. I, uh...
Just don't be mad at me, okay?
Use your dead bolts, Alice.
Dead bolts. Okay? Just lock up.
I'm gonna empty my bladder.
- How's your bladder?
- I gotta go. How's yours? Hey!
No, no. No, don't do that.
Okay.
There's a lot of folks
looking for you.
I guess that makes you
the smart one, huh?
Put your hands on the wheel.
Both your hands on
the wheel. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Don't mention it.
- Where's my partner?
- Who? Oh!
I... He's okay.
But here you are with a gun to your
head asking how your partner is.
You might be okay. Um...
He'll have a headache
for a couple of days.
Are your intentions here honorable?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Uh, they...? Uh, with Alice.
I mean, what...?
Think of me as her guardian angel.
That's ironic because we're
here to protect her from you.
No, you're here because you thought
I'd show up, so that's why you're here.
- Seemed like a possibility.
- Well...
What about your intentions?
Are they, uh...
- ...honorable?
- Uh.
Yeah.
I'm not a violent man.
No, I'm not by nature.
I'm not a violent man, Mr. Lowry.
But if you hurt Alice in any way...
or anything like that,
I'll kill you.
Does that seem honorable enough?
Well, um, maybe.
Are you pretending?
Yes, yes...
Sorry.
It's got to be here.
Thank God.
- May I help you, sir?
- Yeah.
Okay. Uh...
- I need to scan it.
- All right, put it through.
No, this side.
Okay, just... I'll do it.
I'll do it. Just...
Bingo! "Catcher in the Rye."
Location is 33 East 17th
Street, Barnes and Noble.
Where's...?
- I'm just putting it in a bag, sir.
- I don't want a bag.
- I got the exact change for you.
- Okay.
Make life easy for you.
- Your receipt.
- Yeah. Thank you.
You're welcome.
"Catcher in the Rye."
- Yeah.
- It's a classic.
- Have you read it?
- You know, I've...
- ...never read it.
- Never?
No, I haven't. I never read it.
We're going silent, guys.
Confirm silent.
Exploit the art
And watch hip-hop fall apart
But I'm a do my part to stay true but please
don't try to tell me what I can not see
Could I have a pretzel?
And expect all props
I'm gettin' dropped like hot rocks
So stop what they doin'
'Cause I'm about to ruin
I got him.
There he is.
Just one.
Hurry up.
Sorry.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Bomb! There's a bomb under my seat!
Be calm! Remain calm and move
out in an orderly fashion!
There he is!
I'm not sorry.
Leave me alone, will you?
I'm turning into a Jerry.
I've been given a cease and desist on
all matters related to Jerry Fletcher.
We are not to discuss him with the
press, N.Y.P.D., or anyone else.
Building security is gonna
arrest him on sight...
and we're to report any attempt
he makes to contact you.
I don't like it. Something's
not right here.
Dr. Jonas thought you might
be inclined not to cooperate.
Why is that?
Well, we don't know
who Dr. Jonas is.
We don't know who we're
cooperating with.
I had a lot of credentials
flashed in my face.
And after yesterday,
I know not to ask questions.
We're out. We're shut off.
We're terminated.
Understood?
Understood.
They can't see the
trees for the forest.
Hello?
Hi, may I speak with
Mr. Ketcham, please?
This is Mrs. Ketcham.
Hello, Mrs. Ketcham. Your husband
receives our newsletter.
I wanted to see if he would
like to renew his subscription?
My husband is dead. He was killed
last night in a car accident.
- Miss Sutton here?
- Yes.
Sign here, please.
- Hey, here, wait.
- Thank you.
These just came for you.
- Want a vase?
- Yes, please.
"Go out the building to the right.
Take the first bus."
Claudia, tell Jill I'm expecting
a call from Milwaukee.
Transfer the calls to my mobile.
- Will do.
- Thank you.
Got her.
Subject is on the move.
Okay, she's on the bus. Go!
Subject on bus 1648.
Will follow.
What the hell?
Keep going!
Ha-ha-ha! Like a Roadrunner
cartoon. See that?
- No, see what?
- You didn't see it?
- Nobody ever sees what I see.
- Jerry, Jerry, Jerry.
- What?
- Where did you get your five subscribers?
I put an ad on the
computer bulletin board.
Logged in at the library
so they couldn't trace it.
They're dead.
Four out of five of them.
I've checked. All in the last 24 hours.
One accident, two heart attacks, a stroke.
This one I can't reach.
Henry Finch.
They're dead. Dead.
I did that.
Heart attacks and strokes,
that's CIA. Henry Finch!
Oh, my God!
I should've realized.
They monitor absolutely everything.
Elaborate on "they." They?
They?
There's lots of groups, actually.
Lots of initials.
CIA. FBI. IMF, you name it.
They. But they're part of the
same two opposing factions.
- Which are?
- Which are, one...
One. Some of them are really,
really wealthy families.
Their thing is to maintain stability.
That's what they call it.
The other is Eisenhower's
industrial-military complex.
And they want
instability, so they say.
So you're saying that group one
is warring with group two?
Yes, at some levels. But at
others, it's the same group.
It's scary! It's hand and glove.
Cold wars, hot wars.
- They sit back and watch the whole damn show.
- Jerry. Take a breath.
The latest casualty in the whole fiasco
is one of the richest men in America:
Ernest Harriman.
He was murdered.
- Murdered?
- Here in Manhattan.
No, Jerry, I read in the
paper, he was, um...
He drowned in a swimming pool. It
was an accident, it was in Newport.
No. Nobody dies in Newport. They couldn't
even kill Sunny Von Bulow in Newport.
He drowned, but not in Newport.
Where, then?
Right here, the 7th
Street subway station.
A billionaire waiting on the subway?
Why didn't they drown him in his limo?
No, don't you read the papers?
I mean, don't you watch television? Huh?
Last week, this place
was under water.
- A water main broke.
- I know.
But you know what's right above
this area? The Harriman Building.
The whole substructure was flooded.
I'm telling you, he didn't drown in a pool.
Call the, uh, coroner in Rhode
Island or wherever it was...
and ask if he had chlorinated
water in his lungs.
- Okay, I will.
- You will?
Yeah, if you want, I will.
I don't know what to say.
I love you.
- What?
- I...
I...
It's like I resolved to...
call you up a thousand times a day.
And, um, ask you if
you'll marry me...
in some old-fashioned way.
Everything you do is magic.
Those are song lyrics, Jerry.
Yeah, I know. I know that.
Uh, I know that. Look.
I'm nervous. I reached out and grabbed
hold of the first thing I could think.
I know they're song lyrics.
- But I know how I feel.
- Jerry.
I think you're confused.
It's been a long day.
I'm not confused. I'm not. You wanted
to know, that picture on the wall.
- How that was possible.
- I don't think we should...
Yes, we should. It's Geronimo.
That's love. And love
gives you insight.
Love lets you see things that
you wouldn't normally...
I just know that I've loved you...
- ...since the first time I saw you.
- Jerry. No, no.
You don't love me.
- Sure I do.
- No.
- I don't?
Uh...
I thought that, uh...
Well, I thought...
I just thought that maybe...
Jerry.
Jerry!
Jerry! Jerry.
I'm sorry. Jerry, I'm sorry.
- Hello?
- Alice, we have a call...
- ...from the Milwaukee post office.
- Yeah?
The mail for Henry Finch is being
forwarded here to Manhattan.
Where?
Foley Square. The
Criminal Courts Building.
I'd like to see Mr. Finch, please.
- Who?
- Henry Finch.
Is he expecting you?
My name is Sutton with
the Justice Department.
I'd like to see
Mr. Finch immediately.
- He'll be right with you.
- Thank you.
What the hell is going on here?
I'm very impressed, Alice.
How's Jerry this morning?
The more important
question is, who are you?
Those are much bigger
questions than you think.
Please sit down.
For...
reasons that will soon be...
regrettably clear, I'm going
to tell you a secret.
Then you can judge
what and who I am.
Years ago...
I worked for the Central
Intelligence Agency...
on the MK ULTRA program.
Are you familiar with it?
It was mind control.
"Manchurian Candidate"
kind of stuff.
That's a vulgar generalization.
But yes, uh, you take
an ordinary man...
and turn him into an assassin.
That was our goal.
Now, MK ULTRA was
terminated in 1973.
But...
not the...
research.
That, I continued.
Shall I go on?
"The truth will set you free."
it involved hallucinogenic
research...
electroshock to induce
vegetative states...
terminal experiments in
sensory deprivation.
Terminal?
As in, "resulting in death."
Alice, I'm, uh...
I'm now trying to pay my penance.
These things that you're talking
about, you did them to Jerry?
MK ULTRA was science,
sanctioned by the government.
It all ended...
the moment John Hinckley
shot Ronald Reagan.
No, that wasn't us.
But the technology had been stolen.
Pandora's box opened.
My subjects were taken from me,
used in the private sector.
Jerry was one of them.
One of your subjects.
It is imperative that I discover
who stole the technology.
Alice, I will do
what is necessary...
to stimulate Jerry into
telling me what he knows.
Jerry is very dangerous.
Jerry has killed.
To find who programmed Jerry...
I have to find Jerry, but I
can't do that without you.
Do you recognize this?
Where did you get that?
You do recognize it, then?
Of course I do.
It belonged to my father.
Where did you get it?
Alice, what do you know
about your father's death?
He denied a man in prison
appeal for a new trial.
Ezekiel Walters.
Walters had nothing to do
with your father's murder.
When they found him,
he was holding his wallet.
The only thing missing
was this photo.
Where did you find it?
Jerry's safe deposit box.
Alice, when do you think Jerry
first took notice of you?
What is it the two of
you have in common?
I was mugged and he saved me.
He may have saved you, Alice,
but that was no coincidence.
Come on, you're a lawyer.
Think like one.
Your father was assassinated.
And the sick son of a bitch has
been obsessed with you ever since.
I am so sorry, Alice.
I truly am.
- Miss Sutton?
- Uh...
Hold on one second.
- Alice, you order pizza?
- No.
- Oh.
- Hold it.
"Go to the northeast corner..."
of Greenwich and Battery Place.
"Bring the pizza. I have something
important to tell you."
Call Bill in Security and tell
him Fletcher's in the area.
I will, sir.
"I have something
important to tell you."
Alice.
I have tried everything
I know to get Jerry to talk.
Would you try?
I promise you,
you'll be perfectly safe.
No way. No way. Alice...
you don't have to do this.
- I will.
- Good girl.
I want a bug in this
box, audio and track.
Right away.
Hey, that still hot?
Hop in. Doesn't pay to
stand around too long.
This is 42-K. We're on him.
Thanks.
I'm starving.
Unh.
This is good.
Have some.
- Do you have him on that?
- We still got him.
Are you okay, Alice?
No, you're not. I shouldn't have
said all that stuff I said before.
I won't do that anymore. Creeped
you out. I can't help the way I feel.
Jerry, what did you want
to talk to me about?
Ah.
I can feel what I... I mean,
I can think? No, I can feel...
what I want to say, but I can't
think it. No. I can't get it out.
I got blank spots...
I've heard enough. Stop the car.
- I want her out of there.
- No! Keep driving.
It's kind of like, um, you know,
if you sing along with the music.
If there's no music, then you
know the words with the music.
- But if there's none, you're helpless.
- I don't understand.
Is something wrong?
No. Don't worry about it.
I want to take you where
the music's playing.
The music is playing in Queens?
What? Oh. Uh, no, not today.
- Did she say Queens?
- Yes.
This is air unit one.
We've lost visual.
He's on the lower level. We'll
pick him up on the other side.
- Where is he?
- Straight ahead.
About 300 yards.
- What?
- Nothing.
You see something?
- Hang on.
- Aah!
What are you doing?
Let's go.
- The pizza!
- Whoa, sorry. Sorry!
- The pizza.
- We don't need it.
I'll get you another pizza.
It wasn't that good.
- What's this?
- He stopped.
I have to go back
and get the pizza.
- Aah!
- It'll all make sense in a minute.
Stop, stop, stop!
Okay, this is us. Hop in.
All mobile units watch him.
What do you see?
Slide across. I'll crank her up.
Yeah. Yeah, coming.
Air unit one, what do you see?
We see no traffic.
Repeat, no traffic.
We'll go down and take a look.
They've exited the vehicle.
- The pizza box is still in the car.
- Go.
Where are we going?
Connecticut.
We shut the bridge down. All
off-ramps. Both levels. Got it?
Roger that. I'll take the west end.
Where are we going?
- Shh. Can you hear it?
- What?
The music, I can almost hear it.
I almost hear it.
We will.
Mr. Wilson's office.
Hello? Hello?
David Berkowitz.
Ted Bundy. Richard Speck.
What about them?
Serial killers.
Serial killers only have two names.
You ever notice that?
But lone gunman assassins...
they always have three names.
John Wilkes Booth.
Lee Harvey Oswald.
Mark David Chapman.
John Hinckley, he shot Reagan.
He only has two names.
Yeah, but he only just shot
Reagan. Reagan didn't die.
If Reagan had died,
I'm pretty sure...
we probably would all know what
John Hinckley's middle name was.
Mr. Wilson's office. Hello?
It's her. The line's open.
Get a trace on it.
- Hot one, line three trace.
- We got a cell trace.
This is my father's place.
This is where the music's playing.
I just thought of another one.
James Earl Ray. The guy
that got Luther King.
Then there's Sirhan Sirhan.
I haven't figured that out.
Maybe it's Sirhan Sirhan Sirhan.
Here we got the stables and
the main house is over there.
I guess I should
just follow my nose.
What's your middle name, Jerry?
What? What do you mean?
- Did you kill my father?
- No.
Maybe.
- Maybe?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- No...
Ugh.
You were at the horse
show that day. And, uh...
You never rode again after that.
I think maybe you blame yourself.
Oh, God, it's on the tip
of my brain. I just...
He died right here.
Did he see you coming, Jerry?
Huh? Did he beg for his life?
You put a gun to his head and you
shot him, didn't you? Didn't you?
He died in the dirt, like an animal!
Jerry, you killed my father!
Answer me! I have to know!
Tell me, please. Please, tell me.
Please tell me!
Please tell me. Please.
I...
went to the court to
kill your father.
I'm sorry.
That what I was programmed to
do that. The Ezekiel Walters hearing.
I had a gun, and...
I couldn't shoot him. I couldn't
do it because I saw you.
That was the first
time I ever saw you.
That's the first time we met.
And, oh, boy, I knew that
if I was to screw up...
that Jonas, he was gonna send somebody
else to do the job I didn't do.
So I decided to watch
him and make him safe.
- Make it safe.
- Safe?
- He started carrying a gun.
- Oh, I know.
I know. He stuck it in my face the first
time I tried to introduce myself.
And I had to... Had to...
Uh...
I didn't kill him.
I didn't kill him. We
became friends. Yes.
Oh.
He made really good coffee.
And he tried to help me
remember all of this stuff.
One of Jonas' guys...
No. One of... Unh.
When I got here,
he was already dying.
When I... He was dying
when I got here.
What does Jonas have to
do with Ezekiel Walters?
Ezekiel Carl Walters.
Ezekiel Carl Walters. Ezekiel
Walters is one of Jonas' fall guys!
He's the three name thing!
Ezekiel Carl Walters! You see? He...
Oh, he was innocent,
innocent of everything.
Your father was gonna reopen the case.
He was gonna reopen the case because...
he didn't accept the
official story.
- Why?
- Because...
Because he believed me.
He believed me.
And...
He believed that I couldn't do
what I was meant to do to him...
and he was gonna blow
it all wide-open...
before Jonas sent someone
else. He was gonna...
Oh.
When he was dying...
he was still really
worried about you.
He took your picture
out of his wallet.
He called you his baby.
I told him I'd keep you safe.
And I kept your picture, and I've
been watching you ever since.
I didn't... I didn't kill him.
But I was late and...
I'm sorry.
I believe you.
He made great coffee.
Heh, yeah.
- What the?
- They traced my phone. Sorry. Oh, God!
- No! Before I go, I have to ask you one thing.
- What?
- Did you switch the charts?
- Now is not the time.
Now is all I got! Did you
switch them? Did you?
- Yes.
- I knew it. I knew it!
Freeze!
- Freeze!
- Get away from her!
- Get off me!
- Leave her alone!
Get off me!
Let go of me! Jerry!
Get off her!
Jerry!
You really embarrassed me, Jerry.
You made certain people take
notice of me who shouldn't have.
Alice, are you all right?
Wilson!
Alice.
You shouldn't watch, Jerry.
It's a moment without hope.
You've never seen her run.
Agh!
This will put my
words in your mouth.
Once this does its job, you'll swear
that you killed her yourself.
She's dead, you know.
Well, then you can't
hurt me anymore.
I'll be the judge of that.
Come on in. I'll get the lights.
Holy shit.
- We need to talk.
- Yeah.
When I was in here last night,
there were, like, desks.
That's messed up. I'm going to call
management right now. This is not good.
You guys, I'll meet you
downstairs. Go ahead.
Come on.
Who's the Deputy
Director of the FBI?
You think we have time
for 20 Questions?
Hold it right there. Put
your hands in the air.
What gave me away?
Nothing. I just
wanted to make sure.
Who are you guys?
If the intelligence
world was a family...
think of us as the uncle
no one ever talks about.
We watched Jerry.
Jerry's the bait for Jonas.
Jonas has shown himself.
Why don't you take him?
Jonas builds assassins.
We need to know who they are, where
they are and who Jonas works for.
Jonas had my father
killed, didn't he?
We think so.
- Do you know where Jerry is?
- No.
I wish I did. Honest.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna find him...
because he'd find me.
- Let's work together on this.
- I don't think that's a good idea.
Let me give you a number where
you can call if you need me.
Hey! Hands in the air.
I'm sorry.
Everybody's sorry.
Geronimo.
Son of a bitch.
The president left the
area moments earlier...
and is currently safe in Germany.
The quake in southern Turkey
measured 7.3 on the Richter scale.
Thousands are feared missing or
dead. More on this story as it...
Can I help you?
Yes. I'm with the
Justice Department.
I need to see any male patients who have
been brought in in the last 12 hours.
Justice Department? You got some
credentials, a badge or something?
This is the Treasury Department.
But it'll do. Come on, let's go.
You're just too good to be true
That's better.
Yo, Marie! What happened to those
two guys came in this morning?
They were transferred to
Mount Vernon immediately.
Sorry.
Jerry?
Jerry? Hey, Jerry!
Jerry, can you hear me?
Jerry. Jerry?
Can you hear me, Jerry?
You're just too good to be true
Jerry, tell me where
you are. Jerry!
Jerry?
I love you, baby
And if it's quite all right
I need you, baby
Through all the lonely nights
Hi, Alice.
Hi, Jerry.
- Alice, I'm sorry you're dead.
- Jerry.
- Unh.
- Jerry, tell me where you are.
Right here.
Uh...
- Um...
- Where's "here," Jerry?
On the floor. I'm... Uh...
Behind a waffle or a...
The paint is peeling
on the ceiling.
That rhymes.
Peeling on the ceiling.
Nice views, and I can...
I can see the smokestacks
in the light.
Good views.
Where can you see the
smokestacks in this building?
Smokestacks? Um, smokestacks.
That would be the power station.
You can see it from the north wing, upstairs,
but that's been closed for two years.
Take me there, right now. Jerry,
I'm coming to get you. Come on.
Alice? Alice?
You can fit through there?
Around this corner.
Down the hall.
Just honk the horn. I'll come out.
Yeah, this is it.
- You have a key?
- I don't have a key.
- Can you break it open?
- Lady, hundred bucks doesn't cover this.
I'll clean the place up. I'll...
Whoa! No, wait!
- Let's think about this! Wait, come on.
- Come on.
This is as far as I go, lady.
Call the police and this man.
Tell them where I am.
I'll call for backup. Agh.
I'll call for backup.
Call Roto-Rooter, that's the name.
What'd you think this
would get you, Jerry?
Ugh, how would I know?
I'm tied up on the floor.
I don't know, maybe
I wanted some attention.
I was lonely.
Wow.
Ooh, heh.
Are you all right?
Are you all right, huh?
This is, like, the best
dream I ever had.
- Alice.
- Yeah?
Could you untie me?
Oh, my God, yes,
of course. I'm sorry.
- North wing?
- Can I see some ID?
ID him, Flip.
- Through that door, but it's abandoned.
- No matter.
Oh, God! I'm sorry.
Can you walk?
I think so.
- Kiss me.
- What?
For luck.
Kiss me and...
- Jerry, you're crazy.
- No, I'm certifiable, I know...
but kiss me once. Come on.
Kiss me, then we'll go.
Jerry, you continually surprise me.
Go. Go!
Alice.
I always seem to come between
you and the men in your life.
No!
- Somebody help me!
- Unh.
Help me!
- Throw down your weapon!
- Don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
Get an ambulance here, now.
Geronimo.
Is that this place?
No, not anymore.
It's love. And...
love gives you wings.
And helps you fly and
we can fly away.
Yes, I do.
I do so.
I love you.
I do.
I love you too.
Now you tell me.
Jerry.
Jerry. Jerry.
Jerry. Jerry! Jerry. No! Jerry.
Somebody help me, please!
Somebody help me! Jerry.
I'm right here. I'm here with you.
It's gonna be okay.
No, I want to go with him. I want
to stay with him! No! Please.
Stop pulling on me.
Jerry, I'm right here!
- Clear!
- Jerry!
Jerry! Jerry, look at me!
I miss your face.
Hi.
I'm back...
if you'll have me, Johnny. Hmm?
Is that a "yes"?
Geronimo.
As long as they think
you're dead, she's safe.
I kept my end of the bargain.
What about yours?
Yeah, I'll tell you
all I can remember.
I'll give you all the gravy on
Jonas and his operation and...
You're gonna have to
help me, though, Lowry.
It's coming back, but slow.
You got it.
By the way, my real name's Hatcher.
Pleased to meet you.
- Ow. Go easy on me.
- Oh, sorry about that.
I guess nothing was what
it seemed to be, huh?
Guess not.
Except her.
Son of a bitch.
- Brought the morning paper for you.
- Thanks, Flip.
- It is Flip, isn't it?
- Yes, it's Flip.
Don't even think about it.
At least not for now.
And if it's quite all right
I need you, baby
To warm the lonely nights
Baby, trust in me when I say
Oh, pretty baby
If it's quite all right
We're all right.
Baby
We got a future.
Hold you tight
And let me love you, baby
Let me love you