- Ray, you up?
- Yeah.
Jacks are gonna jump on you, tomorrow.
Two bell.
I figured, I owe you.
Yo..Did you hear what I said?
I heard.
Thanks.
Prison guard: Everybody, down.
Now!
On the ground!
You, inmate. On the ground.
Now!
- Get down.
- You heard us.
On the fucking ground.
You are up.
To your left.
On the line.
Step to the right.
Hands?
Enjoy.
Let's go.
Lunch time, inmate.
Eat your vegetables.
Ready to go.
Hey, Roag?
- Yeah?
- You got the time?
What the fuck do you care?
You got a date?
No.
Maybe, you've got a sister or cousin.
You got your head smashed?
No, I'm groovy.
It's 5:04.
Wise ass!
Hey, fruit cake? Let's go.
Eight..nine..
Ten.
290.
291.
292.
293.
294.
295..296...297298.
299..
300.
You okay?
I got everybody.
- What the fuck is going on?
- We got fire at B2.
- All prisoners, back to their cell.
- Copy that.
What the fuck?
We got a runner. I repeat..
Prisoner is Ray.
Nice ride.
Hushe's idea.
That's right.
How's this side, Boss man.
This side's great.
I warden was about you.
You know, If you wasn't out soon.
I would've break in,
that motherfucker pulling your ass out.
The only ex-con I know,
who gets out and wants to go back in.
I didn't say, wants.
I said, I would.
There's a difference.
Don't spend it all on one place.
We have an escape from
Bendwater Penitentiary.
Step out from the booth,
with your hands in the air!
Show time.
Put your hands in the air, now.
Hands in the air.
Put your hands behind your head,
lock your fingers.
Do not move.
A beautiful day.
- What the hell is going on her?
- Calm down, Warden.
I am Lester Clark.
I am C.E.O of the CEE Security.
You may have heard of us?
No?
Al right, well..we are an independent
security company.
Hired by the
federal bureau prison.
To test the integrity of their,
maximum security, facilities.
Nation wide.
This is Ray Breslin,
He is partner..and uh..
Resident Houdini.
Warden.
Now, for the last seven years.
Ray has been inserted into every
maximum incarceration facility.
In the system.
He is there to ensure that
each and every one of them is 100%
escape proof.
And apparently, yours wasn't.
And he got out.
Ta dah!
Okay, fine.
I suppose, you're gonna tell me
how you did it?
You think he wants to know?
Doesn't seem like it.
Ray, you are on.
Warden, let's start from the top.
Any break requires, three things.
Knowing the lay out,
Understanding the routine and
help from outsiders the realm.
If you know the lay out,
the weak side is obvious.
In Bendwaters case...
is the secure housing unit.
With the government expenditure with
17 Million dollars, building the facility.
State of the art.
The only problem is...
It's located next to
unsecure fire crash.
First, I needed to get inside,
so, I made some enemies.
Once inside, it was obvious
you are short staff.
Federal guidelines recommend
two guards present when
transferring high risk inmates.
You only use, one.
Knowing the guard's routine
was the next step.
30 seconds into my rec. Time
my C.O took a smoke break.
7 minutes of everyday
there were no eyes on me.
Two, three..
After I knew the routine.
All I had to do, was pick a date.
And arrange for a distraction
at the front gate at exactly 4pm.
But still at this point,
you're locked inside a steel box
to get out,
you had to have a key code.
You very good chocolate milk.
See, the carton container has
a thin layer of wax linen.
Lay it over the keypad to impress
within the key, with four keys to impress.
With the four keys, its just numbers
game to identify the correct sequence.
I just needed to get to the keypad.
After, I had to cover my tracks,
I had one minute to
make to the fire response shift.
Before the team did.
I know the guards were still on the roof,
doing what they do.
Which is wasting time.
Before you know it,
I am right where I wannabe be.
Just in time, to catch my ride.
And your men drove me
right off the grounds.
You have any questions?
Yeah, one.
What kind of man would choose to spend
most of his life in prison?
Don't take it personally, Warden.
Over the years, Ray has broken out
of 14 like this institutions.
Some people has a talent to paint.
Some, uh..to sing.
Me? I sing.
Ray Breslin, He possesses a unique
set of skills. He is able break out..
Of any prison designed by man.
I take it, you have been good?
Yeah. You?
You a good boy inside?
Well, of course. Okay..
How did that thing with that guy go?
- What guy?
- What guy.
When I was gone, you were
angry about that there's some guy.
Some bozo?
Oh, yeah. That bozo ended before dessert.
- That's his loss.
- Yeah, they are all losers.
How many times have I told you that?
You want to get something to eat,
while we get by?
Is there a problem?
You're a horrible cook.
That's nice. Well...
You can complain in the morning.
Ouch!
Good morning, sir.
How can I help you?
Oh, Mr. Breslin.
I'm so sorry. I am Jules.
That's okay.
You're new here?
No, Sir. I've been here 5 months.
- 5 months?
- Yes, sir.
What have you got for me?
Check it out.
That is good.
Very smart.
Did you do this all by yourself?
I'm impressed. Genius..
You are smart but..
Sorry. Not smart enough.
Don't be bitter.
Morning, guys. Abbey?
Nice to meet you.
Your work is the gold standard in field.
What you've accomplished is remarkable.
(mimes)- remarkable.
Thank you,
and..you are here because?
She is 'Agency', Ray. As in..
Central Intelligence Agency.
- You, a spy?
- Worse..I am a lawyer.
Ray, hear her out.
She's legit.
I called into Langley, myself.
Fine, I'll just listen.
Go ahead.
Mr. Breslin..after ending extra ordinary
renditions, the agency is looking
for alternate situations for incarcerating
this sort of people who commit acts
so despicable, they are best..
Well...
how can I put it.. Eliminated?
'Disappeared'.
We are currently testing a prototype
to deal with people,
no government wants on their books.
But first and foremost..
The people financing this, need to
know these facilities are escape proof.
Before, the whole systems go online,
globally.
Which is really saying is that, none of
this is officially sanctioned by anyone.
Close. What I'm saying Ms. Rose..
Is that these facilities
are privately funded and administered.
So, the word 'official'
doesn't really apply.
So, if anything goes wrong, nothing comes
back to bite you people in the ass?
Whoa, whoa..this is not
your concern. Hey! I owe him.
I don't owe you.
My job is to make sure that
the united states is in safe hand.
Al right, can we just cut the crap
and call it like it is?
These institutions are off the grid.
With no trials,
there's no convictions;
This people just disappears
and you want him,
to go in and test it?
Maybe it's time for me to interject
to the conversation that
they have offered,
double your standard fee.
That's five mils..Ray.
In advance.
So, you like this?
Look.. I'm the numbers guy.
You are the artist, Ray.
And from the financial stand point,
I like it. I like this very much.
Beyond the money, Mr. Breslin.
The people send to this place shouldn't
be allowed out into the real world.
Everyone of them is potential
game changer. For the worst.
Al right.
- Guidelines?
- The usual full works.
Alias, cover story..contacts.
Event number.
Well, the only difference is
to fully test the security
of the system; It's essential that
non of you know
the location of the incarceration.
- Will that present a problem?
- Yes. Yes, it would.
When do we start?
You just did.
Your entered new identity..
Would be picked up from this location.
By private contractors
24 hours from now.
I don't like this.
And, you don't like her.
Man, don't flatter yourself.
We are going against every
protocol and guidelines
that you, yourself has insisted on
every single time that you go in.
- And, I don't like her.
- You're right.
She doesn't like anything.
Because she's ambitious and greedy.
You say that like its a bad thing.
Profile?
Okay. Name - Anthony Portos.
Born - Madrid.
Mother died, when you're 13.
Raised by your father, in the U.S.
You're suspected of manufacturing
bombs that has been used
in dozen political bombings across
Europe and South America
- for the last, 10 years.
- Contact on-site?
The Warden's name is Riordan Watch.
- Evacuation Code?
- 310275.
- Al right, let's do it.
- Tagging.
No, I don't need this. Really.
Yeah, you do.
This is not Old school.
You think, I'm gonna let you go in, cold?
This gets old.
- Man, you're fucked up.
- Try it sometime.
Sounds good, boss man.
Any time you wanna retire, you know
I've been taking notes.
I'm ready to step up.
Where am I gonna find another techno thug
who's as good as you are here?
- A freak of nature.
- Yeah, very rare.
There you are baby,
transponder is good.
It's like having me around
in your shoulder.
What else?
Hey, don't forget to write us, alright?
Shit.
Time to sleep.
Prisoner, 17458.
Portos..welcome.
To the international detainment, intake.
I am Warden Hobbes.
Where is Warden Marsh?
There is no Warden Marsh.
What am I, disoriented..excited?
I guess, that must be it.
And I didn't see a man killed on
a transport helicopter
thrown out of it, right?
Mr. Portos, your intake is finished.
Wait?
My evacuation code is 310275.
- Evacuation code?
- Yes, evacuation code.
And you giving me a number and..
Walk out of here.
Free as a bird?
No,
I don't think so.
You come in here, now
you belong to me.
Your intake is finished.
Wait..Wait. Come here, back.
- Anything?
- I'm getting cold response, same as yesterday.
You ran a full diagnostic on the system?
- Twice.
- Run it again.
P.A -All prisoners in A Block
proceed to dock 5.
All prisoners in A Block
Portos?
Hey, ???
Go make some friends,
You gonna need them.
Damn!...Stay down!!
Stay Down !!
New fish..we own you.
Back Off!
Last time...?
Back away.
Portos?
Rothmayar.. Emil Rothmayar.
I'm really not in hand shaking mood,
right now.
Okay...
Your name..
The fourth musketeer.
It's a good name.
Why are you in here?
Why do you care?
I used to run security for
a guy..
By the name of Mannheim.
Have you heard of the name?
Mannheim..let me see?
No.
- He is a genius.
- Really?
He has this habit of taking money from
the rich and giving it to the poor.
- You've heard that story before..
- I've heard the story, yeah.
Now, they're trying to find him.
But, I'm making it hard for them.
Okay.
So, fuck 'em.
Right, fuck 'em.
Portos,
- don't get killed.
- If you say so.
Last time they killed a guy in here..
They let his body
rot for three days.
Oh..and cancel the prison dance.
Wouldn't want to fuck up the prom.
Morning, sir.
That's another beautiful piece, sir.
You lied to me.
I lied to you?
- I'm not sure...
- No..no.
You say nothing.
What am I suppose to tell the client
about the man you killed.
That he just jumped?
Like you said?
This isn't a free for all.
We are paid to prevent
him from jumping.
And I can't get proof of life,
from a dead man.
So..
You will be dock the entire price
of the asset.
The entire price of the asset
it goes on my months of my pain.
Then, you're lucky this man you killed
wasn't high value.
That is all, Gerry.
Hey, Portos..
Look at this.
There is no sunrise or sunset,
still, they pray all the time.
Don't you find that interesting?
Not really.
You look like, the kind of a guy
that find this interesting.
That kind, before?
Why all the questions?
It's how I learn things.
You really ought to study
somebody else.
- Portos?
- What?
You need a favour?
Favour man.
Compromising Correctional Institution
Security - Ray Breslin.
Well, for a man who is not interested.
You are doing a lot of looking.
What do you need?
I need to get into the isolation area.
No, you really don't.
Yeah, I really do.
Call it..a favour.
Okay?
Okay.
That's your favour?
This one's gonna straight us good.
Really?
Come on.
Let's see what you can do.
Alright.
You hit like a vegetarian.
- Really?
- You can do better than that.
Come on.
- Let me see it.
- Try this.
You hurt?
- That's good.
- The good one's coming.
Relax..let's pretend.
I guess, boys will be boys.
That's enough.
Bring them in the barn now.
You can thank me later.
Think.
They knew, he was tagged.
Of course, they knew.
Who do you think, this guys are?
Who do you think?
They are a bunch of...
Yahoos..from one of those
BOP facilities?
This is the shadows world.
These guys, they invented
this shit.
Why do you think
they are paying us all that money?
Remember, what the guidelines were.
What the fuck are you talking about?
There are no guidelines.
You call that CIA bitch.
Hush?
Motherfucker.
Alright..
I'll make the call.
Abigail, you gotta keep him..
Away from me. Alright?
Give me your arm.
You will live.
How do a doctor work,
in a place like this?
Would you prefer,
there wasn't a doctor here?
Where is here?
Hey Doc, let's wrap it up.
What did he asked you?
He wanted to know his..
Dehydration is; Compared to the others.
And what did ya tell him?
I don't care.
That's what I told him.
Get him out of there!
Did you find what you're looking for,
In the box?
All prisoners back to your cell.
Who were you before you
came in here, Portos?
You are always, watching the room..
Always watching everything.
Are you asking me,
what I used to do?
Yeah.
I'll tell you.
But I need a another favour.
Fuck that.
Alright, don't do it.
Alright, I'm listening.
What's the favour, this time?
I need a piece of metal.
About 3 inches wide..
Round, smooth.
Oh, no problem.
I'll be right back, okay?
If you get me that piece of metal,
I might be able to get you.
Out of here.
Tell Hobbes, I want to talk.
You've been six months now, Mr. Rothmayar.
So, you know how this works.
10 seconds.
Where is Victor Manheim?
You know to my people,
- He is a hero.
- 9 seconds.
Do you have a pencil and
a piece of paper?
8 seconds.
I could draw you a map.
- Of what?
- Where you could find him.
You know when I was a kid..
I always wanted to be an artist.
My god, you're pushing it.
The problem was..
I had no talent.
- 6 seconds.
- I tried.
- And I tried and tried.
- 5..
- Do you have dreams?
- 4...
Did you always wanted to be..
- This?
- 2..1!
Done.
There.
I told you.
No talent.
Records indicate that you are
highly intelligent, huh?
Yeah.
As such, I'd have expected you
to see the situation,
and understand it for what it is.
In here, you have no control
over any part of your life.
Except, your breathing.
And you just lost that privilege.
Get him down.
Keep going.
Enough.
- What happened?
- Nothing.
I am still here.
Now, it's your turn.
I break out of prisons,
for a living.
For the past 8 years, I've been breaking
out of facilities
for the federal bureau of prisons.
I think, Hobbes been hired
for this place to make it unbreakable.
Someone wanted this place tested.
But it was a set up.
They wanted to bury me.
I don't know who.
But I'm gonna find out.
I need you to set up
another diversion.
What now?
You gotta go back, in the box.
No fucking way.
Wanna get out of here?
Okay. I'll do it.
But if I don't get out...
I'll kill you.
Fair enough.
The success for a break out
depends on three things.
- Layout, routine and..help.
- What if this thing isn't build that way?
It's not.
Something under the box,
I think it's a cover.
If it is,
how do we know where it goes?
Anyway, I'm gonna find out.
- Eat.
- It's disgusting.
The mind of an inmate works
differently than someone on the outside.
He sees things differently.
The architecture is vertical.
The cell blocks, the outer locks..
The box, the mess...
everything is in large
vertical compartment.
The best guess is they
build down underground,
In large natural fixtures.
Like caves.
If I can get in there.
Follow where it goes,
I just might find out a way to the surface.
If you are right,
How do you dug a metal?
It don't cut, don't cut at all.
This place is sub-terrainial.
There's moisture in the air.
Whoever build this place,
should've used aluminium.
Which means, the whole panelling
is done with steel.
Steel rust over time.
The way around that is concentrating
the heat to boost through this.
This will panel with snap right
the fuck off.
- Concentrated heat?
- Yeah. With the piece of metal you gave me.
We exposed it with the toothpaste
polished to rinse the metal.
- To some heat.
- With the lamps at the box.
Right.
At a 100 degree centigrade steel
on those panel with 3 cubic centimetre
those bolt will come right off.
What?
- You don't look so smart.
- You don't either.
See most prison are locked
to small towns.
With an hour or more,
we need supplies and workforce.
Now, if I get to the surface,
I don't who can take me over the wall.
But first, I'm gonna need that
diversion in the box.
How much time do you need then?
3 to 5 minutes.
No problem.
- Step back.
- I know you.
You don't know shit.
You can't see that.
Now, step back.
I know half of your brother.
Right.
Your mother,
she was my favourite whore in marrakech.
Man, she could polish that horn..
Damn!
You're killing me!
What is he onto?
Hey, shut the fuck up.
You german dog!
Just hold him till I get there.
Hey, I got a camera
malfunction in box 2.
Roger that.
Just reboot the system.
Shit!
Should we restrain and drug him, sir?
Not yet.
Lights off, box 4.
A rough day, Mr. Rothmayar?
Forgive me, Lord...
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name;
Thy kingdom come; Thy will be done;
On earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread.
And forgive us our trespasses, as we
forgive those who trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation;
But deliver us from evil.
You're a bad person!
You are filled with the devil!
Do not listen to those crazy...
Who is lit
lantern in the bright morning,
then go to the market...
He continued to shout:
" I seek God!"
Here's what you should know.
I don't care, sooner or later
you will tell me what I want to know.
It's inevitable.
Like dying.
Know this,
there will come a point;
Where I don't give a shit about you..
Or whatever the fuck
you think you are doing right now.
So, have a lovely day, Mr. Rothmayar.
Report.
Valve breach on level two sir.
Electrical malfunction.
Sir?
- Did you make it?
- Yeah.
Where are we?
- Where are we?
- I don't know.
They froze the check.
What are we talking about here?
The payment for Ray's services.
They froze the check.
Not frozen, it's on hold.
Alright, it's very common.
- On 2.5 Million dollar transaction.
- No..no, no.
Common would be a week,
maybe 10 days.
- This has been way longer than that.
- Listen Abbey.
It's the federal government.
You know how they work.
- Did you call that woman?
- Yeah, I called. Everything's fine.
Then, where is he?
He is on the job,
That he was hired to do.
So, you're saying
it's all good?
It's all good.
Where was the breach?
The auxiliary balance system sank outside.
Premise 5 and 7 has been compromised.
Navigation ventilation is shocked on box 2.
Portos?
Layer is full of rust.
Water pressure must've
snapped em clean off.
Maybe.
Portos isn't his name, is it?
Why wasn't I alerted?
Our client's been paying lots of money
to make sure that facility is unbreakable.
Now, he is there to prove that,
not even he
can get out. Now you make sure
he's there forever.
Do you have a problem with that?
No. No, not at all.
Just the opposite.
Fucker.
There's one more thing.
The chinese bank..
Have joined the Brazilians, the russians
the english and the U.S
and the swiss banks they're all paying
to find about the whereabouts of
this Manheimler fellow.
Word on the street is that
he's developed
a programme to turn the entire
world banking system
into fucking confederate.
Rothmayar worked with that
asshole, he knows where he is.
Your job, is to get that
information out of him.
Well, it just so happens that
since Breslin has got close to Rothmayar,
Rothmayar has developed a new edge,
to his defiance that was not
there before.
I think Breslin is to blame.
- Then, break Breslin.
- Thank you.
I have an assignment
I know you will enjoy.
Get on your feet!
Wakey, wakey.
Talk to me.
Come on, You must fight.
Get up!
Stay on your feet.
If we're on a ship.
We would know.
No. Not if you're over a
thousand feet long.
200 feet high and stabilized
we wouldn't know a damn thing.
Wakey, wakey.
Get him on his feet.
You can do it.
- You are gonna do it.
- Can't get out of here.
- Yes, we can.
- No!
Get on your feet.
Stop it now, Ray.
Don't give up.
Don't let them break you.
What made you want
to spend your life in prison?
Hmm? Tell me?
What made you do it?
Tell me!
I was a lawyer,
a prosecutor.
The man that I put away,
made a promise to me.
This man thought about this promise
everyday for three years.
Planning his way out of prison.
Planning on how
he's gonna keep his word;
Taking a man's life is nothing.
Taking his heart?
That's everything, Isn't it?
Everything.
You see, putting people in prison
wasn't good enough.
I had to. I wanted to..
Make sure they stay in there.
Not getting out.
I understand.
I have a daughter.
Never forget that.
You have a choice.
You can die in here...
or you can get out with me.
Punishing,
who put you here.
- You hear me?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Good news and bad news.
I was thinking about
that first meeting.
Privatized Incarceration.
Off the grid,
international profile..
And I started digging.
Code name - The Tomb.
Completely for profit.
Totally, legal.
Run by ex-military ass holes.
Blackwater rejects..
You know bad dudes.
If Ray is anywhere, it's here.
Where is here?
That's the bad news.
I don't know.
We need excess to any layout.
No blind times.
We are in the middle of
the fucking ocean.
I wouldn't be content
if we didn't find our team.
They've scrambled the guards shift
so they are never the same.
But they can't change the routines
of the guards themselves.
We don't know where they start.
We don't know when they end.
But I do know
where they're gonna be..
Based on habit.
See the guy coming down the stairs,
see how he's walks
all pigeon toe?
- The duck.
- Yeah, well..
Yeah, the duck always
work with the guy with grey on his neck.
- Hives.
- Yeah, Hives.
When Duck and Hives work together,
they always do it circular.
And they do it,
at random times a day.
It doesn't matter when they do it.
It always end up getting
a 120 strides each.
Then, they spit up.
Watch.
Now, they each take a side.
Duck walks 53 strides,
Hives 65, then they meet up at the top.
The guard down there at the bottom.
That heavy set guy,
He doesn't move much.
My guess is he hasn't been here a while,
and only does what he has to do.
Louisa.
- Louisa?
- His standing style reminds
me of my first girlfriend.
Nice.
That guard over there
could create a problem for us.
- He is always looking around.
- The Chicken man.
Chicken man, right.
My guess, Chick is new here.
Does everything by the book.
How do you know
when the shift ends?
I don't.
Around this time, your girlfriend
Louisa starts looking at her watch.
My guess, it's lunch time.
- Welcome back.
- Thanks.
But now that we got the routine,
We just got to ask
the good doctor,
Where the hell we are.
I'm not permitted to give you
anything for the pain.
So, don't request it.
Hey, Doc..
You took an oath.
'According to my ability and judgement'
' I'll protect my patients from
harm and injustice'.
What exactly is that you
want from me?
I wanna know,
where the hell I am.
It's okay, it's under control.
Put him back here.
Sorry.
- So?
- No luck.
Push him harder.
Pushing him is no hopes.
What are the options?
Plan-B.
You always gotta have a plan-B.
Did you get it?
Now, I need his glasses.
Sir?
Take a look at this.
It's a makeshift sextant.
Will it work this?
It works.
But it will only give us
half of our location.
Bring Breslin.
Ill explain how it works later,
But first, we gotta get this outside.
Watch out there.
Welcome to your new hole,
Mr. Breslin.
Actually, I've been waiting for??
You know who I am?
I do, now.
I've studied your work,
very closely.
It's quite brilliant.
As a matter of fact...
It is what I used as reference guide
in designing..
This facility.
If you know what I am.
Let me go.
No, no, no..no. Mr. Breslin,
It's not how this works.
Not this time.
You see, the people who paid
for you to be here;
Want for you forever.
And knowing that,
knowing who you are..
Well, who you were.
I can't have you
communicating with Rothmayar.
Or with anybody else,
for that matter.
This is the reality.
And there is no way out.
This can go, two ways.
You let me go and I'll pretend
this never happened. If you don't..
I'll burn this fucking place
to the ground on my way out.
Effective right now.
No mess, no rec time and
no showers.
I can get you Victor Mannheim.
Rothmayer trust me.
So, you say.
- Not good enough.
- What've you got to loose?
Finding him can be worth a lot more
than what you're paying for me.
- Right, Hobbes?
- It's a nice idea but...
As it stands right now,
I'm in line to get both.
You will never break Rothmayer.
He'll die before he turns.
I'm the only chance
to get what you want.
I want Mannheim and his whole network.
Names, locations in real time.
Get back and if it checks out,
I'll let you go.
But know this..
You tell me every word that
you and Rothmayer shares or
I will personally pull
the fucking life out of you.
Fair enough.
So, what happened?
I'm playing you.
Last night, Rothmayer told me he started
his network with 5 guys
in his hometown.
He said, he could trust his life
with this guys.
Give Javed the sextant.
Show him how to use it.
And tell him,
it's his ticket out of here.
Javed?
He would rather see us dead.
He'll be the last one they suspects.
The (?) network caused the bank collapse
in Iceland six years ago.
I don't give a shit about
six years ago.
I wanna know where he is now.
You wanna die?
Do you wanna get out?
Today?
- They are planning an escape.
- An escape?
Really? Who and when?
I don't know the details.
Just some.
Tell me the details you know.
You get me fixed first.
Mr. Alfredo..Affidi, or whoever the fuck
your name is.
Your Opiate drug cartel friends
have paid a lot of money
for you to be here.
Of course, they did.
Those fucks.
So, aside from your freedom,
what else can I give you?
I want the guards
to leave my people alone.
The Holy Qur'an
I want one in my cell.
And I want to say
the name of Allah..
And the prophet Mohammad in the open air.
I want to be seen by my God.
When I say my evening prayers.
That's all?
That's all.
I wanna be seen by my God, Mr. Hobbes.
90 degrees 22 minutes.
- ...
- North or south?
The water basins turn clockwise,
above the equator, means we're in north.
Did we get the longitude?
The batch of fish in yesterday,
he said it's november 20th.
Without warm air,
or sea, november.
How do you build a secret facility
and put it underwater.
You have a terrific reason
toward northern latitude.
Cos you wanna avoid rough water.
So, you're gonna stay away
from the Caribbean and pacific sea.
And you stick to China sea.
If I was a betting man I'd say it
could be off the coast of Morocco.
It's just a guest.
In any case, its close to that sea.
That's my educated guess.
I know a guy there, A Casablanca,
who owes me big time.
Enough to come and get you?
Huh, he'd still owe me.
Is there a way to get a message out?
My god.
What is this?
You swallowed a clotting powder?
Listen to me.
I know you think,
I'm playing you.
In Hobbes's office,
there is a book.
Compromising in Correctional Institution
Security By Ray Breslin,
On page 8 is a detailed description of
cell block C of Lewis berg Federal Prison.
- Guards?
- Check it out.
And remember your oath.
I can't stall Hobbes any more.
- I gotta give him more location.
- We still doesn't have a plan.
It's in the doctor's hands.
The Hippocratic Oath.
Guards?
Bring me prisoner Portos.
From A Block.
Hobbes's orders, do it now.
Breathe in.
Okay.
I saw the book.
How did you know?
What do you want me to do?
The doctor is in.
Now, Javed has to do his part.
The man you hunts base of operation
is 20 miles outside Sierra Russo.
That's on the Bulgarian-Romania border.
See?
Ratting out a friend ain't so hard.
We got 24 hours, before Hobbes realizes
that he Bulgarian location is bullshit.
Who do we know in C block?
You've got permission
for your midnight prayer?
So, what do you have for me?
- Lock in Breslin.
- Yes sir.
What are you up to?
Louder... louder.
Got cha!
Decode it.
I need you in 24 hrs 30 degrees 22(N)
23 degrees 6(W) 5:00PM sharp tomorrow.
BBQ and pool party. Don't forget
to tell the kids. Bring all toys.
Rothmayar.
Stop it.
Zoom in.
Its McMayer's son.
Breslin is gonna have the sons help
breaking from cell block C.
We have the time frame.
And we have a location.
Cell block C.
Triple the guard force there.
I wanna know everyone
who is involved here.
You will sir.
P.A: Cell block C prepare for inspection.
Cell block C prepare for inspection.
Louisa and Chicken man.
They sent everyone else
to Cell block C.
You better be fucking right.
Don't worry.
Hey, you fucking white trash
scum bag’s bitch!
Where's do you think
you're fucking..
- Your fucking sister..
- Fuck you.
Motherfucker!
The riot was suppose to break
from block C.
Move the men from block C
to Babylon.
Right now.
Come on.
Where the fuck is Breslin?
Go, go..go.
Let's move.
We got 11 minutes to get to the top
let's hope the doc has made contact.
What are you doing?
All the cameras are connected.
We gotta block them out.
Sir?
Say, cheese!
Fire ventilation. Let's go.
Engage security protocol 5.
We're out gunned.
The walls are locked outside.
8 minutes.
They are out of moves.
Drake, take two men.
Drag the rats back to cages.
Javed!
Open Gate 3!
Go, go..go!
Don't fucking loose them.
Breslin.
We gotta move.
As soon as that door's down.
I'll cover you guys from the other side.
Breslin, how the hell did
they know where we are?
You turned off the cameras, right?
Motion detector.
Sir?
Out.
You can play your games all day, Mr. Breslin.
But I am still in control.
Whatever you do,
I have the power.
I own your ass.
You guys can get up that ladder.
I gotta find the engine room.
We shut the power and wait them down.
Those magnetic glasses door
open for about 5 seconds,
before the back-up generator
kicks in. You understand?
It's all the time you're gonna have.
Take this, take it.
You are a good man.
Go for it.
What about you?
I'll be right behind you.
But what if you're not up
there on deck in 5.
Do what you gotta do.
There's always plan B.
Come with me, let's do it.
I'm dead man.
There is no way out.
You're coming with me.
I'll carry you up there.
- I'm not gonna leave you behind.
- Give me your gun.
Just give me your gun.
I'll see you up there.
Now, go.
Take care.
- Report.
- Fuck you, motherfuckers.
We are taking gunfire
at the lower deck.
If they're at lower deck
it's going to be their exit route.
Meet me at the engine room.
I'm coming down.
Copy.
- Get that fucker out.
- Yes, sir.
Yeah. Whatever.
Come on.
I'll fucking kill you, motherfucker!
- Yeah, he is here.
- We are on our way.
- I'll take care of it.
- No, wait..wait!
What the fuck?
- Fuck me.
- No one gets off this ship.
We have to move now!
Not yet.
Give yourself up, Mr. Breslin.
Give a look around,
make some noise.
This is no cell block.
You can't get out.
Not really.
I know about your wife...
your son.
I know every detail.
So, thank you.
For pointing out all the small flaws
in my creation.
I'll be sure to fortify them.
Cos your time is up.
You hear me?
Breslin?
Your time is up.
Go in there.
Search every inch of this fucking room.
Breslin?
Go, down!
Rothmayar! Gun!
- Gun?
- Give me your gun.
Boom.
Have a lovely day.
Asshole.
Now, what?
Relax.
- You met her before.
- Jessica Miller.
It's an honour to meet you.
Your work is a gold standard in field.
She's been my eyes and ears
inside the Agency.
Hello, Dad.
And she's also my daughter.
Hello, darling.
Thank God, you made it.
I've missed you.
What happened?
Oh, nothing.
Don't worry about it.
You are Mannheim.
Didn't see that coming.
You shouldn't.
Yeah.
How did you do it?
We have code names.
Code name Rothmayar, meant
maximum security incarceration.
When my dad was picked up.
It activated the code.
- And that's when you...
- I needed the best.
And after you agreed to do it.
I used my contact deep inside
the DHS to get you in.
And the name you gave me
was the ID code?
Portos.
Rothmayar, Emil Rothmayar.
And I became your best friend.
You are not easy friend to have there.
I mean, I had to work very hard.
That damn box.
I mean, that was hot.
Didn't think you had warm yet.
But it doesn't matter.
What matters is that I am out,
so are you.
Don't sweat for no time.
You wanna try it again?
You son of a bitch.
- I hope, I never see you again.
- Well, that hurts.
One more thing.
- How much does Les really know?
- Only what I told him at first.
But the next thing I know,
he's going around me
and offered his services
to the backers of The Tomb.
So, he knew where I was being sent?
He arranged your transport.
You need a ride?
No, thanks.
I've made my own arrangements.
It wasn't tracking.
We knew something wasn't right.
Red flags going up all over the place.
Clark was too calm about it.
So, we started digging.
We found out,
he'd been offered the CEO job
of running the whole
tomb programme.
As a prototype, he would bear the proof
that it was inescapable.
With a salary of 5 million a year
plus stock options.
Tell me, you've tracked
him down.
Just like you asked.
The plan is in motion as we speak.
Sleeping time, motherfucker!
Oh, fuck!
Hush.
What did he say?
It's all good.
Good.
- What's that?
- Job offers.
Ignore them, maybe later.
Why don't you and me
have a very special dinner?
No, I'll cook.
Haven't I suffered enough?
www.moviesubtitles.org