||....FAST FIVE....||Enjoy!
Subtitle created by sijuvrm
Dominic Toretto,
you are hereby sentenced
to serve 25 years to life
At the Lompoc maximum
security prison system.
without the possibility of early parole.
This is all the aftermath
Of a daring daylight breakout.
There were 26 high risk inmates.
Every one on board has been
accounted for
Except for one - Dominic toretto.
Police believe the identity of men they
believe had orchestrated the shocking escape
has resulted amazingly in no fatality this afternoon
He is former federal agent
brian O'Conner.
Appears to be a manhunt
underway for three fugitives tonight
Multiple federal and local agencies
have joined forces
In the search for - Dominic toretto and his
accomplishes Brian O'Conner and mia toretto.
Despite every eye in the country
looking for them
Where toretto and O'Conner are now
is any ones guess
Let's get out of here
Mia...
Buster....
Dom here yet.
No. - When was the last
time you heard from him?
A couple of weeks ago, up
in ecuador or somewhere.
How does it feel ? - Whats that?
Beyond the other side of a wanted person.
Nice long. Yes.
Why Rio vince?
You mean after you everything
screwed up in LA ?
Made me free-Fall in South America after....
We kept on going if not for rosa...
So...listen.
There is a job coming up
I was hoping Dom was gonna
be here by now, but...
This one's clean enough,
we can do it without him.
Its a big gig.
Couple of high end cars, easy targets.
*** is putting together a team
to swipe them
Just need a few more willing bodies.
But, I don't know.
Look, the way car seem is down here, we
can unload them quick and get top dollar.
Its easy money.
From where i am seeing,
It looks like you both
could use a pay day.
What are you reading?
Tour guide.
Yeah? Hmm..
Tokyo.
You know what all of these
places have in common.
No?
All.
Here we go.
Excuse me, buddy
Yeah, we have found them.
Yeah, second through last racer.
What, what is it?
DEA tags, this car is en-Seized.
Look, who showed up.
Oh! GOD, i am so happy you are ok.
I thought i told you to lay low
- we were running out of fuel.
Had to make a call.
Hey quit talking, we only
got a two minute window.
Lets go, vince.
Ladies first.
See you baby.
Change of plans,
wait for my call
Lets go.
Where is she going?
We are being robbed, go and pullover the train.
Access card, get the access card.
Dom, there is a bridge.
First is clear
We are going to next ***
Freeze.
We had to make a call, huh.
Shitty call, O'Conner.
Shitty call
You two started quite a
bit of trouble today.
Three of my men dead.
Three dea agents, along with.
Of course, this is business.
Sometimes things go stray.
All i care about is the car.
Tell me where it is.
And i will let you go
*** full of shit
I do not know how you guys do business
in your part of the world.
But here in Rio... i like all parties
to know what they are up against.
That's funny, because it goes both ways.
You know...
I hear your sister is
very beautiful.
Wherever she hides, i will find her
Mia?
Hey ..
You ok? - Yeah, you all right?
And,here you are? Just like a toretto.
Where's vince?
That's a good question.
He'll be here.
Guys, we are all over the news,they are blaming
us for killing of those DEA agents on the train.
Which means we just jump to the top of
the wanted list.
The feds will get us anywhere,
their agents are off the limits.
They are gonna send their best guys,
we gotta get out of here
One thing we know for sure
Is that, they wanted this car.
Something's in it. We find out what it is.
We know what we are up against.
Alright, listen up. The men we're after are professional runners.
They like speed and guarantee to go down the hardest possible way.
So make sure you got a lot of firearm.We find them,
we take them as a team and we bring them back.
And above all else, we never ever let
them get into cars.
*** lets go hunt.
Agent Hobbs? Chief of police.
Sorry to hear for loss of your men.
Is all this really necessary to apprehend two men?
Let me tell you little something about these two men.One's
a former federal officer, been in deep cover for 5 years.
Knows everyWay we are gonna come from.The other
one's a professional criminal, escaped prison twice,
Spent half his life on run avoiding folks like you.
Well, if there's anything we can do to help...
Two things.
One - I need a translator.
Alright, We have plenty...
Elena Neves.
- A patrol officer?
You heard me.
But why? We have many more
experienced people.
I like her smile.
What's the second thing.
Stay the fu*k out of my way!
Brian.
There is something i have to tell you.
Oh, damn.
What a mess.
Where you have been Vin.
You better check that tone.
You better answer some goddam questions.
Stop it, both of you.
Where were you vince.
Guys all over are asking
questions about you
Couldn't get out of there without
leading them straight to you
Had to wait them out.
That is such a horse shit,
that was your job.
Enough O'Conner! If he said he
didn't do it, he didn't do it.
Go walk it off.
Look, i would love to expand my
operations in your country
But quite frankly.
No business methods are hard to find.
Let me tell you true story
500 years ago
Portuguese and spanish came here.
Each trying to get the
country from there methods.
The spanish arrive guns blazing,
determine to prove who is boss.
But, the natives killed every
single spaniard.
Personally, i prefer the
methods of the portuguese.
They came bearing gifts.
Mirrors, scissors, things that the
native couldn't get own their own.
But, to continue receiving them would
require will of portuguese
And that's why all brazilians
speaks portuguese today.
Now, if you Dominate the people with
violence, they will eventually fight back.
Because, they have nothing to lose.
And, that's the key
I go into the favals, and give
them something to lose
Electricity, running water,
school room for their kids
And for that taste of the better life
I own them.
Gentlemen.
Pardon me gentlemen.
I almost wish i didn't see it.
Almost.
Wait, Dom
Mia was on that train
I didn't.....i didn't know
i wouldn't do anything to hurt her.
You set off the deal
I thought the job was for the cars
I did not know. All they
wanted was the chip.
Damn.
You should have come clean.
What's going on out here?
Nothing. Please, Dom.
Just, let me have the chip.
I can take this to them and set things right.
Get out!
What?
You never listened to me.
Not when i told you he was a cop
and not now.
You never trusted me.
Now, look where its gotten us
Look at our family now,
i can't go home.
Your sister is stuck in this life
and where is letty Dom?
Where's letty?
Plasma cover, Wilkes i want a list of every place
within 50 miles that distribute compressed gas tank.
Pass me that evidence bag.
Officer Neves, i have been waiting for you.
You asked for me ? I did.
May i ask, why?
My smile is not that great.
Your husband was an officer,
who was gunned down in Favela.
Six months later you up and join the force?
You are motivated.
Plus i procure you are only the real one
who can't be brought. Am i right?
Yes.
Of course i am.
We have got some bad news.
You don't like my deserve first
I checked the rail-Line like you asked, found a
couple of spots where they unloaded the cars.
One set of tracks headed west until it hit
the main highway and then disappeared
And the another set of tracks headed east
170 inch wheel base, half inch track.
The GT 40 ? -That was missing from the manifest,pretty
easy on this rug. Can't move without leaving signs.
Give me the damn stretches
The ground rolls into a hard pack
and we lost the track too.
Not necessarily.
That road hits through
hill into the favelas
Couple of years ago it was washed out by a storm.
So, is dirt from a mile from where you were.
If you headed that way,
you will pickup the tracks there
Come prepared?
I'm motivated.
All right then, lets find ourselves a car.
What do you think?
Its definitely not just a chip.
Look at all these side menus here,
for data entry. Lets check this one.
Look at that. Same building,
same order every week.
Its a delivery schedule.
Drugs? No, that's a dealer pack.
See, the most major player they weigh their money so
they don't have to cost somebody to account it.
Right there that's 49 kilos.
49 kilos is a million in twenties.
So, you are saying each one of these
shipment is worth 10 million dollars.
Yeah.
I thought so....
So, what is that?
A 100 million plus in cash oasis?
That how it keeps it off the grid.
I can say this one is razor smart about this pack. I mean
its whole network right there, just laid out on its inn
Wilkes and tom go from the
middle, rest flank north
What about me?
Stay here.
Police! On the ground!
I got torreto.
Hey! Police!
They already know who you are.
Let's go.
You ok here ? Yeah.
Almost, thank you.
They are gonna be looking for the
three of us together now.
We need to split up. You and mia head south
i will lead them away.
No.
Dom's right.
We got lucky to get away, but what happens next time?
We have no choice but to split up
I am pregnant
I already lost my family once
I am not gonna do that again.
Are you kidding me?
No.
I'm not going anywhere. Ok.
Dom, promise me we stick together.
I promise.
Family just got bigger... ye..H.
Something doesn't add up.
Toretto and O'Conner...
They stay when they are supposed to run
They steal gas and then give it away?
And now they killed three
federal agents?
It doesn't make any sense.
Here's what makes sense.
All these guys names are on a list. They come up, we
take'em down.Not a phone call more, not a bullet less.
Wilkes! We get anything?
Standard forensics, sweep prints,
hair fibers. Prints are all over the car
Anything else?
Yeah, we track the owner
off the vehicle ID
They are couple of shell companies in between a
corporation owned by a investor named Hernan Reyes.
Investor?
If there is anything illegal
happening in Rio, Reyes is involved.
Okay, then so are we.
If you can ***
I want every thing on him
Chato, be on the roof. I want you on watch
in case somebody comes back for something
Mac give me a cross-Check on Reyes, full specs, he goes
to the john, i want to know how many times he shakes it
You got it boss
Lets put all this mess together.
Well, that's gonna take a while.
- Then you better get started.
They were taking this
car apart for a reason.
Lets put it back together
and find out whats missing.
Hey Dom, what do you remember
about your father?
My father...
He used to....he used to
have a barbeque every sunday after church
For everybody in the neighbourhood.
If we didn't go to church
we didn't get any barbeque.
Every single day he was in the shop
And, every single night he was at the kitchen
table with mia helping her with her homework.
Even after she went to sleep he would
stay up for few more hours.
So he could learn the next chapter and help her next day
I remember everything about my father.
Everything.
That's just it.
I Don't know shit about my dad
I don't remember him yelling,
I don't remember him smiling.
To be honest with you,
I don't remember what the hell he look like
I had all the memories....he is just
never there
You ain't gonna be like that Brian
We can't keep running Dom
We got to get out
We got to get out, now.
You're right.
This is how we are gonna do it.
We are gonna use this
into one last job.
We are gonna take all the Reyes money
Every dime of it.
And then, disappear.....forever
New passports, new life,
and no more looking over our shoulder
And we are just gonna buy our freeDom.
- That's right.
You realize we are talking about going up
against most powerful guy in all over Rio.
Yes. We are.
Then we are gonna need a team.
Alright, lets go through the basics
real quick.
What do we got?
First, we are gonna need a chameleon.
Someone who can blend in
Anywhere.
What else?
A fast talker. Someone who can
bullshit the way out of anything
I got that.
These guys are gonna have a lot of surveillance we are
gonna need someone who can schedule the circuits.
And with those circuits,
Reyes is gonna have a "wall"
We are gonna need the guys
who can punch through those wall
What else? Utilities and weapons
Someone who ain't afraid to throw down
someone who backup every position
Yeah? What else we need ?
Most importantly we are gonna
need two persistent drivers
Guys who don't crack under pressure.
Guys who never lose.
You know we got that.
Ah.....hell not
I see they really stared the
bottom of the beer..Huh
I guess they did, since your ass is here.
When you are gonna give martin
luther king his car back?
As soon as you give rick james
his jacket back.
Sexy legs baby girl.
What time do they open?
They open the same time
when i pull this trigger
Want me to open them?
Yeah anybody can talk shit
in spanish
Two fails, i am not fail.....two fails
Who are these clowns men?
Circus clowns
I see, you have all met.
Here he is.
You know when you called me to come to Rio, i assumed
it would be for something more exciting than this
This is Tej, the best
circuit men in the east coast.
This is my boy Roman Pearce, we go way back
from juvenile
I pulled that job with him Miami.
I heard about you. - Nice stakes.
Yeah, the rest were sold out.
So, whats this all about Dom?
Yeah man, why you drag us
half way around the world.
Because we got a job.
Alright, so target's name is Hernan Reyes.
He runs the drug scene out there
He has never been busted because
he doesn't leave a paper trail.
No paper trails means no banks.
No banks means cash houses.
That's right.
To tell you exact, its
spread throughout the city
And we are gonna hit them all?
All of them.
All of them
Sounds crazy. Bring us to whole another country
so, that we can rob the dude who runs it
I thought this is business
Sounds personal to me.
Is that what this is?
I got love for you all,
but personal ain't good business
I can't do this homie.
So, what we are talking about
is a 100 million dollar.
You sa..Y...wha...t ? Hun...hun...
See, sometimes i be over-Thinking maybe
and you know i know...we just met...but.
You just kinda...gotta.
A 100 million dollars.
And everything we take,
we split even.
So, that's 11 million a piece,
I am down
I am in
11 million? Sounds like a whole
lotta vaginal activity to me.
You can't pull off all the heist
on the same mark, you just can't.
Yeah, as soon as we hit the first one they are gonna
do everything they can to protect their assets.
Exactly.
That's all of it.
You're dead men. You're all dead men.
You don't have a place to hide.
Who is hiding?
Are you crazy ? Are you crazy?
Do you know whose house this is?
Whose money are you stealing?
We ain't stealing.
You tell your boss, exactly who did this.
Tell him there is more coming
Wallah...
Turn it over
Its running alright, checks out fine.
Keep looking.
Boss, if something was missing
we would know.
Its a goddamn shame to put a bullshit
like that on a classic
Here, as well slap some on light on it.
They took the chip.
We got a hit on the police scanner.
Armed robbery in the house of golan.
Alright if that's our guys then whatever was
on that chip led them directly to that house.
Its them for sure.
How do you know that ? - Because no one
else in Rio is stupid enough to rob Reyes.
Number 1 is in motion.
Two is on the move.
Yeah, i got mine
I got eyes on five
I know you said they were consolidating
money somewhere
But you all ain't gonna believe it.
Well, this job has got a little harder.
If he is moving it into a police station he
has got some serious brass in his pocket.
Hell yeah, we can't do this.
We can't or we shouldn't.
I think it doesn't change a thing
I say we stick to the plan.
You say wha...this shit just went from mission
impossible to mission freakin' insanity.
Whatever man!
I ain't scared. I am just lettin you all know..
Going in that bouty, its just crazy. - I got this.
What time is robbery
Around 11' o clock
Here we go
Enhance it.
There faces are covered.
Run it through FRS.
Well, hello you son of a bitch.
Wilkes, run the photos of known associates of torretto and
O'Conner against custom entries in brazil within last 2 weeks.
Check planes, trains, boats and everything
short of a goddamn space shuttle.
They can change their names
but, they can't change their faces.
Something big is going down.
That's a 1970 charger.
Let's go.
Upload these facts into the database
have the computer cross-Check them with
The overhead satellites at every 15 minutes.
Stand behind in two.
If these vehicles move on the streets
of Rio, i wanna know about them.
The beauty of police offices.
A blueprint?
This is where they are keeping the money.
The vault's in the evidence room.
Yeah..Um. Can i get everyone's attention right here for a
second, we are talkin about breaking into a po-lice station.
Is anyone listening to those words?
Anybody? Po-Po.
Five o, one time, peaks
people we don't like.
You know police stations are designed
actually to let people in and out.
That's why its a stealth mission.
We move in and out before they even know we are there.
Well, we need to get eyes in there.
At least, to find out the
model of that vault.
Who's the folk you know, do all this.
Wait...wha do you mean?
Why me?
Because, Out of all of us, you
got the biggest mouth.
That is for damn certain.
Hello beautiful......look at those dimples
sexy.........sexy.
Love those glasses,
where did you get them from.
Is it gucci frames or somethin?
No, no...
Who are you sir?
Special agent O'Conner.
Us federal bureo of investigation.
It says caucasian?
Well, its the tan....you know tan.
Look....i am working this case
and i got some evidence here to be held.
But i need to get in....and check your
storage facility first.
Nope. - Look man i know you are a true
professional and i respects you, i promise.
You know...it look like you workout a little bit too.
Whats you benchmark 3-350.
My boss sent me here to just make sure
everything was safe.
It will be safe. - Ok..Well let me
just come in and take a quick peek.
Nope. - Come on man.
Hook a brother up please.
No. And you are not my brother.
Brother from another mother?
Look..No one enters the facility
but authorized evidence personnel
Now stop wasting my time.
I am going to call
the embassy. No...no, no.
We good...we don't need to call them..For
what?
We good.
Here, i got the box.
We all good, i promise you.
Thank you so much for your time
I swore to god, if I was on the other side of the
glass I will bust your damn face and translate that.
You see, I think I make a better
special agent than you ever did
Well, that depends on how you
define special.
Oh..Man, lets see what we got.
Have fun.
Alright come on.
Though, you still can drive. You see...
now i see why you always gettin accidents
You can't drive a damn
remote control car
I don't need this, i don't....
-Its a crisis. -Shut up right now.
I am not gonna shut up...
alright, strap him in his safety belt...man.
Give me the remote...going left. Its look like
something right over there to the left...what is that?
Bingo.
What is this ? 6 x 6?
8 x 12
7 x 12. 18-Inch thick steel. Re-Enforced wall, with
insulated copper core to protect it against thermal lance.
The class 3 electronical lock would sure fire..
And a biometric palm scanner.
Ten times the top of the line security.
Do i wanna know, how you know all that?
I had a life before you know me O'Conner.
Lets just leave it with that, alright.
She is a beauty, though.
Beauty as in good?
Beauty as in you know...
start off playing hard to get
And, no matter how much i caress her, no matter how much i
love her in the end she still ain't gonna give up that ass
I got this....relax man relax.
Got it...we got it.
Yeah...we are looking at four cameras.
Now, that's some high end shit too.
Marker optics.
They refill the view,
10 seconds oscillation.
Nah...that's a narrow window man?
Can we just stop the scanner
and replace the image.
Nah...its hooked up into a digital sync.
Ain't no way around the system.
The best we can do is peek.
We are gonna need some real
fast cars to get to this.
And, not just fast...
we need a hard ride and air
We need something agile.
You guys mark up a track.
O'Conner, lets go get some cars.
....Interval...Go have something!
//subs dedicated to ma mom and bumbo//
Home...sweet home.
Now that.
How about that?, all motors and no tuning issues?
I always wanted one of those.
Held the record on the
envadeda 3 years running.
You got a lot of bones to bring
your problems here torreto
Not to mention a cop
Yeah, we can keep that on the low
Word on the street is that a
lot of people are looking for you two.
But, you didn't think
we would recognise you
Well, what kind of car you own
That little cool may run the street around here but
that monster has never seen a set ot tail lights, ever
Well she is about to.
Lets go......legend
Car for a car.
Car for car?
If you want it, come and get it.
Really?
Whe..Whe..Where did you get that from?
Popa's mark.
Ok O'Conner, give me your best shot.
How was that one ? Camera caught you.
What? Yeah it still caught you - Then i
will milk the hell out of that thing too.
We are gonna need a faster car.
Exactly why your ass ain't been
driving. You gotta re-Blaze
I think, i am in love.
That was a real solid work but
i think camera 3 still caught you though.
Let's do it again.
That's your piggy bank ? You kiddin me
yup?
Where the hell can i get one of these?
Well we had a life
before you met us.
Alright, well i get to work
on the electronics tunneler
But there's still another problem
Palm scanner
And without Reyes hand-Print,
Houdini himself can not open this bitch.
How do you know its Reyes's hand-Print?
You got 100 million dollars in a safe
You gonna put somebody
else's hand-Print on it.
How are we supposed to get
Reyes's hand-Print?
Han, you are up.
Sure, gotta make the easy stuff.
Lets go, i will drive.
That makes six bodyguards.
Seven, do you think that guy with
a funny look is a tourist?
So, how long were you in the army?
I got out of military probably the same
time you quit smoking
The amount of chips you ate.
The way you always had to keep
your hands and mouth busy
You are a two packs a day.
For sure
Un-Filtered.
Well, this is a bust.
How you gonna get Reyes
fingerprint out of here
You need to do some more recon.
Kinda couple extra guys.
Alright, you don't send a man
to do a woman's job
We gonna figure this out, i promise you.
Whats up?
I thought she was more of a thong man?
We got the prints.
Where?
Ok. That's crazy.
So, did he just like slap that ass
Or, did he like grab and hold on to it?
Yeah..Hey...this will work.
I'm impressed. - Got it?
Got it. But, you still
didn't answer the question.
Guys...guys...guys....we have a problem.
The whole team just got burned
now we are all wanted.
Hang on a second.
Us diplomatic security service
issued the warrants.
Agent L.Hobbs.
Hold on a second.
Hey Dom,
Is that the guy you saw in the favela ?
Yeah.
Hobbs is the leader of the
elite task force for the DSS.
So. He is good?
When the FBI wants to find somebody
that's who they call.
Because he never misses his mark.
This guy is....he is old testament.
Blood, bullets, rap the GOD
that's his style.
And right now he is hunting us?
Dom, we are gonna move up
our time line.
Yes, but how?
This thing has already been difficult
If it ain't that..
We need more room to breathe.
Roman is right.
We need to get some fresh air.
Its got a hit.
Let's move
Move....move....move
Stopped...about a block ahead.
Park it...we are going on foot.
Hey.......toretto.
You're under arrest.
Arrest?
I don't feel like i am under arrest.
How about you brian?
Nah....not a bit.
Not even a little bit.
I will just give a minute...it will sink in.
We didn't kill those feds.
That's Reyes. I don't give a shit.
Just here to bring in two assholes
whose names hit my desk.
Yeah, that's sound like a real hero.
That's funny
From a guy who took the oath of a cop and
then went against everything he stood for?
Or, some wanna be tough guy prick who beat
a man half to death with a socket rinch.
That real tough.
You turn around and put
hands behind your back.
I don't think so. - You are so mistaken
to think you got a goddamn choice boy
Your mistake ? Thinking you are in america.
You're a long way from home.
This is brazil!
Come on boss, another day.
Come on, its way too heat.
I will see you soon, toretto.
I am looking forward to it.
Yep.
Tracker's on.
Got him.
I don't understand. Why come here?
Why risk it all for
20 dollar worth of silver?
Because its worth it.
You should run you know!
Hobbs will find you
You have every reason to leave
why stay ? - Why do you?
My husband was a good police officer...an
honest man...we both grew up here.
Three years ago, has was murdered in
the streets
Right outside out our door.
Reyes owns this place
He give things to people
And, everything has a price.
People here need a new start.
They need to be free.
You didn't killed those men in the train
did you?
Now, why would you believe anything
I would tell you.
Hey!
Was she so special to you?
I never thought anyone could
understand how much.
But you do.
Close, but not enough.
Time window is too small, man.
The only way we can beat the cameras,
is with invisible cars.
And i know, just where to get them
Lets take a ride boys.
Don't hurt yourselfs.
Its been a while since i hv'been behind
the wheel of one of these.
First time I ever been in the front seat
Hey, rom what took you so long.
I thought for sure, you be showing up
with some chrome spinners or somethin.
Ha.....hah....real funny
I got a 100,000 that says i can
take you all in the next quarter mile.
Yeah, you broke that like
you got a 100 grand.
If we pull off this job, I will.
Next two lights, a 100,000.
If we don't pull this job off,
we are probably dead anyway.
Lets, make it a million
I like that.
Alright, million dollar a quarter mile.
Alright then.
We only live once, lets do it.
What do you say Dom?
Are we talking or we racing?
Just don't cheat this time.
You gotta let that go.
Yeah, owned you....owned you.
Good race, O'Conner. Thanks, Dom.
The man right there!
He left off the throttle with a mile.
You didn't do nothing.
He let you win.
Bullshit.
Vince, what are you doing?
Quite, you have been tracked.
Its..Ok...wait.
Reyes's guys were waiting for
me at the market
And, vince saved my life
You hungry?
Yeah, sure
Good!
B'cause you are saying grace.
Thanks vince.
Cheers...cheers.....cheers.
So we in brazil,
still a good life.
Yeah.
So, you got a.....you got a little
more than 10-11 million dollars coming.
Whats you gonna do with your money?
Me?
Yeah.
Actually...man, i have been thinking
about opening up a garage back home.
A place where people can bring their cars, and they
get completely ripped off, you know what I mean?
Really?
Yeah.
So, your dream is to start a day job?
That's...that's stupid...man, why would..
Nah...that's not stupid at all..Man
I love what I do.
You wanna know what i am
gonna do with my money.
Find some cooking lesson for my man.
See, see? There you with that theory man?
You know me...
Its gonna take a little more than
money to learn how to cook...that's all.
But, i heard they were looking for a chef.
Down at this animal shelter.
Where you might....wanna.
Hey Dom,
Listen, i know you have a separate
job tomorrow.
If you need an extra men
Mike, you are in
You always have been a family.
Thank you!
Get something to eat.
Yeah
She might be right.
You really like doing that stuff, huh?
When your life is on the line,
that's when you manner by yourself.
That's a fair deal?
We are less than 24 hours from biggest
celebration of our life.
You gotta re-fill.
This is some seRious stuff.
No, I am good...I am good...
.No...thank-You!
No, she can't.
What do you mean?
She can't.
What do you mean, she can't?
Are you seRious right now?
Is that the reason you let him beat
you in the quarter mile?
That was a baby gift.
No, that's messed up.
But, still its a baby gift.
No, you are not taking that from me.
Wait, wait...hold on a second.
Did he just smack that ass or,
Did he grab the ass...
Thanks .. Thank you ..
Its your boy. Why would you keep
somethin like that away from us.
You did it again, huh
I have no idea what they
are talking about?
Toast!
Money will come and go, we know that.
The most important thing in life
Will always be the people in this room.
Right here, right now
Salute, de favelia...
salute...salute...
I'm all set
Santos, all good
Yeah, i am always good bro.
Hobbs is on the other side of the city.
We are not gonna get
a better window.
Ok guys, its showtime.
First team in position,
lets go. -Come on lets do this.
Hey Dom, i got eyes on mia
Moscow, berlin, goa, hong kong.
What do they have all in common
We are one hour away from rest of that.
Yeah.
Police!
You just made a big mistake
Took me while to find
out that tracking chip.
But, not as long to flip the receiver.
You're going down torretto.
I'm right here.
Dom!
Stand back, i got this.
Dom, please Dom.
Stop!
Dom!
Yeah?
We are coming in now
Tell the marshals to prepare a
vehicle to home back.
Ambush!
Wilkes, suppressing fire.
Set them down.
Macroy, cover me
Watch that
Cut us loose! Come on!
Cut us loose!
Everything all right? Let's go!
Let's go!
Hey Dom, you didn't meet my son
Nico
I will
He is a good kid
You know, we named him after you
Dominic.
You have my word vince.
You were always my brother.
See, you my brother.
We need to move, we don't
have that much time
I got some flight out,
that leaves Rio-de-janeiro in next 5 hours.
Not to run away....
To finish the job.
Are you crazy Dom ? We can't.
Its a suicide mission.
That's your man over there
on the table.
The plan is busted, this is bullshit man.
Reyes knows we are coming.
He's right.
They tripled the detail of the police
station its gonna be a wall of gunfire.
Reyes doesn't get away with this.
Its a trap man, you know that.
Dom! Listen to them.
Run, before its too late.
Leave Rio, you can be free
I don't need freeDom.
You should know that...
You are all free
to make your own choices
I am in.
I will ride with you toretto.
At least, until we kill that
son of a bitch.
So, whats the plan Dom?
Can't just go sneaking around
any more
We don't sneak
The only thing that he cares
about is his money.
If we pull that, we pull him.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Holl it out, mia?
You got a straight shot,
two blocks
Go right.
Got it
Wow, the plans working
You guys have every cop car
in Rio on your tail.
Whats the best drop?
Ok..Keep going straight
another half mile at du-Luff-Seeker
And then go left.
It ain't gonna work
Spikes ahead Dom....we got spikes.
We are going right
Nah...its too tight...
we are not gonna fit.
We have no choice.
Now.
Sh...it!
Holy....shit!
Guys i am hearing all this chatter,
you just take out a bank ?
Two in-Bound.
Alright! There is an ally
coming on your left
Yeah! I got it.
Alright Dom, right turn right here
Ok guys, there is a big group
coming at you from south.
You have do something, now
Lets go wide.
Yeah!
You all clear on the left.
Good afternoon officer.
License and registration please
Yeah! This is big boy stuff
We are clear on the right
Thanks guys.
-Anytime
I see you on the other side
You guys just copped out a
10 second window, make it count.
No...there is too many of them
We are not gonna make it.
You're right, we aren't
You are.
What are you talking about
Just let the vault go.
Get out of there.
You're father now, brian
No i am not even....
you stick with the plan
It was always the plan.
Take care of mia.
Dom you listen to me ..Now..Ok
-you cut loose right now
I thought i told you to go on.
Yeah! I had to make a call.
Help me.
That's for my team
you son of a bitch.
Its hell of a mess.
Yeah, it is.
You know, i can't let you two go
I ain't made that way
I will see to it that you bring
yourselfs 24 hours.
The money stays though.
If i were you, I would probably
use the time
Make peace with whatever
things you got left
Because come tomorrow,
I will found you.
Toretto
I'll see you soon.
No...you won't.
Thanks guys.
I see you on the other side.
You guys just copped out a
10 second window
Make it count.
Come on baby, don't be mean.
Right this way, my dear
Stay right here,
I will be right back.
So, this is your dream..Huh
That's enough of me man
I take you are enjoying?
Absolutely...whats up..Boy,
whats going on?
You good.
Yes, yes.
You know what's crazy?
There is only four of those cars
in the whole world.
And i got the only
one in western hemisphere
I made a sheikh in abu dhabi
an offer he could not refuse. -Huh
And, that's a nice lady
you got there too. -Oh...absolutely
Well...we got to go man.
Lets do this
Ok, i will drive
In that? Come on man..No...no way
No..Not...not in this,
in that!
Are you seRious right now.
Oh..Man...this is crazy.
Yeah.
So, i guess that means there
are two in the western hemisphere..Huh...huh
Whats your smart ass gotta say now?
Well...you know what,
we can always shine together baby.
Get dressed man,
we got things to do.
So, where to now?
I don't know
Never been to madrid.
I thought you wanna go to tokyo..
We will get there...
Eventually...
This is the happiest i have
ever seen my sister
It goes with free.
You know? I wanna another shot.
Yeah?
Yeah.
No wagers, no Body-Else
just you and me, once and for all
You sure, you gonna handle
the disappointment?
Are you?
Alright, O'Conner
Lets see what you got
You need to look at that
Berlin, 3 am this morning.
A team of hikers,
hijacked a military convey.
Torreto. -Nope
ain't interested
Yes you are, keep looking
You believe in ghosts.
....www.subscene.com....