Half-hour 'till the ball drops.
Tony Stark, great speech, man!
I gave a speech?
How was it? - Edifying. - Unintelligible.
Really?
That's my favorite kind, a winning combo.
Hey, uh, where are we going? - Uh, to
town on each other, probably back at
your house. I want to see your research.
Okay, you can see my research, but that's...
I'm not going to show you my "town".
Mr. Stark, Ho Yinsen.
- Hey, I finally met a man called Hope.
I'd like to introduce you to our guest, Doctor Wu.
Oh this guy.
- Mr. Stark.
Hey.
Perhaps another time?
Bern, Switzerland 1999
The old days,
I never thought they'd come back to bite me.
Why would they?
Hey Tony!
Aldrich Killian, I'm a big fan of your work.
My work? - Who is he? He means me.
Well, of course, but Miss Hansen, my organization has
been tracking your research since year two of M.I.T.
Oh wow, he made it. He made the cut.
What floor you going to, pal?
- Well now, that is an appropriate question.
The ground floor, actually,
of a proposal I'm putting together myself.
It's a privately-funded think tank
called "Advanced Idea Mechanics"
She'll take both.
One to throw away and one to not call.
"Advanced Idea Mechanics"
or AIM for short, you get it?
I see that 'cause it's on your t-shirt.
Ladies, follow the mullet. Ladies first.
Thank you. I'll call you.
I am titillated by the notion of working with you.
I'm going to ditch these clowns;
I'll see you up on the roof in five minutes.
I'm just going to try to get my beef wet real
quick if you know what I'm talkin' about.
I'll see you up there!
Damn betcha.
Come on, I thought that was just a theory.
Well... it was.
If I'm right, we can access the area of the brain
that governs repair and chemically recode it.
That's incredible.
Essentially, you're hacking into the genetic
operating system of a living organism.
Exactly.
Can you not touch my plant? It's not...
she doesn't like it. She perfers -
She's not like the others.
Come on, let's go to the bedroom.
Happy, leave her ficus alone. - No, seriously, don't
- And you're starting with plants?
- For now, yes.
I'm calling it "Extremis" - Well, its
- human application - Exactly!
Dentra-degree vitalization
Disease prevention
Even limb regrowth.
You're the most gifted woman I've ever met.
Wow... - In Switzerland.
That's better. - This week
You almost bought it, didn't you?
This is what I'm talking about, the glitch.
- Have you checked the telomerase algorithm?
We're good.
Stay down.
You're right on me...
What the hell was that?
What the hell was that? - It's a glitch in my work...
- She was just talking about it.
Glitches happen. - Oh, it's not Y2K...
Hey, Happy New Year
- Happy New Year - Happy New Year
Alright, I'll see you in the morning, okay?
Good night.
You good? - Yep. - I'll be right outside. - Okay, cool.
So, why am I telling you this?
Because I had just created demons,
and I didn't even know it.
Yeah, those were good times.
Then I moved on.
After a brief soiree in an Afghan cave,
I said "Goodbye" to the party scene.
I forgot that night in Switzerland.
These days I'm a changed man.
I'm different now.
I'm... well, you know who I am.
...Sir, please may I request
just a few hours to calibrate -
Nope!
Micro-repeater implanting sequence complete!
As you wish, sir. I've also prepared a
safety briefing for you to enitrely ignore.
Which I will.
Alright, let's do this.
Dummy
Hi Dummy. How did you get that cap on your head?
You earned it.
Hey. Hey! What are you doing out of the corner?
You know what you did.
Blood on my mat; handle it.
Sir, may I remind you that you've
been awake for nearly 72 hours
Focus up ladies. Good evening
And welcome to the birthing suite.
I am pleased to announce the imminent
arrival of your bouncing, badass baby brother.
Start titan and go white. Stamp date and time.
Mark 42 autonomous prehensile propulsion suit test
Initialize sequence.
Jarvis - drop my needle
Crap
Alright, I think we got this. Send them all.
Probably just a little fast... slow it down.
Slow it down just a... little bit.
Cool it, will you Jarvis?
Come on.
I ain't scared of you.
I'm the best
As always sir, a great pleasure watching you work.
I guess 72 hours is a long time between siestas
Didn't think it could get any worse
Then they had to go and turn on the TV.
That's when 'He' happened.
Some people call me a terrorist
I consider myself a teacher
America...
Ready for another lesson.
In 1864 in Sand Creek, Colorado,
The U.S. military waited until the friendly
Cheyenne Braves had all gone hunting
Waited to attack and slaughter the families left behind
And claim their land
39 hours ago,
the Ali Al Salem Air Base in Kuwait was attacked.
I did that.
A quaint military church,
filled with wives and children of course
The soliders were out on manuvers.
The "Braves" were away.
President Ellis,
you continue to resist my attempts to educate you, sir.
And now, you've missed me again
You know who I am. You don't know where I am
And you'll never see me coming.
...and now that we seem to be back, let's recap
some of the frightening developments in this story.
American airways were hijacked.
The nation remains on high alert.
All attempts to find the Mandarin
have so far proved unsuccessful.
Central to my administration's response to this
terrorist event is a newly-minted resource.
I know him as Colonel James Rhodes.
The American people will soon
know him as the Iron Patriot.
And how is President Ellis responding?
By taking the guy they call "War
Machine" and giving him a paint job
The same suit but painted red, white,
and blue, look at that
And they've also renamed him Iron Patriot
You know, just in case the paint was too subtle
It tested well with focus groups, alright?
I am Iron Patriot. - Listen.
War Machine was a little too aggressive, alright.
This sends a better message.
So what's really going on? With Mandarin
Seriously, can we talk about this guy?
It's classified information, Tony.
Okay, there've been nine bombings - Nine...
The public only knows about three.
But here's the thing... nobody can ID a device.
There's no bomb casings - You know I can help
Just ask. I got a ton of new tech.
I got a prehensile suit. I got
Bomb disposal
Catches explosions mid-air
When's the last time you got a good night's sleep?
- Einstein slept three hours a year. Look what he did.
People are concerned about you, Tony.
I'm concerned about you.
You gonna come at me like that?
- No, look, I'm not trying to be a dic-
- tator. - Would you mind signing my drawing?
If Richard doesn't mind. You alright with this, Dick?
- Fine with me.
What is your name? - Erin.
By the way, I liked you in "A Christmas Story".
Listen, the Pentagon is scared.
After what happened in New York... aliens, come on.
They need to look strong.
Stopping the Mandarin is a priority, but it's not
- It's not superhero business.
No, it's not, quite frankly.
It's American business.
Are you okay?
I broke the crayon. - Are you okay, Mr. Stark?
Take it easy. Tony...
....How did you get out of the wormhole?
Tony - What'd you say?!
Sorry. Have to check on the suit... make sure...
Check the heart, check the, check the, is it the brain?
No sign of cardiac analomy or unusual brain activity
Okay, so I was poisoned?
My diagnosis is that you've
experienced a severe anxiety attack.
Me?
Come on man, this isn't a good look. Open up.
- Sorry, I gotta split.
Badge... badge... badge
Badge, guys. I put a memo in the toliet; come on.
Tony has got them in his basement, they're wearing
party hats, this is an asset we can put to use
Uh-huh. So, you're suggesting that I replace
the entire janitorial staff with robots?
What I'm saying is that the human element of
Human Resources is our biggest point of vulnerability
We should start phasing it out immediately.
What!? - Excuse me, Bambi
Did you just say that? - Security
Happy, okay, I am thrilled that you're
now the Head of Security, okay; it is the
perfect position for you. - Thank you
However, - I do appreciate it
Since you've taken the post,
- You don't have to thank me.
We've had a rise in staff complaints of 300 percent
Thank you. - That's not a compliment.
"That's not a compliment"? It is a compliment!
Clearly somebody is trying to hide something.
Excuse me. - Yes? - Miss Potts, your four o'clock is here.
Did you clear this four o'clock with me?
- Happy, we'll talk about this later
But right now I have to go deal
with this very annoying thing.
How so?
I used to work with him, and he used to ask
me out all the time, so it's a little awkward.
I don't like the sound of that.
Pepper. - Killian?
You look great... you look really great.
God, you look great. I... I... I can't...
what on Earth have you been doing?
Nothing fancy,
just five years in the hands of physical therapists
And please, call me Aldrich.
Uh, you were supposed to be issued a security badge
- Happy, it's okay.
Yes? - We're good.
You sure? - Yes.
Stand down. - I'm going to linger
Thank you. - Right here, okay.
It's very nice to see you, Killian.
Hey, guy
Merry Christmas
After years dodging the president's
ban on "immoral biotech research",
My think tank now has a little something in the pipeline.
It's an idea we like to call "Extremis".
I'm gonna turn your lights down.
Regard the human brain
Uh, wait, hold on, hold on; that's,
that's the universe, my bad.
But if I do that...
That's the brain, strangely memetic though,
wouldn't you say?
Wow, that's amazing! - Thanks, it's mine.
What? - This... you're inside my head.
It's a live feed. Come on up, I'll prove it to you.
Come on.
Pinch my arm. I can take it. Pinch me.
What is that? - The primary somatosensory cortex
It's the brain's pain center, but this...
is what I wanted to show you.
Now, "Extremis" harnesses our bioelectrical potential
And it goes... here.
This is essentially an empty slot, and what
this tells us is that our mind, our entire DNA
in fact, is destined to be upgraded. - Wow.
Hello? - Is this forehead of Security?
What? You know, look, I got a real job. What
do you want? I'm working; I got something
going on here. - What? Harassing interns?
Let me tell you something, you know what
happened when I told people I was Iron Man's
bodyguard? They would laugh in my face.
I had to leave while I still had a shred of dignity.
Now I got a real job; I'm watching Pepper.
What's going on? Fill me in.
For real? - Yeah.
Alright, so she's meeting up with this scientist...
rich guy, handsome
I couldn't make his face at first
And you know I'm good with faces.
- Oh yeah, you're the best.
Yeah, so I run his credentials, I make him.
Aldrich Killian. We actually met the guy...
where were we in 1999? The science conference?
Switzerland. - Right, right, exactly.
Killian, I don't remember that guy - Of course you
don't remember; he's not a blonde with a big rack.
At first it was fine, they were talking business, but now
it's like getting weird... he's showing her his big brain.
His what? - Big brain, and she likes it.
Here, let me show you. Hold on. See?
Look at what? You watching them?
Flip the screen and then we can get started.
I'm not a tech genius like you,
just trust me, get down here.
Flip the screen, then I can see what they're doing.
- I don't know how to flip the screen!
Don't talk to me like that anymore. You're not my boss.
Alright, I don't work for you, and I don't trust this guy.
He's got another guy with him; he's shifty.
Relax. I'm just asking you to secure the perimeter.
Tell him to go out for a drink or something.
You know what? You should take more
of an interest in what's going on here.
This woman is the best thing that ever happened to you
And you're just ignoring her. - A giant brain?
Yeah, there's a giant brain, there's a shifty character...
I'm going to follow this guy.
I'm going to run his plates and if it gets rough, so be it.
I miss you, Happy.
- Yeah, I miss you too but the way it used to be.
Now you're off with the 'superfriends'...
I don't know what's going on with you
anymore. The world's gettin' weird
Hey I hate to cut you off, do you have your taser
on you? - Why? - I think there's a gal in HR who
is trying to steal some printer ink. You should
probably go over there and zap her. - Yeah, nice.
Imagine if you could hack into the hard drive
of any living organism and recode its DNA
It would be incredible.
Unfortunately, to my ears it also
sounds highly weaponizable
As in enhanced soldiers,
private armies, and Tony is not-
Tony, Tony
You know, I invited Tony to join AIM
13 years ago and he turned me down
But something tells me now there is a new genius
on the throne, who doesn't have to answer to
Tony anymore and who has slightly less of an ego.
It's going to be a "no", Aldrich...
as much as I'd like to help you.
I can't say that I'm not disappointed,
but as my father used to say
"Failure is the fog through which we glimpse triumph."
It's very deep, and I have no idea what it means.
Well, he was kind of an idiot, my old man.
I'm sure I'll see you again, Pepper.
Happy - The car is ready... if you're ready to go.
Yes, I just um, God,
I forgot my other thing so I'm just gonna...
I'm sorry I'm late. I was... what is that?!
You're wearing this in the house now?
What is that, like Mark 15?
Yeah, something like that.
You know everybody needs a hobby.
Oh, and you have to wear your hobby in the
living room? Just breaking it in, you know, it's
always a little pinchy in the GUI-bagger at first.
Oh hey, did you see your Christmas present?
Yes, I did. I don't know how I could
have missed that Christmas present.
Is it gonna fit through the door? - Well actually,
uh, that's a good question, I got a team of guys
coming tomorrow. They're gonna blow out that wall.
So, uh, tense? Good day?
Oh shoulders, a little naughty. Naughty girl.
I don't want to harp on this,
but did you like the custom rabbit?
Did I like it? - Nailed it, right? - Wow.
I appreciate the thought very much. So why don't
you lift up that facemask and give me a kiss.
Huh, yup, damnit. No can do.
You want to just kiss it on the, uh, facial slit?
Why don't I run down to the garage and see if I
can't find a crowbar to jimmy that thing open?
A crowbar? Yeah...
- Oh, except there's been a radiation leak.
I'll take my chances. - That's risky
At least let me get you like a Hazmat suit
or a Geiger counter or something like that
Busted. - This is a new level of lame.
Sorry. - You ate without me, already?
On date night?
He was just - You mean you
Well yeah, I just mean we were just...
just hosting you while I finished up a little work.
And yes, I had a quick bite.
I didn't know if you were coming home
Or you were having drinks with Aldrich Killian.
What?
Aldrich Killian? What are you checking up on me?
Happy was concerned - No, you're spying on me.
I'm going to bed. - Hold on. Come on. Pep-
Hey, I admit it! My fault. Sorry.
I'm a piping hot mess. It's been going on for a while...
I haven't said anything.
Nothing's been the same since New York. - Oh really?
I didn't notice that, at all.
You experience things and then they're
over and you still can't explain them.
Gods, aliens, other dimensions...
I'm just a man in a can.
The only reason I haven't cracked up
is probably because you've moved in.
Which is great. I love you; I'm lucky.
But honey... I can't sleep.
You go to bed, I come down here.
I do what I know; I tinker.
The threat is imminent.
And I have to protect the one
thing that I can't live without...
That's you.
And my suits; they're uh...
Machines. - They're part of me.
A distraction. - Maybe.
I'm gonna take a shower. - Okay.
And you're going to join me. - Better.
Tony!
Power down!
I must have called it in my sleep...
that's not supposed to happen.
I'll recalibrate the sensors.
Just let me catch my breath, okay?
Don't go, alright? Pepper?
I'm going to sleep downstairs. Tinker with that.
Can you regulate?
- Yes, I can regulate.
Are you sure about that? - Yes.
It's a decent batch.
Don't say I never did nothing for you.
- Thank you... I mean for understanding.
Ah, I'm sorry, buddy.
What're ya doing, buddy?
You out by yourself? A little date night?
Watching your favorite chick flick maybe?
Yeah, a little movie called "The Party's Over"
Starring you and your junkie girlfriend,
and here's the ticket
No kidding... that doesn't belong to you.
Savin! Help! Help me!
A true story about fortune cookies
They look Chinese. They sound Chinese.
But they're actually an American invention
Which is why they're hollow, full of lies,
and leave a bad taste in the mouth
My disciples just destroyed
another cheap American knock-off
The Chinese Theater. Mr. President,
I know this must be getting frustrating
But this season of terror is drawing to a close
And don't worry...
the big one is coming: your graduation.
Hi. - Oh, uh. - Mind leaving that on? - Sure.
- Sunday night's PBS "Downtown Abbey"
That's the show. He thinks it's elegant.
One more thing... make sure everyone wears
their badges. He's a stickler for that sort of thing,
plus my guys won't let anyone in without them.
We're awaiting the arrival of Tony Stark.
We're hoping he'll give us the reaction...
His reaction to the latest attack.
Mr. Stark!
Our sources are telling us that
this is another Mandarin attack.
Anything else you can tell us?
Hey Mr. Stark!
When is somebody going to kill this guy? Just sayin'.
Is that what you want?
Here's a little Holiday greeting I've
been wanting to send to the Mandarin.
I just didn't know how to phrase it until now.
My name is Tony Stark and I'm not afraid of you
I know that you're a coward so I've decided
That you just died, pal.
I'm gonna come get the body.
There's no politics here;
it's just good, old-fashioned revenge.
There's no Pentagon; it's just you and me.
And on the off-chance you're a man,
here's my home address:
10880, Malibu Port, 90265.
I'll leave the door unlocked.
That's what you wanted, right?
Bill me.
I've compiled a Mandarin database for you, sir,
Drawn from S.H.I.E.L.D., F.B.I., and C.I.A. intercepts.
Initiating virtual crime scene reconstruction.
Okay, what do we got here?
His name is an ancient Chinese war mantle
Meaning "advisor to the King"
South American insurgency tactics
Talks like a Bapist preacher
There's lots of pagentry going on here... lots of theatre.
Close. - The heat from the blast was
in excess of 3000 degrees Celsius.
Any subjects within 12.5 yards were vaporized instantly.
No bomb parts found in a 3-mile radius
of the Chinese theatre. - No, sir.
Talk to me, Happy.
When is a bomb not a bomb?
Any military victims?
- Not according to public records, sir.
Bring up the thermogenic signatures again,
factor in 3000 degrees
The oracle cloud has completed analysis.
Accessing satellites and plotting the last 12
months of thermogenic occurances now.
Take away everywhere that
there's been a Mandarin attack.
Nope.
That. You sure that's not one of his?
It predates any known Mandarin attack.
The incident was the use of a bomb to assist a suicide.
The heat signature is remarkably similar.
That's two military guys...
Ever been to Tennessee, Jarvis?
Creating a flight plan for Tennessee.
Are we still at "ding-dong"?
We're supposed to be on total security lockdown.
Come on, I threatened a terrorist. Who is that?
There's only so much I can do, sir,
when you give the world's press your home address.
Right there's fine.
You're not the Mandarin, are you? Are you?
- You don't remember.
Why I am not surprised? - Don't take it personally,
I don't remember what I had for breakfast.
Gluten-free waffles, sir. - That's right.
Look, I need to be alone with you,
someplace not here... it's urgent.
Normally, I'd go for that sort of thing,
but now I'm in a committed relationship
It's... with her. - Tony,
Is somebody there?
- Yeah, it's Maya Hansen.
Old botanist pal that I used to know, barely.
Please don't tell me that there is a 12-year-old
kid waiting in the car that I've never met.
He's 13. No, I need your help. - What for? Why now?
Because I read the papers, and, frankly,
I don't think you'll last the week.
I'll be fine.
I'm sorry.
With Happy in the hospital,
I didn't know we were expecting guests.
We weren't.
And old girlfriends - She's not really.
No, not really. It was just one night.
Yep. - That's how you did it, isn't it?
It was a great night. - Well... you know - Yeah.
You have saved yourself a world of pain.
- What? - Trust me. - I'm sure.
We're going out of town.
Okay, we've been through this. Nope. - Yep!
The man says no - Immediately and indefinitely.
Great idea. Let's go. - I'm sorry.
That's a terrible idea. Please don't touch her bags.
Tony, this is how normal people behave.
- I can't protect you out there. I challenged-
Is this normal? - Sadly, that - Yes, this is normal!
Is very normal - It's a big bunny, relax about it!
Calm down! - I got this for you.
I'm aware of that. - You still haven't even told me
that you liked it! - I don't like it! - I asked you three-
You don't like it?!
We are leaving the house; that's not even up for
discussion. - I said no. - Guys... do we umm...
What? - Do we need to worry about that?
I got you. - I got you first.
Like I said, we can't stay here.
Move! I'm right behind-
Get her, I'm going to find a way around.
Stop stopping! Get her; get outside! Go!
Oh my God. Tony!
Sir, Miss Potts is clear of the structure.
Jarvis, where's my flight power?!
Working on it, sir. This is a prototype.
That's one.
Sir, the suit is not combat-ready.
That's two.
Tony!
Sir, take a deep breath.
Flight power restored.
Sir.
Sir! - Alright, kill the alarm.
That's the emergency alert triggered
by the power dropping below 5 %.
Snow? Where are we, upstate?
We are 5 miles outside of Rose Hills, Tennessee.
Why?!
Jarvis! Not my idea! What are we doing here;
this is thousands of miles away,
I've gotta get Pepper, I've got to-
I prepared a flight plan.
This was the location.
Who asked you? Open the suit.
- I think I may be malfunctioning, sir. - Open eject.
That's brisk!
Maybe I'll just cozy back up for a bit.
- I actually think I need to sleep now, sir.
Jarvis.
Jarvis?
Don't leave me, buddy.
Stark Secure Server:
Now transferring to all known receivers.
Pepper, it's me.
I've got a lot of apologies to make and not a lot of time,
so first off
I'm so sorry I put you in harm's way.
That was selfish and stupid and it won't happen again.
Also, it's Christmas time. The rabbit's too big. Done.
Sorry.
And I'm sorry in advance because...
I can't come home yet
I need to find this guy.
You gotta stay safe. That's all I know.
I just stole a poncho from a wooden Indian.
Let's get you comfy.
You happy now?
Freeze!
Don't move. - You got me.
Nice potato gun.
Barrel's a little long.
Between that and the wide gauge,
it's going to diminish your FPS
And now you're out of ammo.
- What's that thing on your chest?
It's a electromagnet. You should know,
you've got a box of them right here.
What does it power?
Oh my God!
Is that Iron Man? - Technically, I am.
Technically, you're dead.
A valid point. - What happened to him?
Life. I built him; I take care of him.
I'll fix him.
Like a mechanic. - Yeah.
If I was building Iron Man and War Machine,
It's Iron Patriot now. - That's way cooler!
No, it's not.
Anyway, I would have added in the retro-
Retroreflective panels? - To make him stealth mode.
You want a stealth mode? - Cool, right?
That's actually a good idea.
Maybe I'll build one.
Not a good idea!
What are you doing? You're going to break his finger?
He's in pain; he's been injured. Leave him alone.
Sorry. - Are you?
Don't worry about it; I'll fix it.
So, uh, who's home? - Well, my mom already left for
the diner and dad went to 7-11 to get scratchers.
I guess he won 'cause that was six years ago.
Which happens, dads leave. No need to
be a pussy about it. Here's what I need:
a laptop, a digital watch, a cell phone,
The pneumatic actuator from your bazooka over there,
a map of town, a big spring, and a tunafish sandwich.
What's in it for me? - Salvation. What's his name?
Who?
- The kid that bullies you at school, what's his name?
How'd you know that?
I got just the thing.
This is a pinata for a cricket. I'm kidding;
it's a very powerful weapon. Point it away
from your face, press the button on top,
It discourages bullying.
Non-lethal
Deal. Deal? What'd you say? - Deal.
What's your name? - Harley
And you're? - The mechanic
Tony
You know what keeps going through my head?
Where's my sandwich?
Stark Secure Server - Retinal scan verified.
Pepper, it's me.
I've got a lot of apologies to make and not a lot of time,
so first off
I'm so sorry I put you in harm's way.
That was selfish and stupid and it won't happen again.
Why were you at the house tonight?
What was so important that you had to speak to Tony?
I think that my boss is working for the Mandarin.
So if you still want to talk about it,
I suggest we get ourselves someplace safe
Your boss works for the Mandarin you think,
but Tony says you're a botanist
That figures. What I actually am is a biological DNA
coder running a team of 40 out of a privately-funded
think tank, but sure you can call me a "botanist"
This boss of yours, does he have a name?
Yeah, Aldrich Killian.
Well we took the house down sir,
but there's no sign of a body.
I see. - No Stark.
I have to go.
The Master is about to record and he's a little...
Well you know how he gets.
Keep your appointment tonight
and call me when it's done.
Alright everybody. No talking and no eye contact,
unless you wanna get shot in the face.
The Master is travelling.
Well then, what are we waiting for?
The sandwich was fair, the spring was a little rusty,
the rest of the materials I'll make do
By the way, when you said your sister had a watch,
I was kinda hoping for something a little more than that
She's six! Anyway, it's limited edition.
When can we talk about New York?
- Maybe never, relax about it.
What about the Avengers, can you talk about them?
- I don't know; later.
Hey kid, give me more space.
What's the official story here? What happened?
I guess this guy named Chad Davis,
used to live roundabouts
Won a bunch of medals in the army,
One day, folks said he went crazy and made,
you know, a bomb
Then he blew himself up right here.
Six people died, right? - Yes.
Including Chad Davis? - Yea.
Doesn't make sense.
Think about it. Six dead, only five shadows.
Yeah, but people said these shadows are
like the mark of souls gone to Heaven
Except the bomb guy,
he went to Hell on account of he didn't get a shadow.
That's why there's only five - Do you buy that?
That's what everyone says.
You know what this crater reminds me of?
- I have no idea; I don't care.
That giant wormhole, in um, in New York.
Does it remind you?
- That's manipulative. I don't want to talk about it.
Are they coming back? The aliens?
- Maybe, can you stop?
Remember when I told you that I have an anxiety issue?
Does this subject make you edgy? - Yeah, a little bit.
Can I just catch my breath for a second?
- Are there bad guys in Rose Hills?
Do you need a plastic bag to breathe into?
Do you have medication?
- Nope.
Do you need to be on it?
- Probably.
Do you have PTSD?
- I don't think so.
Are you going completely mental?
I can stop, do you want me to stop?
Remember when I said to stop doing that?
I swear to God, you're going to freak me out.
Ah man, you did it, didn't you? You happy now?
- What did I say?
Hey, wait up! Wait, wait.
What the hell was that?
- Your fault, you spazzed me out.
Okay, back to business. Where were we?
The guy who died... relatives?
Mom? Ms. Davis, where is she?
Where she always is. - See, now you're being helpful.
Sorry. Lady, this uh,
Thank you - Nice haircut, suits you.
Nice watch. - Yeah, limited edition.
Oh, I don't doubt it.
Well have a good evening.
Ms. Davis,
Mind if I join you?
Free country.
- It sure is.
Alright
Where'd you like to start?
- I just want to say I'm sorry about your loss.
I want to know what you think happened
I brought your damn file. You take it and go.
Whatever was in here, he wanted no part of it.
Clearly, you were waiting for someone else.
Supposed to meet somebody here?
Yeah.
Ms. Davis, your son didn't kill himself; I guarantee
you he didn't kill anyone. Someone used him.
What? - As a weapon
You're not the person who called me after all, are you?
Actually, I am.
Hey, hey! What's all this about?
The hell's going on here?
It's called an arrest.
Sheriff, is it? - Yes ma'am, it is. And you are?
Homeland Security. We good here?
- No, we're not good.
I need a little more information than that.
- Well, I think it's a little above your pay grade, Sheriff.
Yeah, well, why don't you get on the
horn to Nashville and upgrade me?
Alright, you know what,
I was hoping to do this the smart way, but uh,
The fun way's always good
Deputy, get this woman and-
Hey hot wings, you wanna party? You and me, let's go.
Crazy, huh? - Yeah.
Watch this.
You walked right into this one;
I've dated hotter chicks than you.
That's all you got? Cheap trick and a cheesy one-liner?
Sweetheart, that could be the
name of my autobiography.
Let me go! - Help me! Help me!
Hey kid, what would you like for Christmas?
- Mr. Stark, I am so sorry.
No, no,
I think he was trying to say "I want my goddamn file."
It's not your fault kid.
Remember what I told you about bullies?
You like that, West World?
That's the thing about smart guys
We always cover our ass.
You're welcome!
For what? Did I miss something? - Me saving your life.
A: Saved you first, B: Thanks, sort of
And C: If you do someone a solid,
don't be a yutz alright, just play it
cool otherwise you come off grandiose
Unlike you?
Admit it: you need me. We're connected.
What I need is for you to go home, be with your mom,
keep your mouth shut, and protect the suit.
And stay connected to the telephone
because if I call you better pick up. Okay?
Can you feel that? We're done here.
Move out of the way or I'm going to run you over.
Bye kid.
I'm sorry kid. You did good. - So now you're
just going to leave you here, like my dad?
Yeah. Wait, you're guilt-tripping me, aren't you?
- I'm cold
I can tell. You know how I can tell?
'Cause we're connected.
It was worth a shot.
What happened to the picture?
The entire East coast... the satellites are down.
We have an unauthorized broadcast
Mr. Vice President, I think you should see this
Oh my God, not again. Is the President getting this?
Mr. President
Only two lessons remain.
I intend to finish this before Christmas morning.
Meet Thomas Richards.
Good strong name, good strong job.
Thomas here is an accountant
for the Roxxon Oil Corporation
And I'm sure he's a really good guy.
I'm going to shoot him in the head,
live on your television, in 30 seconds.
The number for this telephone is in your cell phone.
Exciting, isn't it?
Imagining how it got there
America, if your president calls me
in the next half-minute, Tom lives.
Go.
How did he hack my phone?
- We can't allow terrorists to dictate-
I have to make this call.
- I'd strongly advise against that.
This is the right thing to do.
There's just one lesson left, President Ellis,
so run away and kiss your children goodbye
Because nothing, not your army, not your red, white,
and blue attack dog, can save you.
I'll see you soon.
Tell Rhodes, find this lunatic right now
- Sir, we tracked the broadcast signal.
We have a possible point of origin in Pakistan and
the Patriot is ready to strike. - Right now! - Yes, sir.
Don't move!
Uh, hang on a second.
Hello. - You ever look up and everything starts
glowing from the inside out, a kind of bright orange
Yeah, I've had that. Who is this? - It's me, pal.
Now last time I went missing,
if I remember correctly, you went looking for me.
What are you doing? A little talking,
making friends in Pakistan. - What are you doing?
Your re-design, your big re-brand, that was AIM, right?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna find a heavy-duty comsat right now,
I need your login.
Same as it's always been, War Machine 68.
- And password please?
Well, look, I gotta change it every time you
hack in, Tony - It's not the eighties, nobody
says "hack" anymore, give me your login.
"War Machine Rox" with an X, all caps.
Yeah okay. - That is so much better than Iron Patriot.
That ain't gonna cut it.
Excuse me sir, I don't know who...
Mom, I need to call you back,
something magical is happening.
Tony Stark is in my van. - Keep it down.
- Tony Stark is in my van! - No, he's not.
I knew you were still alive!
- Come on in and close the door.
Wow, can I just say sir? - Yeah.
I am your biggest fan.
- First, is this your van or is anyone else gonna come in?
No, no, it's just us. - What's your name?
Gary. - Gary. - Oh wow.
Right there's fine. I get a lot of this, it's okay.
- Can I just say?
Yeah. - I don't know if you can tell but I have like
Patterned my whole look after you. My hair's a little,
it's not right because there's some product in it
Right.
I don't want to make things awkward for you
- No. - But I do have to show you... boom!
Hispanic Scott Baio?
Oh, I'm sorry, is that me? - Yeah.
It's... I mean. I had them do it off a doll that I made,
so it's not like it's off a picture. So it's a little bit-
Jerry, for a moment, listen to me here.
I don't want to clip your wings here;
we're both a little over-excited.
I have an issue. I'm chasing bad guys, trying to grapple
with something from some hard-crypt data files.
I don't have enough juice.
I need you to jump on the roof, recalibrate the ISDNs
Pump it up by about 40 %.
- Got it. - Alright, it's a mission.
Tony needs Gary
and Gary needs Tony - Be quiet about it.
Go.
What would you regard as the
defining moment of your life?
Well uh, I think that would be the day
I decided not to let my injury beat me.
Can you please state your name for the camera?
- Ellen Brandt.
Okay, so, the injections are administered periodically.
Addiction will not be tolerated and those who
cannot regulate will be cut from the program.
Once misfits, cripples...
you are the next iteration of human evolution.
Hi everybody. Before we start, I promise you,
looking back at your life there will be nothing
as bitter as the memory of that glorious
risk that you prudently elected to forego
Today is your glory. Let's begin!
We gotta get out of here! Gotta get out of here!
Get 'em out! Get 'em out of here!
A bomb is not a bomb when it's a misfire
This stuff doesn't always work, right, pal?
It's faulty, but you found a buyer, didn't ya?
Sold it to the Mandarin.
What happened? Fun fact
Before he built rockets for the Nazis
The idealistic Werner von Braun
dreamed of space travel... he stargazed
You know what he said when the first V2 hit London?
The rocket performed perfectly
It just landed on the wrong planet.
See we all begin wide-eyed... "pure science"
Then the ego steps in, the obsession
And when you look up, you're a long way from shore
You can't be too hard on yourself, Maya.
I mean you gave your research to a think tank.
Yeah but Killian built that think tank on military
contracts - That's exactly what we used to do
So don't judge yourself
Thank you, Pepper.
I really appreciate that.
Hi, good evening - Good evening. - Come on in.
Maya, run!
Hi Pepper.
So you want to tell me why you
were at Stark's manison last night?
I'm trying to fix this thing. I didn't know you
and the Master were gonna blow the place up.
Oh I see, so you were trying to save Stark... when he
threatened us - I told you, Killian, we can use him.
Pepper, Pepper, Pepper - Look if we want
to launch product next year, I need Stark.
He just lacked a decent incentive. Now he has one.
This is Support Team Blue 0, sending coordinates
for suspected Mandarin broadcast point of origin.
Copy.
Nobody move!
Support Blue 0, unless the Mandarin's next
attack on the U.S. involves cheaply-made
sportswear, I think you messed up again.
Yes, you're free, if you weren't before. Yes ma'am
Iron Patriot on the job, happy to help,
no need to thank me, it's my pleasure.
Savin, I've acquired the Patriot armor.
You want this suit? You're going ot have to pry my cold,
dead body out of it.
That's the plan, Colonel.
Harley, tell me what is happening, give me
a full report - Yeah, I'm still eating that
candy, do you want me to keep eating it?
How much did you have? - Two or three bowls.
Can you still see straight? - Sort of.
- That means you're fine, give me Jarvis.
Jarvis, how are we? - It's totally fine sir. I seem
to do quite well for a stretch and then at the
end of the sentence I say the wrong cranberry.
And sir, you were right. Once I factored in
available AIM downlink facilities I was able
to pinpoint the Mandarin's broadcast signal.
What're we talkin'? The Far East, Europe,
North Africa, Iran, Pakistan, Syria, where is it?
Actually, sir, it's in Miami.
Okay, kid, I'm going to have to walk you
through rebooting Jarvis' speech drive, but
not right now. Harley, where is he really?
Just look on the screen and tell me where it is.
It does say Miami, Florida
- Okay, first things first, I need the armor.
Where are we at with it? - Uh, it's not charging.
Actually, sir, it is charging,
but the power source is questionable.
It may not succeed in revitalizing the Mark 42.
What's questionable about electricity?
Alright, it's my suit and I can't... I'm not gonna...
Oh God, not again. - Tony
Are you having another attack? I didn't even
mention New York. - Right, and then you just
said it, by name, while denying having said it.
Okay, um, uh
Oh God, what am I gonna do?
- Just breathe, really just breathe
You're a mechanic, right? - Right.
You said so. - Yes, I did.
What don't you just build something?
Okay, thanks kid.
Why is it so hot in here? I told you to put it at 68.
My fault again... let me tell you something sweetheart,
I am not your personal-
I wouldn't go in there for twenty minutes!
Now, which one of you is Vanessa?
Ah, Nessie
Did you know that fortune cookies aren't even Chinese?
- There's some guy over here-
They're made by Americans,
based on the Japanese recipes
Hey! - Bloody hell, bloody hell - Don't move.
If you want something, take it, although the
guns are all fake because those wankers
wouldn't trust me with the real ones.
What? - Hey, do you fancy either of the birds?
You're not him, the Mandarin, the real guy, where?!
Where's the Mandarin?! Where is he?!
- He's here. He's here.
But he's not here. He's here but he's not here.
- What do you mean?
It's complicated, hey, it's complicated, alright?
- It is? - It's complicated.
Uncomplicate it. Ladies out,
get out of the bed, get in the bathroom.
Sit.
My name is Trevor, Trevor Slattery. - What are you?
What're you a decoy? You're a double, right?
- What? No. An understudy? Absolutely not.
Don't hurt me please! I'm an actor.
You got a minute to live, fill it with words.
- It's just a role. "The Mandarin", see, it's not real.
Then how did you get here, Trevor?
Um, well, uh, I have a little problem
with, um, substances, and I ended up
doing things... no two ways about it
In the street that a man shouldn't do - Next!
Then, they approached me about the
role and they knew about the drugs
What'd they say they'd get you off them?
- Said they'd give me more
They gave me things. They gave me this palace.
They gave me plastic surgery. They gave me things.
Did you just nod off?
No, the lovely speedboat!
And the thing was, he needed someone
To take credit for some "accidental explosions"
"He"?
Killian? - Killian.
He created you? - He created me.
Custom-made terror threat - Yes!
Yes, his think tank thinked it up,
the pathology of the serial killer
The manipulation of Western iconography
Ready for another lesson? Blah blah blah.
Of course, it was my performance
that brought the Mandarin to life.
Your performance? Where people die?
No, no, look around you, costumes, green screen
Honestly, I wasn't on location for half this stuff,
and when I was, movie magic, love
I'm sorry but I got a best friend who's
in a coma and he might not wake up
So you're going to have to answer for that.
You're still going down, pal.
Okay, Trevor, what'd you tell him?
- I didn't tell him anything.
Nothing?
No. - You should have pressed the panic button.
Well I panicked, but then I handled it.
Just like old times, huh?
- Oh yeah, with zip-ties. It's a ball.
It wasn't my idea. - Okay, so you took Killian's card
I took his money
- and here you are 13 years later in a dungeon
No. - Yeah.
No, you're in a dungeon. I'm free to go. - Yeah...
A lot's happened Tony and I'm close.
Extremis is pratically stable. - I'm telling you it isn't.
I saw him on the street, people are going 'bang',
they're painting the walls. Maya, you're kidding yourself.
Then help me fix it.
Did I do that?
Yes. - I remember the night, not the morning
Is this what you've been chasing around?
- You don't remember? - I can't help you.
You used to have a moral psychology.
You used to have ideals.
Wanted to help people, now look at you.
I get to wake up every morning with someone who...
still has a soul.
Get me out of here, come on
You know what my old man used to say to me?
His favorite of many sayings
"The early bird gets the worm;
the second mouse gets the cheese"
You're not still pissed about the Switzerland thing,
are you? - How can I be pissed you, Tony?
You've given me the greatest gift
that anybody's ever given me.
Desperation. If you think back to Switzerland,
you said you'd meet me on the rooftop, right?
Well for the first 20 minutes, I actually thought
you'd show up. For the next hour, I uhh
Well I considered taking that one step
shortcut to the lobby, if you know I mean
Honestly, I'm still trying to figure out
what happened to the first mouse.
But as I looked out over that city, nobody knew I was
there, nobody could see me, no one was even looking
I had a thought that would guide me for years to come.
Anonymity, Tony.
Thanks to you, it's been my mantra ever since, right?
You simply rule from behind the scenes.
Because the second you give evil a face
Bin Laden, Gaddafi, The Mandarin
You hand the people a target - You're something else
You have met him, I assume?
- Yeah, Sir Lawrence Oblivion.
I know he's a little over the top sometimes...
it's not entirely my fault
He has a tend... he's a stage actor.
They say his Lear was the toast of Croydon,
wherever that is.
Anyway, the point is ever since that big
dude with the hammer fell out of the sky
Subtlety's kinda had its day
What's next for you in your world?
Well, I wanted to repay you for the same
gift you so graciously imparted to me
Desperation. Now, this is live.
I'm not sure if you can tell
But at this moment the body is trying to decide
whether to accept Extremis or just give up
And if it gives up,
I have to say the denotation is quite spectactular
But until that point, it's really just a lot of pain.
We haven't even talked salary yet.
What kind of perk package are you thinking of?
- Let him go.
Hold on, hold on. Maya - I said let him go
What are you doing?
- 1200ccs, a dose half of this size and I'm dead
It's times like this my temper is tested somewhat
Maya, give me the injector.
If I die Killian, what happens to your soldiers?
What happens to your product?
We're not doing this, okay? - What happens to you?
What happens if you go too hot?
The good news is,
a high level position has just been vacated
You're a maniac. - No, I'm a visionary
But I do own a maniac, and he takes the stage tonight
When we get the Iron Patriot,
it'll take me nine to ten minutes to disassemble it.
That's great.
The last time I looked there was somebody inside of it.
Good evening, gentlemen
Hello Colonel
Step aside.
We'll get you out of there, don't worry.
- You'll damage the armor.
Yes, I will, but you can fix it, right?
I'm going to take the suit up to base camp,
and I want Potts with me.
She's still in Phase 2.
You're not going deaf, are ya?
Careful there, it's a limited edition.
Hey, uh, ponytail express
What is the mileage count between
Tennessee and Miami? - 832 miles
Very nice.
Are you gonna stop that? - Break it you bought it
Okay, that wasn't mine to give away, that belongs to
my friend's sister, and that's why I'm gonna kill you first.
What're ya gonna do to me? - You'll see.
You're zip-tied to a bed. - This.
That.
Are you comin' out?
Do not open, do not open, don't open,
don't open, don't- Alright, let's go.
You breathe fire? Okay.
It's a glorious day, Savin.
This time tomorrow I'll have the West's
most powerful leader in one hand
And the world's most feared terrorist in the other.
I'll own the War on Terror
Creates supply and demand for
you and your brothers and sisters.
Trust me, you're going in a puddle of blood
on the ground in 5, 4, 3, Come on!, 2
How did we get this shit? - Alright, I'm going to give
you a chance to escape, put down your weapons
And tie yourselves into those chairs and I'll let you live.
In 5, 4
You should be gone by now, you should have
already been gone. - I'm just beyond terrified.
Here it comes.
3, 4
Shut up. - 54321
I told you.
Where's the rest?
Honestly, I hate working here... they are so weird.
Better late than never.
Not this time. Not the face.
Phew, it's good to be back. Hello, by the way.
- Oh, hello sir.
All personnel, Stark is loose and somewhere
in the compound. Repeat: Stark is
loose and somewhere in the compound.
Ah, crap.
Tony - Rudy, tell me that was you in the suit.
No, you got yours?
- Uh, um, kind of. Main house as fast as you can,
Somebody I'd like you to meet
You, you. Move! Get out!
The room is secure. I have eyes on the Mandarin.
- What's this? I had winner's.
What've you come as?
- Make a move and I'll break your face.
I never thought people had been hurt. They lied to me.
This is the Mandarin? - I know, it's, it's embarrassing.
Hi, I'm Trevor, Trevor Slattery.
I know I'm shorter in person, I'm a bit small, everyone
says that, but, uh, hey, if you're here to arrest
me, there are some people who I'd like to rat on
Here's how it works,
you tell him where Pepper is and he'll stop doing it.
Stop what? Well, I understand
I do not know (Piper) but I know the plan
Occur - Do you know what who did Bhlta?
No, but Shaddt the beach when something related
to a large compound Bomkanni pick you up there
Tony, I swear to God, I'm going to blow his face off.
Oh this next bit may include the Vice President as well.
Is that important? - Somewhat. - Yeah, a little bit.
So? - Uh, what are we gonna do.
We don't have any transport.
Hey, Ringo,
didn't you say something about a "lovely speedboat"?
If he's right about the location, we're 20 minutes
from where Pepper is. - But we also have to
figure out this Vice President thing, right?
I wonder who I'm calling right now.
Oh, that's the Vice President.
Hello. - Sir, this is Tony Stark.
Welcome back to the land of the living. - We
believe you're about to be drawn into the
Mandarin campaign, and we've got to get
you somewhere safe as soon as possible.
Mr. Stark, I'm about to eat honey roast
ham surrounded by the agency's finest.
And the President is safe on Air
Force One with Colonel Rhodes
I think we're good here. - Sir, this is Colonel Rhodes!
They're using the Iron Patriot as a trojan horse;
they're gonna take out the President somehow.
We have to immediately alert that plane.
Okay, I'm on it. I'll have security lock it
down. If need be, they can have F22s in
the air in 30 seconds. Thank you, Colonel.
Rhodes and Stark out.
Everything okay, sir? - Couldn't be better.
I love you, little one
Colonel Rhodes. Glad to see you could make it, son.
I feel safer already
We gotta make a decision. We can either save
the President or Pepper. We can't do both.
Sir, I have an update from Malibu.
The cranes have finally arrived and the
cellar doors are being cleared as we speak.
And what about the suit I'm wearing?
- The armor is now at 92 %.
That's gonna have to do.
Oh, here he comes, here he comes, get a quick picture.
- Sure.
Is everything all right, Colonel?
It is an honor, Mr. President
If you're gonna do it, do it.
That's not how the Mandarin works. - Sir.
Air Force One's been compromised.
Internal shots, temperature spikes. - Get me
eyes on it now. - Image coming through now, sir.
Is that Rhodes?
The President. Now.
He's not here.
Try the jet stream. Speaking of which, go fish!
Walk away from that, you son of a bitch.
How many in the air? - Thirteen, sir.
How many can I carry? - Four, sir.
Slow down, slow down.
Relax, what's your name? Heather..
Listen, see that guy? I'm going to swing
by him and you're just going to grab him.
You got it?
I'll electrify your arm; you won't be able to
open your hand. You can do this, Heather.
Easy, see? Eleven more to go.
Remember that game called Barrel of Monkeys?
That's what we're going to do.
18,000 feet - Come on, everybody, grab your monkey!
Nice! - 10,000 feet.
6,000 feet - Come on, people.
Come on, come on, come on
Yeah! - 1000 feet.
800 feet. 200 feet, sir.
- It's a tricky monkey, let's get him.
Hello.
Nice work guys. Excellent.
Good team effort all around. Go us.
Alright, Jarvis, but it's only half done,
we still gotta get Pepp-
That came out of nowhere.
Gimme some good news man.
- I think they all made it. - Thank God.
Yeah, but I missed the President.
You couldn't save the President with the suit,
how are you gonna save Pepper without it?
Uh, say Jarvis, is it that time?
- The "house party" protocol, sir?
Correct.
Hi.
You think he's gonna help you... he won't.
Having you here is not just to motivate Tony Stark;
it's actually more embarrassing than that.
You're here as my, um - Trophy.
Good evening, sir.
Welcome aboard, Mr. President.
You ever heard of an elephant graveyard? Well, two
years ago, the elephant in the room was this ship.
This is the Roxxon Norco.
Of course you remember when she spilled
100 million gallons of crude off Pensacola.
Thanks to you, not one fat cat saw a day in court.
What do you want from me?
Uh, nothing, sir.
I just needed a reason to kill
you that would play well on TV.
You see, I've moved on.
I've found myself a new political patron, and
At this time tomorrow, he'll have your job.
String him up.
Come on.
You're not gonna freak out on me, right?
- I hope not.
Oh my god.
He's strung up over the oil tank;
they're gonna light him up, man. - Viking funeral.
Public execution.
- Yeah, death by oil.
Broadcast will commence shortly. Take final positions.
Okay, that's great. Now give me cameras
A through E and do a full tech rehearsal.
Is your gun up?
Yup, what do I do? - Stay on my six, cover high,
and don't shoot me in the back. - Six, high, back. Alright.
You see that? Nailed it.
- Yeah, you really killed the glass.
I was aiming for the bulb?
You can't hit a bulb from this distance.
I'm out. Gimme, gimme, you got an extra magazine?
- They're not universal, Tony.
I know what I'm doing, I make this stuff. Gimme
another one. - I don't have one that fits that gun.
You've got like five of them. Alright, here's
what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna spot. Ready?
What'd you see? - Too fast, nothing. Here we go.
Three guys, one girl, all armed.
God, I'd kill for some armor right now.
- You're right, we need backup. - Yeah, much.
You know what?
Is that?
- Yep.
Are those?
- Yeah.
Merry Christmas, buddy.
Jarvis, target Extremis heat signatures.
Disable with extreme prejudice. - Yes, sir.
What are you waiting for? It's Christmas.
Take 'em to church.
Jarvis, get Igor to steady this thing.
This is how you've been managing your downtime, huh?
- Everybody needs a hobby.
Heartbreaker? Help Red Snapper out, will ya?
Nice timing.
- Oh yeah, that's awesome. Give me a suit, okay?
Oh, I'm sorry. They're only coded to me.
What's that mean?
- I got you covered.
Good evening, Colonel. Can I give you a lift?
- Very funny.
Sir, I've located Miss Potts.
- About time.
Stop, put it down, put it down, put it down.
See what happens when you
hang out with my ex-girlfriends?
You're such a jerk.
- Yup, we'll talk about it at dinner.
Come on, a little more, baby.
Is this guy bothering you?
Don't get up!
Is it hot there?
Stuck? Feel a little stuck?
Like a little turtle, cooking in his little turtle suit?
Tony
She's watching.
I think you should close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes; you don't want to see this.
Yeah, you take a minute.
Jarvis, give me a suit right now!
Aw, come on!
Mr. President! Just hold on, alright? I'm coming.
Just hold on. Hold on.
Buh-bye.
Brace yourself!
You look damn good, Mr.
President, but I'm gonna need that suit back.
The President is secure, Tony.
I'm clearing the area.
Nice work. - Ready sir?
- What do you mean "ready"?
Pep, I got you. Relax, I got you. Just look at me.
Honey, I can't reach any further,
and you can't stay there, alright? You gotta let go.
You gotta let go. I'll catch you, I promise.
What a shame; I would have caught her.
Well here we are, on the roof
Mark 42 inbound. - Well I'll be damned.
The prodigal son returns.
Whatever.
You really didn't deserve her, Tony.
It's a pity.
I was so close to having her... perfect.
Okay, okay, wait, wait, slow down, slow down.
Okay, you're right. I don't deserve her.
But here's where you're wrong:
She was already perfect.
Jarvis, do me a favor and blow Mark 42.
NOOOO!
No more false faces.
You said you wanted the Mandarin.
You're looking right at him.
It was always me, Tony,
right from the start. I am the Mandarin!
I got nothing.
Jarvis, subject at my 12 o'clock
is not a target, disengage!
What? Oh, what, are you mad at me?
Honey.
Oh, my god.
I was really violent.
You just scared the devil out of me. I thought you were
- I was dead. Why? Because I fell two hundred feet?
Who's the hot mess now?
- Still debatable.
Probably tipping your way a little bit.
Why don't you dress like this at home?
Hmm? Sports bra, the whole deal.
You know I think I understand why
you don't want to give up the suits.
What I am gonna complain about now?
Well, it's me. I'll think of something.
Don't touch me. No, I'm gonna burn you! - No, no
You're not hot.
Am I gonna be okay?
No, you're in a relationship with me,
everything will never be okay.
But I think I can figure this out, yeah.
I almost had this 20 years ago when I was drunk.
I think I can get you better.
That's what I do. I fix things.
And all your distractions?
Uh, I'm gonna shave them down a little bit.
Jarvis, hey.
- All wrapped up here, sir. Will there be anything else?
You know what to do.
The "clean slate" protocol, sir?
Screw it, it's Christmas. Yes, yes.
Okay so far? You like it?
It'll do.
And so, as Christmas morning began,
my journey had reached its end.
You start with something pure, something exciting
Then come the mistakes
The compromises
We create our own demons.
It's great to see you.
As promised, I got Pepper sorted out;
it took some tinkering.
But then I thought to myself,
"Why stop there?"
Of course,
there are people who say progress is dangerous.
But I'll bet none of those idiots ever
had to live with a chest full of shrapnel.
And now... neither will I.
Let me tell you: that was the best sleep I'd had in years.
It's okay, it's okay. - No!
So if I were to wrap this up
tight with a bow or whatever,
I guess I'd say my armor was
never a distraction or a hobby.
It was a cocoon.
And now, I'm a changed man.
You can take away my house,
All my tricks and toys
One thing you can't take away...
I am Iron Man.