Original Subs: Tarafa@alkadah.com
Tranlated Subs: Kaizer
Tales of a legendary warrior
Who's kungfu skills with the stuff of legend
He traveled the land
in search of worthy foes
I see you like to chew
Maybe you would like to chew
on my face!
The warrior said nothing
for his mouth was full
then he swallowed
then he spoke
enough talk! Lets fight!
He was so deadly in fact that
his enemies would go blind
exposure to pure awesomness
How can we repay you?
There is no charge to awesomness
or attractiveness
It mattered not to how many foes he faced
they measured not to his bodacity
"there is no need by" Banda  Mohab
and beloved
even the most powerful heroes  in China
five Angry  We respected teacher and a great
must spend time together
Agree
but spend time await
it while facing thousands of 10000  demons of the mountain
... There is one thing of interest .... is
conduct than the work
Bo) conduct)
Why do you have?
NONE
(monkey), (Mantis)  (stork)
(snake), (Tigress)
Bo) to go)  late to work
coming
Unfortunately, Pope
word, unfortunately, are not Noodle Soup
What were you doing there  what all this uproar?
dreamed crazy dream
what?  How would you dream of?
why ...
... I dream of b
barley
barley?  you dream of barley?
Yes, I dream of what other?
Warning
my son finally had a dream Noodle
do not know how much I was waiting for this moment
this reference
reference Why?
you ready to be reliable  component secret
Soup for the secret
and then will or your sorrow  and manage the restaurant
who received from his father  who received from his father hired by friend and has done
Papa was just a dream
No, it was important to dream
barley in the veins
But Papa pain ... Is to do something else?
addition to the Noodle
in fact, when I was young and crazy  I started to run away
"and learn how to prepare" Toe Foo
Why not done?
because it was just a silly dream
you can not imagine that I am prepared "Toe Fu"?
"Toe Foo"
all of us our place in this world
and my place here  and Place
know here
No, go to the table 5, 7 and 12
service with a smile
Hey, students
If you were trying Viejo I think
Tigress), more speed)
monkey) top speed)
stork) high)  snake) rush)
(Mantis) -  (teacher (Shiva --
Why?
teacher (Togo) wants to see you
teacher (Togo) demand?  Is there a problem?
why there is a problem  so I want to see my old friend
If no problem?
did not say this
you say
We are haunted by a vision
Tai Long) will return)
this impossible  is in prison
nothing is impossible
Zeng 00:06:43:10 00:06:48:07) wing of the prison)  and ask them to redouble guard
redouble weapons  redouble everything
Tai Long) would not leave the prison)
lectured milestone
one meets its destiny on the road  chosen by the
must do something  can not leave, walking in the Valley
and revenge
reason of such water, my friend  when disturbed
becomes difficult vision
but if left stabilizes  answer becomes clear
Lviv Dragon
time
but it? Who is qualified to be  reliable secret of boundless power
to become combatants Dragon
do not know
extremes
Warning -  sorry --
Unfortunately 00:07:43:22 00:07:45:06
Why?
teacher (Togo) chooses  Dragon Warrior today
everyone go  Palace good
one of the five will happen  Scroll to the Dragon
I waited for a thousand years for this
Go
the greatest day in the history of the Congo Fu  Go
Bo) Where To Go?)
"to the" good
but you forgot cart barley
entire valley there will be  and you will sell them all barley
sell barley?
but my father I was thinking -  yes --
I was thinking 00:08:21:20 00:08:23:25
we can sell beans  before they spoil
This is my son
I told you that the dream of a reference
Yes  I'm glad I saw
almost out
Why?
not
sorry you shouted  I will bring you commemoration
No, I go to you in commemoration
that wonderful day
well as teacher Alice (Togo)?
Yes 00:09:50:07 00:09:51:17
and will not live to see
Do your students ready?
(Yes teacher (Togo
Warning, my friend, who chose  will not bring peace, according to Valley
but also you
to start the competition
No, wait  my way
open the door
Turkish Enter
you, the citizens and led peace
honour to extend to you  (Tigress), (snake)
(stork), (monkey)  (Mantis)
five Angry
of preparing warriors
thousand tons of fire
to see this
You Get
(and finally tagged (Tigress
believe me, you citizens  did not see anything yet
Learn 00:12:06:03 00:12:07:21
tagged (Tigress) facing unarmed  swords death
felt that our Dragon Warrior
you, the citizens and led peace
teacher (Togo) will choose now  Dragon Warrior
not wait
What are you doing?
What seems I do?
stopped  go to see the Dragon Warrior
but I do not understand  I have dreamed a dream finally barley
has lied  not dream of barley Pope
love Kung Fu
Come on, Beni  to prepare for action
Well 00:13:43:14 00:13:46:03
What is being?
... Where
to indicate why?
Well, unfortunately, 00:14:26:24 00:14:31:22  I wanted to see who is the Dragon Warrior
This is an interesting
milestone Are you referring to me?
is -  from? --
you -  I? --
universe send us Dragon Warrior
Why? -  Why? --
Why?
stopped waited  ... Who told you
teacher (Togo) Wait
this "Banda" can not be the solution to our problem
(I was about to refer to (Tigress  and fell in front of this thing
was just a coincidence
no coincidence
plight of any teacher  have deserted
"No, if no surrender" Banda  morning with solutions
I'm the one who I would be letting down
wait
(brought a letter from the teacher (Chivu
Why? Doubled guard  backup safety procedures
prison may not be safe?
questioning the security of prisons?
both certainly  Chevy) of the question, I'm just a messenger
(I will give you a message for teachers (Chivu
escape from prison, "Chordam" impossible
impressive is not it?
this very impressive
one way to enter  and one way out
A guard and one prisoner
(yes, but this is a prisoner (Tai Long
took me down
(witness (Tai Long
wait here
none Concerned about  completely secure place
Dear forces you heard?  Togo) to finally give Dragon Scroll of a person)
and you will not be
What are you doing?  does not make it angry
and what he will do?  has made him totally immobile
Is planted on the tail, small Zareef?
Well, I saw enough  will say l (Chevy) that there is nothing to worry him
both no
I will tell him this
wait
I think there is a small error
... Everyone thought I
Hall holy fighters
impossible
Look for this place
shield (for what to where) the teacher
I thought that damaged
Saif Champions
said to be very sharp, so  wounded seen
Shaft much unseen
I saw the paintings of this painting just
not
jar legendary ex Ham
said to contain the lives of the army of "ecstasy" whole
Hello -  Is Terminated vision? --
unfortunately he should come to see you I.
Sabri running out
if you were not going to somewhere
turn -  certainly --
someone break this , but I fittest
parents .. Glue
if you are legendary warrior?
think so -  error --
am not a belligerent dragon and will never be  even learn the secret of the Dragon Scroll
how successful this?  Deek peace? Or Trumblin?
believes that the matter so easily?  I recognize the secret of force untold
not
First you have to master the highest  level of Kong Fu
And this of course is impossible for a person like you
person like me?
Yes, you see  fleshy
and this silly Potbelly
addition to the complete neglect of personal hygiene
waited for this little Hardwood
does not stop at this proximity  I can smell yourself
Togo) said that I)
(maintained finger (Ho Chi
Alamsake know this?
(developed by the teacher (Ho Chi  in the third generation ... Yes
You must know what is happening  while Eloy finger
not
You know what the hardest part?  door is clean holes
Submit
"I hear you very well" Banda
may be (Togo) chose  But when you finished
I promise you that you wish did not do
of our Will?
Yes  of our very
well, I'm eager to begin
to begin
Wait
now?
Yes now 00:22:22:09 00:22:24:07
(unless you think that (Togo  was wrong and you do not Dragon Warrior
do not know if I can do everything  these movements
unless we try not know
yes, but perhaps we can find something  suited to getting more
and what is your?
I do not know milestone  But let's start from zero, zero
there is no level of zero
perhaps I could begin this
this? We use this to train children  and keep the door open when it is hot
But if you insist
five Angry  you more photo
(except you, O (Mantis  You are the same size
"Come on," Banda  us what you can do
will see you?  Or to wait even longer to work
strike
I just ate so I still digestible
Kung Fu movements therefore may not be  would also be good later
strikes only
Why you?
You do not have anything  because I have everything here
Is harassment friends?  attending to feel the thunder
blow feet crazy  Wondering
Come 00:23:39:02 00:23:40:20
saw no way BEAR
(Wright (Mantis
(or method (the monkey
(or (snake
Hla hit
why not try again  stronger
How this?
this painful
This will be easier than I thought
sensitive regions
how IMO?
Now there is zero level
not words
do not understand the thinking of Bam  (teacher (Togo
poor will cause the death of
is very strong
Dragon Warrior
fell from the sky  ball fire
while walking the earth shakes
(one might think that the teacher (Togo  will choose who knows Kung Fu
yes or at least can  fingers touched the feet
fingers, or even finds his feet
Well 00:25:56:14 00:25:57:11
Hello  You awake?
too far
You ... What a day
Kung Fu Saab, right?
has been a long day  and disappointing somewhat
So ... Yes, we must sleep now
Yes Yes  course
But I admire a large  you dramatically in the battle of the river
outnumber, each one thousand , but you did not stop
sorry about this
listen, you do not belong to this place
I know I know 00:27:01:01 00:27:04:00
You are right 00:27:04:01 00:27:05:14
... During my whole life you dream
No, I mean you do not belong to here  in this room
these rooms  (Property (Whale
Yes true 00:27:16:07 00:27:19:08
want to sleep  I stay awake
and you have something important tomorrow
You are wonderful  last thing I am going to say
what was this?
did not say anything
Well, Good night  from well
seems strange situation
mandate tagged (Tigress) did not mean that awakens
You do not belong to here
Yes of course this room
I mean do not belong to the Palace of good
Shame on you Alkong Fu, and if  you have any respect for us and what we do
You have to go by morning
large fan
I see you found the sacred tree of peaches  of divine wisdom
Is this what?  unfortunately I thought it extraordinary tree Lepage
understand, you're erosion  when uncomfortable
am not uncomfortable  Why think I'm disturbed?
Why are you disturbed?
may have been on the worst day  in the history of the Congo Fu
in the history of China
in the history of bad
mostly
and five .. We must see them  idea that they
full
(how Hula Teacher (Shiva  of Dragon Warrior?
I do not like the five  I do not have talons
no wings  not cm
(even (Mantis  have these things
may be surrendered and come back for cooking barley
surrender .. No surrender
Noodle  not Noodle
you worried by what was often  and what will
There is a saying  Yesterday is history
tomorrow is a mystery
but today is a gift
- this is called the present - the gift
not -  What happens? --
fired
(must be careful (Chivu
will not go any place
Let me 00:30:42:00 00:30:43:15
that come here to
will not depart
throwers shares
We Dead  very Dead
Not yet 00:32:16:22 00:32:19:12
can not escape now?
Yes 00:33:06:19 00:33:08:12
I am delighted that the (Chevy) e-mail
I think they started Sasson
wing of there and tell them that the Dragon Warrior  real return
Good Morning milestone
Banda
Banda you wake up
has surrendered
what we are doing now any teacher  and went Banda
who will be the Dragon Warrior?
what we can do is continue training
with the passage of time will show  combatant real dragon
What are you doing here?
Hello  Good Morning milestone
I thought that little mastication
has been suspended
suspended?
not
Yes, we have suspended
assisted
My God 00:34:33:14 00:34:34:18
when preparing the third
Thank you -  do not remember it --
not really -  never --
I thought that you can dismiss the entire  during one night
require years to develop this flexibility
years and the longest battle for application
toss this, the only trophy we collect here  joints are bloody and broken bones
Yes 00:35:11:20 00:35:13:03
excellent
to begin
Are you Msttad
.... I was born ready
sorry I thought you said you're ready
this wonderful  to restore it
I have been with you any leniency Banda , but not longer
your opponent will be the next Anna
Well  to start
progress
order to win you have to find  weak point your opponent
and make them suffer
take power and use that against him
until fall or surrender
true warrior, but do not surrender  Do not worry any teacher will not surrendered
whether intelligent  will climb grades
but he will do
will not surrender  is not it?
will depend on collision
I thought you said that it makes us feel IMPROVES
Trust me, but makes no  easy to find a clique
under all this -  fur fat --
I was going to say fur
course
Who am I to judge the combatant  Based on size
see me
here
perhaps you should take a look at this again
Well 00:37:14:15 00:37:17:07
know that the teacher (Chevy) tries to inspire
but I did not know that well  I said to be trying to get rid of me
I know it seems harsh , but it was not always so
according to legend there was a time  where he was a teacher (Chevy) smiles
not
wear
but this was before
before Why?
(before (Tai Long
not supposed to be talking about
if it will remain here should know
(I know about (Tai Long
The pupils, from the first perfected  thousandth of skill Kong Fu
and then turned to evil and went to prison
was not just pupils
Shiva) and a small Jeddah)
Oh, Kabineh
while the boy showed skill in the Congo Fu
Shiva) and finally)
believed in him, told him that the ability of great
(not only never (Tai Long
wanted to Dragon Scroll
but (Togo), the overwhelming opinion in his heart  and rejection
Tai Long) have wreaked havoc valley)  angry
tried to forcibly take Scroll
and (Shiva) was forced to destroy what created
but how can?
Shiva) loved (Tai Loong) also did not like)  one of the pre -
or timely
and now has the opportunity to correct things  trains combatants for the real dragon
and has been suspended with you
Banda large fleshy  deal with the matter Packet
ended up
Wait  Zanby has finally addressed the League
and perhaps his heart stopped
internal peace
.... Home  internal peace
whoever does this sound  of silent
Zhang), excellent)
could benefit from good news now
any teacher
to ... That
bad news
Larry 00:40:47:14 00:40:49:19
they merely News  No news good and bad
teacher seeing you were correct
Tai Long) escaped from prison)  that way
this bad news
if that were not believed Dragon Warrior  can stop it
Banda?
any teacher that Banda was not Dragon Warrior
was not supposed to be here  was a coincidence
no coincidence
Yes, I know  I said this before
twice
these were not also a coincidence
three times
my friend old panda  will not achieve their own destiny and you do not
if they did not abandon its control
they?
(yes to see this tree (Chivu
I can not Set bud  when it is off to Shizam
and I can not aimed Set EXAMINED  before that time comes
but there are things we can control
I can control the time the fall fruit
... And I can control
where farm seed
This is not, you are a teacher
Yes, but do whatever  those of cottonseed to become the largest tree Lepage
might want Apple or orange
but you get Lepage
(peaches, but can not be defeated (Tai Long
possibly can if you are prepared to guide  and development
and the faith
but how  How
I need you to help teachers
No, you need to believe
(Aden (Chivu
Eden will ensure that you
will
will try
good
perhaps the time has come
must continue journey without
... What
any teacher
can not be left
must be secured
any teacher
might be more panda bears scaring "" in the region
", but you riding Balakechbc"
really? How I came out of there alive?
did not say this actually , but I thought in my head
if he could read my thoughts  of what was said
hope that you love
this good
must try soup Abe secret
is, in fact, knows the secret component
Why talk about? This wonderful
you cook a good reality
was wishing that my mouth more
mandate (Tigress) must try this
Dragon Warrior said to be able to live  full month on nothing but a small paper
and energy the universe
I think that my body does not know  I Dragon Warrior after
would need more than this to  juice and the universe
Why?
(None teacher (Chivu
will not become a combatant Dragon  unless lost 500 thousand kilometers and cleaned teeth
what this commotion is issued?  laughed? I have not heard of before
I work hard maybe one day  your ears would authorize
This is good 00:45:03:08 00:45:05:06
ears?  Worked with you
I thought it a good
(that (Chivu
course (Chevy) What do you think  I do
(teacher (Chivu
you believe that this funny  Tai Long) escaped from prison and you are adopting children)
Why?
is coming to Dragon Scroll  and you can only stop
and I say that you do not have  sense of Humor
Are you serious?
teacher (Togo) stopping  done this before already again
Togo) can not)  no longer
Our only hope is the Dragon Warrior
Banda? -  Yes Banda --
(teacher please let us stop (Tai Loong  to this path
(No, not our ability to defeat (Tai Loong  but the ability
where he went?
You can not leave  true warrior does not surrender
is watching
(God you, how to defeat Lee (Tai Loong  I can not precede the drawer
defeated because you Dragon combatant
You do not believe this  not believe this never
from the first moment they arrived here  I tried to get rid of me
Yes, I also
but now I ask you to trust teachers
as teachers Sathag
You are not teachers  and I'm not Dragon Warrior
Why, then, did not surrender?  you know I try to get rid of you
but you stayed
Yes, stayed
because every time I offered folds on the head  or I said that I was hurt bad smell
but not therefore more than ever  in my life because I am what I am
stayed because I thought .. If they can be  anyone can change
that makes me what I am  You will
greatest milestone Kong Fu in the whole of China
but you can change
may turn to Dragon Warrior  and I will do
Come on, (Tai Loong) in the way now
even if it takes a hundred years  Getting to here
how this will transform you to Dragon Warrior?
How?
How? -  I do not know --
do not know
This is what I thought
This is what she trains for it
(mandate (Tigress
not try suspensive
not trying to stop -  Why? --
coming with you
Why?
I eat while I would be uncomfortable
no need to explain  (I thought you (the monkey
is in store for candy in the top shelf
(do not tell (the monkey
see you
know, I'm cinnamon
No, I mean how arrived there?
do not know
did not know I was brought sweets
but you at a height of 10 feet on the ground  and I fully REVOKE
No, this?
... These  coincidence
no coincidence  Come with me
know you're trying to be vague  and nature Kong Feuilles
but you can not tell me that at least  Where are we going?
I have come to me here for the bathroom?
Banda you do not wash the body  in the holy lake of tears
... Lake
revealed here (Togo) puzzle  harmony and focus
born here, where Kung Fu
Want to learn Kung Fu?
Yes 00:52:11:01 00:52:12:01
if I am teacher
Well 00:52:15:01 00:52:17:06
not your books
Well 00:52:19:10 00:52:21:05
while focusing on the Congo Fu  while focusing
you bad
but perhaps this Zanby  I can not be coached and trained five
I see now that the road to enter you  This is
wonderful because I am hungry
well, while practicing erosion
to begin
from you after you Banda
So?  Not booby
not walked for ten miles
has vowed to train  and has trained
you can eat
Enjoy 00:54:14:10 00:54:15:23
I said you can eat
you can eat
Can I? -  Are You? --
m not hungry
any teacher
segments
Where Dragon Warrior?
How do you know that you do not consider it?
think I am foolish  I know that you are not fighting the dragon
not one of you
heard how fell from the sky  ball fire
that combatants do not like anything  world saw
Bo)?)
if this name
(Bo)
Finally, the deduction worth fighting
battle will be epic
we were still in this  helped
(O (monkey
Jump
(O (Mantis
now
Shiva) well-coached)
but he did not know everything
IMO has done well any Banda
IMO done well?
I have been a wonderful
hero is the real sign of humility
But yes  you are wonderful
five
has died  No, they breathed
asleep?  Not open their eyes
we were not equals to attack the nerves
become stronger
Tai Long)?)  stronger
is very fast
(sorry (Bo
I thought that we can stop him
could have been killers
Why did he do?
to return and scares  here in our hearts, but will not succeed
may succeed  slightly
I'm afraid 01:00:11:22 01:00:14:05
you can defeat any Banda
Are you kidding?  They can not
are five teachers
I'm only one
but you have something that  not owned by one another
actually think I'm ready
(you ready .. (Bo
grabbed the Dragon Scroll
it for you
waited .. What happens when read?
No one knows, but legend says  he will be able to hear butterfly flap
really? Hmaraa
Yes, sees light at the depth of the cave  hair is around you and movement
Could I broke through the walls  Could I do that my heart
focused
Yes 01:01:47:20 01:01:49:04
read it and achieved or your sorrow
read it and became belligerent Dragon
impossible reopened
Thank 01:02:09:01 01:02:10:21
maybe you just analysed
Well Here is the
it empty -  Why? --
you -  No, I'm not allowed to consider it --
empty
do not understand
Well 01:02:43:24 01:02:46:02
Togo) turtle was crazy in the end)
No, (Togo) was the wisest of us all
Come 01:02:53:08 01:02:54:15
faced matter, has chosen passerby
course, I'm not Dragon Warrior
of deceptive?
but it will stop (Tai Long)?
would destroy everything  and every one
not
evacuated valley  (must protect villagers from the wrath (Tai Long
What about you?
I am the killer -  Why? --
could delay sufficient  so that everyone escapes
but you (Chevy), killings
time I had finally paid  eighth mistakes
Asamaoni all of you
is time to supplement  trip without
I'm proud of that I tagged
must be knocked out safely
Dear Little Come to find as
mandate (snake) Friday Villagers southerners
you (Mantis) northerners
O (stork) from here
see that Dragon Warrior
Hello Abe
Hello 01:04:34:08 01:04:36:03
quality of your return Bani
It's good to come back
(to go (Bo
us in the following must face it
future of barley  pieces with vegetables
well as I was thinking maybe this time  will have a kitchen that can stand it
Ayajbk this?
Bo) ... I'm sorry that things did not succeed)
was estimated to be
Bo) Lance anything else)  still awaiting determination does not
We makers Noodle
place in the veins
do not know my father
honestly?
sometimes can not believe I am your son
Bo) .. I think it is time)  to tell you something he should tell the
long time ago
Well 01:05:51:10 01:05:53:08
component of the secret ballot Soup
Come ... Component is the secret
NONE
heard me  NONE
There is a secret
waited  only normal Noodle Soup
adds a special sauce  or something like that?
unnecessary, in order to create something distinctive  believes that it must be distinguished
There is a secret
has promised to house any teacher
This is no longer your house  and I am not prepared teacher
Yes, you have a favorite new pupil
where (Bo) this?
Is abated?
this battle between me and you
So things will?
thus must be
has Rot in jail for 20 years  due to weak
obey the teacher is not vulnerable
knew I Dragon Warrior
(always you know, but when he (Togo  What did I do something contrary?
What did I do?
None
was not destined to be a combatant you Dragon  This is not Zanby
not their fault?  Of letting down?
of taught me that even with super breakup?
of deprivation of fateful?
was never resolutions
it is now
Give me Scroll 01:08:33:12 01:08:36:17
prefer to die
Tell me 01:09:32:23 01:09:34:14
Tell me 01:09:34:15 01:09:37:14
for as long as you are proud of your
from the first moment I was proud of your
and was proud that Oman
I loved it very much to see what you turn him
what I do for you I
... I  I'm sorry
do not want an apology
I want to girls
Why?
where is it?
Dragon Warrior taking Scroll  other Party of China now
(you will not see Scroll (Tai Long
never
from you?
you shouted ... I Dragon Warrior
you?
is?  This Banda
You Banda  Why do you much? Sitting on?
does not spur  Now I will use this
wants Come and Take
Finally 01:11:22:08 01:11:23:17
this I Scroll
Scroll give strength
Finally 01:13:57:01 01:13:57:25
Yes 01:13:57:25 01:14:00:06
force Scroll dragon is me
NONE
did not quite understand it  also the first time
Why?
There is a secret
that you're only
stop
do not
can not be defeated
You ... Just
Banda large fleshy
am not a large fleshy Banda
Anna Banda big chaff famous
(maintained (Ho Chi
know this Alamsake
deceive you?
Shiva) did not teach you this)
No, I discovered myself
Look 01:16:41:23 01:16:42:22
Dragon Warrior
In this  Warrior Kung Fu is a great beloved son
Thank Abe
Hi guys
any teacher
milestone
teacher?
teacher (Shiva)?
any teacher
(Chevy)  Are you okay?
Bo)?)  You are alive
or we both Dead
not teachers  not complete
(We have defeated (Tai Long
really?
(as was the case (Togo
You combatant dragon
has brought peace to the Valley
and I  Thank
Thank  (Bo)
Thank
No, teachers do not
not been (Chevy) Please
did not complete my Duffer
O Dragon Warrior
I simply live with peace  Finally
if we must stop talking
if you can
Will I get something to eat?
Yes
The End