Prince of Persia - The Sands of Time
IRE
Long ago, in a land far away,
There once rose an empire that
stretched from the steppes of China,
to the shores of the Mediterranean.
That empire was Persia.
Fierce in battle,
wise in victory,
where the Persian sword went,
order followed
The Persian King Sharaman
ruled with his brother Nizam
upon the principles of loyalty
and brotherhood.
The King had two sons who gave
him great joy.
But in the eyes of the gods the
King's family was not yet complete.
Not until the day he witnessed a
single act of courage
by an orphan boy on the streets
of Nasam.
Get out of the way!
Stop!
Run!
Run, Dastan!
Stay here!
Getting away! He's getting away!
Let go of me!
- In the King's name!
- What is your name, boy
- Dastan, Sir.
And your parents?
Boy...
Brother, take him up.
Moved by what he saw, the King
adopted the boy Dastan into his family.
A son without no royal blood
and no eye on his throne.
But perhaps there was something
else at work that day.
Something beyond simple understanding.
On that day, a boy from the unlikeliest
of places
became, a Prince of Persia.
IRE
Translation and adaptation: CyroBM
Completely redone: IRE
The fabled Alomet.
Even more stunning than I imagined.
That is all beauty, Prince.
It's a city like any other.
Soft countries make soft men.
They stooped to treachery and must now pay for it.
The Father made clear, Alomet was not to be touched.
Some consider it sacred.
And since our wise Father isn't here,
the decision rests with me.
I'll have one last council with my noble
and my two brothers,
Trusted Garsiv and...
Where's Dastan?
- Come on! I bet my entire month's allowance on this!
This is embarrassing!
- Why don't you give it a try?!
Give it to them!
Is that all you got?
Prince Dastan!
Where's Prince Dastan?
Prince Dastan isn't here.
Your Highness, please,
Prince Tus convened a war council.
I'm on my way.
Our finest spy
intercepted a caravan,
leaving Alomet.
Swords of the best workmanship.
Steel-tipped arrows,
a promise of payment from the
warlord Kosh, to Alomet.
They're selling weapons to our
enemies, Dastan.
An arrow such as this slew
my horse in Koscan
Blood will run in Alomet streets
for this,
or our soldiers
will fall from its walls.
Our orders were to Koscan,
not to attack Alomet.
Wise words, little brother.
Words won't stop our enemies,
once they're armed with Andalucian
blades.
We attack at dawn.
Well if that is your decision,
then let me go in first.
- What do you think, Garsiv?
- I run the Persian army,
Dastan leads a company of street rabble.
They may not be much for manners,
but they're pretty handy in a fight.
The honor of first blood should
be mine.
- Garsiv, you've got your hands on your sword again.
- That's where it should be.
Oh my brothers...[chuckle] ever eager.
It's said the Princess of Alomet is a
beauty without equal.
We'll march into her palace to
see for ourselves. [Chuckling]
There'll be no doubt of your
courage, Dastan,
but you're not ready for this.
Garsiv's cavalary would lead the way.
Princess Tamina,
the Persian army, my Princess, has not moved on.
Their faith has little love for
any truth, other than its own.
Perhaps it would be safer
if you didn't stand so close?
Whatever their faith, their
bows aren't that strong, nor is their aim.
Gather the Council,
tell them I sit in the High Temple.
I must pray.
High Temple? Alomet hasn't
been breached in a thousand years!
Everything changes with time.
We should know this best of all.
Remind me why are we disobeying
your brother's orders?
Because Garsiv only knows how
to attack head-on.
It would be a massacre.
Alamutienii will be busy
the main gate.
We'll slip through the side.
Have you been drinking?!
That's our way in.
There are two gates.
The outer one's easy,
but it's the inner gate that's impossible.
The gate mechanism is protected by
two man-guard towers
Yeah, there's always in, Bis.
You take care of the outer gate.
You leave the impossible one to me.
Yeah, that's how you won't be
happy until you get us all killed.
Ooh, wonderful speed, Bis.
Rousing.
Sound the alarm!
Help!
Hold this.
Watch your back.
- Eastern gate's opened.
- That's Dastan's men. He's gotten in.
Dastan's done it.
Redeploy to the Eastern Gate.
Redeploy to the Eastern Gate!
They've breached the Eastern Gate.
Collapse the passages to the Chamber.
Princess...
Go now, everyone.
You know what you must do.
Alomet must be kept safe.
Out of the way!
Silly songs and scented smoke will
do nothing for you now!
I think you'll find there's more
to her than that,
hey Garsiv?
So for once, the stories are true.
We know you secretly build weapons
for enemies of Persia.
- Now show us where.
- We have no forges here,
and what weapons we had, you overcame.
Our spies say differently.
You can save a lot of pain.
All the pain in the world will
not help you find something that does not exist.
Spoken like one
wise enough to consider
a political solution.
Join hands with Persia's future King.
I'll die first.
That can be arranged.
Prince Tus!
Promise me the people of Alomet
will be treated with mercy.
Hey, the Lion of Persia!
Lion of Persia!
They're calling you
the Lion of Persia!
You've never excelled at
following orders, Dastan.
- I have some explaining to do, Tus...
- No. No.
No! You've some celebrating to do.
There is, however a tradition.
Since you took the honor of the first assault,
you owe me a gift.
Homage.
What a beautiful dagger!
He's delivered you the city
and its Princess, I think that's homage enough.
So it is.
First dispatch my Prince.
Wonderful news.
Your father's disrupted his prayers
at the Eastern Palace
to join us.
No doubt to commend us
on our great victory.
We've had indication that Alomet
was arming our enemies.
Indications? You've got to have
more than indications
to occupy a holy city.
With my troops!
This, tsk, adventure,
won't sit with our allies.
But I suppose,
you didn't take that into account.
Don't look for your uncle. Boy!
The decisions and its consequences
will rest with me.
I know you're eager
to wear the crown,
But trust me when I tell you,
you're not ready.
No man would know better than you, Father,
because your trust is something I deeply cherish,
I will oversee the search for weapons myself.
I vow I will not stand before you
until I hold proof of Alomet's treachery.
[Cheering] The first step is the hardest!
Brother! Brother!
We've uncovered signs of tunnels on the
eastern edge of the city,
- I'm on my way there now...
- Ah! Ah! But you'll miss your banquet.
You and Garsiv can handle Father in my absence
You do have a gift to honor him with?
Of course!
- Bis, gift.
- What?
- It's been momentarily misplaced.
- I knew you'd forget...
The prayer robe of Alomet's regent.
The holiest in Eastern lands,
a gift that a King
will appreciate.
You fought like a champion
for me, Dastan,
gald to return the favor.
A rare jewel.
Present her to the King for
me this evening, Dastan.
You sure you want another wife, brother?
Listen to me, Dastan!
A marriage to the Princess
assures me the loyalty of her people.
Unbound to us, she's a
dangerous liability.
If Father doesn't approve our union,
I want you to end her life
with your own hands.
So, I'm escorted by Prince Dastan,
the Lion of Persia.
Must feel wonderful for winning such acclaim
for destroying such an innocent city.
Ah, pleasure to meet you too, Princess.
Allow me to offer that
if punishing the enemies of
my King is a crime, then it's
one I'll gladly repeat.
Then you are a true prince of Persia,
brutal and without honor.
Don't make the mistake that you
know me, Princess.
Oh? And what more is there?
Wait here with her Highness.
If you can manage it,
I suggest a hint of humility
when you're presented to the King.
For your own good.
You Father's, eh, Uncle?
One day, you'll have the pleasure
of being brother to the King, Dastan.
As long as you remember your most important
duty
you should do well.
Oh, and what's that?
Making sure his wine glass stays full.
I'm told that another of my sons
has joined the rank of
great Persian warriors.
Thank you.
We missed you, Father.
I...was praying for you and your
brothers, Dastan.
Family, the bond between brothers
this is the sword that defends our empire.
I pray that that sword
remains strong.
I was hoping my actions would
spare our men into heavy losses.
A good man would have done as you did, Dastan,
act boldly and courageously to
bring a victory
and spare lives.
A great man would have stopped
the attack from happening at all,
a great man would have stopped
what he knew to be wrong.
No matter who's ordering.
The boy that I saw in that square,
was capable of being more than just good
but to be great.
Well in the meantime, I have a gift for you.
Some questions the wisdom of my
bringing a boy from the streets into
my family, but I saw a boy
whose blood wasn't noble,
but whose character was,
a King in spirit.
Thank you, Father.
May I present the prayer robe of
Alomet's regent.
What can I grant you, in return?
Braham!
May I present the Princess Tamina.
Tus wishes to make a union
with her people through marriage,
it is my deepest wish, that
this wins your approval.
In all my travels,
I have never looked upon
a more beautiful city, Your Highness.
You should have seen it before your
horde of camel-riding illiterates descended upon it.
Clear as well that you will make a fine queen.
But, Tus already has enough wives
you, Dastan, might take fewer
chances if such a
jewel waited in your chamber.
The Princess of Alomet will be your
your first wife.
Oh, what say you, Dastan?
He plunged into a hundred foes without thought
but before marriage he stands frozen
with fear,
and, for those who say he is not yet wise!
I need a drink.
- Stand aside!
- Out of my way!
Father!
God help us, the rubies, it's poisoned!
- Somebody help him!
- The robe Dastan gave him!
- Why?
- Somebody help him!
- He's the murderer!
Stop!
Cease him!
- Bis! Bis!!
- Come with me!
- What do you think you're doing?
- I'm going to get us out of here!
You're going to need my help!
Come on!
- Close the gate!
- That way!
- Get down!
There!
Onto the murderer!
He's on my horse!
He's stole my horse!
My loyal subjects
the whole world grieves at the
death of our beloved King.
We all stricken by his loss.
That the murder came at Prince Dastan's hand
only makes our pain worse.
I did not kill my father.
The robe was given to me by my brother
Tus did this.
And now he stands to be crowned king.
I didn't kill my father.
I believe you.
You shouldn't be here.
I shouldn't have let you come.
But you did.
I promised my brother that I'd kill you
if he couldn't have you.
Well, the solution would be to kiss me
and then kill me,
but I have a better solution.
I kill you!
And your problems are solved.
Perhaps we could find another solution!
Well, the solution would be to kiss me
then kill me,
but I have a better solution.
I kill you!
Give back what you stole, Persian!
No!
- Did you see that?
- See what?
Go for that sword again and
I swear that I will break your arm.
Again?
- You used up all the sand.
- What?
What is this?
Incredible!
Releasing the sand
turns back time.
And only the holder of the dagger
is aware of what happened.
He could go back and alter events, change time,
and no one knows but him.
How much can it unliken?
Answer me, Princess.
You destroyed my city.
Apparently it wasn't about a weapons audit,
it was about this dagger.
After the battle, Tus asked for this dagger as tribute.
I didn't think anything of it, but now I see.
With it, he could change anything.
He could change a critical moment in battle,
he could foresee the blade of a rival.
He wouldn't just be king,
he would be the most powerful
ruler Persia's ever seen
greater even than my father.
It was all about this dagger.
My treacherous brother must be
brought to justice.
And as such I have doubled the
reward for his capture.
Meanwhile I shall strive to protect our empire
as my father would have demanded.
A new reign has begun.
- What are you doing?
- Garsiv can't be far behind us.
She's the most famous horse in the empire.
This would skew his tracks.
Tracks where?
Where are you going?
To Abrat, where my father will be buried.
You're wanted for the King's murder
and you're going to march into his funeral
- in alongside thousands of Persian soldiers?
- Well, Nizam will be there. He's the
only one I can trust.
He'll see it was set up by Tus.
Step aside, Princess.
Every road to Abrat will be
covered by Persian troops.
Well, I'm not taking roads,
I'm going through the Valley of the Slaves.
No one goes near that wasteland,
it's filled with murderers and cutthroats.
- Yes, so they say.
- Your whole plan is suicide!
My brother murdered my father,
and it's his blood on my hands
if I die trying to set that right,
then so be it.
Ah! So you're going to leave me here
in the middle of nowhere?
Noble Dastan abandoning a helpless woman
in the wilderness,
what does your precious honor
have to say about that?
Oh, give me the strength not to kill her.
Mount up, we can't be far behind him.
Without the right sand
it's just another knife.
Not even very sharp.
- This sand is there more of it?
- Of course not.
Where do I find more?
Try standing on your head and
holding your breath.
- See what you were looking for, Prince?
- Start walking.
So if you can't prove to your uncle how
the dagger works,
why would he believe you?
It's not your problem, Princess.
You know, you really walk like one.
Head held high, chest out, long
stumping strides.
The walk of a self-satisfied Persian prince.
No doubt it has come from being told since birth
the world is yours.
- And you actually believing it.
- I wasn't born in the palace like you.
I was born in the slums in Mysaf.
where I lived if I fought
and I clawed for it.
- Then how did you become a Prince?
- King marches in the market one day,
and he...
I don't know...he...
he found me.
He took me,
he gave me a family, gave me a home.
What you're looking at is the walk of
a man who's just lost everything.
Welcome to the Valley of the Slaves, Your Highness.
I'm desperate for a drop of water.
Well that's more than we had
when you emptied our canteen hours ago.
I wasn't born in this desert like you Persians,
or shrivelled and angry...
My constitution is much more...delicate.
I think you're being spoiled.
The wells of Alomet are famed for
their clean, cold water.
Perhaps less time admiring your wells
and more time guarding your walls,
you wouldn't be here. [chuckling...]
Ah, a miracle!
I've silenced the Princess!
Tamina?
Can you hear me?
Yes, Dastan, I hear you.
Do you know where you are, Persian?
And yet you enter still?
In the heart of Sudan is a tribe
of warriors known as the Um'Bakr.
They strike fear into the hearts of
all they cross.
The Um'Bakr are masters of the throwing knife.
Wielding blades said to
have been blessed by the Creator himself.
Their aim is so murderously accurate
they can decaptitate three men with one strike.
Oh, I wouldn't bother doing that if I were you,
Do you know why? This is Seso. He's an Um'Bakr.
I have the good fortune of saving his life,
which means that he is now enduringly indebted to me.
So tell me, Persian, is there any good reason
why I shouldn't tell Seso
to put his next throw a little higher?
- So? This is the one, eh?
- Yes...
you're right, she's not bad.
She could smell a bit better though.
Still we have a deal.
- Clever Princess.
- Deal? What deal?
- Such a noble prince...
- Such a gentle princess...
How taken you were with my ainting act
eagerly leaping to assist the fallen...
- Who said you're beautiful?
- There must be a reason why
you can't take your eyes off me.
You are...
I...I don't trust you.
And you're not my type.
I'm not some desperate slave girl,
- I'm actually capable of voicing my own thoughts.
- Too many for my taste.
Yeah, she'll make a very nice addition.
What do you do with it?
Yes, do tell him, can you not see how concerned he is?
- Give me a moment.
- Yeah.
It's hard for me to admit,
but you were right.
I did see what I was looking for.
- Dastan, listen to me.
- When my uncle sees the power of this dagger,
he'll believe me.
Dastan I know ...
I haven't been entirely honest with you.
Oh, but your lies are so clever.
I am the guardian of the Divine Covenant.
- Oh, oh.
- That dagger is sacred.
It was being smuggled to safety
when you stole it
- If the dagger gets into the wrong hands...
- I will take care of your knife.
You don't want to miss this.
You don't understand what's at stake!
This is a matter of the gods, not man!
Your gods, not mine!
Come on!
- Ostrich racing?
- Yeah, every Tuesday and Thursday.
Whatever they lack in beauty
they make up for in fighting spirit.
And the races are easy to fix!
I heard all these terrible stories of this place.
The black, thirsty slaves? Murdering their masters?
[laughing] There's a good story,
it's well-told everybody, but alas untrue.
- But skeletons that we saw...
- Ah bull, they're from a gypsy in Pecara.
Now I crafted our lurid reputation in order
to fend off
the most insiduous evil that's been lurking
this forsaken country of ours.
You know what I'm talking about? Taxes!
Now these Persians, their army, their fortresses
their roads, their...
Who pays for it all, eh?!
The small businessmen!
Yeah, that's why I started a little campaign
to spread some false notoriety
I spread like a veneral disease in a Turkish harem.
Behold the mighty ostrich!!
[laughing]
Come on, my beauty!
I love this!
And the tax collectors stay clear of me
and my customers, everybody's happy.
Hey! Get the girls on!
Get the girls on! Come on! Crowd control!
[whistling]
Don't just stand there! Run, don't walk!
Hey, you drop anything, you pay for it!
Out of your wages.
Now, don't you look at me like that.
You know what I'm talking about.
Do your job, crowd control!
Thank you!
You know, our little arrangement's
going to work out very well, young man.
Oh ho ho! She's a lively one!
Where did you find her?
In the slave marts of Glor.
I was headed to Iraq to trade her for a camel when
she attacked me.
- The camels are safer.
I appreciate your hospitality.
You run a fine establishment.
but if you could give me
the supplies...
You know something, Persian?
You bear a remarkable resemblance to
the disgraced prince who fled
after murdering the king.
- Have I told you about the Um'Bakr?
- Yes, you have.
Nothing beats a good story, eh. But yours however,
trading her for a camel, please?
I mean, look at her.
She's worth at least two.
And as for you, young man, did you know
your brother has offered a reward
that quite frankly for you that, between you and me,
borders on the obscene?
I'd trade in my mother for
for that kind of gold.
What? And you didn't know what she was like?
Take him down to the Persian outpost.
Wait! Wait!
Nice knife.
- No, no, no, that's worthless.
- Really?
Melt it down for the jewels.
What's the boy doing?!
No! No! You might kill a bird!
Hey, over here!
- Oh, oh, I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- Get to the tunnel!
Oh look at this. That's it!
No more fermented goat's milk till
after the third race, you hear me?!
Get off, come on!
Get him!
Stop!
- Lift the lever, open the gate!
- Give me the dagger.
- This is not the time...
- Give me the dagger!
Don't think it didn't cross my mind.
Move, Princess!
Get him!
Dastan!
Looking for this?
This? Oops.
Next time you...aargh!
They've all come
for my father's funeral.
There are a hundred Persian
soldiers watching that gate.
Maybe more.
If you want to stay close to the dagger,
you should help me get into Abrat.
All these foreign dignitaries,
I'm guessing you know a few?
Couldn't you have found somebody lighter?
Dunghals of the Hindu Kush are a noble people.
You should be honored.
Oh yes, terribly.
Dastan, where's the dagger?
You're welcome to search me for it.
You'll have to be very thorough.
Tus isn't here.
He's probably still in Alomet.
The sand that fuels the dagger,
there's more of it in Alomet, isn't there?
That's why Tus stays there.
That's what he's got our army searching for.
I have to get a message
to my uncle to meet me.
That's impossible.
Difficult but not impossible.
- Well, more proof you're insane.
- Why do you look so impressed?
Out of the way!
Make way!
- Turn around! Turn around!
- What?
You used to buy those
for me when I was a boy.
You used to spit the seeds
on Garsiv.
- You should not have brought me here, Dastan.
- I had no choice, uncle.
Follow me.
I didn't kill father.
- You know that I would never do such a thing.
- Your actions speak otherwise.
But...but I had no choice,
but to flee.
Tus gave me that cloak.
He was the one who poisoned it.
- Dastan...
- But he's not here, is he?
At his father's funeral,
instead he remains at Alomet.
Eyes will see
that our invasion was just.
Search for weapons forges
is important.
Yes, but not if there are none.
The invasion of Alomet is a lie.
Tus was after power
that's why he murdered father.
And now he searches not after weapons
but for the sand
- that fuels a mystical device.
- This is why you brought me here, Dastan?
Mystical device?
You remember after the battle
you stopped Tus from taking the dagger I'd won?
That dagger is the
reason he invaded Alomet.
- This dagger, you have it with you?
- Yes.
It has incredible powers.
Is this some sort of a joke, Dastan?
What? No, it was in there.
And where is your so-called evidence?
Tamina...
I...
The...
Your hands are burned.
Yes, from trying
to pull the poison cloak off your father.
Is something wrong, Dastan?
- No, no...
- You certain?
You know that you can trust me, boy.
It...it's just that Tus is my brother.
- How could he betray me like this?
- I can't say, Dastan.
Perhaps he never respected you
as it deserved and he saw you as
someone he could use.
Someone to keep his wine glass filled.
My service to your father was different.
We shared the same blood, Dastan.
How many times did Father
speak of you saving him from that lion?
- That was his favorite story.
- Yes, of many, yes.
No, that was his favorite.
I'm afraid you're speaking
in riddles, Dastan.
Wait, Dastan!
Murderer!
I didn't kill father!
Out of the way!
Get out of the way!
Get him!
What are you doing now?
Dnelor ...
Prince Garsiv!
Where is he?
Where is he?!!
Garsiv.
- I didn't kill father.
- Then god will pardon you.
After your head rolls.
We're not fighting with sticks
anymore, little brother.
That's all you got?
- Your Majesty, I thought you were staying in Alemot.
- Tell me about Dastan, uncle.
Dastan came to Arbat to kill me.
In the market place.
I just got away.
Tus, my death would weaken your young reign.
Dastan hopes to start a rebellion.
- He wants the throne?
- I'm fear so, my Lord.
Putting Dastan on trial would
only give him a stage for his sedition.
My advice would be
to avoid a trial.
Don't bring him back to Nasaf for life.
Whatever Dastan's crimes,
a public trial will best communicate
the king I hope to be.
Strong. Honoring the rule of law.
We are not savages.
You grow more a king every day.
Dastan must be found.
He must be brought to justice.
I need to speak with our guests.
About them my lord. Their practices are unusual.
The servants have seen things,
heard strange sounds.
Last week one of the horses vanished.
Well just make sure that the servants keep their
mouths shut
or I promise you they will vanish as well.
I have another task for you, Hassansin,
but you have to be quick,
- your prey has a head start.
- You brought what I requested?
These practices, they don't interfere
with your skills?
In a trance we see the visions of far future,
vision of death,
Destiny...
and a curse.
In trance we can find anything.
Including your nephew,
Prince Dastan.
Then I hope you shall see more death...
soon.
Get down!
It's a Persian patrol!
Garsiv...
What aren't you telling me?
The transmen left. Maybe they tired
of your pawnshop for lies and back-stabbing.
I had no choice,
but to leave you.
I take it your uncle didn't listen?
It wasn't Tus that killed my father.
It was Nizam.
- Your uncle?
- His hands were burnt.
He said he had been trying to pull off the
cloak that killed my father.
I've gone over and over it in my mind.
He never touched the cloak.
He must have handled it before.
It was Nizam that poisoned it.
What good does turning back a few
moments of time do my uncle?
None.
He murdered my father for more
than just a dagger.
What aren't you telling me?
Here, you've got quick eyes.
So do I.
If you want it back
tell me everything.
No more games, no more lies.
Can we get out of here?
Only a princess could think she
could outrun a sandstorm.
Nizam's coming to kill us.
He needs me dead.
I need to know why.
In Amolet lies the beating heart
of all life on earth.
The Sandglass of the gods.
Long ago, the gods looked down on man
but saw only greed and treachery.
So they sent a great sandstorm
to destroy all, wipe clean the
face of the earth.
But one young girl asked the gods to give
mankind another chance.
Offering her life in exchange.
Seeing the purity within the gods were
reminded of mankind's potential for good.
So they swept the sands into the Sandglass.
The dagger was given to the girl
who saved man,
making her the first Guardian.
The dagger blade is the only thing that
can pierce
the Sandglass and remove the Sands of Time.
But the handle only holds one minute.
What if one were to place the Dagger in
the Sandglass and press the jewel button at the same time?
Sand would flow through endlessly.
Time would flow back as far as you like.
Yes, but it is forbidden.
When my father was a boy,
Nizam saved his life hunting.
One day, two Princes
were stalking a beautiful buck
but they were unaware of a lion
that was stalking them.
Nizam saved Sharaman.
My father told us this story
over and over again.
- I don't understand.
- Nizam wants to go back in time
and undo what he did and not save my father,
and let him die.
Then he'll be king for a lifetime. And my
brothers would never be born.
The storm's passed.
Dastan, the sands contained within
the Sandglass are incredibly powerful.
Opening the dagger while it's inside
the Sandglass breaks the seal
and destroy the Sandglass
causing it to crack and shatter.
The Sands of Time
can no longer be contained.
And they would carry with them the gods' wrath with them once more.
Destroying everything in their path.
And all of mankind will pay for Nizam's treachery.
This is what that would be left of us.
The secret guardian temple
outside Alomet is a sanctuary.
The once place where the Dagger can be hidden safely
and the only way to stop
this Armageddon.
That's the truth, Dastan.
Give me the dagger back
so that I can take it there.
No, I can't do that.
I'm coming with you.
You're going to help me?
We can sit here and chat
or you can sit on the horse.
Our journey is blessed.
We'll stop for water and push
for the mountain pass before nightfall.
You enjoy telling me what to do.
Only because you're so good at following orders.
Yeah, don't press your luck.
Dastan!
We parted under such rushed circumstances.
We didn't have the chance to say goodbye.
We've been tracking you for a week.
That little riot you started,
it went on for two days!
My beloved race track.
All washed away like footprint in sand.
See the nigger there?
She's all that's left of
my gaming empire.
And no matter your skills as a promoter
you can organize an ostrich race
with just one ostrich!
Am I right?
Yes, sir.
Come with me.
Did you know that ostriches have suicidal tendencies?
Look at this poor thing.
She used to be a grand champion
and now must watch her day and night
to make sure that she doesn't do anything stupid.
So it occured to me the only way to recoup my
tragic losses
was to track down the two young lovers
who cast the dark cloud upon me.
Ah yes, I'm going to need the
price on your head.
Your brother will be very pleased to see...
Sand dervishers, Persian.
They come in as camel...
- Sheik, listen to me!
- I'd rather not.
- Nice knife.
- Noble Sheik,
we are on a sacred journey
to the temple.
Temple? What temple? There is nothing more sacred
than Persian gold.
- Give me the dagger.
- There are too many of them.
- You can't kill them all. You want to live?
- Give me the dagger!
Give me the dagger!
Persian, how did you do that?
Instinct.
We've got to get out of here.
- What happened last night?
- Those vipers were controlled by Hassansins.
- Hassansins?
- For years, they were
the covert killing force for the Persian kings
but my father ordered
them disbanded.
Nizam must have disobeyed my father's orders,
kept them intact.
It's an secret government killing activity.
- That's why I don't pay taxes.
- We can't stop.
Perhaps you can't, but we can.
We could use your help getting
to the Temple.
By crossing the Hindu Kush with the
a storm blowing?
You attract trouble like flies
around a rotting mango.
- Are you insane!
- There's gold in the temple.
More than 10 horses could carry.
Tax-free.
Sir!
Do you have any idea where you're going?
I memorized this path
as a child.
Every Princess must.
It's sacred.
It's here.
The Sanctuary, the one place the
Dagger can be hidden safely.
I was expecting to golden statues, waterfalls.
Give me back the Dagger,
so I can take it there.
Don't cut yourself, Princess.
Hey! Here!
Not long dead.
Last night maybe.
Tortured first.
Hassansin.
Nizam knows this place.
All dead.
The entire village...
- uh, my gold...
- Where you going?
- There is only one way to stop all of this.
- What?
To make sure the Dagger is safe.
The Temple holds the stone the
Dagger came from.
What tem...this is a pile of stones and rocks.
The first thing we learned
was, all else fails,
put the Dagger back in the stone,
the stone will envelop it,
pulling it into the mountain,
returning it to the gods.
The Original Promise...must be paid.
What Promise?
The gods must take
back the life they spared.
That means...you'll die.
Stay there!
- Listen to me! Listen to me!
- Give me your sword!
Give me your sword or do you fortake given that honor.
There are bodies down there murdered by
Hassansin's on Nizam's order.
- He's the traitor!
- Hassasins no longer exist!
- You always thought you were so clever.
- This is no trick, Garsiv.
Sir!
All dead inside, sir, more in the village.
- There's one in there...
- Stay there!
Nizam wants me dead, wants me silenced.
A trial would be too public.
You know this?
He said this much, didn't he?
I know hate has been between
us, Garsiv, but still...
- We are brothers!
- Touching words,
with my sword at your throat.
You often question why
Father spends so much time in prayer.
Before he died he told me
that the bond between brothers
is the sword that defends our empire.
He was pryaing that that sword
remains strong.
Why would I go to Abrat
to Father's funeral,
when I knew it was so dangerous?
Nizam recommended your death.
Tus disagreed, ordered you brought back alive.
Nizam wants me dead
and he's hired the Hassansins to make
sure that that does happen.
He is afraid of what I might say.
And who I might tell.
Tell me, brother.
Garsiv?
Wai...Garsiv?
Garsiv!
Hassansins!
Shut up, shut up!
Protect the Dagger!
Dastan!
Behind you!
Tamina!
Forget them! Throw these!
Find her!
Hey! Hey, over here!
Ha! You know what they say about men
with big swords?
Tamina!
Let me do it.
Only a Guardian
can return the Dagger.
This isn't something
you can do, Dastan.
I'm ready for this.
I'm not.
Tamina!
Enough!
Get out!
Garsive!
- Garsiv!
- Dastan, I'm sorry.
[gurgling] Save the empire.
Brother...
- Where's the Dagger?
- It's gone.
Protect the Dagger,
no matter the consequences.
That was my sacred honor.
And was my destiny.
We make our own destiny, Princess.
We'll get it back.
We're going to need another horse!
- Where will you go?
- To Alomet.
Nizam will use the Dagger
to pierce the Sandglass
- He must be stopped.
- "He has to be stopped. He has to be stopped." [chuckle]
What? Oh, a knife-thrower with conscience?
Our friends in the palace say that
the Persians that have broken through to
the first levels of the tunnels.
They will reach the Sandglass within hours.
Nizam's keeping the Dagger in the
High Temple,
guarded by some sort of demon
covered with spikes.
The Hassansin that killed my brother.
It's the only thing that stands
between us and the Dagger.
No man can stand within
20 yards of him and live.
Some don't need to get that close.
Spare some water, sire?
You sure about this?
- I owe the boy.
- But, you are an Um'Bakr...
Scourge of the Namidian plain.
Me? I'm a slightly dishonorable entrepreneur,
this nobility business is not the cloth
we're cut from.
- Hurry!
- My friend, has anyone ever told you
- that you talk too much?
- Uh huh.
All right.
Come on!
Did I told you about the Um'Bakr?
Yes, you have.
I hope your brother
listens to you, Persian.
He's here.
Seal every gate!
Find him!
- It's clear.
- Dastan!
- I don't think you should do this.
- Is it concern I hear?
- Caution.
- Sprinkled with concern.
- You flatter yourself, Prince.
- And you used to be a better liar, Princess.
Perhaps I'm out of practice...
This won't be the
last time we'll be together.
- Where is the Dagger?
- You Persian bureaucrats...
- such soft hands.
- You!
- It's been found, my Lord.
- The Sandglass?
I don't have the Dagger.
Leave me.
Hello, Tus.
Dastan!
- We need to talk.
- Talk.
- Alone.
- Wait outside the chamber.
Now!
We are brothers, are we not?
The robe that killed Father
was poisoned by Nizam.
- Nizam? You're mad!
- Who gave you the robe, Tus? Who gave you the robe!
You trust him?
As did I.
But Alomet wasn't supplying
our enemies with weapons.
- Nizam lied to us.
- Why would he do such a thing? What would he gain?
Listen to me carefully.
Under the streets of the city lies
an ancient force, a container
holding the fabled Sands of Time.
Nizam wants to use it
to corrupt history.
He wants to turn back
time and make himself King.
Sands of Time?
Heresy, Dastan!
Pagan madness!
I've seen its power with my own eyes, Tus!
Nizam discovered its resting place.
If we don't stop him
our world could end.
If you want to kill me,
best you do it now.
This is no ordinary dagger.
Pres the jewel on its hilt
and you will see.
Should have had the strength
to do this before we invaded the city...
- What are you talking about?
- To act on what I know is right.
No matter the consequences.
- The soldiers remain out...
- Stay where are you!
He took his own life.
Then God have mercy on the
traitor, for he chose the path of the coward.
We know that both Dastan
was many things, but not a coward.
"This is no ordinary dagger."
"Press the jewel on its hilt
and you will see."
No matter the consequences.
Stop!
A moment ago you
died before my eyes.
- You pressed it...
- How did you know I would?
Because we are brothers.
On the day we left for war,
our Father told me that a true king
considers the advice of counsel,
but always listens to his heart.
You shouldn't have had
to go so far for me to believe you.
Your Majesty, the soldiers tell me that...
I see that Dastan has indeed returned.
Tus, remember what I told your!
No! A moment...
Poor Tus...so eager for the crown.
And you, Dastan, always charging in,
so desperate to prove you're
more than something the King
scraped off the street.
What a glorious mess we are.
It seemed that the bond between brothers is no
longer the sword that defends our empire.
Yes!
He was one of us.
He was a priest of the temple.
That's how Nizam discovered the existence
of the Sandglass!
They corrupted the Guardians,
infected us.
We are no longer pure.
We must hurry.
Pulley.
The pulley!
Now!
Guardians built tunnels underneath the city
as secret access to Sandglass.
If we move fast enough,
we can get there before Nizam.
That pulley descends to the Sandglass chamber.
There is only one safe path!
Faster!
Follow in my footsteps.
Nothing can touch the surface,
other than where I step.
Run, Dastan!
Run!
Dastan!
Nizam!
You killed your own family.
Sharaman was your brother!
And my curse.
I looked up to you.
Dastan!
I never understood
why my brother brought trash into the palace.
Enjoy the gutter, Dastan,
it's where you'll stay under my reign.
Tamina!
Nizam!
Don't use the Dagger to alter your path!
- It will unleash...
- Unleash what?!
Dezlnui not nothing.
Don't do this!
Stop him,
if the glass shatters
the world dies with it.
It is not my destiny, it's yours.
It always has been.
Let me go.
I won't.
- Let me go.
- I'm not letting you go!
I wish we could be together...
No!
No! No! No!
- Dastan!
- Noo!
Tamina!
No!
- Dastan!
- Tamina!
Prince Dastan!
Bis?
- You're here.
- Of course I'm here.
Our army has surrounded Alomet's palace.
The battle is over.
Not yet.
Wait!
Soldiers of Persia!
We have been deceived
into attacking this Holy City.
- Alomet, has no weapons forges...
- Dastan!
Have you gone mad?
I cannot stay silent in the face of treachery.
This war was set up by one,
trusted above above all else.
Our Uncle Nizam.
Dastan has fought hard today,
perhaps too hard.
What he needs now is to get out
out of this burning sun to rest,
gather his wits!
Why haven't we found out forges?
There are no weapons here, Uncle, and you know it.
And this spy
which has supposedly intercepted weapons
was hired by you to persuade
all of us to invade Alomet!
What is this, Dastan?
Victor's remorse?
You yourself led the attack,
brought us this great triumph!
I should never have let the attack happen.
I knew in my heart that it was wrong.
It will never be.
You will never be King.
You don't have the heart.
You will die in the shadow
of a great man.
Get him down from there before he
makes an even bigger fool of himself!
Tus...
Before we left Nasaf, Father
told you this:
that a true King considers the advice
of counsel,
but he always listens to his own heart.
Father and I were alone,
- how could you know that?
- He was right,
he knows us, he knows what we are capable of.
Just listen to your heart.
He defies your order
and leads the attack on his terms.
Tus.
Take measure here.
The spy knows the truth!
Find the spy! Bring him to me!
We'll wring it from him!
You had what every man could ever dream of.
Love, respect and family.
But that wasn't enough
for you, was it?
Princess of Alomet...
and I was misled to attack your city.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
Let me try to make amends.
It would be to our mutual advantage
that our Nations to be united by a
bond stronger than friendship.
Marriage.
Your marriage to one who is both so
conqueror, and savior, of your city.
Dastan.
Royal blood or not,
he is every bit a son to our father.
Every bit a brother to Garsiv and me.
A true Prince of Persia.
Go out there before I take your place.
Hello, Princess.
It, it is customary to accompany a proposal
with gifts
but, um, I was surprised and, alasm I'm unprepared.
I have nothing for you.
Save, that which is already yours.
Walk with me, Prince Dastan.
How can I trust
a man who breached the walls of my city?
Well, I started to think I'm no longer
the same man who breached those walls.
That's a short time for
a man to change so much?
Perhaps.
It sounds as if you have discovered something here.
What would that be?
A new spiritual awareness...
- A destiny.
- Yes. Exactly.
I believe we make own destiny, Princess.
You have an unfortunate lack of curiosity.
No doubt one
of my many flaws.
Please don't mock me, Prince.
Oh, I hardly think we know
each other well enough for that, Princess.
But I look forward to the day we do.