OVER HERE.
EVERYBODY OUT
OF THE TRUCK.
OVER TO
THE AMMOS DUMP.
GET THE HELL GOING
IN A HURRY.
CASPER, COME ON.
I HEARD
THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR PROFESSIONALS
IN AFRICA.
WHAT,
WHORES?
NO, MERCENARIES,
SARGE.
MEXICO AND LATIN
AMERICA, TOO.
I HEARD YOU GET
$1,300 A MONTH
PLUS
TRANSPORTATION.
I WANT COMBAT SOLDIERS,
CASPER, NOT TYPISTS.
I WAS TOLD TO REPORT
TO YOU, SERGEANT.
I'M HARDIN.
RIFLEMAN CHARLES HARDIN,
CORPORAL.
WHERE YOU FROM,
CHARLIE?
EL PASO.
IS THAT RIGHT?
HOW DO YOU LIKE
BEING IN THE LOUISIANA
NATIONAL GUARD?
I DON'T.
BUT THEN
I DIDN'T MUCH LIKE
BEING IN
THE TEXAS GUARD EITHER.
NOT LIKING THE TEXAS
GUARD MAKES SENSE.
NOT LIKING THE
LOUISIANA GUARD
CAN GET YOU
INTO TROUBLE WITH ME.
YOU GOT THAT?
I GOT IT.
NOW, YOU GET YOUR BUTT
ON OVER TO SECOND SQUAD.
YOU'LL RECON
WITH THEM.
CASPER,
SHOW HIM THE WAY.
INTRODUCE HIM
TO THE BOYS.
RIGHT.
[Simms] MAN, WE SURE GET ALL
THE GOOD DETAILS AROUND HERE.
[Bowden] THIS'LL BE GOOD
EXERCISE FOR YOU.
PUT A LITTLE MUSCLE
IN YOUR PANTS.
THAT'S THE LAST THING
I NEED, COACH.
UNLESS YOU WANT
TO TAKE CARE OF IT.
LISTEN, STUCKEY.
MAYBE I'LL JUST MAKE YOU AN ASS
SO YOU CAN TAKE CARE
OF IT YOURSELF.
[Men arguing]
KNOCK IT OFF!
LISTEN, STUCKEY, I LIKE
A JOKE JUST LIKE ANYBODY.
BUT I DON'T LIKE
THAT ONE.
COME ON, MAN.
I'M WITH YOU, COACH.
SPEAKING FOR MYSELF,
I LIKE WOMEN.
YEAH, WE WON'T BE
SEEING MANY OF THEM.
LIFE'S FULL
OF SURPRISES.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I'VE ARRANGED A LITTLE TREAT
FOR THE WEEKEND, BOYS.
SIX WHORES TO COMBAT
ARE WAITING ON US ALL.
THEY'LL FUCK US
IN A MORE INTERESTING WAY
THAN THE LOUISIANA
NATIONAL GUARD.
YOU AIN'T KIDDING,
ARE YOU?
I NEVER JOKE
ABOUT WOMEN.
WOMEN?
WHAT WOMEN?
HE'S GOT SOME HOOKERS AT
THE END OF THE LINE, COACH.
YOU MEAN
PROSTITUTES?
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I MEAN.
THIS IS A NEW LOW,
SPENCER.
EVEN FOR YOU.
THEY'RE SCHEDULED
TO MEET US
OUTSIDE OF
CATAHOULA.
THEY'LL BE THERE
BY THE TIME WE EMERGE
FROM THE GREAT
PRIMORDIAL SWAMP.
YOU GOT ONE
FOR ME?
ME?
YOU MEAN US,
DON'T YOU?
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE?
BOYS, THE PURPOSE
OF THE NATIONAL GUARD
IS TO KEEP YOU
DARKER BROTHERS AWAY
FROM DECENT
SOUTHERN WOMEN.
MAN!
HOWEVER, IN THE SPIRIT
OF THE NEW SOUTH
I'VE MADE
FULL ARRANGEMENTS.
HOW ABOUT YOU,
HARDIN?
I GOT A WIFE.
YOU CAN COUNT ME
OUT OF THIS ONE.
I SUPPOSE YOU'RE USED TO
MORE SERIOUS SOLDIERING
OVER IN EL PASO.
WE HAD THINGS ORGANIZED.
ALL WE DID WAS
WATCH THE BALLGAME ON TV.
SHOOT DICE AND SLEEP.
THE LOUISIANA GUARD'S
A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
THEY HAVE US DOING
IMPORTANT THINGS
LIKE BEATING UP
ON COLLEGE KIDS.
TEAR-GASSING NIGGERS.
"PLEASE,
MR. GUARDSMAN.
"NO MORE CANISTERS.
"DON'T SET
THE SHEPHERD DOGS
ON ME."
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
WE HAVE A LONG AND
NOBLE MILITARY TRADITION.
HEY, CASPER!
TURN IT OFF,
STUCKEY,
YOU DAMN,
DUMB SON OF A BITCH.
[Soldiers laughing]
IN THE REAL WORLD,
DO YOU DO SOMETHING USEFUL
OR ARE YOU LIKE
THE REST OF THE MEN
OF THE SECOND SQUAD?
I WORK FOR
TREMCO.
CHEMICAL ENGINEER.
COLLEGE MAN.
THEY'RE KIND OF RARE
IN TEXAS, AREN'T THEY?
THEY MANAGE TO
COME UP WITH ONE
EVERY NOW
AND THEN.
ONE MIGHT GET
THE IMPRESSION
YOU DON'T ENJOY
THE OCCASIONAL CHAT
WITH YOUR
FELLOW GUARDSMAN.
GUESS WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WELL, I CAN'T SAY AS I BLAME
YOU HERE AND THERE.
REECE IS UNDER THE
IMPRESSION MOST OF THE TIME
THAT HE'S
IN A DIME NOVEL.
STUCKEY,
HE'S NOT SMART ENOUGH
TO READ
A DIME NOVEL.
THE COACH, WELL...
I THINK I KNOW
THE TYPE.
LOOK, THESE GUYS
ARE OKAY.
THEY JUST WANNA HAVE
FUN WITH YOU,
BEING THE NEW BOY.
THEY'RE NOT OKAY.
THEY'RE JUST
LOUISIANA VERSIONS
OF THE SAME
DUMB REDNECKS
I'VE BEEN AROUND
MY WHOLE LIFE.
2, 3, 4.
COME ON, BOYS, COME ON.
WHEN I WAS TRAINING
IN FORT POLK ONCE,
OUR INSTRUCTOR GOT BIT.
RIGHT HERE.
BY A CORAL SNAKE.
HE JUST PUT HIS HAND
ON A LOG,
TOOK HIS MACHETE OUT
AND CUT IT RIGHT OFF.
TOOK IT RIGHT OFF.
HORSESHIT.
I SWEAR,
IT'S THE TRUTH.
FUCK YOU.
I DON'T GIVE A SHIT
IF YOU BELIEVE IT OR NOT.
FOR THOSE OF YOU
WHO ARE INTERESTED,
WE'RE GOING ON AN OVERNIGHT
RECON AND PATROL.
HUSH UP AND LISTEN UP.
WE'VE BEEN DESIGNATED
"BRAVO."
THAT IS, "BRAVO TEAM."
RECON AND SECURITY.
RENDEZVOUS POINT:
CHARLIE.
THAT IS, CHARLIE
JUST OUTSIDE CATAHOULA.
WE'RE GOING TO TRAVEL
IN FILE FORMATION
WITH MAXIMUM USE OF
COVER AND CONCEALMENT.
WE'RE TRAVELING TO MAKE TIME.
NO TENTS,
NO SLEEPING BAGS.
PONCHOS
AND LINERS ONLY.
WE'LL HAVE ALL KINDS
OF WEATHER OUT THERE.
SUN, RAIN,
COLD IN THE MORNING.
GET USED TO THIS IDEA
YOU'RE GOING IN THE WATER,
AND IT'S GOING TO BE COLD.
CRIBBS! YOU WITH US?
SURE I AM, SARGE.
I'M REALLY UP
FOR THIS ONE.
GOOD, BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING
TO BE MY PACE MAN.
HA, HA, HA!
REECE, YOU'LL BE POINT.
NOW, WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT 38 KILOMETERS.
MAKE SURE YOUR CANTEENS
ARE FILLED
AT THE WATER BUFFALO.
NOW, EACH AND EVERY
MEMBER DOES THEIR JOB.
I DON'T WANT NOBODY
DOGGING IT OUT THERE.
YOU'RE ALL BUDDIES.
YOU'RE COUNTING AND
DEPENDING ON EACH OTHER.
EVERYBODY DOES THEIR JOB.
NOW, PLEASE,
FOR ONCE IN YOUR LIFE,
TRY TO LOOK LIKE SOLDIERS.
"CIVILIAN IN PEACE.
SOLDIER IN WAR."
[All]
"I AM THE GUARD."
THAT'S RIGHT.
TRY TO REMEMBER THAT.
[Stuckey]
LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY BUILT
A WHOLE NEW OCEAN HERE.
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO BE
AT THIS COORDINATE.
EITHER THE MAP
IS WRONG
OR ALL OF A SUDDEN
I CAN'T FIND MY WAY
AROUND THE BLOCK.
THE CHANNEL
MUST HAVE SHIFTED
WITH WINTER RAINS.
WHAT SHOULD BE LAND
IS UNDER WATER.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO RAISE COMPANY?
THERE'S NO NEED FOR THAT.
IT'S REAL SIMPLE.
EITHER WE CAN
GET ACROSS
GOING DOWN
THIS POINT OF LAND
AND IT DON'T
LOOK GOOD
OR WE GO
ALL THE WAY BACK
AND START OVER.
[Whistles]
OVER HERE.
DAMN.
SOMEBODY SHOT RUDOLPH.
WHO DO YOU THINK
THESE CANOES BELONG TO?
US.
THEY BELONG TO
AN INDIGENOUS PERSON.
DON'T FUCK AROUND
WITH THEM.
THINK THEY FLOAT?
HELL, YES.
THEY'RE PIROGUES.
CAJUNS BACK HERE
USE THEM ALL THE TIME.
WELL, THEY AIN'T
USING THEM NOW.
WHAT SAY WE TAKE THEM
DOWN THE BAYOU?
YEAH.
I CAN DEAL WITH THAT,
THE WAY MY BACK FEELS.
WE MIGHT
MAKE CATAHOULA
AND I'LL PUT THEM WOMEN
UNDER MARTIAL LAW.
WHAT WOMEN
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
SPENCER'S RUNNING
SOME LADIES.
HEAR HE'S GOT SOME SKIRTS
WAITING FOR US.
[Spencer]
ALL SET.
NOLEEN AND HER
BAYOU QUEENS.
JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR MORALE.
REALLY?
LET ME ADD, SERGEANT
THAT THESE WOMEN
ARE EXPECTING SOME
SMALL-UNIT
MILITARY PENETRATION.
HA! HA!
WE SHOULDN'T TAKE
THE CANOES.
THEY'RE NOT OURS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
LET'S GET IN THEM
AND TAKE OFF.
HOLD ON, FUNGO.
NOBODY GAVE YOU
AN ORDER.
HOW ELSE
WE GONNA GET THERE?
MAYBE YOU GOT
A POINT THERE, REECE.
HELL, YES.
LET'S MOVE.
WAIT.
HOW WILL THE RIGHTFUL OWNERS
GET THOSE BOATS BACK
WHEN THERE'S NO OTHER
ACCESS TO THE FAR SHORE?
WE ONLY NEED THREE.
THEY CAN USE
THE OTHER ONES
TO GET THEM BACK.
A LITTLE R AND R
NEVER HURTS.
CATAHOULA, HERE WE COME.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
[Flies buzz]
OKAY. BOWDEN,
WRITE THEM A NOTE.
YES, SIR.
[Men yelling]
ALL RIGHT,
GET THOSE SHIELD POTS OFF.
HOOK THEM ONTO YOUR BELT.
SHAPE UP NOW!
[Sgt. Poole]
SHAPE UP.
GET IN THE GODDAMN BOAT
AND LOOK LIKE SOLDIERS.
COME ON, FOLKS.
HEY!
LOOK OVER THERE!
THERE THEY ARE.
THESE MUST BE THEIR CANOES.
HEY, THERE. READ THE NOTE.
WE LEFT YOU A NOTE.
DUMB COON ASSES.
THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I HOPE THEY FIND MY NOTE.
MAYBE THEY ONLY
SPEAK FRENCH.
WELL, DOES ANYBODY
SPEAK FRENCH?
YEAH.
VOULEZ-VOUS FUCK ME?
REECE,
KNOCK THAT SHIT OFF.
WE'RE BRINGING THEM BACK.
LET 'EM HAVE IT!
TAKE NO PRISONERS.
STUCKEY, YOU ASSHOLE!
CASPER, GET YOUR BOAT
OVER TO THAT POINT
OF LAND NOW.
[Gunshot]
SARGE.
POOLE!
[Soldiers screaming]
HIT IT.
TAKE COVER.
THEY SHOT HIM.
[Reece]
GET DOWN!
SPENCER, OVER HERE.
OVER THIS WAY.
JESUS CHRIST,
HIS HEAD!
THEY'RE STILL SHOOTING.
WHERE ARE THEY?
I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T SEE THEM.
GET DOWN, MAN!
WE GOTTA GET POOLE.
YOU TAKE CARE OF IT.
I'LL GO
AND LOOK OUT FOR THEM.
COME ON.
[Casper]
COME ON, LET'S GO.
[Unloading gun]
GODDAMN YOU,
STUCKEY.
NO SIGN OF THEM.
WHERE THE HELL'S
THAT DAMN MAP?
[Simms] HE WAS HOLDING IT.
I REMEMBER.
DAMN.
COMPASS IS GONE.
HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?
IT'S IN THE WATER.
WHAT THE HELL YOU THINK?
AND GUESS WHO PUT IT THERE?
THAT'S RIGHT,
BOWDEN.
WHAT THE HELL'D YOU
TIP US OVER FOR?
I DIDN'T TIP THE CANOES.
YOU STARTED IT.
IT'S YOUR FAULT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU FUCKING PANICKED,
YOU ASSHOLE.
I'LL SHOW YOU PANIC,
YOU FUCKING REDNECK.
[Soldiers arguing and yelling]
WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS?
WE'RE ALL
SOLDIERS TOGETHER.
DAMN IT, YOU GUYS,
SHAKE HANDS.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
OKAY, GOOD.
SIMMS,
WHERE'S YOUR RADIO?
IN THE WATER,
WHERE DO YOU THINK?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
IN CHARGE OF IT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
LOOK.
WE HAVE A DEAD MAN HERE.
NOW,
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
LET'S GO GET
THE COCKSUCKERS
WHO SHOT POOLE.
I'LL DECIDE WHERE
WE'RE GOING AND WHEN.
LET'S HAUL ASS.
WHAT ABOUT
SGT. POOLE?
I SAY LEAVE HIM,
UNLESS YOU
WANT TO CARRY HIM.
[Casper]
HE'S AN AMERICAN SOLDIER.
HE'S GOT A BRONZE STAR,
A PURPLE HEART,
A VIETNAM SERVICE MEDAL.
WE'RE NOT LEAVING HIM.
THE QUICKER WE GET OUT,
THE QUICKER
THEY CAN COME FOR HIM.
WE'LL PURSUE OUR MISSION.
IT'S OUR RESPONSIBILITY.
COME ON, CASPER,
LET'S GET GOING.
NO, GODDAMN IT,
WE'RE NOT LEAVING HIM HERE.
WHO SAYS?
I SAY.
I'VE GOT THE STRIPES.
I'M IN CHARGE
AND I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
ANYMORE SHIT ABOUT IT.
NOW, LET'S JUST GO.
STUCKEY, YOU WERE SURE
ONE DUMB SON OF A BITCH,
FIRING THAT MACHINE GUN.
YEAH, STUCKEY.
NOBODY GAVE YOU
AN ORDER TO FIRE.
IT WAS ONLY
A GODDAMN JOKE.
IT WAS ONLY BLANKS.
FORGET IT.
FORGET IT?
SHIT.
THIS MORON GETS
SOMEBODY KILLED
AND YOU SAY,
"FORGET IT?"
I GOT SOMETHING
FOR YOU BOYS TO REMEMBER,
STUCKEY
DIDN'T SHOOT POOLE.
BIG THING IS,
AFTER WE GET POOLE
TO THE HEADQUARTERS
WE'LL COME BACK
AND GET THESE CAJUNS.
HELL YES.
ALL WE NEED TO DO IS SWIM
A COUPLE OF HUNDRED YARDS
AND THEN FIND THEM
IN THAT FOREST.
AFTER WE DONE THAT,
WE CAN CAPTURE THEM AND
SHOOT THEM WITH OUR BLANKS.
[Reece]
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS BAYOU FORKS TO THE EAST.
EASIEST TO GET
WHERE WE WANT THAT WAY.
[Spencer]
WE SHOULD HEAD NORTH.
INTERSTATE'S NORTH.
[Reece] WE'RE GOING
TO THE INTERSTATE.
[Spencer]
NOT IF WE GO EAST.
[Reece]
FUCK YOU.
WHAT THE FUCK
DO YOU KNOW?
[Spencer] I KNOW THE BIG
FIREBALL RISES IN THE EAST,
AND WE'RE WALKING
RIGHT INTO IT.
[Reece] YOU GOTTA GO EAST
TO GO NORTH.
[Spencer]
YEAH, RIGHT.
[Cribbs] YOU WANT TO
RUN THAT BY ME ONCE MORE?
WE GOT TO GO WHERE
TO GO WHERE?
[Hardin] CAN SOMEBODY
FIGURE OUT WHERE WE'RE GOING,
AND QUICK?
[Casper]
SHUT UP.
IT'S MY RESPONSIBILITY,
AND WE'RE GOING EAST
TO GET NORTH.
[Spencer] GO AHEAD
AND DO WHAT YOU WANT.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT THE
HELL I'M GONNA DO, SPENCER.
[Casper] NOW, LET'S MOVE
YOUR ASSES. COME ON.
TURKEY.
TURKEY MEAT,
TURKEY SKIN,
CRACKER MEAL,
TURKEY FAT, SALT.
SMOKES MADE IT THROUGH
THE WATER, HUH?
YEAH, I SAVED A PACK.
LUCKY, HUH?
MAYBE IT'S ABOUT TIME
WE DIVIDE UP THE BULLETS.
WHAT BULLETS?
REECE HAS GOT
SOME AMMO.
HE ALWAYS
BRINGS SOME ALONG
JUST IN CASE HE RUNS
INTO ANY BIG GAME.
BACK AT BIVOUAC
HE WAS SHOWING OFF
A BOXFUL OF 5.56S.
WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS ANYWAY, MAN?
SOME MILITARY SECRET
OR SOMETHING?
NO WAY.
I BROUGHT ALONG
ONE BOX OF SHELLS
FOR MY OWN USE.
I'M LOCKED
AND LOADED DOWN
IN CASE I MEET THE SONS
OF BITCHES THAT SHOT POOLE.
LET ME SEE YOUR WEAPON.
YOU JUST STAY ON BACK.
GIVE ME THE AMMO,
WE'LL DIVIDE IT EVENLY.
WE'LL SHARE THEM.
BULLSHIT.
IT'S MINE, AND THAT'S IT.
IT'S NOT RIGHT, REECE.
GIVE HIM THE BULLETS.
IT'S A MILITARY SITUATION.
I'M GIVING YOU
A DIRECT ORDER, REECE.
GIVE THEM TO ME.
YOU COME ONE STEP CLOSER,
CASPER,
AND I'LL GIVE YOU
SOMETHIN' ELSE.
THAT'S A COURT-MARTIAL
OFFENSE, MAN.
GIVE ME THE AMMO,
AND WE'LL DROP IT RIGHT HERE.
OTHERWISE I'M GONNA
TURN YOUR ASS IN.
I DON'T GIVE A SHIT WHAT YOU--
QUIT FUCKING AROUND
AND GIVE HIM THE RIFLE.
NOW.
I'LL TAKE HARDIN'S
AND GIVE THEM TO HIM.
OKAY.
HERE'S YOUR AMMO.
BLADE TO THE THROAT, HUH?
IS THAT HOW THEY DO
THESE THINGS IN EL PASO?
YEAH. THAT'S HOW THEY DO
THINGS WHERE I GREW UP.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SOME KIND
OF CHEMICAL ENGINEER.
I AM.
I'M OUT OF THE HABIT
OF SPENDING TIME
WITH A BUNCH OF
GUN-TOTING REDNECKS.
WELL, YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
IN LOUISIANA,
WE DON'T CARRY GUNS.
WE CARRY ROPES.
RC COLAS AND MOON PIES.
WE'RE NOT TOO SMART,
BUT WE HAVE
A REAL GOOD TIME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
CRIBBS?
I'M ON SENTRY.
YOU WANT A HIT
OF SOME OF THIS STUFF?
HOW CAN YOU SMOKE
THAT CRAP?
I AIN'T ON YOUR TEAM,
COACH.
YOU COULDN'T MAKE
THE SQUAD.
THAT STUFF KILLS
YOUR WILL TO WIN.
HOW'D YOUR BOYS DO
THIS YEAR?
THIS WAS A REBUILDING YEAR.
WE HAD INJURIES
TO KEY PERSONNEL.
WE FINISHED 3 AND 7.
WHAT DO YOU DO
FOR A LIVING?
I PICK UP
A LITTLE CASH PIMPING
BUT MOST OF WHAT
I TURN OVER
COMES FROM SELLING DOPE
TO HIGH-SCHOOL KIDS.
YOU'RE LUCKY
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
NO, IT'S TRUE.
SOME OF MY BEST CUSTOMERS
ARE AT FREMONT HIGH.
THEY WERE 10 AND 0
THIS YEAR, COACH.
I DON'T HAVE TO LISTEN
TO THIS BULLSHIT.
HEY, LONNIE.
HUH.
WHEN WE GONNA KICK
THAT BOY'S ASS
ALL THE WAY
BACK TO EL PASO?
SOON AS WE GET UP
TO THE RENDEZVOUS.
THEN WE GONNA COME BACK
FOR THESE COON ASSES
THAT GOT POOLE.
LONNIE,
DO YOU THINK
THIS WHOLE THING
IS MY FAULT?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S DONE.
HEY.
HOW CAN YOU GUYS
PLAY CARDS
WITH SGT. POOLE
LYING DEAD OVER THERE?
YOU GOT ANOTHER IDEA
ABOUT WHAT
WE SHOULD BE DOING?
JUST DON'T SEEM RIGHT.
POOLE DOESN'T CARE.
HE'S DEAD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ANY OF US
CAN DO ABOUT IT.
WHY NOT PLAY CARDS?
JUST DON'T SEEM RIGHT.
IT'S UP THIS WAY.
OVER THERE.
OKAY. COME ON.
KEEP MOVING.
SPENCER, WHAT ABOUT
COMPANY COMMAND?
SHOULDN'T THEY BE
WONDERING ABOUT US?
NO, NOT YET.
WE'VE BEEN OUT OF CONTACT
FOR 12 HOURS.
THEY SHOULD BE
LOOKING FOR US.
NO WAY.
IT'S THE NATIONAL
GUARD, REMEMBER?
WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO MEET THE TRUCKS
20 MINUTES AGO.
IN ANOTHER
HOUR AND A HALF,
THE TRUCKS WILL SHOW UP.
AT 2:00,
THEY'LL ASK
IF ANYONE'S SEEN US.
AT 3:00, THEY'LL START
CHECKING THE BARS.
AT 4:00, THEY'LL
REALLY GET STEAMED.
AT 5:00, IT'LL OCCUR TO
SOMEONE MAYBE WE GOT LOST.
AT 6:00, CAPTAIN'LL CONSIDER
CALLING THE BATTALION.
AT 7:30, HE WILL.
THE BATTALION WILL SAY
IT'S TOO LATE.
NOTHING ANYONE
CAN DO TILL MORNING.
THERE'S A CABIN.
[Reece]
IT'S HIM, THAT SON OF A BITCH.
WHERE'S THE OTHERS?
THERE'S MORE.
FAR AS I CAN TELL,
HE'S ALONE.
WE'LL CAPTURE HIM.
I CAN GET HIM
FROM HERE.
THIS IS THE LOUISIANA
NATIONAL GUARD,
NOT THE GODDAMN
VIGILANTES.
NOW, LET'S MOVE
OUR ASSES.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, HERE'S THE PROGRAM.
WE FOUND ONE OF THE
CAJUNS THAT SHOT POOLE.
WE'RE GONNA CAPTURE HIM.
HE'S UP ABOUT
250 METERS UP AHEAD.
YOU SURE
HE'S ONE OF THEM?
OF COURSE.
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK?
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
TALKING TO HIM
BEFORE BLOWING
HIS HEAD OFF?
SIMMS, REECE,
STUCKEY AND I
ARE THE ADVANCE UNIT.
THE INITIAL ACTION
MUST BE DECISIVE.
SURPRISE IS THE KEY.
HEY, CASPER.
DID YOU HEAR
WHAT I SAID?
I HEARD YOU.
WE'LL TALK TO HIM
AFTER WE CAPTURE HIM.
THE REST OF YOU
ARE REAR ELEMENT.
STAY 100 METERS BACK
AND KEEP DOWN.
WE'LL MARRY UP AFTER
THE OBJECTIVE'S SEALED OFF.
LET'S GO.
WAIT.
I VOLUNTEER
FOR THE ADVANCE PARTY.
FORGET IT.
YOU DO WHAT THE HELL
YOU'RE TOLD!
JESUS, THIS IS BULLSHIT.
THAT'S JUST
WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
YOU ALWAYS
GET OUT OF
EVERYTHING?
I DIDN'T SEE YOU
VOLUNTEER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M NOT GONNA RIDE SHOTGUN
WITH THESE DUMBBELLS.
FOUR OF THEM
WITH AUTOMATIC RIFLES
AGAINST SOME
SWAMP RAT.
I'LL MAKE IT EVEN MONEY.
[Cribbs]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, COACH?
SHUT UP.
AH!
LET'S GO. COME ON.
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST.
HARDIN,
GET THE HELL AWAY
FROM THAT PRISONER.
I TOLD YOU TO STAY BACK.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED,
SERGEANT.
BULLSHIT.
YOU USED
YOUR REAL BULLETS,
JUST PISSED THEM AWAY.
I DIDN'T PANIC.
ALL RIGHT. EASY NOW.
WE GOTTA INTERROGATE HIM.
[Speaking Cajun French]
SURRENDER.
DROP THE KNIFE.
[Speaking Cajun French]
SON OF A BITCH.
I SAID, "DROP THE KNIFE!"
[Speaking Cajun French]
ARGH!
SON OF A BITCH.
YOU COULD HAVE
BUSTED HIS JAW.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE WANT HIM
TO TALK.
YOU ALMOST KNOCKED HIS MOUTH
CLEAR DOWN TO HIS ASS.
JESUS CHRIST, SIMMS.
WE GOTTA
INTERROGATE THE MAN.
HOW CAN HE TALK TO US
IF YOU GO AND BREAK HIS JAW?
THAT'S HIS
FUCKING PROBLEM.
WHAT DID YOU DO
THAT FOR?
THAT SON OF A BITCH
SHOT POOLE.
OH, FUCK HIM.
COME ON, LONNIE.
LET'S GO SEE WHAT'S INSIDE.
CAN YOU TALK?
[Speaking French]
WHERE'S YOUR BUDDIES?
HOW MANY OF THEM
ARE THERE?
[Speaking French]
WHAT KIND OF SHIT
IS THAT?
THIS CAJUN GOT HIMSELF
A COUPLE OF MINK THIS MORNING.
GODDAMN,
THIS BOY'S A POACHER.
WE POACHED
THE POACHER.
HEY, LONNIE.
YEAH, HE'S SHINED
HIS LAST JIGGER.
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON HERE, CASPER?
WE GOT OURSELVES
A PRISONER.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I THINK YOU GUYS HAVE DONE
A WONDERFUL JOB.
DID YOU HAVE TO CUT
HIS ARM OFF, TOO?
I'D SAY HE USED
THIS DYNAMITE TO KILL FISH.
WE GOT US A GENUINE OUTLAW.
CASPER, ALL KINDS
OF GOOD SHIT IN HERE.
SIMMS,
I DON'T WANT YOU
HITTING HIM AGAIN.
YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT BELTED HIM?
GODDAMN RIGHT.
NOW, WHAT YOU WANNA
GO AND DO THAT FOR?
I DUNNO.
JUST GOT PISSED.
HELL, MAN,
THIS ARMY BULLSHIT
IS GETTING TO YOU.
BEANS, HOMINY, SPINACH.
THIS IS BETTER
THAN SEA RATIONS.
GUNS, KNIVES,
AMMO, SUPPLIES.
WE GOT IT ALL RIGHT HERE.
I'D SAY WE'VE CONDUCTED
OURSELVES
A PRETTY
SUCCESSFUL LITTLE RAID.
WE CAN PACK
THIS SHIT OUT LATER.
LET'S GO INTERROGATE
THE PRISONER.
CRIBBS.
YEAH?
TIE UP THE PRISONER.
HOW AM I
TO TIE UP A MAN
WHEN HE ONLY HAS ONE ARM
TO DO THE TYING?
[Spencer] MAYBE WE OUGHT
TO TRY TALKING TO HIM.
DO YOU SPEAK ENGLISH?
DOES ANYBODY HERE
SPEAK FRENCH?
BOWDEN?
YEAH.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU,
COACH?
DON'T BOTHER ME.
NOT NOW, NOT EVER.
WELL, I'LL GIVE IT A TRY.
I HAD A COUPLE OF YEARS
OF  PARLEZ-VOUS  IN HIGH SCHOOL.
UH.
[Speaking French]
SHIT, I CAN'T REMEMBER
HOW TO SAY "SHOOT."
HOW ABOUT, "BANG-BANG"?
[Speaking French]
BANG
[Speaking Cajun French]
I THINK HE'S SAYING
HE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
IT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE
ANY FRENCH I EVER STUDIED.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
I SAW HIM.
I WAS THERE, TOO,
I COULDN'T SWEAR TO NOTHING.
I CAN'T REMEMBER
IF THE MAN HAD ONE ARM.
HE WAS 100 YARDS AWAY,
REMEMBER?
WE'LL TAKE
THIS PRISONER BACK
TO STAFF COMMAND
FOR INTERROGATION.
THEN HE CAN
STAND TRIAL.
EVERYONE OVER
TO THE RAIN BARREL.
FILL YOUR CANTEENS.
I WANT TO
PUT SOME MILES
BETWEEN US
AND HERE.
LONNIE.
[Glass shattering]
BOWDEN, YOU DUMMY,
THERE'S DYNAMITE IN THERE.
HIT IT!
GET DOWN!
THAT'LL TEACH HIM
TO FUCK WITH US.
YEAH, RIGHT.
CAN'T ARGUE WITH THAT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, BOWDEN?
YOU BLEW THE SHIT
OUT OF EVERYTHING.
WELL, I DO WHAT I DO.
WHAT'D YOU PAINT THE CROSS
ON YOUR CHEST FOR?
IT WAS PART OF THE JOKE.
WHAT JOKE?
IT'S A CORPORAL JOKE, PRIVATE.
WHAT THE HELL, BOWDEN?
YOU DUMB SON OF A BITCH.
YOU BLEW UP ALL THE
SUPPLIES WE CAPTURED.
ALL THE GUNS,
THE AMMO, AND THE FOOD.
CASPER.
SOMETIMES YOU MUST ABANDON
PRINCIPLES TO DO WHAT'S RIGHT.
MAYBE WE BETTER
FIND THE INTERSTATE.
LET'S GET GOING, CASPER.
YOUR LITTLE RAID'S
ABOUT FINISHED.
YEAH, RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, MOVE OUT.
GET ON.
THAT DUMBSHIT, BOWDEN.
DEMOLITION
OF THAT DAMN SHACK,
WE LOST EVERYTHING
WE CAPTURED.
YEAH, AND IT COULD'VE
WORKED AS A SIGNAL
FOR THIS BASTARD'S RELATIVES
TO GATHER ROUND.
YOU THINK
WE STILL GOTTA WORRY
ABOUT THOSE
COONEY ASSES?
HELL, YES.
WE GOT A LOT MORE WORRY
ABOUT THAN ME AND YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME.
YEAH, THEY THINK
YOU BOYS ARE BAD LUCK.
THEY MIGHT BE RIGHT.
I'VE HUNG AROUND
NIGGERS MY WHOLE LIFE
AND I HAVEN'T
GOTTEN A BREAK YET.
LISTEN, FELLAS.
SORRY ABOUT THAT
INCIDENT BACK THERE.
I GUESS I WAS A LITTLE, UH,
OVER-EMOTIONAL.
YEAH,
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
YOU COULD ALSO SAY
YOU WERE TOTALLY
OUT OF CONTROL.
I'M SORRY,
BUT I ADMIRED SGT. POOLE
A GREAT DEAL.
I LIKED HIM A LOT.
I HOPE THAT'LL EXCUSE
MY EXCESSIVE BEHAVIOR.
SURE.
SAY, COACH...
AT THE RISK OF A PUNCH
IN THE MOUTH--
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT, HARDIN.
WHY'D YOU PAINT
THE CROSS ON YOUR CHEST?
YOU KNOW THE AVENGING ANGEL
AND ALL THAT?
I THOUGHT AT LEAST
YOU MIGHT GET IT.
SORRY TO DISAPPOINT YOU, COACH.
OH, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I THINK I SHOULD APOLOGIZE
TO THE REST OF THE MEN.
[Walking through water]
I GOT NEWS FOR YOU.
HE'S NUTS.
I MEAN REALLY FUCKING NUTS.
THIS IS NOT EXACTLY NEWS
TO THE REST OF US.
IS THAT ALL
YOU'VE GOT TO SAY?
AFTER THAT WHOLE NUMBER
HE PULLED BACK THERE?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO SAY?
HE'S A DUMB
SON OF A BITCH.
HE'S REAL EMOTIONAL
AND HE GOT PISSED OFF.
"HE GOT PISSED OFF."
SO HE PAINTS HIMSELF RED,
LAUGHS LIKE A FUCKING MANIAC
AND BLOWS OFF
LIKE A VOLCANO.
WHAT IF HE IS CRAZY?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO DO ABOUT IT?
PUT HIM IN A CAGE?
SHOOT HIM?
EITHER ONE SOUNDS OKAY TO ME.
ANY CHANCE
WE'LL EVER GET OUT OF HERE?
DAMN RIGHT WE ARE.
I FIGURE IT'S TWO HOURS TOP
AND WE HIT THE I-10.
WHAT'S ALL THIS
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
DON'T MEAN NOTHING.
JUST SOME DUDE
DRYING HIS SKINS.
IT'S A FUNNY WAY
OF STRETCHING A SKIN.
YOU SURE THEY WEREN'T
LEFT FOR US?
THERE'S EIGHT OF THEM.
SO WHAT?
THERE'S EIGHT OF US.
WHAT ABOUT THIS SHIT?
YOU KNOW WHAT IT MEANS?
[Speaking Cajun French]
COME ON,
LET'S KEEP GOING.
RIGHT.
WE'RE NOT DOING ANY GOOD HERE
NO MATTER WHY THEY WERE LEFT.
[Stuckey]
GODDAMN IT, CASPER,
WHERE'S THE HIGHWAY?
IT'S BEEN HOURS.
PROBABLY RIGHT UP
AHEAD HERE.
CAN'T BE TOO FAR.
[Spencer]
RIGHT.
USED TO RUN RIGHT
THROUGH HERE.
THOSE ECOLOGY BOYS
MUST HAVE MOVED IT.
[Casper]
FUCK YOU, SPENCER.
ALL RIGHT, HOLD UP.
EVERYBODY TAKE FIVE.
I'M GONNA GO GET
OUR BEARINGS.
WITH WHAT? WE DON'T HAVE
A COMPASS, REMEMBER?
EVER HEAR OF TAKING
A READING OFF THE SUN?
SURE. RISES IN THE EAST,
SETS IN THE WEST.
INTERSTATE'S NORTH.
IF YOU ASK ME THAT'S NOT
WHERE WE'RE HEADED,
SO WHY DON'T YOU GO
READ THE SUN?
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I'M GONNA DO. THANKS.
SAY, MAN, THIS CAT
KNOW WHAT HE DOING?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THEN WHY THE HELL
ARE WE FOLLOWING HIM?
HE'S GOT STRIPES,
THAT'S WHY.
[Reece] MAYBE SOME
OF YOU BOYS
OUGHT TO REMEMBER
THAT THIS IS
A MILITARY OPERATION.
COMING FROM YOU, REECE,
THAT'S A REAL CLASSIC.
[Dogs barking]
HEY.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
DOGS, MAN. WHAT YOU THINK?
IT'S HUNTING DOGS.
HUNTING DOGS MEAN HUNTERS.
THEY CAN SHOW US
THE WAY OUT OF HERE.
GETTING CLOSE.
YEAH.
GREAT!
CASPER, WE GOT SOME
HUNTING BOYS NEARBY.
THEY CAN SHOW US
THE WAY OUT OF HERE, CASPER.
THEY CAN SHOW US THE WAY OUT.
[Dogs barking]
[Dogs growling]
LONNIE.
ARGH!
GODDAMN IT.
GODDAMN, HE GOT ME.
DAMN BASTARDS.
SHIT! OH, SHIT.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HARDIN, HOW BAD?
IS HE OKAY?
I THINK SO. SHIT!
SPENCER?
YEAH.
REECE?
SONS OF BITCHES!
GODDAMN, SICKING THEIR
GODDAMN DOGS ON US!
HOW COULD
THEY DO THAT?
THEY SICKED THEIR
GODDAMN DOGS ON US!
REECE!
KNOCK IT OFF, DAMN IT!
THEY WEREN'T
HIS DOGS.
THE HELL
THEY WEREN'T.
WHOSE SIDE ARE
YOU ON, ANYWAY?
WELL, I AIN'T
ON YOURS, REECE,
THAT'S FOR
DAMN SURE.
REECE,
KNOCK IT OFF!
ALL OF YOU,
KNOCK IT OFF.
THAT'S JUST WHAT
THE ENEMY WANTS,
IS US FIGHTING
AMONG OURSELVES.
GODDAMNIT.
EVERYBODY
JUST TAKE FIVE
AND PULL
YOURSELVES TOGETHER.
AND YOU
GO COOL OFF.
COME ON, MAN.
SPENCER?
YEAH?
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
THE FUCK'S GOING ON HERE.
I DON'T GET YOU.
WELL, I'LL MAKE IT
REAL SIMPLE.
MY COMPANY TRANSFERS ME
TO BATON ROUGE.
I BEEN DOWN HERE
ABOUT 6 MONTHS.
NOW, I DON'T KNOW
A GODDAMN THING
ABOUT THE SWAMPS OF LOUISIANA.
I GET SENT ON SOME BULLSHIT
MILITARY EXERCISE
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
GUYS START COMING AT US
FROM OUT OF THE TREES.
NOW, I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN:
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON HERE?
AND I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I'M JUST A CITY BOY.
YOU GOT A QUESTION
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
I HAVEN'T THE SLIGHTEST
FUCKING IDEA.
WE RAN INTO SOME
REAL WEIRD PEOPLE
AND MAYBE THEY'RE
TRYING TO KILL US.
ALL BECAUSE SOME ASSHOLE
FIRED BLANKS
OUT OF HIS
DAMN MACHINE GUN.
YEAH.
BECAUSE A BUNCH OF ASSHOLES
STOLE SOME BOATS.
YEAH.
[Reece]
CASPER, HE'S GETTING HEAVY.
IT CAN'T BE TOO
MUCH FARTHER.
WHY DON'T WE LEAVE HIM
AND COME BACK?
[Casper] NO,
I TOLD YOU BEFORE.
THIS SON OF A BITCH
WEIGHS A TON.
[Casper]
DON'T CALL POOLE THAT.
WELL,
HE CAN'T HEAR ME.
WELL, I CAN.
SHIT, CASPER,
THE COCKSUCKER'S DEAD.
I'M JUST TALKING
ABOUT THE BODY.
GODDAMN IT, REECE
I TOLD YOU I DIDN'T
WANT TO HEAR YOU
CALLING HIM
ANY OF THAT SHIT.
WATCH OUT.
WHAT?
WHAT YOU
ALMOST STEPPED IN.
[Casper]
JESUS CHRIST!
LOOK AT THEM
BASTARDS.
JUST LIKE
A STEEL PUSSY.
WHAT KIND OF WOMEN
YOU BEEN HANGING OUT WITH?
ALL LAID OUT.
SEVEN OF THEM.
LIKE THE RABBITS.
THERE WERE 8 RABBITS.
THEN HOW COME THERE'S
ONLY 7 OF THESE?
DID WE LOSE
ANYBODY?
THEY WERE
SET FOR US?
EITHER US,
OR THE LAST SEVEN BEARS
IN THE STATE OF LOUISIANA.
HEY.
[Speaking French]
WHAT'D YOU
ASK HIM?
I ASKED HIM WHAT
THEY WERE DOING THERE.
YOU SON OF A BITCH,
ARE THERE ANY MORE?
HUH? HUH?
I'M TALKING TO YOU!
REECE, CUT IT OUT.
COME ON, KNOCK IT OFF.
NOW, LOOK.
THEY DIDN'T GET US
AND THEY'RE NOT GONNA.
LET'S SADDLE UP.
WE'RE WASTING TIME.
THE INTERSTATE
AIN'T THAT FAR.
NOW, LET'S MOVE OUT.
CRIBBS, YOU TAKE POINT.
COME ON, TYRONE!
DAMN, CASPER,
I DON'T SEE WHY I'M POINT.
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THE HIGHWAY IS.
YOU'RE ALWAYS
TALKING LIKE YOU KNOW.
WHY DON'T YOU
COME UP HERE AND BE POINT?
[Casper]
NO UNNECESSARY NOISE
AND NO TALKING IN FORMATION.
ARGH!
CRIBBS!
JESUS CHRIST, CRIBBS!
[Bowden]
OUR FATHER, WHO ART IN HEAVEN,
HALLOWED BE THY NAME
THY KINGDOM COME,
THY WILL BE DONE
ON EARTH AS IT IS IN HEAVEN.
GIVE US THIS DAY
OUR DAILY BREAD.
AND FORGIVE US
OUR TRESPASSES
AS WE FORGIVE THOSE
WHO TRESPASS AGAINST US.
LEAD US NOT INTO TEMPTATION
BUT DELIVER US FROM EVIL.
FOR THINE IS THE KINGDOM...
THINE IS THE KINGDOM...
AND THE POWER
AND THE GLORY,
FOREVER. AMEN.
WE GIVE THIS PRAYER
AS DEAD MEN
ASKING FOR
OUR SALVATION.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ANY
MORE OF THAT KIND OF TALK.
NOW, WE'RE AT WAR,
AND THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
I WANT YOU TO START
LOOKING LIKE SOLDIERS
AND NOT LIKE MAILMEN.
WEAPONS CARRIED
AT THE READY.
NOW, WE'VE ONLY GOT ABOUT
A HALF HOUR OF DAYLIGHT LEFT.
SO, THIS IS IT.
WE'LL BIVOUAC HERE.
A CLEARING THIS BIG
WILL MAKE IT TOUGH
FOR THOSE BASTARDS
TO COME SNEAK UP ON US.
ALL RIGHT.
CASPER, WAIT A SECOND.
LET'S TALK
A FEW THINGS OVER.
TOMORROW MORNING,
HELICOPTERS WILL BE
LOOKING FOR US.
GOOD CHANCE
THEY'LL FIND US,
IF WE STAY
IN CLEAR GROUND LIKE THIS.
SO, ALL WE HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT UNTIL THEN
IS THE CAJUNS, RIGHT?
WE DON'T KNOW
THE ENEMY'S STRENGTH
OR HIS DISPOSITION.
HE MAY HAVE THE ADVANTAGE
OF FAMILIAR TERRAIN
BUT WE HAVE THE ADVANTAGE
OF MILITARY TRAINING.
THAT'S A TERRIFIC SPEECH,
BUT I WANT TO IMPROVE
OUR ODDS A BIT.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING AFTER, SPENCER?
[Spencer] MAYBE THEY WANT
THIS TRAPPER BACK.
MAYBE HE'S ALL
THEY WANT.
LET'S TAKE THE CHANCE
AND LET HIM GO.
THAT MAN KILLED POOLE.
THE ONLY PLACE HE'S GOING
IS WITH US.
WE DON'T KNOW
THAT HE KILLED POOLE.
HE'S JUST THE FIRST CAJUN
WE RAN INTO.
SPENCER,
YOU KNOW
THEY'RE FIXING TO KILL US ALL.
YOU GOT IT.
LOOK, I'M TIRED OF HEARING
ABOUT ALL THIS.
REECE, YOU AND STUCKEY
GAG THE PRISONER
AND TIE HIM TO A TREE.
SIMMS, GO ON SENTRY.
CASPER,
YOU'RE A DUMB ASSHOLE!
YOU LISTEN TO ME, SPENCER,
AND YOU LISTEN REAL GOOD.
NOW, TOMORROW MORNING,
WE'RE HEADING NORTH
WITH THE PRISONER.
THE MAN WHO KILLED POOLE.
THE MAN WHOSE BUDDIES
KILLED TYRONE CRIBBS.
IN CASE YOU'VE FORGOTTEN,
SPENCER,
THEY WERE FRIENDS OF OURS.
NOW, LET'S ALL GET UNPACKED
AND BEDDED DOWN.
NO FIRE TONIGHT.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M OKAY.
YOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT
ABOUT THE TRAPPER.
WHY THE HELL
DIDN'T YOU SAY ANYTHING?
MAYBE I CAN'T BELIEVE
ANY OF THIS SHIT, THAT'S WHY.
HUH.
WELL, LET ME KNOW
WHEN YOU START.
LOOK, THE PROBLEM ISN'T
WHAT THE HELL I BELIEVE IN
OR DON'T BELIEVE IN.
WELL, WHAT IS?
HOW LONG
WE'RE GONNA FOLLOW
THIS DUMB BASTARD
CASPER.
LOOKS TO ME
LIKE HE'S LEADING US
AROUND IN CIRCLES.
AND?
MAYBE WE NEED
A NEW LEADER.
YOU VOLUNTEERING
FOR THE JOB?
I'M THE NEW BOY,
REMEMBER?
YOU KNOW THESE GUYS.
IT'S YOUR MOVE.
BESIDES, I'M NOT
THE VOLUNTEERING TYPE.
HA! HA! HA!
YOU'RE TERRIFIC, HARDIN.
YOU DON'T WANT TO VOLUNTEER,
BUT YOU DON'T MIND
VOLUNTEERING ME
FOR THE COURT-MARTIAL.
FUCK YOU.
I GOT SOMETHING
TO TELL YOU, CASPER.
FRAGMENTATION.
WHAT?
REMEMBER, YOU'RE TRAINING.
I'M MAKING A GRENADE HERE.
SEE, EVEN BLANK ROUNDS
CAN SAVE YOUR LIFE,
IF YOU IMPROVISE.
DAMN IT,
DON'T GIVE ME THIS CRAP.
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
IT'S BOWDEN.
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG.
HE WON'T TALK.
SPENCER SAYS
HE'S JUST GONE TOTALLY CRAZY.
YOU BETTER COME OVER,
I THINK HE'S RIGHT.
COME ON.
[Casper]
LOOK, BOWDEN.
NOW, IT'S BEEN KIND OF
ROUGH ON ALL OF US.
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE
NOT FEELING TOO GOOD.
WHY DON'T YOU
TALK TO US ABOUT IT?
COME ON,
BOWDEN.
BOWDEN, I'M GIVING
YOU AN ORDER.
NOW, DAMN IT,
TALK TO US!
HELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I DO.
THE MOTHERFUCKER'S CRAZY.
WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO WITH HIM?
LEAVE HIM THERE.
MAYBE HE'LL BE BETTER
IN THE MORNING.
THE HELL WE ARE.
THIS GUY MADE HIS OWN BOMB,
REMEMBER?
YOU'RE GONNA TIE HIM UP.
WE DON'T WANT HIM UP
WHILE WE'RE SLEEPING.
HE'S WAY TOO BIG
AND DANGEROUS.
USE YOUR HEAD, CASPER.
HE'S RIGHT.
[Simms]
HE IS, CASPER. WHAT THE HELL?
[Reece] WON'T HURT NOTHING
TO TIE HIM UP.
AIN'T NO GOOD TO US, ANYHOW.
NEVER WAS,
AS FAR AS THAT GOES.
IF HE'S TIED UP,
WE LOSE POTENTIAL FIREPOWER.
JESUS CHRIST, CASPER,
GET A GODDAMN ROPE
AND QUIT JERKING OFF
ABOUT FIREPOWER.
REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
YOU MOUTHED OFF TO ME?
BULLSHIT, CASPER.
THIS AIN'T A GODDAMN GAME.
ALL RIGHT, THERE'S 40 FEET
OF ROPE IN MY PACK.
GO GET IT, SIMMS.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING, REECE?
THIS MAN'S GONNA TALK TO ME.
LET HIM UP.
YOU STAY OUT OF THIS.
I SAID, LET HIM UP.
SURE.
NOW YOU HAPPY?
THAT'S THE SECOND TIME
YOU ASKED FOR IT WITH ME.
THIS TIME YOU'RE
GONNA GET AN ANSWER.
ABOUT TIME
I PAID YOU OFF, COWBOY.
HOW ABOUT I BLOW
YOUR FUCKING HEAD OFF, REECE?
YOU AIN'T GOT THE BALLS.
OKAY, YOU GOT IT.
[Speaking Cajun French]
KILL HIM!
ARGH!
HE'S DEAD.
REECE IS DEAD.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR PRISONER
GOT AWAY, CASPER.
[Stuckey]
LONNIE!
LET ME GO,
GODDAMN IT!
I'M GONNA GET YOU,
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
YOU HEAR ME?
I'M GONNA GET YOU!
HOW MANY MORE GRAVES
WILL WE BE LEAVING HERE?
NO MORE OF OURS,
I CAN TELL YOU.
YOU CAN TELL ME THAT.
SHUT UP!
YOU TALKING TO ME?
I'M TALKING TO EVERYBODY,
INCLUDING YOU.
KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT
AND DIG THE GRAVE.
WHY DON'T YOU DIG IT?
YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT KILLED HIM!
I'M NOT GONNA TELL YOU AGAIN.
KEEP YOUR FUCKING MOUTH SHUT
AND DIG THAT GODDAMN GRAVE.
I DON'T WANT TO BLOW
THE SHIT OUT OF YOU.
LOOK, JUST DO WHAT
THE HELL HE SAYS.
DIG.
[Thunder]
[Casper]
WE'VE HAD 3 CASUALTIES.
WE'RE NOT GONNA HAVE
ANY MORE.
SURVIVAL IS A MENTAL OUTLOOK.
NOW, IF YOU'RE NOT PREPARED
MENTALLY TO OVERCOME
ALL OBSTACLES AND HARDSHIPS
THE CHANCES
OF YOUR COMING OUT ALIVE
ARE GREATLY REDUCED.
WE'RE GETTING TIRED
OF LISTENING
TO ALL THIS, CASPER.
GODDAMN YOU, SPENCER,
I'M TRYING TO DO MY BEST!
I KNOW YOU ARE,
CASPER.
BUT QUOTING THE MANUAL
ISN'T HELPING MUCH.
YOU THINK YOU COULD
DO ANY BETTER?
YEAH, I DO.
BUT I'M
THE TEAM LEADER.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN A CORPORAL,
YOU'RE JUST A P.F.C.!
I'M GETTING TIRED
OF THIS DAMN CRAP.
I'M WITH YOU,
SPENCER.
CASPER, YOU ARE
NEVER GONNA FIND
THAT FUCKING HIGHWAY.
CASPER.
DO YOU PROMISE ME
THAT THIS TEXAS ASSHOLE'S
GONNA BE COURT-MARTIALED?
HE'S GOT TO BE.
HE KILLED
A FELLOW SOLDIER.
THEN I'M WITH YOU.
HARDIN.
WHAT'S THIS VOTING BULLSHIT?
LET'S GET MOVING.
[Spencer]
COME ON, BOWDEN. LET'S GO HOME.
SPENCER, YOU JUST CAN'T
WALK OFF LIKE THIS!
WE'RE A SQUAD, A UNIT!
WE'RE "BRAVO TEAM."
YOU GUYS ARE DESERTING.
YOU BET YOUR ASS
WE ARE.
YOU COMING?
COME ON, STUCKEY,
LET'S GO.
[Spencer] HOW'S
YOUR ARM?
[Bowden] IT'LL BE
ALL RIGHT.
[Spencer] LOOK, FOR WHAT
IT'S WORTH,
I KNOW REECE WAS
A REAL SON OF A BITCH.
[Bowden] I DON'T WANT TO
TALK ABOUT HIM.
[Spencer] YEAH, WELL,
MAYBE IT WAS SELF-DEFENSE.
[Bowden] LOOK,
LET'S JUST DROP IT.
IT'S OVER WITH.
RIGHT.
[Simms]
HEY, SPENCER,
WHAT CHANCE
DO WE GOT?
YOU WERE ALWAYS
SO SMART ABOUT EVERYTHING.
NOW YOU'RE
THE LEADER.
SO GIVE ME AN ANSWER.
[Spencer]
WELL, THEY GOT STATE TROOPERS,
HELICOPTERS, HOUND DOGS.
EVERYONE IN LOUISIANA
LOOKING FOR US.
[Simms] I TELL YOU, SPENCER,
I'VE HAD IT
WITH THEM HOUND DOGS.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING ELSE,
WHOEVER'S LOOKING FOR US,
THEY BETTER MAKE IT QUICK.
HEY!
[Gunshots]
COME ON!
SIMMS!
WHAT THE FUCK
IS GOING ON?
I THOUGHT
I SAW SOMETHING.
WHERE?
OVER THERE.
ARE YOU SURE?
I DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING.
ME NEITHER.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR IT?
YOU MUST'VE HEARD IT!
I DIDN'T
HEAR NOTHING!
[Casper]
YOU WASTED YOUR BULLETS
JUST LIKE BOWDEN DID.
WELL, THERE'S
NOTHING NOW.
WHAT THE FUCK?
COME ON,
LET'S TAKE OFF.
MOTHERFUCKERS!
[Gunshots]
[Spencer]
SIMMS!
NO MORE!
CHRIST.
THEY DUG THEM UP.
THEY DUG THEM ALL UP.
[Men shouting]
THEY'VE OUTFLANKED US.
WE'RE PINNED DOWN.
WHY DON'T YOU
COVER ME, SIMMS?
WITH WHAT?
ALL I GOT IS BLANKS.
NO RADIO, NO AMMO,
NO AIR SUPPORT, NO MORTARS:
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO FIGHT?
DON'T FUCKING ASK ME.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO KNOW THAT.
WELL, FIRE
THE GODDAMN BLANKS!
USE ANYTHING
YOU GOT.
I GOT 4 BULLETS.
WHAT ABOUT MINE?
YOU SHOT YOURS,
ASSHOLE.
GET READY.
COME ON,
WE'RE GONNA RETREAT.
[Casper]
RETREAT! FALL BACK!
LISTEN.
WHAT?
LISTEN!
I DON'T HEAR ANYTHING.
I CAN HEAR IT.
[Helicopter]
THERE!
[Men yelling]
HEY! DOWN HERE!
HEY!
WELL, IF HE SAW US,
HE'S GOTTA COME BACK.
HE COULDN'T LAND HERE.
THERE'S TOO MANY TREES.
HEY.
WHERE'S STUCKEY?
PLEASE!
HELP ME!
STUCKEY!
ALL RIGHT, SPREAD OUT.
WE GOTTA FIND HIM.
TEAMS. HARDIN
AND I'LL TAKE BOWDEN,
CASPER GOES
WITH SIMMS.
WHEN YOU FIND HIM,
FIRE EVERY 5 MINUTES,
THE OTHER TEAM
WILL FIND ITS WAY.
WHAT IF WE DON'T FIND HIM?
[Spencer]
WAIT AN HOUR.
FIRE 5 BLANKS,
THEN ONE EVERY 5 MINUTES.
BOTH TEAMS WILL WORK
BACK TO EACH OTHER.
LET'S GO.
STUCKEY!
STUCKEY,
YOU FUCKING REDNECK,
WHERE ARE YOU?
SHIT!
DIRTY SONS OF BITCHES.
GO ON, SIMMS,
GET BACK TO THE OTHERS.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
GO ON.
YOU HEARD ME.
GO ON, GET OUT OF HERE!
[Gunshot]
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE!
[Gunshot]
STUCKEY!
[Spencer]
I THINK ALL WE'RE DOING
IS TELLING THE OPPOSITION
WHERE WE ARE.
[Hardin] THEY AIN'T HAD
TOO MUCH TROUBLE
FINDING US UP TILL NOW.
CASPER!
SIMMS!
COME ON,
LET'S GO.
WE'VE GOTTA GO
FOR OURSELVES NOW.
THE OTHERS MAKE IT,
THEN THEY MAKE IT.
YEAH,
OKAY.
BOY, THIS IS A GREAT STATE
YOU GOT HERE.
THEY SENT OUT
ONE FUCKING HELICOPTER.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU
WANT THEM TO DO,
SEND OUT
THE NATIONAL GUARD?
"CIVILIAN IN PEACE.
"SOLDIER IN WAR.
I AM THE GUARD."
BOWDEN?
HEY, BOWDEN,
DO YOU WANT
TO TALK?
HEY, COACH?
[Sighs]
WHAT DOES HE COACH,
ANYWAY?
FOOTBALL,
WHAT ELSE?
I THINK HE TEACHES HISTORY
OR SOMETHING, TOO.
LOOKS LIKE
IT'S ALL HISTORY FOR HIM NOW,
POOR BASTARD.
COULD BE HISTORY
FOR US, TOO,
IF WE DON'T GET A BREAK.
YEAH.
TOMORROW, YOU'LL BE
SITTING IN YOUR DEN
WITH A BEER IN YOUR HAND
LISTENING TO
YOUR OLD LADY BULLSHIT.
I DON'T HAVE A DEN.
I'LL BUY YOU ONE,
IF WE EVER GET OUT OF HERE.
GREAT.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN MARRIED?
FIVE YEARS.
HAPPY?
HUH?
AS IN, "HAPPILY MARRIED."
YEAH.
I LIKE HER, SHE'S GOT
A GOOD SENSE OF HUMOR.
WHAT'S IT TO YOU?
I JUST THOUGHT IF I GOT OUT
OF HERE AND YOU DIDN'T,
MAYBE I'D LOOK HER UP.
I SAID SHE HAD
A GOOD SENSE OF HUMOR.
I DON'T.
YEAH, MINE'S STRETCHED
A BIT THIN, TOO,
AT THE MOMENT.
SINCE THEY GOT
THE TRAPPER BACK
THEY MUST BE HUNTING US
JUST FOR THE FUN OF IT.
YOU GOT AN IDEA OF SOMETHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT IT,
OR YOU JUST TALKING
FOR THE RECORD?
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT I'M SAYING FOR THE RECORD.
I WANT TO LIVE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
I'M GONNA DO IT.
BUT I'M GONNA FIGHT
MY WAY OUT OF HERE.
WELL, DON'T FORGET
TO SAVE ME A SEAT, PAL.
DON'T WORRY, YOU GOT IT.
[Wind howling]
[Train whistle blows]
LET'S GO!
POOR SON OF A BITCH.
I WON'T KILL YOU ALL,
IF I DON'T GOT TO.
I GOT A BAYOU OVER HERE.
TAKE IT.
STAY TO THE WEST SIDE.
YOU WANT TO FIND A ROAD
ABOUT A MILE UP THERE.
DO YOU MIND TELLING US
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S REAL SIMPLE.
WE LIVE BACK IN HERE.
THIS IS OUR HOME
AND NOBODY DON'T FUCK WITH US.
WHAT ABOUT HIM?
[Cajun man]
DID HE DO IT TO HIMSELF
OR DID YOUR FRIENDS
HELP HIM OUT?
[Gunshot]
IF I WAS YOU, I'D QUIT
ASKING QUESTIONS AND HAUL ASS.
MY BUDDIES,
THEY'RE NOT NICE LIKE ME.
ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO SAY THANKS?
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO SAY NOTHING, SOLDIER.
COME ON, HARDIN.
OVER THERE.
TRUCK.
FUCKING TRUCK.
[Speaking Cajun French]
HUH?
YOU LOSE YOU IN THERE.
YEAH.
YOU WANT A RIDE, HUH?
OH, GOD, YES.
[Speaking Cajun French]
THROW YOU IN THE BACK.
SURE, YOU BET.
NEXT TOWN, RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT, YEAH.
GREAT.
[Pigs grunting]
*[Traditional Cajun music
playing]
[Dog barking]
[Truck honking]
[Hardin] CAN'T BE CATAHOULA.
JUST SOME BACKWOODS STOP.
WHAT ABOUT THE TOWN
THEY WERE TAKING US TO?
GUESS THIS IS IT.
SAY, WHERE'S
THE TELEPHONE?
WE GOT ELECTRIC LIGHTS
BUT NO TELEPHONE.
WE WANT TO GO TO A TOWN
WITH A TELEPHONE.
EAT FIRST.
WE GO IN TOWN MORE LATER.
NO, WE WANT TO GO
TO TOWN NOW.
NO, HAVE SOMETHING TO DRINK.
PASS A GOOD TIME WITH US.
[Speaking French]
YOU MAKE THAT TELEPHONE
MORE LATER.
[Cajun woman]
YOU ALL COME WITH ME.
I'LL SHOW YOU WHERE
YOU CAN WASH YOURSELVES.
[Speaking French]
WASH UP?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK I'LL FEEL BETTER.
CLEANER, ANYWAY.
YEAH?
BUT WHAT ABOUT SAFER?
WELL, I WOULDN'T LIE DOWN
AND GO TO SLEEP.
MAYBE WE SHOULD FORGET
ABOUT MR. AND MISS CAJUN.
TRY TO FIND THE NEXT TOWN
BY OURSELVES.
WHAT FOR?
THEY'RE STILL LOOKING
TO SURPRISE US IN THE SWAMP.
BE SAFER HERE.
OKAY.
WE'LL GRAB A RIDE WITH
THE FIRST THING OUT OF HERE.
MERCI.
RELAX, HARDIN.
THESE ARE THE GOOD CAJUNS.
THEM OTHER GUYS
ARE A LONG WAYS BACK.
YOU RELAX.
*[Playing
traditional Cajun music]
LOOK AT THOSE 2 GUYS.
WHAT 2 GUYS?
GETTING OUT
OF THE BOAT.
YEAH.
YOU THINK THEY'RE THE ONES
THAT HAVE BEEN AFTER US?
HELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I NEVER SEEN THEM.
I THINK IT'S THEM.
DON'T GO GETTING
PARANOID ON ME.
I GOT REASON TO BE PARANOID
AND SO DO YOU.
THEY GOT TO KILL US.
WE'RE THE ONLY WITNESSES.
DON'T SWEAT IT.
THEY CAN'T PULL ANYTHING
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
[Woman speaking French]
I'M TELLING YOU,
HARDIN, RELAX.
RIGHT.
[Gunshot]
EXCUSE-MOI.
[Music stops playing]
*[Music plays]
[Man]
HEY!
OH!
[Music stops playing]
[Bang on door]
AH!
AHH!
[Heavy breathing]
*[Music plays]
AHH!
*[Singing in Cajun French]
UGH!
AH!
UH!