I'm so worried for that boy.
Joe's going to be okay.
She was everything to him.
Jack's going to step up.
He's a good man.
But he has never had
to be a father before.
I don't think he understands Joe.
How long had she work there?
Five years?
- I think it was six.
What do you think was in the coffin?
Jesus, shut up.
I was thinking how she died.
You guys weren't wondering that.
No, I'm eating macaroni salad.
I was wondering about that too.
I heard it crushed her completely.
Steel beams.
Those things weigh a ton.
Literally.
I don't know how you guys can eat.
Try the turkey and you'll discover how.
Lucy, down.
Get out.
Joe.
Have you seen Joe?
Bet Joe's not going to want
to do my movie anymore.
Why?
Why do you think why?
The story is about the living dead.
His mum is not a zombie.
But she's dead, shit head.
It's troubled his heart pretty good.
- Told you.
Get him out of here!
Just wait a minute.
Wait!
Jack!
Jack, just let me out!
Get out!
Hey Jack!
It was a mistake.
Get out! Come on!
Get in!
Joseph, I will be home soon.
Oh my God. That was
the longest day ever.
Here.
- What's this?
New scene. Check it out.
Detective Hathaway has a wife now?
I don't know. I think it
might make a better movie.
I need a better story
line and production value.
Hey guys. Martin...
It was the grosses one yet.
Oh my god, shut up!
So who's going to play the wife?
Jen?
No way. I told you what
she did to my top pack.
What wife?
- Alice Dainard.
I was returning that book
on 'Codes and Ciphers'.
She was in the silent reading section.
And I asked her if she'll
play Hathaway's wife.
Wait. You talked to
Alice Dainard, really?
You aren't suppose to talk at
all in the silent reading section.
Shut up.
- It's for silent reading.
She said 'yes'.
We're filming tonight and she's driving.
Driving? Driving where?
That was a really good zombie murder.
But it's not a story yet.
All the kids that are
entering this film festival,
fifteen and sixteen years old,
have better stories and
casts and production value.
I've got nothing.
- Charles, dinner.
I'm coming.
There is this article
I want you to read this.
It explains everything about stories.
I just don't understand how
the wife helps make it a story.
Jesus, what have I been explaining?
The scene we're filming
tonight, where the
wife's telling the detective that
she cares for him, that she loves him.
I can't believe you
talk to Alice Dainard.
Charles, come on, move it!
I'm coming!
And watch your head this time!
So when he investigates
the zombie stuff,
you feel something.
You don't want him to die
because they love each other.
Make sense?
Alice Dainard, that's awesome.
You're impossible.
- Charles, now!
God mum! I'm coming!
Midnight okay? Don't forget.
I won't forget.
Read this.
It's not fair I cannot go to Wendy's.
Every single person
will be there except me.
Well then, every single
person and tell you how it was.
Move the puzzle, get the napkins.
Mum...
- It's your turn to babysit.
Why can't I switch with Charles?
Maybe it's because you
crushed Charles' top pack.
You ever think of that?
Oh really, guess what? We're switching.
Oh really? Guess what? No, we're not.
Okay, that's enough. Charles,
take this to the table.
Benji, time for dinner.
Hi Joe.
Goodnight, Mrs Kaznyk.
Take a seat. We have lots of food.
Oh no, I'm okay,
really. Thank you though.
See you tomorrow, Charles.
- Later.
There's always a place for you Joey.
You know that.
Yes sir, thank you.
Dad?
Hey.
I'll be out in a minute.
Six week program.
Hands on training with college coaches.
You'll like it. I know I did.
I thought I was going to
have this summer to myself.
Things have obviously changed for us.
And it will be good for
you to spend some time
with kids who don't run around
with cameras and monster make-up.
I have to help Charles finish his movie.
I have got nothing against your
friends, I like your friends.
Except for Cary who can't seem
to stop lighting things on fire.
You'll like it there.
It's what we both need.
Okay, it's time. Don't get caught.
Over.
I won't. Over..
Wait guys, people are
turning into zombies
because of the chemical Rago, right?
I don't see how the guy
playing detective Hathaway
could ask where the
zombies are coming from.
Well technically, Hathaway...
Is that a rock?
Hey guys look. Guys!
Hey Alice.
Joe Lamb?
Ya.
What the hell is he doing here?
Make-up and sound's special effects.
He's the deputy's kid.
So what?
- You knew that?
Charles, I don't have a license.
I can't drive with him.
You want Joe to stay back, I guess...
It's too late. He has seen
me in the car right now!
You can trust me.
My dad will never know.
I won't tell him anything.
Get in.
So I wrote a couple of
new lines. Can I show you?
What?
- New lines?
Charles, do I have new lines?
- It will all be great.
This is if you could cry in the scene.
Can you do that?
No.
Do you know the first place I would
like to get my driving license?
Newcastle, Pennsylvania.
Wildest capital of the world.
Guys, there's an electrical
outlet right here!
Charles!
Charles man, do I have new lines or not?
No! No!
Guys, this is going to be great!
Get the lights and camera
set up from that end!
We'll shoot this direction first.
Joe, get the microphone and then make
sure the new batteries are in the camera
before you do the
make-up. - Okay.
I could afford two packs of
cherry bombs and I made my own MAE.
Do you want to see it?
Your obsession with fireworks,
and I'm saying this as a friend,
concern me and my mother.
Sweet heart, this is my
job. I have no choice.
It's nothing you need to worry about.
What am I suppose to do?
Go to Michigan with you?
Martin, I wrote a new line.
What? No.
What do you mean no? It's awesome.
Do you mind?
No.
Here...
There.
Thanks.
Now, I'm not prepared.
Look, it flows better.
Honey, I love you.
I love you too.
See it flows.
- I know.
But you keep changing things and
making it more difficult for me.
My dad works at the mill.
Could you close your eyes please?
Ya.
So the scene is very emotional.
Alice,
Mrs. Hathaway doesn't
really want her husband
to keep investigating these murders.
- Ya, I know, we read it.
You got them, I'm just directing.
Martin, get in position.
You need to re-assure her.
Wait. Do you know what
're-assure her' means?
Ya, I think so.
Okay, we're going to shoot
on Alice's side first.
Okay Preston, so a few
seconds after I say 'action',
I want you to walk to the pay-phone.
You know, make the place
look like it's busy.
Hello, hello...
- I know what that looks like.
Asshole.
Can you stop blowing shit up for
two seconds and deal with the camera?
Guys, sorry man.
Okay you guys lets rehearse this.
But remember, save the real
performance for when we're filming.
Here we go, positions and...
action!
So I'm going to stay
here and investigate.
I think it'll be safer if you
left town for a couple of days.
John, I don't like it,
this case, these murders.
Well, what am I suppose to do?
Go to Michigan with you?
Mackinac Island is beautiful
is time of the year.
Sweet heart, this is mine job.
The dead coming back to life.
I think you're in danger.
I have no... I have no choice.
You do have a choice.
We all do.
John,
I've never ask you to stop.
I've never ask you to
give up or walk away.
But I'm asking you now.
Please.
For me.
Don't go.
Don't leave me.
I need to know this isn't the
last time I'm going to see you.
Just love you so much.
I love you too.
Was that good?
Ya, ya that was... great.
Production value!
Cary, you popped film
in the camera, right?
I didn't put it in.
- What?
Put it in!
Joe, get the microphone! Go! Go! Go!
Come on, get that tripod set up!
Preston, in position!
- I will!
Martin you know your lines!
Cary get the camera ready!
I hope we don't miss it.
Shut up!
- I am trying!
Position, position!
- Ready!
Start filming. Be extra loud
when the train passes by.
Here we go. And 'Action'!
Look, I'm going to stay
here and investigate.
I think it'll safer if you
left town for a couple of days.
John, I don't like it.
This case, these murders.
What do you want me to do?
Go to Michigan with you?
Mackinac Island is beautiful
this time of the year.
The dead coming back to life.
I think you're in danger!
I don't have a choice!
You do have a choice!
We all do!
John, I've never ask you to stop!
I've never ask you to
give up or walk away!
But I am asking you now!
Please, for me. Just don't go!
Just don't go back. Don't leave me!
I need to know this isn't the
last time I'm going to see you!
I love you so much!
- I love you too!
Guys watch out!
Joe, what the hell...
Oh my God! Run!
Oh my God!
Holy shit!
Go! Go! Go!
Alice!
Joe let’s go! We got to go!
Keep going!
Are we alive!
Run!
I don't want to die!
Guys.
I'm okay.
Martin, you okay?
Though I think I'm
having a heart attack.
And I have a scrape.
Joe! Oh my God.
Guys, did you see all the explosions?
You guys seen Alice?
Joe, so unbelievable!
Why is this happening?
- Martin, it's going to be okay.
Martin, it's going to be okay.
No, it's not dude.
Shit!
What's all that blood?
What's the blood?
Someone got hurt?
Joe, what are you doing?
- Joe, stop!
It's mine fake blood. It's fake.
Guys.
Come here, what are these things?
No one cares.
Look around you.
They look like white
Rubik cubes or something.
I don't think that's what they are.
Maybe white metals, or something.
There's like a billion of them.
What's going on?
Martin, it's going to be okay, alright.
- Are you serious?
Guys, get up here. You can
see everything from up here.
Joe.
According to my uncle Jeff, an accident
like this is exceptionally rare.
It wasn't an accident.
What?
There was truck on the train track.
Are you serious?
- Like driving on the tracks?
There.
Oh my Gosh.
How could a pick-up truck derail a train?
That's impossible.
Obviously it isn't.
Oh shit!
Oh my God. I know that truck.
Guys.
Is that him?
- Yes, it's him.
Who?
- Yes it is, for sure.
Who is it?
Dr Woodward.
Dr Woodward?
Biology.
Honours, Biology.
- Wow!
I am not in his class.
We know.
- Shut up, Cary.
Remember when old man Woodward
told your electronic football?
Yes, he put it in the dungeon
and never gave it back.
Dungeon?
That trailer where Woodward
keeps in the school's parking lot.
Dr Woodward?
Map of the Contiguous United States.
What's the writing?
Date and time.
What's this line?
The schedule for the train.
Who are you?
Dr Woodward,
...it's me,
Charles Kaznyk,
...fourth period.
You've been in an accident.
You're going to be okay.
Oh shit!
Swear... I will kill you.
Do not speak of this.
Or else, you...
and your parents...
will die.
Guys look.
We shouldn't be here.
- Go!
Come on! Let's get out of here!
Guys, come on!
Hurry up! Let's go! Let's go!
Get in!
Did you get the plate?
I didn't get the plate. Did you get it?
Oh God! That was insane!
He had a gun! I've never seen a gun!
My heart is pounding!
That train could have kill us!
Are you okay?
Oh shit, my camera's like shattered now!
Guys, I've never had a
teacher aiming a gun at me!
How can I drive when everyone's yelling?
Guys, keep it down.
You will die, your parents will die.
Guys, that's not good information.
Shit, the focus ring just fell off!
No one cares about your camera!
Guys, am I the only one shaking?
I'm crying.
- We can't tell anyone we were there.
My dad can't find out I took his car.
You guys here me?
It's okay. We're not
saying anything to anyone.
Guys, we are not saying anything are we?
No.
See?
No one is going to know.
We'll sink it here.
Joe.
Thank you.
I never should have done this.
Joe? Joe, wake up.
Make sure you let Lucy out, alright?
- I will.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to be at Charles' today?
Yes, I'll be with Charles.
Alright, I'm heading in. There's
something I got to deal with.
Don't forget to get the Oar.***
- I won't.
Oh, come on.
No, you're not wearing that.
No one in the house is wearing that.
Oh really. Compared to
Debbie, these are long.
Listen to your mother.
So I can't go to Wendy's party
over the shorts? Not fair!
Jennifer, we're not in Africa.
Do we have anymore English muffins?
Why don't you get off and check?
Hey, tell the twins to stop.
- I can't.
Good morning Joe.
- Good morning Mr. Kaznyk.
Hi Joe, did you hear
about the train crash?
No.
- It's on the news.
...use local crews, instead
opting to use military personnel,
which to this reporter, only
adds to the mystery.
Of course we have much more to
the story as it develops.
coming to you live
from Montgomery County
Do you believe this?
No.
It's on the news, that means it's real.
- I know.
Dr Thomas Woodward is still being
treated by air force personnel
after last night's train derailment..
Woodward apparently fell asleep at
the wheel of his pick-up truck.
which was hit by the speeding train.
How about you clean it up?
That would be a great
help, thank you so much.
...largest of accident
in Ohio history..
Condition of Woodward who is currently teaching
in Middle School for the past three years...
Looks like a disaster movie, doesn't it?
My God.
Joe, you're so awesome.
What?
We can use it, we can film it.
You want to go back?
Oh shit, that's mint.
- Really?
You're a total brain. We
got to get the camera fixed
film developed from last night.
- Okay.
I am going to steal
some money from my mum.
If any of the footage is
useable from last night,
that means we need Alice
to play the wife again.
Oh yes, I thought she was really good.
Yes, she was mint but
she's never going to do it.
I think she will.
There's no way. You heard what she said.
But that's before the new scenes, right?
You honestly think she
cares about the scenes?
She was totally vague.
Yes, she was. We all were.
Lens is cracked, focus ring broke.
Do you think it's fixable?
I guess it is cheaper to get a new one.
The camera is busted man. It's over.
We can use my dad's
camera. It's got slow...
Hello?
Hey Alice, it's Joe Lamb.
Hi.
So we have some new
scenes for the movie,
and Charles and I are
hoping you'll be in them.
Oh,... no. I'm done with that.
I need this film developed as soon
as possible. Can you do it overnight?
Asshole, no one can do it overnight.
You want to buy some pot?
No, no, thank you.
Well, what is the fastest you can do?
I can make it a rush.
and get your film back in three days.
And what is your sister up to?
The hot one, not the other one.
I don't know.
watching the crash on the news
Yes, I saw it.
I should go.
Wait, hold on. I'll come over,
I'll bring the scenes.
- No, no!
I'll be right there. It's a good idea.
I don't care what Charles wants.
I said 'no' on the phone.
I know you totally did.
I know that's true but...
Now you are at my house.
I am, which...
I don't understand why you guys
keep working on that stupid movie.
You should go.
What's this?
He was just inviting me to a party.
Good morning, Mr Dainard.
She's not going to your party.
Yes sir.
You, get out of here.
You go home and you
don't come back here!
I don't want to see you.
Ally come inside.
Ally, I'm in the kitchen.
I'll do it.
What?
Cut! That was mint!
Oh my God, with the train, so good.
Joe, reload the cap gun.
- Okay.
We'll shoot another angle next.
Alice that was mint.
Martin go over faster next time.
I'll try Charles. I was just
crying out last night man.
Guys, did it really look good?
You look awesome.
What do you think happened?
You mean why he crashed the train?
I just got a horrible feeling.
Dude, what are you doing?
That whole thing is an Air Force train.
What?
I make models, like plastic ones.
You know, go home, paint them.
And he's not embarrassed by that.
Whose talking, math camp.
Thanks.
Can I have some coffee please?
Cream on the side.
He's so sophisticated.
Shut up. I like coffee.
No one likes coffee.
Air Force trains, even the
models have these hooks.
Oh, they do.
For when the trains are
loaded on the transport ships.
Every car on that crash had...
Joe, you stop talking about it alright?
Wait guys.
Am I the only guy who doesn't
understand any of this means?
Probably 'Smartin'.
- Cary shut up.
I don't like it when you call me that.
I'm sorry 'Smartin'.
Let’s just go cry about it.
Dr Woodward had that map.
He drove onto the train tracks.
Maybe there was something
he wanted to destroy.
You guys should shut up!
Maybe he was sick of living
and wanted to kill himself.
Dumb idea.
He had a gun. Why not use that?
There are infinitely more
effective ways to commit suicide.
Pills, hanging,...
- Hey, Pussy!
Stop taking the fries away!
I order these for a reason.
- Excuse me.
Can we have another order of fries
because my friend here is fat?
Funny chomper, at least I don't
have to use a booster seat.
You can jump from a building.
- Or fall down some stairs.
Oh, that's not really effective.
- Do you think?
If this is the Air Force, what would
the Air Force have on the train?
Jesus, shut up about it!
You heard what old man Woodward said.
We can't talk about this.
Joe, seriously.
Do you really want to take a chance that
something could happen to your dad too?
It's loaded, move out!
- Yes, sir.
Yes, Deputy, I'm told this crash has
caused the whole massive confusion.
Well, as you can expect, the local
authorities are trying to figure out
just what has happened
as well as how to help.
It's all under control.
It'll be a very fast clean up.
Colonel, is there anything
I should know of, Sir?
Not that I can think of, Deputy.
I understand you've
concerns about our cargo.
I like to see that manifest, yes.
Well, that's not going to be possible.
Colonel, I've a lot of people in my town
who're going to want to
know what's taking place.
Which town is that?
Lillian...
Deputy, if you're asking me if there's
any dangerous property onboard this train,
I can assure you that the answer is 'no'.
- Colonel!
Colonel!
Excuse me.
They gave me the round
around for two hours
before they allow me to talk to anyone.
I'll say they had
their hands full, Jack.
Nelec, the Colonel
refused to show the manifest,
He told me they are carrying mostly
aeroplane parts. I don't buy that.
It's Air Force, Jack. The
aeroplane parts ought to make sense.
Sheriff, I'm telling you
there's something else going on.
They taking moulds of tire tracks.
Why would they be doing that?
Who would they be looking for?
And they are packaging these weird
little cubes into these crates.
Weird little cubes, huh?
- They load them on these
red trucks, there are dozens of them!
Sheriff, I think you
need to check it out.
And I think you need to take a break.
Jack, I've been telling
you this since Elizabeth.
You are a good Deputy.
But you need to take a vacation.
Go home.
Take off your uniform. Go fishing.
Give your son a hug.
Hey Breen, I'm not sure Edie's
paying you to listen to the radio!
Breen!
Hey, Sheriff.
What's that?
Walkman.
It's like a stereo.
Plays on cassette tapes.
You want to try it?
I don't think so.
Kids walk around with their
own stereos, just what we need.
It's slippery slope, my friend.
Yes sir.
Sheriff?
You know what, in scene...
Where did you learn to do this?
Mostly the Dick Smith's
"Monsters Make-up" paint book.
Hey Joe, we need more
footage of the train crash.
Obviously.
You know that train
model you've just made?
Yap, your cargo train.
I want to blow it up and film it.
Let me blow it up.
Ya, sure.
- Fantastic!
It's fine. They can blow it up.
I don't care.
Do you want to see it?
The train, my train model?
The train I made.
Wow!
Dude, that's bitching man...
That's like the third
time it has happened.
So how am I suppose to be a zombie?
Pretty much be a lifeless ghoul,
no soul, dead eyes... scary.
Did you ever have Miss Mullen?
- For English?
Yes!
I like her, but 'hungry
for human flesh',
like she wants to turn
somebody into a zombie.
Cause that's how zombies do.
My God, that's really good.
Not bad.
Really?
Really.
Careful, there was a gas spill.
I don't even know how
much fuel I've lost.
You don't seem to be asking very many questions!
- Give the man sometime, Mr. Blakely.
He's only a Deputy,
he's not the Sheriff.
I think this is most
likely a bear attack.
Security cameras showed nothing.
Vicky, you heard from
Sheriff Pruitt this morning?
Negative, still no word.
Vicky, you need to update and
send a CS unit out to Edie's,
And you put an APB out on
the Sheriff and Breen Haskell,
and send units over to their houses
immediately. You copy all that.
Copy, and Jack,
we're getting a lot of unusual calls.
What kind of unusual calls?
I've never seen this
kind of things before!
What the hell am I suppose to do?
The insurance company guys
thought I was joking with them!
Look at my Bonneville over here.
They don't have the
wrench to take that out.
Having problems with
anyone lately, Izzy?
I was thinking you should
talk to Louis Dainard.
I didn't help him out
with financing last year,
and I wouldn't be surprised if this
is some sort of sick retribution.
My generator's mishome...
My dog is gone,... disappeared.
Maybe you should file a report.
I'll have someone come out and
take care of each one of you, okay?
Lucy!
I have four guys on missing cases.
People don't feel safe
around here. And you know why?
Because they are not!
The Air Force doesn't
answer a damn question.
They've got trucks over
at Woodward's house.
Ben heard they're looking
for Woodward's research.
Research?
One of the soldier on the truck,
he had like a scanner in his hand.
- Like a Geiger counter.
They're saying it's just a
clean up at the crash site,
but they're taking
moulds of tire tracks.
That means they're looking for
someone. What does that means?
Have you seen Lucy anywhere?
- No, it certainly will be 'around somewhere.
No, I'm sure she's around somewhere.
I put a couple of slices
in the fridge for you.
Oh! I ate those.
Sorry, kid.
No problem. I'll find something.
Pick that up, will you?
Vicky, do you have power
down at the station?
On and off. The whole
County is in the dark.
Do me a favour and get water
and power up right now, will you?
So the Air Force is looking for a car.
Alice's dad car.
They are taking tire prints
from the crash site, over.
I don't want to hear about it.
That's what I've been talking about.
They could be monitoring us right now.
Jesus, shut up!
Over.
The military is at Woodward's
house looking for his research.
Whatever that means?
Do not freak out on me and be a dick.
Are you going to come
and help me or not?
I need you to make Alice's zombie again.
Okay, I'll do the makeup.
Over.
Cables are gone. All
the posts are empty.
Same thing over here in Rose Hill.
Somebody took the damn wires down.
Holy shit!
Rooney, you got anything?
Rooney, you copy?
- You are missing for at least a mile...
We got a half mile of copper missing.
Lines are back up with M-38.
Truck 14, Rooney's out of the junkyard.
I'll give you an
update when I hear back.
Subtitle By: Firstsub
I want to know who took them.
20 microwaves.
Gone!
From my inventory.
Everywhere you look
things are going missing.
We've got trains
crashing, people vanishing.
Belmont's County is without power.
You know what this feels like to me?
This feels like a "Russian invasion".
I don't think the
Russian has anything to do
with what's going on in the town.
But I'm calling a curfew...
Unless you can tell me who's
been messing with our stuffs.
I say it's the Soviets.
And I think Jack, we
need Sheriff Pruitt back.
We've got good people working on that.
Mr. McCandless.
Since Wednesday morning,
my ham-radio was a mess.
Some frequencies, which I like scan,
I'm hearing military chatter.
But it is distorted. And
I don't know what it is.
Have you heard that?
Mr. McCandless, can I have a
word with you in private, please?
It was like having my radio hijacked.
I'm sure it was very annoying.
You don't know those
frequencies off hand do you?
Oh, sure I do.
13,201,...
Danny, why don't you
get in touch with Vicky.
Hey Dave, have you seen Milner?
No sir, I haven't.
Deputy, something crawled by my
garage! It's paw is almost a foot!
Tom! Have you seen Milner?
- Have you try his office?
...I try to his office.
What are you doing about the
power? We've been off for two days!
Hey Rosko!
Rosko, I need you to get everybody you
have tuned to those frequencies, understand?
No.
Hey Milner, don't you have a
radio scanner with a descrambler?
Voice? I have it at home.
Whatever. Get it. Bring it down here
and set it up. Wouldn't you please?
Jack, what is this?
I think the Air Force
is using our channels.
He was at my house yesterday
morning. Are you aware of that?
We brought him in for the car
lots and other stuffs, he's clean.
I would appreciate it if you inform
your son, my house is off limits.
And so is my daughter.
I think the makeup was better yesterday.
No,... it's good.
I think it looks good.
I should have cleaned up my room.
You made all these models?
Yes. Yes, that one is "The
Hunchback of Notre Dame."
We watch that one on...
This is the train I wanted to destroy.
Looks real.
It looks so old.
Yes, it's dry brush technique.
It runs off a coat of paint. and
then you add something like...
and then you put something like...
- Euro grey over it.
- Euro grey?
Oh yes, there's like 14
different greys. It gets crazy.
What was that necklace?
The one you were holding
at the train crash.
Was it your moms?
My dad gave it to her
the day I was born.
She wears it all the time.
Or used to.
It was bad how she die and...
But my dad got it back.
Guys! What the hell?
No one knew where you were.
We were here.
You got to play the soldier!
I thought you were calling Evan.
Evan blew us off. He is a pussy.
Excuse me.
It's okay.
You got to do it. You're the only one.
What do you mean they
found my dog in Brookville?
That's another county over.
Lucy, that's where she is.
We have more than 30 calls from people
who found local dogs, but the thing is
the calls coming in weren't local.
Like they all just...
ran away in every direction.
This isn't like her.
She doesn't disappear.
Okay, calm down. Just
tell what she looks like.
She's got dark hair and rollers.
You know what rollers are?
Yes, I know what rollers are.
Hang on.
It's definitely Air Force.
It's Air Force. But what does it mean?
Why are they transmitting
on these frequencies?
Maybe it's not even Air Force.
I bet you five bucks it's Air Force.
- Five Bucks?
Sshhh!
We're going to need you to prepare
for Operation "Walking Distance".
What did he say? Operation, what?
"Walking Distance".
What's this?
- He worked at Romero Chemical.
Found out some things
the company was doing.
And after what you told
me last night at the bar.
I thought you should know.
Are we going to be in
trouble for being here?
Production value.
Stop talking about production
value. Air Force is going to kill us!
Don't cover my mouth!
We just make this discovery today.
You understand this is Top Secret.
- Of course.
I would never have given this information,
unless we had worked together in Vietnam.
Those were hard times...
- We better not talk about it.
I understand... I understand.
You're a good friend.
You too.
Nothing so far.
How much more is there?
About 6 more boxes in a basement.
A lot more tax returns.
It's here somewhere, we'll find it.
If not, Woodward will tell us where he is.
What the hell is that?
Joe.
- Hey Mr. Lamb.
Get in the car.
Ahm, Mr. Lamb that's your camera but
technically that's my film.
What the hell.
Is it me?
I would like to help you out deputy, I really would
but we operate on a need to know basis.
Why are your trucks sweeping the town?
We will be out of here by shortly.
Then I'm sure you won't mind me contacting D.C.,
talk to some friends
about "walking distance".
I will do it that way.
Deputy.
Let's talk.
Just not here.
This is new for the both of us.
Dealing with anything.
Just us.
So I'm going to make this
as simple and clear as I can.
You are not friends with Alice Dainard.
When I say 'no', I don't mean maybe.
I don't mean 'yes'.
I mean 'no'.
I've known Louis Dainard
for a lot of years.
He's been nothing but trouble.
Your mother used to say
he's not such a bad guy.
He just need a chance, that he was sad.
Well, I tried to be good to him.
Well I can't. Not anymore.
I will not allow him or
his daughter in this house.
I will not allow you to spend
time with her doing projects
or whatever it is
that you do, that's it!
I hope we are clear on that.
We're not 'clear'.
What did you say?
- We are not in place...
We're not clear!
You and I are not clear about anything!
We couldn't be less clear!
- Joseph...
Just because mum die doesn't mean
that you know anything about me.
You don't!
You don't know anything
about Alice either.
She's kind...
- We are not going to have this discussion...
She's nice to me!
- I don't care what she is!
Her father is an irresponsible
selfish son of a bitch!
You listen to me.
I've got 12 thousand people in this
town who are scared out of their mind.
And they got one person to rely on.
It used to be someone
else but now it's just me.
Here we go.
- Lights on.
Deputy, drop your weapons.
Put your hands on the car.
I'm here to see the Colonel Nelec.
He told me to meet him here.
You're on military
arrest, drop your weapons!
Where Nelec?
I don't want any more trouble, do you?
We've been going
through your belongings.
Looking for evidence.
What he knew? How you knew it?
Who else might know?
I remember you on the lab.
And I recall we didn't
always see eye-to-eye,
but that is no excuse for
doing what you did here.
So in the spirit of moving forward,
and avoiding more trouble.
Why don't you just tell me
where you put your research
and who else knows about it?
I know you had someone
document the crash that night.
Tell me who that was and I'll help you.
I swear to God on my mother's life,
if you help us now, we
will take care of you.
I've seen what happens, Mr. Nelec.
When you take care of people.
- It is mine. He is mine!
I'm going to beat him and catch him.
He is in me, you know.
As I am in him.
So...
when you see him next,
as I'm sure you will,
I'll be watching you too.
Are you... were you sleeping?
Before... earlier... no.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
You want to come in?
- Yes.
Power still out.
The room is still messy.
I couldn't sleep.
I was thinking...
I want to tell you
something before tomorrow.
Don't let Charles blow up your train.
I don't think it is right.
I know he is your friend.
He's so bossy.
I have known him since kindergarten.
He's really nice.
You should know he gets what he wants.
I mean, who always get what they want?
I know I don't know you at all.
Even though, I try to feel like I do.
Do you not... feel like that?
No, I totally do.
I'm just kind of...
in shock at this entire conversation.
Power is back.
No, no, keep it.
It's... it's so weird.
Watching her like this.
as if she's still here.
She used to look at me
this way.
Like really look.
And I just knew I was there.
Like I existed.
He drank that morning.
...my dad.
He missed his shift.
Your mother took it for him.
the day of the accident.
He...
he wishes...
I know he wishes it
was him instead of her.
Sometimes I do too.
Don't say that.
He's your father.
Is this normal?
No, this is new.
Want to tell me where you were?
Or should I tell you?
Sit down.
I should go to bed.
I want to talk with
you, I said sit down.
I don't want to sit down.
Bingo!
Be just like your mother and leave.
Dad.
Ahead, go!
Go!
Alice!
Wait!
Ally, I'm sorry!
Alice!
Ally!
Fire alight at 0500 hours.
Operation "Walking Distance" is in effect.
T - minus 4 hours to evacuation.
Why are you not reacting?
That thing went through my wall!
I told you not to pick
it up in the first place.
What are you so angry about?
That I'm not going to
let you blow up my train?
That's part of it!
Just a part!
Hey, to tell your sister that Donnie
from Allson's broke up with Karen.
That should end about a week ago.
What's your problem?
My whole movie is a
disaster because of you.
I know my dad is a turkey.
Whatever!
We're still going to finish your movie!
- It is not about the movie!
What are you talking
about? Of course it is!
Just forget it!
Why?
- There's nothing wrong!
I can get the camera back.
I know where my dad put it.
We can still make it to the festival.
It's not about the movie.
Then what is it about?
You don't get it, do you?
It's obvious!
What's obvious?
- God, you're a dumb ass!
The night of the crash, you
started getting all weird.
What are you talking about?
- Like Mr. Attitude all of a sudden.
Your movie was over.
That's what you said.
You were upset!
- Oh my God.
I gave you my camera. I helped you!
Don't pretend like you did this for me!
You didn't do this for
me, and you know it!
This was never about me.
This was always about Alice!
Well, you were the one who
wanted the wife in the movie.
Not so you could fall in love with her.
What do you care what I
think about Alice any way?
'Cause I like her!
That's why I asked her to do
this thing in the first place.
So that I could get
to know her, not you!
You like Alice Dainard?
You are such an idiot!
Shit!
All that smoke.
We can't use this.
You won't even let
me blow up your train.
This thing is bogus.
We could make another train blow up.
I do like her.
Sorry about that.
- Shut up!
It's okay.
It doesn't even bother me.
She likes you too.
That's what really bothers me.
I know it sounds stupid.
Why would she ever like me?
I haven't lean out yet.
Doctor says it's going to happen.
I don't know, everything
is just so bogus.
Charles...
Joe, what the hell?
What is that?
Mr. Harkin, what's going on?
Evacuation! The fire!
"...being evacuated due to a wild fire
that is raging out of control,
and threatening to reach the
Lillian Chemical plant."
Please take your essential items only.
If you drive your vehicle, follow
the caravan to the evacuation center.
Please remain calm.
Sir, the town is sealed off.
No one is allowed in.
Charles!
Excuse me.
Charles, thank God
I went back to the
house but you were gone.
Yes, they put us on the bus.
Hey, sweety.
I'm going to find my dad.
You're going to tell him about that too.
Come back if you can't find him!
Mr. Dainard? It's Joe Lamb.
I know you don't like me.
I'm sorry about that, but...
I am looking for my dad.
They took her!
They took Alice!
- What?
I saw it.
It was big and...
I don't know what... it was something...
I've never... I've never seen...
No one believed me. They
just gave me pills...
No one believes me.
I believe you.
That thing took her?
- We have to go back in town!
To find Alice. To
find her. Come on Guys!
Dudes, she's dead! Alice is dead!
- Don't even say that!
First of all, I want to live, okay?
Joe, what do you actually
expect us to do, man?
Town is closed. We're
not allowed to go back!
Look I have an idea.
I'm going whether or not you're
coming, which I really hope you do.
Come on guys!
- I've 6 explosives...
we can fire and blow it to shit!
As if I'm going to help you?
Do this for me...
I'll baby-sit the twins every
single Wendy's stupid party.
I'm not shitting you.
You can't ask me any questions,
and you can't tell anyone.
I'm serious. Nobody!
Does it have to be him?
- Yes or no, you ugly freak.
I'm about to rescind the offer.
This whole evacuation is
really freaking me out.
Making me re-grade my priorities.
I saw you over here and I
thought we could kick back.
We totally could.
Asked Charles about you,
he said you're a great guy.
I totally am.
Will you hate me if I start our
relationship by asking a favour?
There're rules to being in my car, okay?
Where the hell are we going anyway?
We're going to the school and open the
caravan Woodward has in the parking lot.
I bet that's where he's keeping his research.
- What research?
We're going to learn everything
we can about that thing,
so that we can find it. That's
how we're going to save Alice.
Dorks! No shoes on my upholstery!
And no one touches my CB. You got it?
What if there're padlocks on the door?
We're going to the school.
Since when this one becomes the boss?
- I don't know.
I got to take a leak!
What am I suppose to do? Piss in here?
Thanks for the hospitality.
Am I going alone or you're
going to end up coming with...
If the aircraft has already
searched Woodward's house,
wouldn't they search
the whole school too?
Maybe his room but not the dungeon.
Woodward’s has...
- Shut up!
What kind of music does
she like, your sister?
I don't care, disco I guess.
I can get back to disco.
We shouldn't take River Road.
They put a roadblock up.
Dork, I saw it. Observe.
So what, I wait here like a douche?
Yes, thank you so much for doing this.
Do you have a tire iron?
Joe!
- Let me try!
God, I hope my electronic
football is in there!
Joe, it's impossible. There
is no way we can do this!
These things are made by a
bank vaulter, like a safe.
Professional robbers can't even
get in through these things!
They are so strong...
I loosen it for you.
Guys.
- All these junks?
He's got movies in here.
I can't believe we're
breaking into the school.
Who does that?
Nobody does that! Elites do that!
Dr. Woodward was
dishonorably discharged,
from Nellis Air Force base in 1963.
because of subversive
conduct. Whatever that is...
Charles, check it out.
It's old man Woodward.
Back when he's like
middle aged man Woodward.
They've been tracking
this thing seen 1958.
What is this?
It says "April 8, 1963 incident."
I don't know.
Cary!
- What?
We have to find this thing! Come on!
Ok, sorry!
Told them that this creature is much
more sophisticated than any of us.
That his species is
predominantly "subterranean".
Subterranean? And to
have it treated without...
compassion or respect.
I explained that all he wants
is to rebuild his ship.
A craft made up of those cubes of
complex shape-shifting alloys.
Remarkable material that we will
never fully understand.
He has been desperate to reconstitute
his ship since it crashed here in '58.
But instead of giving him the help he
needs, we held him as a prisoner.
Guys it's Dr. Woodward.
He has been restrained
And experimented upon, biopsied
and tortured by Nelec.
Through pain and lack of compassion we
have taught him to hate us all.
We have turned him into an enemy.
I told them I knew these things
because he made contact with me.
That he made a psychic
connection by touch.
Oh, my God!
- Jesus.
What's that thing?
- What the hell...
I can't watch this!
The moment he made contact
I understood him.
And he, me.
What I know is that if we don't
change this and begin helping him,
we will all pay the price.
But Nelec wouldn't listen.
He wasn't trying to kill it.
He had me discharged.
He was trying to help him escape.
But I won't give up.
I'll do everything within my power...
- Oh, my God!
- Guys, hear that?
...help him rebuild that ship...
We've positive ID here.
Just a bunch of kids.
Oh, shit.
Search them. Let me see that.
I bought those and made it myself.
Jesus, Cary, shut up!
You're the Deputy's boy.
No.
Move out!
Shit, oh shit!
Breaker, breaker,
requesting police backup.
Breaker 1-9, is this
the police channel?
Staff Sergeant.
- Hi, how are you doing?
Hey, Mr. Lamb.
Rosko.
Where the hell have you been?
What are you wearing?
Come here!
The Air Force set that fire. They
want the town empty for some reason.
The whole operation, the military operation,
evacuation, everything, it's all bad.
We need to find out...
- Did you hear about Joe?
Look, dispatch just got
a call from Citizen Band.
Joe and some of his friends.
They were grabbed by military
personnel at Middle School.
Preston, you tell me everything
and I won't throw you in jail.
Yes sir.
But I think you should
look at this first.
Mr. Sergeant, dust off 03,
is 20 minutes out.
What's going to happen to us?
I think we're going to die.
Shut up! They won't do that.
I'm not kidding, I think
they're going to kill us.
They are not going to kill us.
You know why?
Why?
- 'Cause we were just...
Hold on!
Is that the same thing from the train?
Why are we stopping?
Contact with the precious cargo!
Driver, do you see anything out there?
No, sir, nothing!
What's that gun?
Sako Bolt Action 30W-6...
Okay, we get it.
Those aren't bullets.
He's loading tracking darts.
Here, tag it.
Yes sir.
Open the door!
Don't they give up this.
Sir, is there a particular area
that you want me to shoot?
Help!
Do something now!
Where are the fire powers?
There's a monster out there, Joe!
- Where the hell is it?
I got it, sir!
Guys, the seat-belt
is killing me! Come on!
This is Nelec. Use the big guns!
Whatever happens to me, do not let it...
Joe, open it!
- Open the door!
It's bolted!
Please, open it!
- Where are the keys?
Overmyer help me, my leg's stuck!
Please, sir, open the door.
Please, open the door!
Another one dead!
Guys, there's broken glass.
Martin, let me get up on your shoulders!
Go, go! Get up!
Here we go.
- Come on Joe!
Come on, you all!
You can do it, Joe! Let’s go!
Joe, you break the glass!
Come on guys, hurry!
We've got some questions
for you. Come on!
Is she dead?
- Just come with us.
Hey, fellows.
I got orders from Colonel Nelec to
personally deliver this man back to base.
He's all yours, Staff Sgt.
Let's go.
- What are you doing?
Where are we going?
To find our kids.
Guys, guys! I found them.
Hey guys, I found my firecrackers!
Congratulations!
- Look guys, they're coming back.
I think we should go! Come on!
Guys, come on!
No, look.
You dorks are alive! I thought...
What the fuck?
- Donnie, Donnie...
We need a ride into town.
Okay but just so you know,
I'm massively stoned right now.
Do you want me to drive?
Guys, what was that?
Sound like gun shots.
- Joe where are we going?
I saw something in the cemetery.
Woodward said it was subterranean.
I think I know where it is.
What the hell is that?
Turn the damn car!
Joe, turn the car around!
- I can't 'cause the tank's behind me!
Guys, we have to run!
Donnie, Donnie, wake up!
He's too stoned!
- Drugs are so bad!
Why are they firing?
Come on!
It's crazy, what is going on?
Sir, the weapons are misfiring!
All of them!
Surface-to-air, radar,
it's a mess out here, sir.
Run!
- Come on!
What the hell?
Come on guys, move!
Did you guys see the explosions?
They were huge!
Oh, my God!
Whose house is this?
It's Kathy's. I got it of the fridge.
Kathy? I know her.
Charles, what are you drinking dude?
It's not yours!
I'm thirsty! I'm in a war zone!
Guys, come on, let's go!
- Where are we going?
To the cemetery...
Guys, what happen to my legs? They hurt!
Oh shit, Martin, you got a
bone sticking out your leg!
Joe, give me that thing of the...
I got to go find Alice!
You guys stay here with Martin!
You going to be okay without me?
Yes!
I've got to go save the girl!
- Go on Cary! Shut up!
Come on!
Jesus, Martin, we haven't done it yet!
Just follow me.
I've been following you
for the last five blocks.
What are we doing here?
Come on, get these doors. Help me.
Help you with what?
We've to get inside.
Okay, for what?
I'll tell you in a second.
Why is there dirt on these windows?
At three, push.
One, two, three!
Wow!
This is scary.
You got any sparklers in there?
Are you kidding me?
Alice is down there.
I came to your house that day,
to tell you that I never
meant to hurt anyone.
I swear to God.
I'm sorry, Jack.
About what happened to your wife.
It was an accident.
It 'was an accident.
Joe, I do not understand...
This way.
It's Sheriff Pruitt.
- I know, Cary look.
There are bodies everywhere.
What is this?
- Water from the water tower, look!
She got to be here. She got to be here.
It's eating a person.
She's here. Oh my God, she's here.
Cary, we need to use your firecrackers.
I don't think that is
going to hurt him, Joe.
There's other tunnels.
- So?
I need you to make noise.
Right here in 2 minutes.
Make it loud and make it last.
Use your sparklers.
Make sure you're gone when it blows.
You can't be here. You got to run!
Where are you going?
Come on, Cary.
Alice, please, wake up.
Alice, Alice.
Please, wake up! Alice!
You're alive! You're alive!
You're alive!
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
What is this?
What are you doing here?
I'm just doing the best
I can to safe you.
How did you know?
Your dad, he told me.
He was worried. He's flipping up.
Really?
- We have to move.
Excuse me.
Where are we?
I left my bag in the car and I when I...
He has been locked up for years.
He's terrified and hungry,
and he just wants to go home.
When he touched, I knew.
I need you help me get the sheriff down.
Follow me this way.
I'll get us out of here.
Sure, we came down...
- Don't argue with me!
You just follow me!
Come on kids, just go with the Sheriff.
This way.
Joe!
I told you to get out.
What are you doing here?
I just lost the way out, I tried.
Hey Alice, welcome back.
Hey! Come on, we got
to get out of here now!
She's gone! It took her!
I don't want to be next!
Go!
You don't want to be here! Go!
Joe, what are you doing?
What the hell is he doing?
We understand!
But not everyone is bad.
I know bad things happen.
Bad things happen.
But you can still live.
You can still live.
Okay, wait a minute.
What?
Look Out! Get down! Get down!
What are you doing?
He's making a model.
I got you.