The Dark Knight Rises
Subtitle by
Amir & Hossein
special thanks to
Antovolk & Peean91
.........
But I knew Harvey Dent.
I was... his friend.
And it will be a very long time before
Someone inspires us the way he did.
I believed in Harvey Dent.
- Dr. Pavel, I’m CIA.
- He wasn’t alone.
- You don’t get to bring friends.
- They are not my friends.
- Don’t worry, no charge for them.
- Why would I want them?
They were trying to grab your prize.
They work for the mercenary.
The masked man.
Bane?
Get ’em on board. I’ll call it in.
The flight plan I just filed with the agency
Lists me, my men, and Dr. Pavel here.
But only one of you.
The first one to talk get to stay on my aircraft.
Who paid you to grab Dr. Pavel?
He didn’t fly so good! Who wants to try next?!
Tell me about Bane! Why does he wear the mask?!
Lot of loyalty for a hired gun!
Or he’s wondering why someone would shoot a man
Before throwing him out of an aeroplane.
At least you can talk.
Who are you?
Who we are does not matter.
What matters is our plan.
And no one cared
who I was until I put on the mask...
- If I pull this off, will you die?
- It would be extremely painful.
- You’re a big guy
- ... for you.
Was being caught part of your plan?
Of course.
Dr. Pavel refused our offer in favor of yours.
We had to know what he told you
Nothing! I said nothing!
Well congratulations, you got yourselves caught.
Sir...
What’s the next step of your master plan?
Crashing this plane...
With no survivors.
Mayday! Mayday!
No!
They expect one of us in the wreckage. Brother
- Have we started the fire?
- The fire rises.
Calm down, doctor.
Now this is not the time for fear.
That comes later.
Harvey Dent day may not be our oldest public holiday...
But we’re here tonight because it’s
one of the most important...
Harvey Dent’s uncompromising stand
against organized crime
Have made Gotham a safer place than it
was at the time of his death,
Eight years ago...
This city has seen a historic
turnaround.
No city is without crime.
But this city is without organized crime
Because the Dent act gave law enforcement teeth in
its fight against the mob.
Now people are talking
about repealing the Dent act.
And to them I say... not on my watch.
I want to thank the Wayne
foundation for hosting this event.
I’m told Mr. Wayne couldn’t be here tonight,
But I’m sure he’s with us in spirit...
Now I’m going to give way to an important voice...
Ever lay eyes on Wayne at one of these things?
No one has. Not in years.
That people put their faith in a
murderous thug in a mask and a cape.
A thug who showed his true nature
When he betrayed the trust of this
great man and murdered him in cold blood.
Sweetheart, not so fast with the chow.
Shrimp balls?
Jim Gordon can tell you the truth
about Harvey Dent...
Thank you.
Let him tell you himself.
Commissioner Gordon!
The truth...?
I have written a speech telling the
truth about Harvey Dent...
Maybe the time isn’t right...
Maybe right now
All you need to know is that
There are a thousand
inmates in Blackgate prison
As a direct result of the Dent act.
These are violent criminals, essential cogs in the
organized crime machine that terrorized Gotham for so long.
Maybe, for now, all I should say
about Harvey Dent’s death is this...
It has not been for nothing.
Did you see the guy who owns the house?
They say he never leaves the east wing.
I heard he had an accident... That he’s disfigured.
Mr. Till, why are your people using the main stairs?
- Where’s Mrs. Bolton?
- She’s up at the bar, sir. Can I help?
The east drawing room.
Unlock the door, place the tray on the table,
Lock the door again.
Nothing more.
I’m sorry, miss Tate, but I’ve tried.
He won’t see you.
Don’t take it personally, Miranda.
Everyone knows Wayne’s holed up in there
With eight-Inch nails, peeing  into mason jars.
Good of you to let me on the grounds.
Why waste your time talking to the man
Who threw away your investment
On some save-The-World vanity project?
He can’t help you get your money back. But I can.
I could try explaining that the save the world project,
Vain or not, is worth investing in, Mr. Daggett.
But you understand only money
and the power you think it buys,
So why waste my time, indeed?
The second shift reports in?
But you should put in some more time with the mayor
That’s your department.
Anyone shown him the crime stats?
He goes by his gut,
And it continues to bother him, whatever the numbers.
Must be popular with the wife.
Not really. She took the kids and moved to Cleveland.
He’ll have plenty of time for visits.
Mayor’s dumping him in the spring.
Really? He’s a hero.
War hero. This is peacetime.
I’m... sorry
I’m terribly sorry, Mr. Wayne.
It is Mr. Wayne, isn’t it?
Although you don’t have the long nails... or facial scars...
Is that what they say about me?
It’s just that... nobody sees you...
That’s a beautiful necklace.
Reminds me of the one that belonged to my mother.
It can’t be the same one
Her pearls are in this safe
Which the manufacturer clearly
explained is uncrackable.
Oops. No one told me it was uncrackable.
I’m afraid I can’t let you take those.
Look, you wouldn’t hit a woman
Any more than I would beat up a cripple.
Of course, sometimes exceptions have to be made.
Good night, Mr. Wayne!
- Can I have a ride?
- You read my mind.
Let's go!
Miss Tate was asking to see you again.
- She’s very persistent.
- And quite lovely,
- In case you were wondering.
- I wasn't.
- What are you doing?
- Examining print dust.
We’ve been robbed.
And this is your idea of raising the alarm?
She took the pearls. Tracking device and all.
- She?
- One of the maids,
Perhaps you should stop letting
them in this side of the house.
Perhaps you should learn to make your own bed, then.
- Why are you dusting for prints?
- I’m not. She was.
Sir! Congressman Gilly’s wife’s been calling.
In apparently the Congressman never made it home
from the Wayne foundation event.
That’s a job for the police?
When you and Dent cleaned the streets you cleaned ’em good.
Pretty soon we’ll be chasing overdue library books.
Yet here you are. Like we’re still at war...
- What's your name, son?
- Blake, sir.
You have something you want to ask me, officer Blake?
It’s that night. This night, eight
years ago. The night Dent died.
The last confirmed sighting of the Batman.
He murders those people, takes out two swat teams,
Breaks Dent’s neck... then just vanishes?
I’m not hearing a question, son.
Don’t you want to know who we was?
I know exactly who he was.
He was Batman.
Let’s go see about the Congressman’s wife...
Master Wayne!
You haven’t been down here in a long time...
Just trying to find out more about our jewel thief.
I ran her prints
Unless she loss a lot of weight,
But she was wearing someone else’s fingerprints.
She’s good.
She may be. But we have the trace on the necklace.
We do, so I cross-Referenced the address she went back to
With police data on
high-End b- And-E’s...
Selina kyle.
The databases are full of close calls, tips from fences...
She’s good, but the ground is shrinking beneath her feet.
We should send the police before she fences the pearls.
She won’t. She likes them too much.
And they weren’t what she was after.
- What was she after?
- My fingerprints.
There was printer toner mixed with graphite on the safe.
Gives you a good pull, and it’s untraceable
Fascinating. Maybe you should
exchange notes over coffee.
Now you’re trying to set me up with a jewel thief?
At this point, sir, I would set you up with a chimpanzee
If I thought it would bring
you back into the world.
- There’s nothing out there for me.
- And that's the problem.
You hung up the cape and cowl, but didn't moved on.
You won’t get out there and find a life. To find someone
Alfred...
Did find someone
I know. And then you lost them.
That’s part of living, sir.
But you’re not living... You’re waiting.
Hoping for things to go bad again.
Remember when you left Gotham?
Before all this. Before Batman.
You've been gone for seven years.
Seven years I waited. Hoping that you wouldn’t come back.
Every year, I took a holiday.
Every year I took my holiday.
I’d go to Florence. There’s a café by the Arno...
Every fine evening, I’ll sit there and ordered a fernet branca.
I had this fantasy..
That one day I’d look across the tables, and see you there
Sitting there with your wife. Perhaps some kids.
You wouldn’t say anything to me, or me to you,
But we’d both know... that you’d made it.
That you were happy.
I never wanted you to come back to Gotham.
I knew there was nothing there for you
But pain and tragedy,
And I wanted more for you than that.
I still do.
They wash up a couple times a month.
More when it gets colder
Homeless sheltering in the tunnels.
We had to pull him from the basin, but
other than that we didn’t touch him...
What?
Name’s Jimmy. He’s at st. Swithin’s.
The boys home where I... I coach some ball.
Jimmy hadn’t been here for months.
- No, why?
- Blake, you know why.
He aged out.
We don't have the resources to keep the boys on after 16.
I thought the Wayne foundation gave money for them.
Not for the past couple of years.
- He has a brother here, doesn't he?
- Mark. I'll tell him.
I'd like to. If that's alright.
What was he doing in the tunnels?
Lot of guys been going down the tunnels when they age out.
Say you can live down there.
Say there’s work down there.
Work?
What kind of work are you gonna find in the sewers?
More than you can find up here, I guess.
- So you know about him.
- Of course.
Do you think he's coming back?
I don't know...
You brought a date?
I like having someone around to open doors for me.
Right hand. No partials.
Very nice!
Not so fast, handsome. You got something for me?
Oh yes.
I don’t know what you’re going to do with Mr. Wayne’s prints...
But I’m guessing you’ll need his thumb.
- You don’t count so good, huh?
- I count fine.
In fact, I’m counting to 10 right now.
Okay...
My friend is waiting outside. Just hit ’send’...
- Place is a little dead.
- It’ll liven up in a minute, trust me.
Is everything okay?
Great. Catch you later.
It would’ve been a lot easier to just give me what we agreed.
We can’t have loose ends.
And even in that dress, no one’s going to miss you.
No. But my friend over there...?
Every cop in the city’s missing him.
Cute. But they’re not gonna be looking in a place like this.
I don’t know... you did just use his cell phone.
Police! Get down now!
Help me!
Keep some pressure on that, sweetheart.
Call me?
- Careful, miss.
- He's bleeding! You gotta help him!
I've got the Congressman.
There!
Manhole! Get this out.
Get the DWP down here, now!
You three, down with me.
You two, head down to cover the next exit
What? He went down there?
- We're going down there, right?
- That was a gas explosion, kid.
Gas? This is a sewer!
No one goes in there till we know what’s down there.
We know what’s down there, sir.
The police commissioner!
Somebody get the hothead out of here.
Where’s the DWP guy?
Why are you here?
Answer him!
I was asking you.
It’s the police commissioner.
- And you brought him down here?
- We didn't know what to do.
- We just thought...
- You panicked.
And your weakness cost the lives of three others.
No, he’s alone
Search him. Then I’ll kill you.
He's dead!
So show me his body!
That water runs to any one of the outflows
We’d never find him.
- Follow him.
- Follow him?
Detective! Detective! Hey!
You awake?
I need to see Bruce Wayne.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wayne doesn't take unscheduled calls,
Even from a police officer.
And if I go get a warrant,
in the investigation of Harvey Dent’s murder?
Would that still count as unscheduled?
What can I do for you, officer?
Commissioner Gordon’s been shot.
He chased a gunman down into the sewers.
When I pulled him out he was
babbling about an underground army.
A masked man called ’Bane’.
Shouldn’t you be telling this to your superior officers?
They asked if he saw
any giant alligators.
He needs you.
He needs the Batman.
If commissioner Gordon thinks
He doesn’t know or care who you are.
But we’ve met before.
There was a long ago,
I was a kid at st. Swithin's...
Used to be funded
by the Wayne foundation.
It's an orphanage.
My mom died when I was small.
Car accident,
I don’t really remember it.
But a couple of years later my dad was shot
Over a gambling debt.
I remember that just fine.
Not a lot of people who what it feels
like, do they? To be angry. In your bones.
I mean they understand.
The fosters parents.
Everybody understands...
...for a while.
Then they expect the angry kid to do what
he knows he can never do.
Move on.
After a while they stop understanding.
They send the angry little
kid to a boy's school.
I figured it out too late.
You got to learn to hide the anger,
practice smiling in the mirror.
It's like putting on a mask.
You showed up one day in a cool car,
Pretty girl on your arm.
We were so excited - Bruce Wayne,
billionaire orphan.
We made up stories about you. Legends.
And you know the other kids,
that's all it was, it's just stories.
But when I saw you,
I knew who you really were.
I seen that look on your face before.
Same one I taught myself.
I don’t know why you took the fall for Dent’s murder,
But I’m still a believer in the Batman.
Even if you’re not.
Why did you say your boys’ home
Used to be funded by the Wayne foundation?
Because the money stopped.
Might be time to get some fresh air
And start paying attention to the details.
Some of those details might need your help.
You checked that name? ’Bane’
He’s a mercenary. No other known name.
He and his men were
behind a coup in west Africa
That secured mining operations
for our friend John Daggett
- Now Doggett’s brought them here?
- It would seem so.
- I’ll keep digging.
- Yeah.
Alfred, why did the Wayne foundation
Stopped funding the boy's home in the city?
The foundation is funded by the
profits of Wayne enterprises.
There have to be some...
Time to talk to Mr. Fox I think.
I'll get him on the phone.
No. Do we still have any cars around the place?
Yes, one or two
And I need an appointment at the hospital.
About my leg.
- Which hospital?
- Whichever one Jim Gordon’s in.
I’ve seen worse cartilage in knees
- That’s good
- No.
That’s because there is no cartilage in your knee.
And not much of any use in your elbows and shoulders.
Between that and the scar tissue on your kidneys,
Residual concussive damage to your brain tissue
And general scarred-Over quality of your body...
I cannot recommend that you go heli-Skiing.
Right.
We were in this together.
Then you were gone...
The Batman wasn’t needed anymore.
We won.
Built on a lie. Our lie.
Now there’s evil rising from where we tried to bury it.
The Batman has to come back.
What if he doesn’t exist anymore?
He must. You...
Goddammit,
- You took my wallet!
- No I didn't!
- Get out!
- She took my wallet...
Now!
Crazy!
I don’t know what he’s so upset
about, he only had 60 bucks in here.
Probably the watch.
Who's that?
Another stiff too old to climb out of his sports car.
Well that's Bruce Wayne!
Bruce Wayne, over here!
- I’m not sure if my assistant put me on the guest list
- Right through here, Mr. Wayne.
Thank you so much.
Bruce Wayne at a charity ball?
Miss Tate, isn’t it?
Even before you became a recluse,
you never came to these things...
Proceeds goes to big fat spread.
This is not about charity.
It’s about feeding the ego of
whichever society hag laid it on.
Actually this is my party, Mr. Wayne.
And the proceeds will go where they should,
Because I paid for the big fat spread myself.
That’s very generous of you.
You have to invest to restore balance to the world.
Take our
clean-Energy project...
Sometimes the investment doesn’t pay off.
I'm sorry.
You have a practiced apathy, Mr. Wayne.
But a man who doesn’t care about the
world doesn’t spend half his fortune
On a plan to save it...
And isn’t so wounded when it
fails that he goes into hiding...
Have a good evening, Mr. Wayne.
Mind if I cut in?
Thank you.
You don’t seem very happy to see me.
- You were supposed to be a shut-In.
- Felt like some fresh air.
Why didn’t you call the police?
I have a powerful friend who deals
with this kind of thing.
Brazen costume for a
cat burglar.
- Yeah? Who are you pretending to be?
- Bruce Wayne, eccentric billionaire.
- Who’s your date?
- His wife’s in Ibiza.
She left her diamonds behind, though.
Worried they’d get stolen.
It’s pronounced ’’Ibeetha’.
You wouldn’t want these
folks realizing you’re a crook
not a social climber.
You think I care what anyone in
this room thinks about me?
I doubt you care what anyone in
this room thinks about you.
Don’t condescend, Mr. Wayne.
You don’t know a thing about me.
Well, Selina kyle,
I know you came here from your walk-Up in old town
Modest place for a master jewel thief.
Which means either you’re saving for your retirement
Or you’re in deep with the wrong people.
You don’t get to judge me because
You were born in the master bedroom of Wayne manor.
Actually, I was born in the regency room.
I started off doing what I had to.
Once you’ve done what you had to
They’ll never let you do what you want to.
Start fresh.
There’s no fresh start in today’s world.
Any 12year old with a cell phone
could find out what you did.
Everything we do is collated and quantified.
Everything sticks.
Is that how you justify stealing?
I take what I need to from those
who have more than enough.
I don’t stand on the shoulders of people with less.
Robin hood?
I’d do more to help someone than
most of the people in this room.
Thank you.
Maybe you’re assuming too much.
Or maybe you’re being unrealistic about what’s
really in your pants other than your wallet.
Ouch.
You think all this can last?
There’s a storm coming, Mr. Wayne.
You and your friends better batten down the hatches,
because when it hits you’re all gonna wonder
How you ever thought you could live so large and
Leave so little to the rest of us.
Sounds like you’re looking forward to it.
I'm adaptable.
These pearls do look better on you
then they did in my safe...
But I still can’t let you keep them.
You scared her off!
Not likely...
I must have lost my ticket
Your wife said you were taking a cab home, sir.
My wife?
Just you, sir?
Don’t worry, master Wayne.
Takes a little time to get
back into the swing of things.
Bruce Wayne. As I live and breathe.
What brings you out of cryo-Sleep Mr. Wayne?
I see you haven’t lost your sense of humor...
Even if you have lost most of my money.
Actually, you did that yourself.
See, if you funnel the entire R and D budget
Into a fusion project that you then mothball,
Your company is unlikely to thrive.
What’re my options?
If you’re not willing to turn your machine on
I can't. I can't, Lucius.
Then sit tight.
Your majority keeps Daggett at arm’s length
while we figure out a future for the
energy program with Miranda Tate
She’s supported your project all the way.
She’s smart, and quite lovely.
We all just want what's best for you, Bruce.
- Show her the machine.
- I think it over.
- Anything else?
- Nope. Why?
These conversations always used to
end with some... unusual requests.
I retired.
Let me show you some stuff, anyway.
Just for old times' sake.
I figured you’d have shut this place down.
Oh, it was always shut down.
Officially.
But all this new stuff?
After your father died, Wayne enterprises
Set up 14 different defense subsidiaries.
I’ve spent years shuttering them and consolidating
All the prototypes under one roof.
- My roof.
- Why?
Stop them falling into the wrong hands.
Now you’re just showing off.
Defense department project for
Tight-Geometry urban pacification.
Rotors configured for maneuvering between buildings
without recirculation.
What’s it called?
It has a long and uninteresting
Wayne enterprises designation.
So I took to calling it the bat.
And yes, Mr. Wayne,
it does come in black.
Works great except for the
autopilot.
Take a
better mind than mine to fix it.
A better mind?
Well I was trying to be modest.
A less busy mind, yours.
It is terribly painful?
You’re welcome to try it, Alfred.
Happy watching, thank you, sir.
Not bad...
Not bad at all!
Master Wayne,
if you’re considering going back out there
You need to hear some rumors surrounding Bane.
I'm all ears.
There is a prison.
In a more ancient part of the world.
A pit. Where men are thrown to suffer and die.
But sometimes, a man rises from the darkness.
Sometimes... the pit sends something back.
- Bane!
- Right.
Born and raised in a hell on earth.
Born in a prison?
No one knows why.
Or how he escaped.
But they know who trained him one he did... Ra’s Al Ghul.
Your mentor.
Bane was a member of the League of Shadows.
And then he was excommunicated.
And any man who is too extreme for Ra's al Ghoul,
Is not to be trifled with.
I didn’t realize I was known for trifling with criminals.
That was then.
And you can strap up
your leg and put the mask back on.
But it won’t make you what you were.
If this man is all the things you say he is,
then this city needs me.
This city needs Bruce Wayne.
Your resources, your knowledge...
Not your body. Not your life.
That time has passed.
That’s what you’re afraid of.
That if I go back out there I’ll fail.
No.
I’m afraid that you want to.
You can’t short the stock because
Bruce Wayne goes to a party
Wayne coming back is change.
- Change is either good or bad.
- I vote bad.
- On what basis?
- I flipped a coin.
No. Rye. I told ’em rye.
Rookie! Lose the helmet! We need faces for cameras.
Come on let's go scalping.
This is a stock exchange,
there’s no money you can steal
Really? Then why are you people here?
You got to get in there!
- It's a hostage situation.
- It’s a robbery!
They’ve got direct
access to the online trading desk.
I’m not risking my men for your money
Sir, you going to ask you to move.
We have a situation here.
It’s not our money, it’s everyone’s!
Really? Mine’s in my mattress.
If you don’t shut these guys down,
The stuffing in that mattress might
be worth a whole lot less, pal.
Cut the fiber line - Shut down the cell tower.
- Thank you.
- That’ll slow them down.
They cut the fiber.
- Cell’s working.
- For now.
Get the barriers up
I want all of them up.
No more in and out on this street!
- Where am I suppose to move it?
- Back it up.
Just stay in your vehicle, okay?
How much longer does the program need?
Eight minutes.
Time to go mobile.
Everybody up!
You two, move!
Thank you.
Steady!
I got something!
Do not shoot! We've hostages!
Hold your fire!
Go! Go!
Hey, let me go!
Please! Hey!
- Shoot the tires!
- There's no shot.
Now back off! Back off!
They've got hostages!
Police are pursuing the 4 suspects from
Downtown in respond to a hostage situation
Gotham PD...
What’s going on with the lights?
I can't pick up anything!
The hell was that?!
Oh boy. You’re in for a show tonight, son.
Please! Help!
Sorry!
Put that thing away before you hurt yourself.
Get in!
Let's go. You, get in the car!
They’ve spotted the Batman!
Call everyone in
Every car patrol, beat cop, off-Duty, too!
Call in now!
I’m gonna do what Gordon never could.
- What's that?
- I'm going to take down the Batman.
.. The 4 suspect are carrying two hostages
That they kidnapped them at
the Gotham stock exchange.
Witnesses reported that...
It seems hard to believe.
But report are suspects
are now being pursued,
What appears to be, the Batman.
Well, what do you know?
Sir, what about the armed robbers?
Please! Let me go! Please!
One bike’s pulled off,
No hostage. Shall we pursue?
Negative! Stay on the Batman!
- But he’s getting away!
- Who do you want to catch?
Some robber, or the son of a
bitch who killed Harvey Dent?
After eight years he has to pick tonight...
He’s drawing the cops off Bane...
Please! Just let me go! Please!
Transferring complete
We lost him.
How could you lose him?
He’s got a lot of firepower
And you don’t?!
He’s heading back downtown...
Then he’s as dumb as he dresses -
Close it down, gentlemen!
Like a rat in a trap, gentlemen!
You might have the wrong animal there, sir
Are you sure that was him?
Bane says the Batman interfered,
but the task was accomplished.
What about the men they arrested?
He says, and I quote,
they would die before talking.
Where does he find these guys?
Open the champagne!
- And can we get some girls in here?
- Careful what you wish for.
- Cat got your tongue?
- You dumb bitch!
Nobody ever accused me of being dumb.
Dumb to show up here tonight.
I want what you owe me
- ’One’ doesn't gets...
- Nice outfit...
Those heels make it tough to walk?
I don’t know, do they?
- So where is it?
- Where's what?
The program. The ’clean slate’.
Oh, yeah - The ultimate tool for a
master thief with a record.
Hold it right there!
- Where is it?!
- The ’clean slate’?
Type in a name and date of birth
And a few minutes they're gone,
every database on earth.
Sounds a little too good to be true?
You’re lying. Rykin data took it to prototype stage
That’s why I bought them.
But they had nothing.
It was a gangland myth.
Stay back!
I'm not bluffing!
They know! They just don't care.
- You got to be kidding me.
- No guns, no killing.
Where’s the fun in that?
My mother warned me about getting
into cars with strange men
This isn't a car.
See you around!
You're welcome!
- I had it under control.
- Those weren’t street thugs
- They were trained
killers. I saved your life.
In return I need to know what you
did with Bruce Wayne’s fingerprints.
Wayne wasn’t kidding about a ’powerful friend’.
I sold his prints to Daggett.
For something that doesn’t even exist.
I doubt many people get the better of you.
- Hey, when a girl’s desperate...
- What were they going to do with them?
I don’t know. But Daggett
Seemed pretty interested in
that mess at the stock market.
Miss kyle...
So that’s what that feels like.
I've seen you in the television coverage,
You seem to have your
taste for wanton destruction back.
I retrieved this.
Shouldn’t the police be gathering the evidence?
They don’t have the tools to analyze it.
They would if you gave them to them
One man’s tool is another man’s weapon.
In your mind, perhaps.
But there aren’t many things
you couldn’t turn into a weapon.
Alfred. Enough. The police weren’t getting it done
Perhaps they would’ve if you
haven’t made a sideshow of yourself.
You thought I didn’t have it in me.
You don’t. You lead a bloated
police force on a merry chase
with some fancy new toys from fox.
What about when you come up against him.
What then?
I’ll fight harder, I always have.
Take a good look. At his speed,
his ferocity, his training.
I see the power of belief.
See the League of Shadows resurgent.
- You said he was excommunicated.
- By Ra's al Ghoul.
Who leads them now?
Ra's al Ghoul was the league
of shadows and I beat him.
Bane is just a mercenary,
we need to find out what he's up to.
Trades of some kind. Coded...
And my fingerprints courtesy of Selina kyle.
Get this to fox
He can crack the code
And tell us what trades they were executing.
I’ll get this to fox. But no more.
I’ve sewn you up and set your bones...
but I won’t bury you.
I’ve buried enough members of the Wayne family.
You leave me?
You see only one end to your journey.
Leaving is all I have to make you understand:
You aren’t Batman anymore
You have to find another way.
You used to talk about finishing.
About life beyond that awful cave
Rachel died knowing we’d decided to be together.
That was my life beyond this cave
And I can’t just move on.
She didn’t. She couldn’t.
- What if he had?
- She was, I can’t change that
What if, before she died, she’d written a letter?
Saying she’d chosen Harvey Dent over you?
And what if, to spare you pain...
I’d burned that letter?
How dare you use Rachel to stop me!
I’m using the truth, master Wayne.
Maybe it’s time we all stopped
trying to outsmart the truth
And just let it have its day.
- I’m sorry.
- You're sorry?
You expect to destroy my world,
...and then think we're going to shake hands?
No.
- I know what this means
- What does it mean?!
It means your hatred.
It means losing the person
I’ve cared for ever since I heard
His first cries echo through this house.
But it might also mean saving your life.
And that is more important.
Good bye, Alfred!
Alfred?
- Answering your own door?
- Yeah.
Page three.
It seems you made a series of large
put options on the futures exchange.
Verified by thumb print.
The options expired at midnight last night.
Long term we may be able to prove
fraud, but for now...
You’re completely broke.
And Wayne enterprises is about to
fall into the hands of John Daggett.
The weapons
- We can’t let Daggett
get his hands on applied sciences
Applied sciences is shut up tight,
and off the books.
The energy project is a different story.
Miranda Tate...
We need to convince the board to get behind her.
Let’s show her the reactor
We’re meeting her there in 35 minutes.
You better get dressed.
You brought me out here to show me this, Mr. Fox?
Bear with me, miss Tate.
Keep your hands and feet inside the car at all times.
This is it, isn't it?
The reactor is beneath the river
So that it could be instantly flooded
in an event of a security breach.
Is Bruce Wayne really that paranoid?
I’m gonna plead the fifth on that one.
I thought you might like to see
what your investment built.
No fossil fuels.
Free, clean energy for an entire city.
Three years ago a Russian scientist
published a paper on weaponized fusion reactions.
One week later your reactor started
developing problems...
I think this machine works.
Miranda, if it were operational,
the danger to Gotham would be too great.
Would it make you feel better to
know that the Russian scientist
Died in a plane crash 6 months ago?
Someone else will work out what Dr. Pavel did.
Someone else will figure out how to turn
This power source into a nuclear weapon.
I need you to take control of
Wayne enterprises and this reactor.
- And to do what with it?
- Nothing.
- Until we can guarantee its safety.
- And if we can't?
Decommission it, flood it.
Destroy the world’s best chance for
a sustainable future?
If the world’s not ready. Yes.
Bruce, if you want to save the
world you have to start trusting it.
I’m trusting you.
Doesn’t count. You have no choice.
I could’ve flooded this chamber any
time in the last three years.
I’m choosing to trust you, Miranda, please.
Alright ladies and gentlemen,
this meeting will now come to order.
I’d like to point out that we have
a non-Board member here.
I is highly irregular, even if it is his family
name above the door...
Bruce Wayne’s family built this company
- And he himself has run it...
- Into the ground, sir!
Does anybody disagrees?
Check the value of your shares this morning.
Gambling on crazy futures didn’t
just lose Mr. Wayne his seat,
It’s lost us all a lot of money.
He needs to leave.
I’m afraid he has a point, Mr. Wayne.
Let’s get down to business.
Wayne, how’s it feel to be one of the people?!
Mr. Wayne, they're towing your car..
I didn't know that you're off the board.
Looks like you need a lift.
Mr. Wayne, will you get a ride?
How the hell did Miranda Tate get
the inside track on the Wayne board?!
Was she meeting with Wayne?
Was she sleeping with Wayne?
Not that we know of
Clearly you don’t ’know of’ anything,
do you?! Where’s Bane?!
- We told him it was urgent
- Then where is the masked...
Speak of the devil...
and he shall appear.
What the hell’s going on?
The plan is proceeding as expected.
Really? You see me running Wayne enterprises?!
Your stock exchange hit didn’t work, friend.
And now you’ve got my construction crews
Working all hours around the city?
How’s that supposed to help
my company absorb Wayne’s?
- Leave us!
- You stay right there!
I’m in charge!
Do you feel in charge?
I’ve paid you a small fortune
And that gives you power over me?
What is this?
Your money and infrastructure have
been important.
Till now.
- What are you?
- Gotham’s reckoning.
Come to end the borrowed time
you’ve all been living on...
You are pure evil.
- I am necessary evil.
- No!
When you began... why the mask?
To protect the people closest to me.
You’re a loner with no family.
There are always people you care about.
You just don’t realize how
much until they’re gone.
The idea was to be a symbol.
Batman could be anybody, that was the point.
- It was damn good to see him back.
- Not everybody agrees.
They’ll figure it out in the end.
Got anything on Bane’s whereabouts?
Yeah, I’ve got 500 pages
of tunnel records and a flashlight.
I could use some help.
You know what? Drop me in old town...
- I don't think so!
- That is not how it works.
He’s not a mark.
And he doesn’t have a cent to his name, anyway.
Yeah, it’s not much.
But it’s more that you’ve got right now.
Actually, they’re letting me keep the house.
The rich don’t even go broke same
as the rest of us, huh?
My powerful friend hopes to change
your mind about leaving.
- And how would he do that?
- By giving you what you want.
- It doesn’t exist.
- He says it does.
- He wants to meet. Tonight.
- Why?
He needs to find Bane.
He says you’d know how.
- Tell him I’ll think about it.
- Okay. I like your place.
Mr. Wayne?
I’m sorry they took all your money.
No, you’re not.
- Can we help you, officer?
- Yeah.
John Daggett’s body was just found
in a dumpster an hour ago.
I thought you
might like to know.
Why?
Well, name is all over the permits...
...I just pulled to map the
tunnels under Gotham.
That's MTA maintenance, sewer
construction and others things...
Where did you get to
with the tunnel searches?
Remind me to tell the detail
to keep hotheads out.
We’ve had teams down there,
but it’s a huge network.
Well, Get more men.
Work a grid.
I want him found.
Yeah... The masked man.
We’re on it.
Lose the uniform
You’re working for me now.
We could use some
hotter heads around here.
Sir, Daggett's just could be a coincidence
You’re a detective now, son.
You’re not allowed to
believe in coincidence anymore.
- Nobody’s answering.
- No.
- I’m on my own now.
- Do you have keys?
Never needed them.
Hope you don’t like me for my money.
Suffering builds character.
I'll take care of
your parents' legacy, Bruce.
Who's this?
Where's Alfred?
He left.
Taking everything.
- What's that?
- I think my power's been shut off.
You're good at that.
When I was a child we had almost nothing.
But on the nights when we had a fire,
we felt very rich indeed.
I assumed your family was wealthy.
Not always.
Not when I was young.
- An old mistake.
- I've made a few myself
More than a few.
We could leave. Tonight.
Take my plane.
Go anywhere we wanted.
Someday perhaps. Not tonight.
Don't be shy.
Wayne says you can
get me the 'Clean Slate'.
- That depends
- On what?
On what you want it for.
I acquired it to keep it
out of the wrong hands
Still don't trust me, huh?
- How can we change that?
- Start by taking me to Bane
You asked.
From here, Bane's men patrol the
tunnels...
...and they are not your
average brawlers.
Neither am I.
- He's behind you.
- Who?
Me.
Where do you think you're...?
Just a little further.
I had to find a way
to stop them trying to kill me.
You made a serious mistake.
Not as serious as yours...
...I fear.
- Bane.
- Let's not stand on ceremony here...
...Mr. Wayne.
Peace has cost you strength.
Victory has defeated you.
Theatricality and deception...
...powerful agents to the uninitiated.
But we are initiated, aren't we, Bruce?
Members of the League of Shadows.
And you betrayed us.
Us? You were excommunicated.
From a gang of psychopaths.
I am the League of Shadows...
...and I'm here to fulfill
Ra's Al Ghul's destiny.
You fight like a younger man.
With nothing held back.
It's admirable. But mistaken.
Ah, You think darkness is your ally.
But you merely adopted the dark.
I was born in it.
Molded by it.
I didn't see the light
until I was already a man.
And by then it was
nothing to me but blinding.
The shadows betray you,
because they belong to me.
I will show you where
I've made my home...
...while preparing to bring justice.
Then, I will break you.
Your precious armory.
Gratefully accepted.
We will need it.
Ah, yes! I was wondering
what would break first...
...your spirit...
...or your body.
Get me Commissioner Gordon.
I got a line on the
Congressman's kidnapping.
subtitle by:
A m i r & H o s s e i n
- Excuse me, Miss.
- Yes?
I'm going to need to see your
ticket and identification, please.
Do you mind?
I showed your picture
to Congressman. Guess what?
- Don't tell me, still in love?
- Oh, Head over heels.
Pressing charges, though.
You've made some mistakes, Ms. Kyle.
- Girl's got to eat.
- And you have an appetite.
Why would you run? You can't hide
from us with a record like this.
- Maybe it's not you I'm running from.
- Who then? Bane?
What do you know about him?
That you should be
as afraid of him as I am.
We can offer you protection.
Okay.
When I spotted you, I was looking
for a friend of mine, Bruce Wayne.
Did they kill him?
I'm not sure.
Why didn't you just kill me?
You don't fear death.
You welcome it.
Your punishment must be more severe.
- You're a torturer...
- Yes.
But not of your body.
Of your soul.
- Where am I?
- Home.
Where I learned the truth
about despair. As will you.
There is a reason that this prison
is the worst hell on earth...
Hope.
Every man who has rotted here over
the centuries has looked up to the light...
...and imagined climbing to freedom.
So easy. So simple.
And, like shipwrecked men turning to
sea water from uncontrollable thirst...
...many have died trying.
I learned here that there can be
no true despair without hope.
So as I terrorize Gotham...
I will feed its people hope
to poison their souls.
I will let them believe they can survive...
...so that you can watch
them clamber over each other...
...to stay in the sun.
You could watch me torture entire city...
...and then, when you have truly
understood the depths of your failure...
...we will fulfill Ra's al Ghul's destiny.
We will destroy Gotham.
And then when it is done
and Gotham is ashes...
...then you have my permission to die.
We're locking her up in here?
The Dent Act allows non-segregation
based on extraordinary need.
First time she broke out of
women's correctional she was 16.
- Little closer, baby...
- Why, honey, you wanna hold my hand?
She's gonna be fine.
Still don't see the need of
a board meeting for the energy project.
Bruce got a lot of things right.
Keeping the board in the dark
wasn't one of them.
Oh, good of you to join us,
Chair, President.
All I need now is one more
Ordinary Board member.
- Mr. Fox, would you like to nominate?
- No. I will volunteer.
Where are you taking us?
You were right, Commissioner!
Would you excuses us, please?
What's happened?
Your masked man kidnapped
the Wayne Enterprises board.
He let most of them go,
but took three down into the sewers.
No more patrols,
no more hide and seek.
Get every available cop
down there and smoke him out!
- The Mayor won't want panic.
- So it's a training exercise.
I'm sorry I didn't take you seriously.
Not you.
You're telling me the Batman have gone.
So you chase up the Daggett leads,
any way you can.
Yes, sir.
He asks how much you would
pay us to let you die?
I told him... I told him
you have nothing.
Do it for the pleasure.
They pay me more than dead
to keep you alive.
He will try the climb.
Has anyone made it?
Of course not.
He says there is one who did.
A child.
A child born in this hell.
- Bane.
- An old legend. Nothing more.
- Don't.
- Whatever it is they want you to see, it's happening soon.
Fire in the hole!
Turn it on.
I only need one other board member.
There are eight others waiting.
I won't do it.
Alright, stop.
Lucius, you'll kill this man and yourself...
...and you'll barely slow them down.
Go on then, do your work.
Take them up to the surface.
People of their status
deserve to experience...
...the next era of western civilization.
I've been to half of Daggett's
cement plants, some odd locations...
...they've poured
for underground construction.
Anything strange about the pourings?
Honestly, Commissioner, I don't know
anything about civil engineering.
But you know about patterns.
Keep looking
It's done. This is now a
4- megaton nuclear bomb.
Pull the core out of the reactor.
No! You cannot.
This is the only power source
capable of sustaining it.
If you move it, the core will decay
in a matter of months.
- Five, by my calculations.
- And then it will go off.
For the sake of your children, Dr. Pavel,
indeed, I hope it does.
Hey! Hey!
That was you in front of
the stock exchange, wasn't it?
- When?
When half the city's cops
were trying to pull onto Castle Street...
...and your truck was shutting them out.
- Oh, yeah. You're the cop
- Detective, now.
And as a detective, I'm not
allowed to believe in coincidence.
What were you doing here?
What are you working on?
Commissioner, it's Blake. I got two dead
witnesses and a lot of questions.
Call me when...
Wait a minute.
They've four barrels of Polyisobutylene.
That looks like motor oil
right next to it. Jesus!
They're not making cement,
they're making explosives.
- Patch me into Foley!
- Foley's overseeing the operation.
They're heading into a trap!
We're seeing literally thousands of
police heading into the sewers.
Mr. Mayor, would literally
thousands of police...
It's a training exercise, that's all.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
I've got tickets to watch
our boys thrash Rapid City.
Foley.
It's a trap!
Pull everyone out!
Bane's been pouring concrete
laced with explosives
Where?
There's a ring around the tunnels.
They're gonna blow it
and trap the cops underground!
Pull 'em out! Pull 'em out, now!
That's a lovely lovely  voice.
Let the games begin.
Gotham, take control...
...take control of your city.
- Foley!
- Jesus, Blake!
Every cop in the city's
down in those tunnels!
Not every cop.
Sir, you're okay? I'm a police officer,
I need your car, right now.
Clear the corners, rookie.
Get my coat, son.
This... This is
the instrument of your liberation.
Satellite shows a radiation spike.
Whatever it is... it's nuclear.
Identify yourself to the world.
Dr. Leonid Pavel,
nuclear physicist.
Pavel was confirmed dead.
Plane crash on an Agency pull-out of
Uzbekistan. But... it looks like it's him.
And what... What is this?
It's a fully primed neutron bomb.
With a blast radius of six miles.
And who is capable of
disarming such a device?
Only me.
Only you...
Thank you, good doctor!
Now, the bomb is armed...
...This bomb is mobile and the identity
of the triggerman is a mystery.
For one of you holds the detonator.
Now, we come here
not as conquerors, but as liberators...
...to return control of
this city to the people.
And at the first sign of interference
from the outside world...
...or to those people attempting to flee...
...this anonymous Gothamite...
...this unsung hero
will trigger the bomb.
For now, martial law is in effect.
Return to your homes...
...hold your families close... and wait.
Tomorrow you claim what is rightfully yours.
Pull back the fighters,
start high-level reconnaissance flights.
Get the President on the line.
Tanks and planes cannot
stop us detonating our device.
Send an emissary to discuss terms of...
...access for supplies and communication.
How many of you are there, son?
You don't have enough men to stop...
...12 million people leaving that island.
No, no, we don't. But you do.
Why the hell would I try to help you
keep your hostages?
If one person crosses this bridge
Gotham gets blown to hell.
The people of
our greatest city are resilient.
They have proven this before,
and they will prove this again.
We do not negotiate with terrorists...
...but we do recognize realities.
As the situation develops, one thing
must be understood above all others...
People of Gotham,
we have not abandoned you.
What does that mean?
It means we're on our own.
I have to get in front of a camera.
Oh, sir, they'll kill you the second
you show your face.
Bane says he's
giving Gotham back to the people.
They need to know that I could lead.
Bane's not gonna let that happen.
- Then he'll show his true colors.
- And you'll be dead.
Behind you stands a symbol of oppression.
Blackgate Prison.
Where a thousand men...
...have languished for years,
Under the name of this man...
Harvey Dent.
Who has been held up to you
as the shining example of justice.
We're gonna keep moving you,
till we can get you in front of a camera.
You've been supplied with a false idol...
...to stop you tearing down
this corrupt city.
Let me tell you the truth
about Harvey Dent.
From the words of
Gotham's Police Commissioner...
...James Gordon.
"The Batman didn't murder Harvey Dent,
he saved my boy.
"Then took the blame for
Harvey's appalling crimes...
"... so that I could, to my shame...
"... build a lie around this fallen idol.
"I praised the madman who
tried to murder my own child.
"But I can no longer live with my lie.
"It is time to trust
the people of Gotham with the truth...
"... and it is time for me to resign. "
And do you accept this man's resignation?
And do you accept
the resignation of all of this liars?
of all the corrupt?
These men, locked up
in Blackgate for eight years...
...denied parole under the Dent Act.
Based on a lie.
Gotham needed a hero.
And needs it now more than ever.
You betrayed everything you stood for.
There's a point.
Far out there.
When the structures fail you.
When the rules aren't weapons
anymore, they're shackles...
...letting the bad guy getting ahead.
One day you may
face such a moment of crisis.
And in that moment,
I hope you have a friend like I did.
To plunge their hands into the filth,
so that you can keep yours clean.
Your hands look pretty filthy
to me, Commissioner.
We take Gotham from the corrupt.
The rich.
The oppressors of generations who've
kept you down with the myth of opportunity.
And we give it to you, the people.
Gotham is yours.
None shall interfere.
Do as you please.
But start by storming Blackgate
and freeing the oppressed.
Step forward, those who would serve.
For an army will be raised.
The powerful will be ripped
from their decadent nests...
...and cast into the cold world
that we know and endure.
Courts will be convened.
Spoils will be enjoyed.
Blood will be shed.
The Police will survive...
...as they learn to serve true justice.
This great city...
...it will endure.
Gotham will survive.
He says you must first fix your back.
How does he know?
He was the prison doctor.
A morphine addict...
...who incurred
displeasure of powerful people.
Including your masked friend.
How?
Many years ago, it was a time of plague.
Some of the other prisoners attacked Bane.
The doctor's fumbling
attempts to repair the damage...
...left him in perpetual agony.
The mask holds the pain at bay.
Bane was child you spoke of?
Was he born here?
The legend is that there was a mercenary
who worked for the local warlord.
He fell in love with warlord's daughter.
They were married in secret.
When the warlord found out...
...the mercenary was condemned to this pit.
But then he exiled him instead.
The mercenary understood that was
the daughter who had secured his release...
But what he could not know was
the true price of his freedom.
She took his place in the pit.
And she was with a child.
The mercenary's child.
Innocence cannot flower underground.
It was to be stamped out.
One day,
the doctor forgot the lock the cell.
But the child had a friend.
A protector...
...who showed the other that this innocence
was their redemption...
...it was to be priced.
The mother was not so lucky.
This is Bane's prison now.
He wouldn't want the story told.
Oh, God!
There's a vertebra
protruding from your back.
- It has to be put back.
- How...?
Stay like this. Until you stand.
Did you not think I'd return, Bruce?
I told you I was immortal.
I watched... I watched you die.
Oh. There are many forms of
immortality.
Once I had a wife. My great love.
She was taken from me.
You were the mercenary.
Bane is your child.
Your heir.
An heir to ensure the League of Shadows...
...fulfills its duty
to restore balance to civilization.
You yourself fought
the decadence of Gotham for years.
With all your strength,
all your resources...
...all your moral authority.
And the only victory
you could achieve was a lie.
Now you understand...
Gotham is beyond saving...
- No!
- And must be allowed to die.
No, No!
- What's that?
- This was someone's home.
Now it's everyone's home.
There's a storm coming, remember?
This is what you wanted.
It's for the bus, in case
there's a chance to evacuate.
- Any news? Is the Commissioner...?
- The less you know, Father.
How're the boys doing?
Well, we've had more power on,
so they got some TV.
- It's good to see you.
- Blake, you be careful out there.
They're hunting down cops like dogs.
- Why build yourself?
- I'm not meant to die in here.
Here? There?
What's the difference?
Deshi Deshi Basara Basara!
I told you it could not be done.
You told me a child did it.
But no ordinary child.
A child born in hell.
Forged from suffering...
...hardened by pain.
Not a man from privilege.
We got Blues in the ground, sir.
Just waiting on intel.
- You have ID?
- Of course not.
- How can we trust you?
- We don't have any choice.
Commissioner Gordon?
Captain Jones, Special Forces.
- Captain, glad to have you here.
- It's our job, sir.
Now, how many of you are there?
Well, dozens.
I'd rather not say exactly.
But the men trapped underground
number almost 3000.
- What kind of condition they're in?
- They've been getting food and water.
- Could we break them out?
- Yes, sir.
Take out the mercenaries guarding
the outflow south of Ackerman Park...
...blow the rubble, you've got
a hole big enough for ten at a time.
I'm in contact with my partners down there.
They're waiting for the day.
Men who haven't seen daylight
for three months?
Police officers who haven't seen daylight
What about the bomb?
The satellite can't pick up
any radiation hot spots.
They keep it on a truck.
It must have a lead-lined roof.
- They move it constantly.
- Good, so you know the truck?
Well, it's one of the three.
We've been tracking it.
Decoy.
You don't really think
he's coming back, do you?
Doesn't matter what I think.
Actually, it does. You should put
your faith in something a little more real.
The routes don't vary much.
- What about the triggerman?
- No leads. It's a bluff.
Bane wouldn't give control of
that bomb to someone else.
We can't take that chance.
Until we have the triggerman,
we just track the device.
And meanwhile,
Gotham lives under a warlord.
Like some failed state?
Dial it back, officer.
This situation is unprecedented.
We can't do anything
to risk millions of lives.
Aren't you gonna tell him? Aren't you
gonna tell him what's really going on?
Captain, the situation is
more complicated than you think.
There's somebody you need to meet.
I came upstairs looking for a vantage point.
Found the people who run the
corporation are living up here.
What corporation?
Wayne Enterprises.
Mr. Fox, Would you
like to brief the Captain?
Miss Tate is fully aware of the situation.
And as CEO of Wayne Enterprises,
I have to take responsibility for it.
- Why?
- We built it.
You built the bomb?
It was built as a fusion reactor.
The first of its kind.
Bane turned the core into a bomb,
then removed it from the reactor.
Now here's the important part.
As the device's fuel cells deteriorate...
...it's becoming increasingly unstable,
until the point of detonation.
- This bomb's a time bomb.
- And it will go off. In 23 days.
Regardless of the Bane's
revolution or what we...
...or the outside
world choose to do.
So, your peace-man plan might not be
as practical as you thought.
Could you disarm it?
I could reconnect it to the reactor.
Stabilize it.
Let's move away from this location,
and call it in.
Alright, let's go!
No, Let me take it from here.
You stay and look after these folks.
Somebody sold us out!
I'll die before I talk.
I'm on your schedule, Captain.
- There were people living upstairs.
- Round them up for judgment.
And hang them where
the world can see.
He says the leap to freedom
is not about strength.
- My body makes the jump.
- Survival is the spirit. The soul.
My soul's as ready to escape as my body.
Fear is why you fail
No, I'm not afraid.
I'm angry.
Bruce...
Why do we fall?
You do not fear death. You think this
makes you strong. It makes you weak.
Why?
How can you move faster than possible?
Fight longer than possible?
Without the most
powerful impulse of the spirit.
The fear of death.
I do fear death.
I fear dying in here,
while my city burns...
...with no one there to save it.
Then make the climb.
How?
As the child did.
Without the rope.
Then fear will find you again.
Ah, Supplies for your journey?
It's wonderful.
- What does that mean?
- Rise.
No.
There's been a mistake!
Take me to Bane!
Where's Bane?
There's been no mistake, Mr. Stryver.
You are Philip Stryver.
Executive vice-president of
Daggett Industries?
Who for years
has been living off the blood...
...and sweat of people
less powerful than him?
Call Bane!
I'm one of you!
Bane has no authority here.
This is merely a sentencing hearing.
Now the choice is yours, exile or death.
- Exile
- Sold...
...to the man in the cold sweat!
You follow the tick ice.
You try to swim... you're dead in minutes.
Has anyone made it?
Where the hell are they?
It's not like we have a lot of time, here.
- How long?
- The bomb goes off tomorrow.
And we've got 18 hours to do something.
To do what?
To mark that truck.
Get a GPS on it...
...so we can start to
figure out how to bring it down.
That's it?
Foley.
Where's Foley, dammit?!
You shouldn't be out on the streets.
Jim. He's not here.
You let your wife come to the door
when the city's under occupation?
Wait in the kitchen, honey.
What did you do,
bury your uniform in the backyard?
Jim, you saw what they did
to those Special Forces.
Have you forgotten all the years
we were out on patrol...
...when every gangbanger wanting to
plant one as soon as our backs were turned?
That was different and you know it.
These guys are running the city.
The government's done a deal with them.
Bane's got their balls in a vice.
That's not a deal.
You move on Bane,
the triggerman's gonna hit the button.
You think he's given control of
that bomb to one of the people?
You think this is part of some revolution?
There's one man with
his finger on the button, that's Bane.
Look, we've all gotta keep our heads down
till they can fix this.
If you still had family here...
This only gets fixed from inside the city.
Look, Peter, I'm not asking you to
walk down Grand in your dress blues.
But, something has to be done.
- I'm sorry Jim. I gotta...
- Keep your head down?
What's that gonna do tomorrow,
when that thing blows?
You don't know that's gonna happen.
I hear you're looking for men, Commissioner.
How about me, instead?
- Miss take, I can't ask you to do that.
- Please.
- What did you take?
- I... Nothing.
I didn't take anything.
You steal from us, you little bastard?
Now, you boys know you can't
come into my neighborhood...
...without asking politely
Never steal anything
from someone you can't outrun, kid.
Pretty generous, for a thief.
- I thought they'd killed you.
- Not yet.
- If you're expecting an apology...
- It wouldn't suit you.
I need your help.
- And why would I help you?
- For this. The "Clean Slate".
You trust me with that?
After what I did to you?
I admit I was a little let down.
But I still think there's more to you.
In fact, I think that for you,
this isn't just a tool...
...It's an escape route.
You want to disappear. Start fresh.
I can't even get off this island.
I can give you a way off.
Once you get me to Lucius Fox.
I need you to find out where
they're holding him. Then take me in.
- Why do you need Fox?
- To save this city.
Who says it needs saving?
Maybe I like it this way.
Maybe you do.
But tomorrow that bomb's going off.
Get your powerful friend on the case?
I'm trying. But I need Fox.
As it approaches, flick the switch.
The needle hits 200,
you give me the signal...
...I'll mark the truck. Okay?
Heads up! Heads up!
- I got it.
- Mercenaries at your 6.
Stand still! Keep your hands
where we can see them!
Commissioner Gordon, you're under arrest.
On whose authority?
People of Gotham.
No lawyer, no witnesses.
What sort of due process is this?
Your guilt has been determined,
this is merely a sentencing hearing.
Now what would it be?
Death or exile?
Crane, if you think we are
going out onto that ice willingly...
...you've another think coming.
- Death, then?
- Looks that way.
Very well... Death...
...by exile.
Bring her to me.
Hey. Going down. Get things ready.
Let's gear on.
Find this one a spot,
he's got a big day tomorrow.
We all do. It's not every day
you bag Bruce Wayne.
- Bruce?
- You okay?
You picked a hell of a time
to go on vacation, Mr. Wayne.
How long until the core ignites?
That bomb goes off in 12 hours.
Unless we can connect it to the reactor.
- Can you get Miranda out of here?
- Not tonight. I'm sorry.
- Do what's necessary.
- Tonight I need you.
- What for?
- To get me back in the game.
Sorry to spoil things, boys,
but Bane wants these guys to himself.
- I won't forget about you, Miranda!
- I know.
- I like your girlfriend, Mr. Wayne.
- He should be so lucky.
Any move I make against Bane or the bomb,
the triggerman sets it off.
But, they won't use radio or cell,
too much interference.
Infrared doesn't have the range.
It'll have to be a micro-burst, long wave.
- Could you block it?
- Yes.
I need the EMP cannon-guidance
mount from the Bat.
Remember where you parked?
- She fly okay?
- Yeah.
Even without the autopilot, thanks.
Autopilot?
That's what you're there for.
Thing's clear. Come on, quick! Climb.
Lock it up!
Who are you?
Light it up.
Mom! Check it out!
Honey, take a look!
Impossible.
Keep her close!
He'll come for her.
- Where's Miranda Tate?
- Bane took her.
He's hold up in city hall,
surrounded by his army.
This blocks the remote detonator
signal to the bomb.
Get into onto it before by sunrise.
They might hit the button when it starts.
- When what starts?
- War.
You missed a spot.
If you're working alone,
wear a mask.
I'm not afraid of being seen
standing up to these guys.
The mask is not for you.
It's to protect the people you care about.
Count to 5 and throw.
Hey, no offense, but you got
something bigger in that belt?
- What now?
- All-out assault on Bane
But you need to get the people
across the bridge.
Why?
In case we fail. Lead an exodus.
Save as many lives as you can.
- You don't need me here?
- You've given me an army. Now go.
- Alright, thanks!
- Don't thank me yet.
Well, I might not get a chance later.
You shouldn't have.
The mid-town tunnel's blocked by debris,
But the cannons have enough firepower
to make a path for people.
Wait until the fighting begins!
You're gonna wage your war
to save your stuck up girlfriend?
To start it, throttle...
I got it.
We've 45 minutes to save this city.
No, I've got forty-five minutes to
get clear of the blast radius...
...because you don't
stand a chance against these guys.
With your help I might.
I'll open that tunnel,
then I'm gone.
There's more to you than that.
Sorry to keep letting you down.
Come with me. Save yourself.
You don't owe these people anymore.
You've given them everything.
Not everything. Not yet.
Disperse. Disperse or be fired upon.
There's only one police in this town...
Open fire.
- Here it comes.
- Get ready!
So you came back
to die with your city.
No. I came back to stop you.
Now!
That's impossible!
Cut over to Fifth!
Get on the bus, go ahead.
You come with me! You too!
Hey you, you and you, come here! Come here!
Everyone else get on the bus, okay?
You guys, you go Knock on doors,
spread the word, okay?
The bomb's going to blow! Get out
by the South Street tunnel...
...or over the bridge!
You go, you do two blocks, then
get back to the bus! Alright? go, go, go!
- Is he back?
- Keep your eyes open. Go!
Cover the doors!
Where's your trigger? Where is it?
You'd never give it to an ordinary citizen.
Where is it?
Where's the trigger?
Where is it? Where is it?
Tell me where the trigger is...
...then, you have my permission to die.
I broke you.
How have you come back?
You think you were the only one
who could learn the strength to escape?
- Where's the trigger?
- But I never escaped.
But the child...
...The child of Ra's Al Ghul made the climb.
But he is not the child of Ra's Al Ghul.
I am.
And though I am not ordinary,
I am a citizen.
Miranda?
Why?
Thalia. My mother named me
Talia before she was killed.
The way I would've been killed
if not for my protector... Bane.
Goodbye.
I climbed out of the pit.
I found my father...
...and brought him
back to exact terrible vengeance...
...but by that time...
...the prisoners and the doctor
had done their work to my friend...
...my protector.
The League took us in. Trained us.
But my father could not accept Bane.
He saw only a monster
Whose very existence...
...was a reminder of the hell
he'd left his wife to die in.
He excommunicated Bane
from the League of Shadows.
His only crime was that he loved me.
I could not truly forgive my father.
Until you murdered him.
He was trying to
kill millions of innocent people.
"Innocent" is a strong word to
throw around Gotham, Bruce.
I honor my father by finishing his work.
Vengeance against the man who killed him...
...is simply a reward for my patience.
You see...
...it's the slow knife...
the knife that takes its time...
The knife that waits
years without forgetting...
...then slips quietly between bones...
...that's the knife that cuts deepest.
Please!
Maybe your knife was too slow.
The truck's under attack.
Gordon. You gave him
a way to block my signal.
No matter.
He's bought Gotham 11 minutes.
Come on!
Stay there! What are you doing?
Blake, MCU,
I'm getting these boys to safety.
You're gonna get us both all killed.
Anyone crosses this bridge
they'll blow the city.
It's gonna blow anyway.
We need to open this bridge now.
Detective, if you take one step forward,
we will shoot you.
If you take two steps forward,
we will blow the bridge.
Go back by the bus and wait for me, alright?
Just go back and wait.
Prepare a convoy.
We must secure the bomb
until it detonates.
Don't kill him.
I want him to feel the heat.
Feel the fire of
12 million souls
you failed.
Goodbye, my friend.
Keep moving forward!
Block them in the stairs!
Shoot them!
Shoot them all!
We both know that I have to kill you now.
You'll just have to imagine the fire.
About the whole no-guns thing?
I don't feel as strongly about it as you do.
Pull up!
Stay level.
We have to force that convoy east,
to the entrance to the reactor.
I need you on the ground,
I'll be in the air. Go!
The situation's changed!
Your orders are out of date!
I'm a cop like you.
And I'm walking out there.
Please do not shoot me.
Shoot at his feet.
Nothing like a little air superiority.
Detective, please stop!
Please, detective! Stop!
Stop walking! Blow it! Do it!
You have to get that bomb here
and you got ten minutes.
They're pushing us
to the entrance of the reactor.
They're gonna try to
reconnect the core.
You idiots!
You sons of bitches! You're killing us!
Just follow your orders!
Alright boys get in circle,
bow your heads.
Not much longer.
Let's get everyone back in the bus.
Okay?
Go! Go! Back in the bus.
There's nowhere to go!
On the bus!
You got to the truck east!
Stay straight!
Give me a hand!
We can get a cable on it!
Fox showed me how to
operate the reactor core.
Oh, dear.
Including the emergency flood.
There is no way this bomb will be stopped.
What're you doing?
Protection from the blast!
We're gonna be alright!
Double time! Go!
It's an atom bomb!
You think they need to
hear that right now?
You want to let them
die without hope? Come on!
Prepare yourselves.
My father's work is done.
- What're you doing?
- I can fly it out over the bay.
- Set it to fly head over the water then eject?
- No autopilot.
You could've gone anywhere.
Been anything. But you came back here.
- So did you.
- I guess we're both suckers.
- I never cared who you were
- And you were right.
But shouldn't the people know
the hero who saved them?
A hero can be anyone.
Even a man doing something as simple...
...and reassuring as putting a coat
around a little boy's shoulders...
...to let him know the
world hadn't ended.
Bruce Wayne?
Vlad, they go! You too!
Come on, father.
Hey, heads down! This is it!
No. No. That's Batman!
That's detonation!
It's out over the bays,
clear of the city.
"I see a beautiful city...
"... and a brilliant people
rising from this abyss...
"I see the lives for which
I lay down my life...
"... peaceful, useful,
prosperous and happy...
"I see that I hold a sanctuary in
their hearts...
"... and in the hearts of
their descendants...
"... generations hence.
"It is a far, far better thing that I do...
"... than I have ever done...
"It is a far,
far better rest that I go to...
"... than I have ever known. "
I'm so sorry.
I failed you.
You trusted me...
...and I failed you.
Can I change your mind...
...about quitting the force?
You know what you said about
structures becoming shackles.
You were right and I can't take it.
The injustice.
I mean... no one's ever gonna know
who saved an entire city.
They know.
It was the Batman.
Mr. Wayne's will was not amended to
reflect his more modest estate.
Nonetheless, there are
considerable assets to dispose of.
The contents of the house are to be
sold to settle the estate's accounts...
...and the remainder is left in its
entirety to Alfred J. Pennyworth.
The house and grounds are left to
the city of Gotham, on condition...
...that they never be demolished,
altered, or otherwise interfered with.
...and that they shall be used for one
purpose, and one purpose only...
The housing and care of the city's
at-risk and orphaned children.
My clerk will help anyone with...
...the smaller
correspondences and instructions.
- Blake, John?
- Nothing here.
Alright, eh...
Try my legal name.
You should use your full name.
I like that name... Robin.
Thanks!
Why are we even worrying
about the stabilization software?
This entire autopilot system
is completely obsolete.
Please, I just need to know
what I could've done to fix it.
But Mr. Fox, it's already been fixed.
Software patch... Six months ago.
Check The ID on the patch.
Bruce Wayne.
- Any news in the missing item?
- Not yet.
Well, they'd better leave
no stone unturned...
We can't leave a string of pearls
on the manifest as "lost".
The End
subtitle by
Amir & Hossein
The Dark Knight Rises
[Eng]