Where have aII the men gone?
They're aII dead from vendettas.
There are the names of the dead.
Hey, hey, take me to the America, G.I. !
CIark GabIe!
America! Take me to the America, G.I. !
CIark GabIe, Rita Hayworth!
Mamma mia what a beauty.
I think you got hit
by the thunderboIt.
In SiciIy women are more
dangerous than shotguns.
Did you have a good hunt?
You know aII the girIs
around here?
We saw some reaI beauties.
One of them struck our friend
Iike a thunderboIt.
She wouId tempt the deviI himseIf.
ReaIIy put together.
Such hair, such mouth!
The girIs around here are
beautifuI...but virtuous.
This one had a purpIe dress...
And a purpIe ribbon in her hair.
A type more Greek than ItaIian.
Do you know her?
There's no girI Iike that
in this town.
My God, I understand!
What's wrong?
Let's go.
It's his daughter.
TeII him to come here.
CaII him.
Fabrizio, you transIate.
I apoIogise if I offended you.
I'm a stranger in this country.
I meant no disrespect
to you or your daughter.
I'm an American, hiding in SiciIy.
My name is MichaeI CorIeone.
There are peopIe who'd pay a Iot
of money for that information.
But then your daughter
wouId Iose a father...
...instead of gaining a husband.
I want to meet your daughter.
With your permission, and under
the supervision of your famiIy.
With aII respect.
Come to my house Sunday morning.
My name is ViteIIi.
What's her name?
I'II knock you dizzy.
Save it for the Iibrary.
We've got to pick up my sister.
What's the matter?
- It was my fauIt!
- Where is he?
It was my fauIt. I hit him.
I started a fight with him.
I hit him, so he hit me...
I'm just going to get a doctor
to take a Iook at you.
Sonny, pIease don't do anything.
What's the matter with you?
What am I going to do?
Make that baby an orphan
before he's born?
You spic sIobs stiII betting Yankees?
TeII them to stop taking in action.
We Iost enough money Iast week.
Come here, come here!
If you touch my sister again, I'II kiII you.
Hey! We weren't expecting you, Kay.
You shouId caII.
Yes, I have. I've tried writing and caIIing.
- I want to reach MichaeI.
- Nobody knows where he is.
AII we know is that he's aII right.
- What was that?
- An accident, but nobody was hurt.
Tom, wiII you give this Ietter to MichaeI.
PIease?
If I accepted that, a court couId prove
I have knowIedge of his whereabouts.
He'II get in touch with you.
I Iet my cab go, so can I caII
another one, pIease?
Come on. Sorry.
- HeIIo?
- ls Carlo there?
- Who is this?
- A friend of Carlo.
Tell him that l can't make it tonight
until later.
Bitch!
- Dinner's on the tabIe.
- I'm not hungry.
- The food is getting coId.
- I'II eat out Iater.
You just toId me to make you dinner!
She has a fiIthy mouth, this Guinea brat.
That's it, break it aII, you spoiIed
Guinea brat. Break it aII!
Why don't you bring your whore
home for dinner?
Maybe I wiII.
- CIean it up!
- Like heII I wiII!
You skinny, spoiIed brat.
CIean it up! CIean it up!
CIean it up! I said, cIean it up!
CIean it up!
CIean it up. CIean that up, you...
CIean it!
CIean it up! Yeah, kiII me.
Be a murderer, Iike your father!
- AII you CorIeones are murderers!
- I hate you!
Come on, kiII me!
Get out of here!
- I hate you!
- Now I'II kiII you.
You Guinea brat. Get out of here!
Connie, what's the matter?
I can't hear you.
Connie, taIk Iouder. The baby's crying.
Santino, I can't understand.
I don't know.
Yeah, Connie.
You wait there.
No, you just wait there.
Son-of-a-bitch.
- Son-of-a-bitch!
- What's the matter?
Open the goddamn gate!
Get off your ass.
Sonny!
- Sonny.
- Get out of here!
Go after him, go on!
Son-of-a-bitch. Come on!
Give me a drop.
My wife is crying upstairs.
I hear cars coming to the house.
Consigliere of mine,
teII your Don what everyone
seems to know.
I didn't teII Mama anything.
I was about to come up and wake you
and teII you.
But you needed a drink first.
Yeah.
WeII, now you've had your drink.
They shot Sonny on the causeway.
He's dead.
I want no inquiries made.
I want no acts of vengeance.
I want you to arrange a meeting...
...with the heads of the five famiIies.
This war stops now.
CaII Bonasera.
I need him now.
This is Tom Hagen. I'm caIIing for
Vito CorIeone, at his request.
You owe your Don a service.
He has no doubt that you will repay it.
He will be at your funeral parlour
in one hour. Be there to greet him.
WeII, my friend, are you ready
to do me this service?
Yes. What do you want me to do?
I want you to use aII your powers
and aII your skiIIs.
I don't want his mother
to see him this way.
Look how they massacred my boy.
It's safer to teach you EngIish!
I know EngIish...
Monday, Tuesday, Thursday,
Wednesday, Friday, Sunday, Saturday.
Greetings, Don Tommasino.
How are things in PaIermo?
MichaeI is teaching me to
drive...watch, I'II show you.
How are things in PaIermo?
Young peopIe don't respect
anything any more...
times are changing for the worse.
This pIace has become
too dangerous for you.
I want you to move to a viIIa
near Siracusa...right now.
What's wrong?
Bad news from America.
Your brother, Santino,
they kiIIed him.
Let's go...you promised.
Get the car.
Are you driving yourseIf, Boss?
Is your wife coming with you?
No, take her to her father's house
untiI things are safe.
Okay, anything you say.
CaIo, where is ApoIIonia?
She's going to surprise you.
She wants to drive.
She'II make a good American wife.
Wait, I'II get the baggage.
Fabrizio!
Where are you going?
Wait there! I'II drive to you.
No, ApoIIonia!
Don Barzini, I want to thank you
for heIping me organise this meeting,
and the other heads of the five famiIies
from New York and New Jersey.
Carmine Cuneo from the Bronx,
and from BrookIyn...
...PhiIip TattagIia.
And from Staten IsIand
we have with us Victor Strachi.
And the other associates that came as
far as from CaIifornia and Kansas City
and aII the other territories
of the country. Thank you.
How did things ever get so far?
I don't know.
It was so unfortunate, so unnecessary.
TattagIia Iost a son, and I Iost a son.
We're quits. And if TattagIia agrees,
then I'm wiIIing to Iet things go on
as before.
We're gratefuI to Don CorIeone
for caIIing this meeting.
We aII know him as a man of his word.
A modest man who Iistens to reason.
Yes, Don Barzini. He's too modest.
He had aII the judges and poIiticians
in his pocket.
He refused to share them.
When did I ever refuse
an accommodation?
AII of you know me.
When did I ever refuse,
except one time? And why?
Because I beIieve this drug business
wiII destroy us in the years to come.
It's not Iike gambIing or Iiquor
or even women,
which is something that most peopIe
want, but is forbidden by the Church.
Even the poIice that have heIped us in
the past with gambIing and other things
are going to refuse to heIp us
when it comes to narcotics.
I beIieved that then...
and I beIieve that now.
Times have changed.
It's not Iike the oId days,
when we couId do anything we wanted.
A refusaI is not the act of a friend.
If Don CorIeone had aII the judges and
poIiticians, then he must share them
or Iet others use them. He must Iet us
draw the water from the weII.
CertainIy he can present a biII
for such services.
After aII, we're not communists.
I aIso don't beIieve in drugs.
For years I paid my peopIe extra, so
they wouIdn't do that kind of business.
Somebody says to them
"I have powders."
"If you put up 3-4,000 doIIar investment,
we can make 50,000 distributing."
They can't resist. I want to controI it
as a business, keep it respectabIe.
I don't want it near schooIs,
I don't want it soId to chiIdren.
That's an infàmia.
In my city we wouId keep the traffic
to the coIoured.
They're animaIs,
so Iet them Iose their souIs.
I hoped that we couId come here
and reason together.
And I'm wiIIing to do whatever is
necessary to find a peacefuI soIution.
We are agreed. The traffic in drugs
wiII be permitted, but controIIed.
Don CorIeone wiII give us protection
in the east, and there wiII be peace.
I must have strict assurance
from CorIeone.
As time goes by and his position
becomes stronger,
wiII he attempt any individuaI vendetta?
We are aII reasonabIe men.
We don't have to give assurances.
You taIk about vengeance.
WiII vengeance bring your son
back to you?
Or my boy to me?
I forgo the vengeance of my son.
But I have seIfish reasons.
My youngest son was forced
to Ieave this country...
...because of this SoIIozzo business.
And I have to make arrangements
to bring him back here safeIy.
CIeared of aII these faIse charges.
But I'm a superstitious man.
If an unIucky accident shouId befaII him,
if he shouId be shot by a poIice officer,
or if he shouId hang himseIf
in his jaiI ceII,
or if he's struck by a boIt of Iightning,
then I'm going to bIame
some of the peopIe in this room.
And that I do not forgive.
But, that aside...
...Iet me say that I swear...
...on the souIs of my grandchiIdren,
that I wiII not be the one to break
the peace we've made here today.
ShouId I insist that aII of TattagIia's
drug middIemen have cIean records?
Mention it. Don't insist.
- Barzini wiII know without being toId.
- You mean TattagIia.
TattagIia's a pimp. He couId never
have outfought Santino.
But I didn't know untiI this day
that it was Barzini aII aIong.
Come on, Nancy.
Keep together, everyone. Brian.
Okay, aII right.
How Iong have you been back?
I've been back a year.
Longer than that, I think.
It's good to see you, Kay.
I'm working for my father now, Kay.
He's been sick. Very sick.
But you're not Iike him. You toId me you
weren't going to become Iike your father.
My father is no different
than any other powerfuI man.
Any man who's responsibIe
for other peopIe.
Like a senator or president.
- How naive you sound.
- Why?
They don't have men kiIIed.
Who's being naive, Kay?
My father's way of doing things is over.
Even he knows that.
In five years the CorIeone famiIy
is going to be compIeteIy Iegitimate.
Trust me. That's aII I can teII you
about my business. Kay...
MichaeI, why did you come here? Why?
What do you want with me after aII
this time? I've been caIIing and writing.
I came because I need you.
I care for you.
- PIease stop it, MichaeI.
- Because... I want you to marry me.
- It's too Iate.
- PIease, Kay...
I'II do anything you ask to make up for
what's happened to us.
Because that's important, Kay.
Because what's important is that...
...we have each other.
That we have a Iife together.
That we have chiIdren. Our chiIdren.
Kay, I need you.
And I Iove you.
Barzini's peopIe chiseI my territory
and we do nothing about it!
- Soon I'II have no pIace to hang my hat!
- Be patient.
I'm not asking for heIp.
Just take off the handcuffs.
- Be patient.
- We must protect ourseIves.
- Let me recruit some new men.
- No.
- Barzini wouId get an excuse to fight.
- Mike, you're wrong.
Don CorIeone...
You once said that one day Tessio
and me couId form our own famiIy.
TiII today I wouId never think of it.
I must ask your permission.
MichaeI is now head of the famiIy.
If he gives his permission,
then you have my bIessing.
After we make the move to Nevada
you can Ieave the CorIeone famiIy
and go on your own.
- How Iong wiII that be?
- Six months.
Forgive me, but with you gone, me and
Pete wiII come under Barzini's thumb.
I hate that Barzini. In six months' time
there wiII be nothing Ieft to buiId on.
- Do you have faith in my judgement?
- Yes.
- Do I have your IoyaIty?
- AIways, Godfather.
Then be a friend to MichaeI.
Do as he says.
Things are negotiated that'II soIve your
probIems and answer your questions.
That's aII I can teII you now.
CarIo, you grew up in Nevada.
When we make our move there,
you'II be my right-hand man.
Tom Hagen is no Ionger consigliere.
He'II be our Iawyer in Vegas.
That's no refIection on Tom,
just how I want it.
If I ever need heIp, who's a better
consigliere than my father? That's it.
- Thank you, Poppa.
- I'm happy for you, CarIo.
Mike... Why am I out?
You're not a wartime consigliere, Tom.
Things may get rough with the move.
Tom.
I advised MichaeI. I never thought
you were a bad consigliere.
I thought Santino was a bad Don,
rest in peace.
MichaeI has aII my confidence,
just as you do.
But there are reasons why you must
have no part in what is going to happen.
- Maybe I couId heIp.
- You're out, Tom.
I can't get over the way your face Iooks.
So good!
This doctor did some job. Did Kay
taIk you into it? Hey, hey, hey!
Leave them out here.
He's tired and wants to cIean up.
Let me open the door, aII right?
- HeIIo, Mike! WeIcome to Las Vegas!
- AII for you, kid! It's aII his idea.
- Your brother Freddy.
- GirIs?
I'II be right back. Keep them occupied.
- Anything you want, kid, anything.
- Who are the girIs?
- That's for you to find out.
- Get rid of them, Fredo.
- Hey, Mike...
- I'm here on business. Get rid of them.
I'm tired. Get rid of the band too.
Hey, take off. Take off. Let's go.
Hey, that's it. Hey, AngeIo.
Hey, come on! Scram!
Come on, honey. I don't know
what's the matter with him, Johnny.
Sorry.
I don't know. He's tired.
What happened to Moe Greene?
He had some business. He said to
give him a caII when the party started.
WeII, give him a caII.
- Johnny, how are you?
- Nice to see you, Mike.
- We're proud of you.
- Thanks.
Sit down, I want to taIk to you.
The Don is proud too.
WeII, I owe it aII to him.
He knows how gratefuI you are. That's
why he'd Iike to ask a favour of you.
Mike, what can I do?
We're thinking of giving up our interests
in the oIive oiI business and settIe here.
Moe wiII seII us his share of the casino
and the hoteI, so we'II own aII of it. Tom!
Are you sure? Moe Ioves the business.
He never said nothing about seIIing.
I'II make him an offer he can't refuse.
See, Johnny...
We figure that entertainment
wouId draw gambIers to the casino.
We hope you'II sign a contract
to appear five times a year.
Perhaps convince some of your friends
in the movies to do the same.
We're counting on you.
Sure, Mike. I'II do anything
for my godfather.
Good.
Hey, Mike! HeIIo, feIIows.
Everybody's here. Freddy, Tom.
- Good to see you.
- How are you, Moe?
Have everything? SpeciaIIy prepared
food, the best dancers, and good credit.
Draw chips for everybody,
so they can pIay on the house.
Is my credit good enough
to buy you out?
Buy me out?
The casino, the hoteI. The
CorIeone famiIy wants to buy you out.
The CorIeone famiIy wants to
buy me out? No, I buy you out.
Your casino Ioses money.
We can do better.
- You think I'm skimming off the top?
- You're unIucky.
You Guineas make me Iaugh.
I took Freddy in when you had a bad
time, and now you try to push me out!
You did that because we bankroIIed
your casino
and the MoIinari famiIy guaranteed
his safety. Let's taIk business.
Yes. First of aII, you're aII done. You
don't have that kind of muscIe anymore.
The Godfather is sick. You're getting
chased out of New York by the others.
Do you think you can come to my hoteI
and take over?
I taIked to Barzini. I can make a deaI
with him and stiII keep my hoteI!
Is that why you sIapped my brother
around in pubIic?
That was nothing, Mike.
Moe didn't mean nothing by that.
He fIies off the handIe sometimes,
but we're good friends.
I have a business to run.
I've got to kick asses sometimes.
We had an argument,
so I had to straighten him out.
You straightened my brother out?
He was banging cocktaiI waitresses!
PIayers couIdn't get a drink.
What's wrong with you?
I Ieave for New York tomorrow.
Think about a price.
Son-of-a-bitch!
I'm Moe Greene! I made my bones
when you were out with cheerIeaders.
Wait a minute, Moe. I have an idea.
Tom, you're the consigliere.
TaIk to the Don...
Just a minute. Don is semi-retired and
Mike is in charge of the famiIy business.
If you have anything to say,
say it to MichaeI.
Mike, you don't come to Las Vegas and
taIk to a man Iike Moe Greene Iike that!
Fredo...
You're my oIder brother, and I Iove you.
But don't ever take sides with anyone
against the famiIy again.
I have to see my father and his peopIe,
so have dinner without me.
This weekend we'II go out. We'II go to
the city, see a show and have dinner.
Your sister wants to ask you something.
- Let her ask.
- She's afraid to.
They want you to be godfather
to their boy.
- We'II see.
- WiII you?
Let me think about it. Come on.
Barzini wiII move against you first.
He'II set up a meeting with someone
you absoIuteIy trust.
Guaranteeing your safety.
And at that meeting
you'II be assassinated.
I Iike to drink wine more than I used to.
- Anyway, I'm drinking more.
- It's good for you, Pop.
I don't know.
Are you happy with your wife
and chiIdren?
- Very happy.
- That's good.
I hope you don't mind the way I keep
going over this Barzini business.
- No, not at aII.
- It's an oId habit.
I spend my Iife trying not to be careIess.
Women and chiIdren can be careIess,
but not men.
- How's your boy?
- He's good.
He Iooks more Iike you every day.
He's smarter than I am. He's three
and can read the funny papers.
Read the funny papers.
I want you to arrange for a teIephone
man to check aII in- and out-going caIIs.
- I did it aIready. I took care of that, Pop.
- That's right. I forgot.
What's the matter?
What's bothering you?
I'II handIe it. I toId you I can handIe it,
so I'II handIe it.
I knew that Santino wouId have to
go through aII this.
And Fredo...
Fredo was, weII...
But I never wanted this for you.
I worked my whoIe Iife. I don't apoIogise
for taking care of my famiIy.
And I refused to be a fooI,
dancing on a string
heId by aII those big shots.
I don't apoIogise. That's my Iife,
but I thought that...
...that when it was your time, you wouId
be the one to hoId the strings.
Senator CorIeone. Governor CorIeone.
Something.
Another pezzo da novanta.
WeII...
Just wasn't enough time, MichaeI.
Wasn't enough time.
We'II get there, Pop. We'II get there.
Now Iisten, whoever comes to you
with this Barzini meeting,
he's the traitor. Don't forget that.
Can I hoId it, pIease?
- Can I water these?
- Yes, go ahead.
Over here, over here.
Be carefuI. You're spiIIing it.
Antony!
Come here, come here.
That's it. We'II put it right there.
I'II show you something. Come here.
Stand there.
Give me an orange!
That's a new trick.
You run in there. Run in there.
Where are you?
Mike, can I have a minute?
Barzini wants to arrange a meeting.
He says we can straighten out
any of our probIems.
- You taIked to him?
- Yeah.
I can arrange security. On my territory.
- AII right?
- AII right.
Do you know how they're going to
come at you?
They're arranging a meeting
in BrookIyn. Tessio's ground.
Where I'II be safe.
I aIways thought it wouId be
CIemenza, not Tessio.
It's the smart move.
Tessio was aIways smarter.
But I'm going to wait.
After the baptism.
I've decided to be godfather
to Connie's baby.
And then I'II meet with Don Barzini
and TattagIia.
AII the heads of the five famiIies.
MichaeI, do you beIieve in God, the
Father, Creator of Heaven and Earth?
I do.
Do you believe in Jesus Christ,
His only Son, our Lord?
l do.
Do you believe in the Holy Ghost,
the Holy Catholic Church?
l do.
MichaeI Francis Rizzi,
do you renounce Satan?
I do renounce him.
And aII his works?
I do renounce them.
Oh, God!
- And aII his pomps?
- I do renounce them.
MichaeI Rizzi, wiII you be baptised?
I wiII.
MichaeI Rizzi, go in peace, and may
the Lord be with you. Amen.
Kay!
Kiss your godfather.
Can't go to Vegas. Something's come
up. Everybody has to Ieave without us.
- Mike, it's our first vacation!
- Connie, pIease.
Go back to the house, wait for my caII.
It's important.
I'II onIy be a coupIe of days.
We're on our way to BrookIyn.
- I hope Mike can get us a good deaI.
- I'm sure he wiII.
SaI, Tom, the boss says he'II come in a
separate car, so you two go on ahead.
- That screws up my arrangements.
- That's what he said.
I can't go either, SaI.
TeII Mike it was onIy business.
I aIways Iiked him.
- He understands that.
- Excuse me, SaI.
Tom, can you get me off the hook?
- For oId times' sake?
- Can't do it, SaIIy.
You have to answer for Santino, CarIo.
- Mike, you got it aII wrong.
- You fingered Sonny for Barzini.
That IittIe farce you pIayed
with my sister.
- You think that couId fooI a CorIeone?
- I'm innocent. I swear on the kids.
- PIease, don't do this.
- Sit down.
Don't do this to me, pIease.
Barzini is dead.
So is PhiIip TattagIia.
Moe Greene.
Strachi. Cuneo.
Today I settIe aII famiIy business,
so don't teII me you're innocent, CarIo.
Admit what you did.
Get him a drink.
Come on.
Don't be afraid, CarIo. Do you think
I'd make my sister a widow?
I'm godfather to your son, CarIo.
Go ahead, drink, drink.
No, you're out of the famiIy business.
That's your punishment.
You're finished.
I'm putting you on a pIane to Vegas.
Tom.
I want you to stay there. Understand?
OnIy don't teII me you're innocent.
Because it insuIts my inteIIigence.
Makes me very angry.
Who approached you?
TattagIia or Barzini?
It was Barzini.
Good.
There's a car waiting outside
to take you to the airport.
I'II caII your wife and teII her
what fIight you're on.
- Mike...
- Get out of my sight.
HeIIo, CarIo.
- I'm trying to teII you...
- Mama, pIease!
MichaeI!
- What is it?
- Where is he?
MichaeI, you Iousy bastard!
You kiIIed my husband.
You waited untiI Papa died,
so nobody couId stop you.
You bIamed him for Sonny.
Everybody did.
But you never thought about me!
Now what are we going to do?
Connie.
Why do you think he kept CarIo at the
MaII? He knew he was going to kiII him.
And you stood godfather to our baby.
You Iousy coId-hearted bastard!
Want to know how many men he had
kiIIed with CarIo? Read the papers!
That's your husband,
that's your husband!
No! No, no...
Take her upstairs. Get her a doctor.
She's hystericaI.
HystericaI.
MichaeI, is it true?
- Don't ask me about my business, Kay.
- Is it true?
Don't ask me about my business.
Enough!
AII right.
This one time.
This one time I'II Iet you ask me
about my affairs.
Is it true?
Is it?
No.
I guess we both need a drink. Come on.
Don CorIeone.
Subtitles by
-=DFN=-