Where are you going?
Help me!
Over here!
Go!
That was a B-29, bub.
There's no outrunning what's coming.
Yashida!
You're better off down here.
I'd hurry if I were you.
Run. Now!
Stay down!
No, wait! No, no. Wait.
No. It's not safe.
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
Wake up.
Where were you?
Nagasaki.
That far back?
You're here.
Of course.
Can you stay?
You know I can't.
Jean, I'm so sorry.
I know.
I'll never hurt you or anyone
ever again.
I made a vow.
A solemn vow?
You're making fun of me.
It's too late.
No! No, Jean!
No, no, no! Please!
You can't hide.
You can't hide!
No, Jean! No!
No.
Whack all of that on store credit.
Thanks, honey.
- Got the arrows?
- Yeah.
Remember the arrows?
Yeah, yeah, Eddie, we got them!
Yeah!
What are you doing?
Man, you almost blew his foot off!
You're not a hunter, are you?
Not anymore.
What the hell?
Don't make me do this.
It must have been
damn near 12 feet tall.
We didn't hear nothing except twigs.
Then it just came upon us.
It got Riley, just gutted him.
It got Eddie.
Ripped through the tent,
knocked over the snowcat like it was a toy.
You the one was attacked by the grizzly?
I'm the one that survived.
I'd like to buy this man a drink.
What's your name, mister?
It's Logan.
And that's a poison broadhead,
which, last I heard, was illegal.
Go ahead, ask me where I found it.
Ask me.
Where did you find it?
Well, funny you should ask.
I pulled it out of
the back of a grizzly.
Whoever shot it, didn't have the wind or
the balls to track the animal properly...
and put it out of its misery.
Instead of dropping
a lethal dose of the poison...
it bled into the bear,
made him crazy, killed five people.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Because I don't dip my arrows
in anything.
In that case,
you got nothing to worry about.
Damn.
That hurt.
Sorry, Jean.
I wouldn't bother with them.
Most of them will die soon anyway,
without your help.
Three of them, a week from now
in the same truck.
This sword is hundreds of years old...
and was named Danzan
by the first samurai who used it.
Danzan means "separator" in Japanese.
The ideal weapon for separating
head and limb from body.
Like so.
I'm parked in back.
Get in.
Sorry, it's a rental.
Who are you?
Me? I'm Yukio.
And?
I've been trying to find you
for over a year.
Why?
To give you that.
My employer wanted you to have it.
Who's your employer?
Master Yashida.
He said it belongs to you,
and that he's paying all debts.
Master Yashida is dying.
He wants to say thank you
for saving his life all those years ago.
He knows that you are a...
busy man.
But he very much wants to
say his goodbye in person.
All right, where is he?
Tokyo.
Wait...
I'm not going to Japan.
It would be dishonorable
for you to refuse his request.
Apologize to Mr. Yashida,
I'm not going to Tokyo.
All right? I've got things to do.
Do not apologize.
It's been an honor
just to meet the Wolverine.
That's not who I am anymore,
you understand?
Interesting.
Why did you go into that bar,
if not to seek justice?
- I don't know.
- You don't know.
- No!
- I think you know.
Pull over.
You are a soldier.
No, I'm not. Pull over.
- You are a soldier.
- Pull over, now!
Now.
You are a soldier,
and you seek what all soldiers do.
And what's that?
An honorable death.
An end to your pain.
Who says I'm in pain?
A man who has nightmares
every night of his life is in pain.
One day.
I say goodbye to Mr. Yashida
and I come right back.
Okay.
Fifteen hours. Depending on the wind.
Fifteen hours?
You don't like to fly?
I love it.
We are almost there.
So, you can see the future?
I can read a map.
You said you knew the future
of those assholes in the bar.
I know they are going to die.
We are all going to die.
You said they would die in the same truck,
in a week.
If you're right, that's quite a talent.
We don't all have claws.
So, do I die on this plane?
No.
Not on this plane.
Master Yashida is not well tonight.
A lot of guns.
There have been attacks.
Attempted kidnappings.
Attempted assassinations.
By who?
The Japanese mob, the Yakuza.
They've grown strong
as the government has grown weak.
Hip replacement.
Hey.
This way.
Who's that?
Shingen, Master Yashida's son.
He's good.
He's all right.
So, what happened
to the badass in boots?
Master Yashida is traditional.
One eye on the past
and the other on the future.
That's Mariko, his granddaughter.
Mariko.
What's wrong with you?
You haven't answered my emails.
I can't tell you now.
Yes, you can.
Who is the caveman?
The man Grandfather wanted me to find.
You can't bring him in like that.
Shizu and Saki
are going to disinfect you.
Give you a shave.
Like hell they are.
Get in the tub.
Whoa.
Really?
All right.
Okay. Okay.
All right, all right, all right.
I can do that bit.
What?
You look nice.
I feel violated.
Prepare two more suppressors
for Master Yashida.
And check his blood pressure.
Yashida-sama.
Kuzuri.
You look the same.
But, then, that is no surprise.
Dr. Green.
Leave us, please.
Five minutes, no more.
My oncologist.
Well done.
The painting is from the village
of my birth.
It depicts the bravery and skill
of the Black Clan.
Ninja warriors.
They served my family
for seven centuries.
I didn't send for you
only to thank you, Logan.
I wanted to repay you.
To offer you something no one else can.
A gift to equal the life you gave to me.
I don't need anything.
Not a thing.
Eternity can be a curse.
It hasn't been easy for you,
living without time.
The losses you have had to suffer.
A man can run out of things to live for.
Lose his purpose.
Become a ronin.
A samurai without a master.
I can end your eternity.
Make you mortal.
What they did to me,
what I am, can't be undone.
Yashida Industries can do anything.
We have reason to believe
your ability to heal can be passed.
Passed?
From you to another.
You have struggled long enough, Logan.
I'm confused.
I came here to say goodbye
to a man I once knew.
I am the same man.
I was not ready to die then.
I am not ready to die now.
But you are...
aren't you?
Are you offering to kill me?
No.
Not right away.
You can live a long and ordinary life.
Fall in love, have a family...
grow old.
And one day, die an ordinary death.
It can be done.
Yeah, look, nice to see you again.
Sorry you got sick.
Please, Logan-san.
I need you again.
I fear for my family.
I fear for everything I have built.
- Enough. You should leave.
- Please, Logan-san.
They're going to kill her.
Who?
Mariko, my granddaughter.
She is my treasure.
She must be protected.
You don't want what I've got.
Kuzuri.
Kuzuri!
He needs a sedative.
Breathe slowly and calm yourself.
Careful, careful.
It's slippery out here.
Let go.
You about done?
Let go of me.
He just wanted to say goodbye, huh?
You two grew up together.
Yes.
But you're not her sister.
No.
Master Yashida found me
on a trip to the South.
He brought Mariko to see a factory
he was building.
I was digging through the garbage
for something to eat.
So they just took you home with them?
It was always difficult for Mariko
to make friends.
I'll see to it
the plane is ready in the morning.
Sleep here.
Eternity can be a curse...
Kuzuri.
You have no pain, Kuzuri?
How old are you?
Interesting offer.
What are you doing
turning the old man down?
I thought you wanted to be with me.
Come here.
He's dead.
I didn't foresee it.
Who's that? With Mariko.
His name is Noburo Mori.
Minister of Justice, a rising star.
He's Mariko's fiancé.
You need to bow.
Bow.
Lord Shingen, this is Mr. Logan.
I know who he is.
Your father was a good man.
He would often say the same about you.
But then, he was always
fascinated with your kind.
Tell me, why do you think
he sent our little Yukio to fetch you?
To say goodbye.
And now you have.
Time for you to go back to your cave.
Anyone else you want me to meet?
I pledge to you...
Master Yashida...
to be vigilant...
and to dedicate my life...
to protect Mariko.
That armor
belonged to Shiruba-Samurai...
the Silver Samurai.
It will stand watch
over the old man forever.
Logan?
Hey. Something's not right.
Let go.
Logan!
Kuzuri.
Let's go. Come on, let's go!
Yukio!
Mariko!
Come on. Let's go, let's go.
Here, here! Here!
Move!
In here!
Keep moving, keep moving.
Move!
You're bleeding. You need help.
Just keep moving.
Thank you for what you did back there.
- Those were Yakuza.
- I'm fine.
Why are they after you?
I'm fine. I can make my way from here.
You should go. Get yourself a doctor.
That's nice.
This is one of those bullet trains, right?
I told you I don't need your help.
So what do they do, like,
300 miles an hour?
This cowardly attack was...
the work of Yakuza thugs.
A violent response to my efforts...
to crack down on organized crime.
They exited the North Gate.
She was with the stranger...
Your gaijin friend, where is he?
Last I saw,
he was protecting your daughter.
You are a toy doll.
A companion for a child
who has outgrown you.
Keep that in mind.
So, where are we headed, Mariko?
Where are we going?
I'm going to the end of the line.
My family has a home in the South.
That's stupid.
No offense, but they're gonna know
to look for you there.
Not this place.
- You want to be left alone.
- Yes.
- I understand.
- Do you?
Oh, yeah. Trust me.
Problem is, if I do that...
I don't think you're gonna live
to see the end of the day.
You can't pretend shit isn't happening
when it is, princess.
Unless you want to die. In that case,
you're playing this perfectly.
What the hell?
What the hell is happening?
What happened to you?
We get off here. Let's go.
Just listen to me, will you?
We need to find someplace safe.
I don't understand.
How do you know they were Yakuza?
They were the same guys from the temple.
How do you know they were after me?
Look, we need to find someplace safe.
We need to get off the streets.
- I don't understand.
- Shut up! Listen.
Do you know this place?
Where's downtown?
Straight ahead.
So, where's the nice part of town?
Another eight blocks that way.
Good. We're staying here.
Let's go.
This is a love hotel.
A what?
A love hotel.
For couples, understand?
Right.
Hey.
Two rooms.
Adjoining rooms, on the same floor.
Right next to each other. Very close.
Same floor. Same floor.
What did she say?
She has no rooms available
next to each other.
She's asking if we prefer
"the dungeon", "the nurse's office... "
or the "mission to Mars. "
This'll do.
Liftoff! We have a liftoff!
Kind of homey, actually.
Where do you plan on sleeping?
I don't.
That's a lot of blood.
I thought you were done being the hero.
But these guys were... trying to kill her.
Just let it go.
It's not hard to die.
Come to me.
This is Mieko from the hotel
and her grandson, Hitoshi.
Is he a doctor?
In a manner of speaking, yes.
He's a veterinarian...
student.
Large animal.
Thanks.
You may have cut him once or twice
while he was stitching you.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey.
Thank you.
I never needed this before.
What? Help?
That doctor, the one who helped
your grandfather, the blonde.
Who is she?
He met her last year
when he was in America for treatment.
Your grandfather told me my healing
could be taken from me, passed on.
I'm not getting better, not like before.
She did this to me.
Blondie!
How much? How much, yeah?
How much?
You kept me waiting two hours.
You have no respect.
So you haven't found them?
Don't play with me, bitch.
I could kill you.
If you could make me feel something,
Harada, that would be sublime.
I can slit your pretty mouth open, before
you open it to say one more stupid...
I asked you to do one thing, little man.
Bring me the mutant.
I don't work for you.
I work for the House of...
You work for Yashida, I get it.
Yet you cannot fulfill his dying wish.
My God, if you had any idea
how much you have failed him.
Where is Logan?
I am not done with him.
The mutant has powers.
He's just a man now.
His flesh is weak now.
I did that.
I suppressed his power so he
could be taken.
You see, it's me you should respect.
Just find them,
before the Yakuza.
We get off here.
Where are we?
Just outside Nagasaki.
This way.
This is the guy from the
funeral, the archer.
He was your boyfriend.
That's Harada.
We were village champions that summer.
He with the bow and me with the knives.
Harada and I were planning to get married.
What stopped you?
Grandfather.
He said we had to wait
until we were at least 15.
From the mountain, from the sea.
Chopsticks upright are a bad omen.
It resembles incense at a funeral.
Nothing is without meaning.
So, the other night at the house,
when you ran out in the rain...
what did that mean?
My grandfather was dying.
You knew he was gonna die.
He'd been sick for a long time.
It wasn't his death I feared.
So, what, then?
What did he tell you that night?
Mariko, why did your father hit you?
I was trying to warn him.
About what?
What did your grandfather tell you?
He told me that...
in three days,
when they read his will...
I will become
the most powerful person in Japan.
He gave it all to me.
The company?
I didn't want it.
He knew that.
I don't understand why he gave it to me.
It was all my father dreamed of.
Well, that's why.
What about this fiancé of yours?
Nostromo.
Noburo.
Does he know about this?
No.
Why are you marrying him?
He seems like kind of an asshole.
My father arranged it last year.
What?
It gives him a better access
to the political theater.
To disobey my father
would be to dishonor him.
I don't expect you to understand.
You're not Japanese.
Our island is long and thin.
Trains only run in two directions.
I assure you Lord Shingen...
my officers are making every effort...
Then they're idiots.
You've wasted enough of my time.
I have my father's affairs to attend to.
Get out and find her!
Tell me you have more promising news
from your contacts.
They open the will in three days.
We are running out of time.
Soon, I hope.
I'm sending men to the South.
That's where we found the bodies.
If the Yakuza got into the funeral...
they had someone inside.
They'll never find me here.
You're not safe.
I'm coming down there.
They'll follow you.
Please.
Wait a few days.
Please. I'm fine.
Logan's here.
He's wounded, Mariko.
Someone's here.
Mariko?
I have to go.
A tree fell on the road.
The men could use some help.
Are you okay?
Tired.
Do you need something?
No.
This will help.
It's time.
What?
Please. Take it.
Thank you.
No.
Two hands.
Japanese sword require two hands.
Like that?
That's it.
It's beautiful, Yashida.
But I can't take it.
Please.
Thank you.
Keep it safe.
Keep it safe for me.
Someday, I'll come get it.
It's time.
I was here when it happened.
It's how I met your grandfather.
We hid in there.
I heard the stories.
My grandfather would say...
what happened here was proof
that everything in the world finds peace.
Eventually.
That man can recover from anything.
Maybe you, too.
You don't sleep very well.
You call out in the night.
Who's Jean?
We should go back. There's rain coming.
This isn't right.
You need this tied
like a proper samurai.
Your grandfather called me a ronin.
A samurai without a master.
He said
I was destined to live forever...
with no reason to live.
Was he right?
Yes.
Still?
Hey.
What are you doing?
This isn't going to end well.
Everyone you love dies.
Kuzuri.
Do you know what that means?
An animal.
A fierce creature
with long claws and sharp teeth.
It fears nothing.
When I was a girl, I had nightmares.
I'd wake up and run to my parents.
My father would get angry.
"Go back to sleep. Face your fears. "
My grandfather was different.
He told me stories about Kuzuri,
his friend.
Who he met at the bottom of a well.
He said the Kuzuri was magical
and saved his life.
He said Kuzuri would protect me, too,
as I slept in my bed.
Who's Jean?
Is she like you?
What happened to her?
She died.
I killed her.
Along with the Kuzuri.
Logan.
Mariko?
Logan!
Mariko!
No! Logan!
No!
Logan!
Mariko!
No!
Logan!
Mariko! Mariko!
Where are they taking her?
Where, you piece of shit?
I no talk, gaijin.
I never talk.
Who hired you?
Uh-oh.
Take me to Noburo.
- Logan...
- Take me to him.
I need to tell you something.
Do it. Now.
You wait in the car.
- Logan.
- What?
I saw you die.
What?
When? Just now?
A while ago.
But it's not like
I get a complete picture.
More like looking through a keyhole.
But I'm always right.
All I can see
is one part of a person's life...
their death.
And I saw yours.
So, what did you see?
I see you on your back.
There's blood everywhere.
You're holding your own heart
in your hand.
It's not beating.
I don't have time for this shit.
When I was five,
I knew how my own parents would die.
Then I watched it happen
from the back seat.
Look at me.
A lot of people have tried to kill me,
and I'm still here.
Yeah...
but you're different now, aren't you?
They can hurt you.
They can kill you.
Just wait in the car.
I said, wait in the car.
You need backup.
You're not safe, not in your condition.
Just think of me as your bodyguard.
Sexy.
Come on!
I'm coming.
Okay, round four. Here we go.
Drink for you, my lady.
Get out.
Not you.
Call me old-fashioned...
but I thought being engaged meant
you were done with this kind of bullshit.
I am the Minister of Justice. Do you
have any idea what I could do to you?
Really? You're gonna try and talk tough,
standing there in your red underwear?
You have ten words...
ten words...
to explain to me why you,
the Minister of Justice...
would want your fiancé
killed by the Yakuza.
If I don't like what you say,
you are going through that window.
You don't have the faintest idea
what's going on...
How many words was that?
Nine.
Nine. You have one word left.
Really?
Shingen. Shingen!
Keep going.
Since he got sick...
old man Yashida spent billions
on doctors, healers.
Stockpiling adamantium
at his lab in the North...
secretly trying to prolong his life.
He brought the company
to the edge of bankruptcy.
He was obsessed with you.
English!
Shingen lied, protected the old man...
concealed the debt
from stockholders and the board.
He tried to be a good son
and thought he'd be rewarded.
And then the old man
left everything to his granddaughter.
If Mariko got all that power,
she would dump his ass.
It's true.
Mariko would have never
gone through with the wedding...
not once the will was revealed.
She never took to me.
Oh, really? A class act like you.
Shingen promised me
a fortune for my help.
So, you put a hit on his daughter.
Is that it?
Political careers don't last forever.
That's right.
Wait! Wait! No!
You wanted the truth.
I told you the truth!
I didn't like it.
Wow.
How did you know
there's a pool down there?
I didn't.
Did you know I studied biology in college?
Genetics.
There are genes that skip generations.
Recessive genes.
Eyes.
Eyes. Hair.
Talent.
Temperament.
Not every child gets the same.
My father saw little of himself in me.
But in you...
he faced a mirror.
How did you convince my father...
to award you control...
of Asia's largest corporation?
You've gone insane.
I'm just waking up.
If you kill me, you will lose...
what little honor you have left.
Fear not Mariko.
I don't want to hurt you.
I want to help you.
Help you end your pain...
what that mutant stopped you...
from doing last week.
I never wanted to die, Father.
It's alright, Mariko.
Come with me.
What is happening?!
More than you can imagine.
You.
Me.
Sorry to interrupt,
but I need your daughter alive.
What are you?
A chemist, a nihilist...
a capitalist, a mutation.
A viper.
Where is the security?
Shingen?
Logan.
This. This here.
Where is this?
Master Yashida's birthplace.
The company built a facility
into the mountainside.
How far?
500 kilometers from here.
I gotta get that thing out of me.
How?
No, stop, Logan.
I saw you die. I'm never wrong.
I'm never wrong.
You're not always right.
You didn't know
the old man was gonna bite it.
I saw you die in a room like this
with your heart in your hand.
I can't leave her with
those freaks and killers.
I'm the only chance she's got,
but not with that thing inside me.
- You're going to die, Logan.
- Maybe that's okay.
No, listen to me, Logan!
No, stop. Logan!
You're not gonna want
to watch this part.
No! Listen to me! Please, no!
No, stop. Listen to me.
Logan!
Move!
Stay away from him.
He killed your master.
Put hands on your sister.
And now you want him?
Oh, no. I can't see.
You'll always be a beggar.
You're crazy.
Oh, no.
Yukio.
Logan!
Logan! Logan!
Don't hit my friends.
Where's Mariko?
She's gone. That Viper bitch took her.
It was my father's obsession...
with mutation, with God's mistakes...
like you and her,
that ruined this house.
You tried to kill your daughter.
Live with that.
What kind of monster are you?
The Wolverine.
Hey, come here, come here. That's it.
I was wrong.
I told you.
Let me have a look at you.
It's nothing.
Hey, thank you.
It's a trap, Logan.
Why have you brought me here?
What are you hiding?
You will soon find out.
Welcome, Mariko.
It's all right, Mariko.
She also serves the House of Yashida.
She serves herself.
She infected Logan.
And what about Grandfather?
What did you infect him with?
I granted his dying wish.
I helped him rest.
Now, it's your turn.
Did you have a nice rest?
I don't know what you said or did
to deceive Harada or my grandfather...
Now, now, calm down.
Your grandfather sought me out.
I am the head of this family now.
And why do you suppose that is?
Why do you think the old man chose you?
Because you are strong?
Or because you are weak?
I see you've come to fight.
It's pointless.
You're weak. You're outnumbered.
The Black Clan has protected
the House of Yashida for 700 years.
Is that all the men you brought?
I'm gonna get her.
We are grateful
for your protection of Mariko.
But there is one more sacrifice
you must make for her family.
Go fuck yourself, pretty boy.
Logan.
Kayla.
- I love you.
- Kayla!
Logan.
Logan!
Mariko!
Jean.
Save me.
Stand back. There is no need.
Where is she? Where's Mariko?
Where is she?
"Where is Mariko?"
Still pining away?
That's so sweet.
Impressive, no?
He is made of adamantium, just like you.
Logan, you know what, I get it.
You're frustrated.
I know she's here. I want to see her.
You want answers.
Yes, I want answers!
I'm sorry, I wish I could say more,
but I was hired in part for my discretion.
I'm sure you were.
That...
and a certain talent for combining
biochemistry and metaphysics.
High-grade toxins are my specialty.
It helps to be genetically immune
to every poison known to man, as I am.
And immune to the toxin
that is man himself...
as I am.
I'll tell you what,
you twisted mutant bitch...
why don't you open these bracelets
and we'll see who's made of what?
The claws. Now we can begin.
I know you care for him.
You need to let go of that.
You are a Yashida.
She betrayed my grandfather...
and so have you.
No Mariko.
We grew up together.
You need to trust me.
Let me go to him!
He saved my life!
Let him go, Mariko!
This isn't easy for me but...
I'm following Grandfather's wishes.
The suppressant bug you
found inside of you was mine.
You took it out on your own.
I didn't see that coming.
The Viper woman is evil...
we both know that.
But she's a means to an end...
Where is she?
An end your grandfather wanted.
You are strong.
You have courage.
Real courage.
But that won't help much now.
What the...?
You need to trust me.
Is that hard?
We were meant to be together.
We still can be.
Perhaps.
Stop!
This is madness.
Let's go.
Go!
Run!
Come on.
- Mariko, come!
- Go! Run!
Mariko, get out!
Come on.
This is not the way.
Two hands.
Master...
Hey! Bub!
Harada.
I'm sorry.
Now, you die.
Today is not my day.
Hey!
Logan-san.
Don't look so shocked.
With you at my side,
I survived Nagasaki.
Surely, I could survive this.
It's all right. It won't take long.
Dr. Green and I have been waiting.
It's only this armor
that's kept me alive.
We built it to make me strong,
so I can take what you would not give.
And transfer your
unwanted healing...
to my body.
My legacy must be preserved.
Your mistake was to believe
that a life without end...
can have no meaning.
It is the only life that can.
Hold on.
We are almost there.
The peace, the peace you've wanted.
Your reward.
You know,
I'm giving you the very death...
you longed for.
This feeling...
to be invincible...
like you.
You are a monster.
Mariko.
It's me. Your grandfather.
I buried my grandfather.
You asked me to come say goodbye.
Sayonara.
Are you all right?
Logan.
You're here.
Of course.
Can you stay?
I can't.
Yes, you can.
This is what you wanted.
Not anymore.
I'm all alone here.
You put me here.
You were hurting people, Jean.
I had to.
I love you, Jean.
I always will.
You are my only family.
Be well, sister.
Am I wrong to think
you might visit me soon?
Stay.
I can't, princess.
I'm a soldier, and I've
been hiding too long.
In our business profile tonight,
Mariko Yashida.
A two-generation passing of the torch
in the Yashida family...
as Mariko Yashida takes the helm from
her grandfather, who built this tech giant.
I know it will always be the purpose
for a corporation to make a profit...
but Yashida Industries believes
we can also work with our community.
So, have you decided?
What?
Mariko says we can go wherever we want.
Just say where.
What are you doing?
I'm your bodyguard.
So, where do you want to go?
Let's just start with up.
And then?
We'll see.
Interesting.
With cutting edge technology,
and the world's leading minds...
we are on the frontlines...
keeping you healthy,
keeping you safe.
Trask Industries.
Solving tomorrow's problems, today.
I'll take the pat-down.
Opt out.
- You can go ahead, sir.
- I'll wait.
What do you want?
There are dark forces, Wolverine.
Human forces building a weapon...
that could bring about the end of our kind.
What do I want?
I want your help.
Why would I trust you?
You wouldn't.
Hello, Logan.
How is this possible?
As I told you a long time ago...
you are not the only one with gifts.