THE GREAT GATSBY
Transcript and sync: jcdr V3 — 10.10.2013
In my younger and more vulnerable years,
my father gave me some advice.
"Always try to see the best
in people", he would say.
As a consequence, I'm inclined
to reserve all judgments.
But even I have a limit.
Back then, all of us drank too much.
The more in tune with the times we were,
the more we drank.
And none of us contributed anything new.
When I came back from
New York, I was disgusted.
I see, Mr. Carraway.
Disgusted with everyone,
and everything.
Only one man was exempt from my disgust.
One man… Mr. Carraway?
Gatsby.
Was he a friend of yours?
He was…
the single most hopeful
person I've ever met,
and I'm ever likely to meet again.
There was something about him,
a sensitivity. He was like…
he was like one of those machines that
register earthquakes 10,000 miles away.
Where did you meet him?
At a… at a party.
In New York.
In the summer 1922,
the tempo of the city approached…
hysteria.
Stocks reached record peaks,
and Wall Street boomed
in a steady golden roar.
The parties were bigger.
The shows were broader.
The buildings were higher.
The models were looser, and
the ban on alcohol had backfired,
making the liquor cheaper.
Wall Street was luring
the young and ambitious,
and I was one of them.
I rented a house twenty miles
from the city on Long Island.
I lived in West Egg, in a forgotten
groundskeeper's cottage,
squeezed among the mansions
of the newly rich.
To get started, I bought a dozen volumes
on credit banking and investment,
all new to me.
The stock market hit another high.
The market's moving up, up, up!
Well, of course, nothing is 100%.
Though I wouldn't go investing every penny.
At Yale, I dreamed of being a writer.
But I gave all that up.
With the sun shining and the
bursts of leaves on the trees,
I planned to spend
the summer studying.
And I probably would have, were it not
for the riotous amusements that beckoned,
from beyond the walls
of that colossal castle,
owned by a gentleman I had not yet met,
named Gatsby.
So, he was your neighbor?
My neighbor…
Yeah.
When I think about it,
the history of the summer really began
the night I drove over
to my cousin Daisy's for diner.
She lived across the bay
in old moneyed East Egg.
Her husband was heir to one of
America's wealthiest families.
His name was Tom Buchanan.
When we were at Yale together,
he'd been a sporting star.
Now his glory days were behind him,
and he contented himself with—
— Telephone, Monsieur Buchanan.
— It's me.
…other affairs.
— I thought I told you not to call me here.
Boaz!
— Shakespeare!
— Tom!
How is the great American novel coming?
I'm selling bonds now, with
Walter Chase's outfit.
Let's say, after diner,
you and I we go into town.
— I can't.
— Catch up with the ol'wolf pack.
— Big day on the job tomorrow.
— Nonsense! We're going.
First team, all American.
See? Made me who I am today.
Forest Hills, played the Prince of Wales.
What a sissy!
Live is something you dominate, Nick!
If you're any good.
Henry! Where are you?
Oui, Monsieur.
The doors! Close them.
Allez!
Sorry. Thank you.
Is that you, my lovely?
Daisy Buchanan. The Golden Girl.
A breathless warmth flowed from her.
A promise that there was no one else
in the world she so wanted to see.
Do they miss me in Chicago?
Uh yes, huh, uhm…
At least a dozen people send their love.
How gorgeous.
They're absolutely in mourning.
They're crying. Yes, they're wailing.
— No. I don't believe it.
— I don't believe you.
— They're screaming, they're shouting,
"Daisy Buchanan,
we can't live without you!"
I'm paralyzed with happiness!
Jordan Baker, a very famous golfer.
She was the most frightening
person I'd ever seen.
Well I— I've seen your face on the cover
of Sporting Life. Nick Carraway.
But I enjoyed looking at her.
I've been lying on that sofa
for as long as I can remember.
This summer, I'll fling
you two together,
I'll push you into linen closets,
and out to sea in boats!
I'm not listening to a word.
So Nick, Daisy tells me
that you're over in West Egg.
Throwing your lot in with those
social climbing primitive new money types.
My little shack's just a cardboard
box at $80 a month.
Your life is adorable.
I know somebody in West Egg.
I don't know a single person
that side of the bay.
Oh! You must know Gatsby.
Gatsby?
What Gatsby?
Madame, the dîner is servi.
Would you like to hear a family secret?
That's why I came over.
It's about the butler's nose.
Things went from bad to worse.
I hate that word, "hulking".
Nicky, I heard a rumor that you were
getting married to a girl out West.
It's a libel. I'm too poor.
They have to be old so they die quickly.
Can't we talk about something else?
— We ought to have plans.
— Anything. Crops.
You're making me feel uncivilized, Daisy.
Civilization's going to pieces.
Have you read "The Rise
of the Colored Empires"?
By this fellow, Goddard.
Everyone ought to read it.
The idea is that it's up
to us, the dominant race,
to watch out or these other races
will have control of things.
Tom's very profound lately.
He reads deep books with
long words in them.
It's been proved. Scientific.
We've got to beat them down.
Buchanan residence?
Monsieur Wilson from the garage.
Monsieur Buchanan?
Excuse me, I'll be right back.
I'm sorry.
Well. This, huh, this Mr. Gatsby
you spoke of. He's my neighbor.
Don't talk. I wanna hear what happens.
I don't care what you do…
Something happening?
Why, I thought everybody knew.
Well, I don't.
Tom's got some
woman in New York.
Got some woman?
She might have the decency not to
telephone at diner time. Don't you think?
- Is that too much to ask?
- Daisy, don't create a scene.
I love seeing you at my table, Nicky.
You remind me of a rose.
An absolute rose, doesn't he?
— So, after diner…
— Well, I'm not even faintly like a rose.
— Nick wanted to go into town.
Right, Nick? To the Yale club.
— Nicky. Stay!
— I have to work early.
— Nonsense.
— There's so much to talk about.
It's just for a drink or two.
None of us could ignore that
fifth guest's shrill metallic urgency.
— Oh! Nicky.
— What?
It's just… Oh you see, I think
everything's terrible anyhow.
— Really?
— Yes.
I've been everywhere and seen
everything and done everything.
I've had a very bad time, Nicky.
I'm pretty cynical about everything.
Your daughter, I suppose she talks
and eats and everything?
Pammy?
Oh, yes.
Listen, Nick. When she was born, Tom was…
God knows where.
With God knows whom.
And I asked the nurse if
it was a boy or a girl.
And she said it was a girl.
And I wept.
I'm glad it's a girl.
And I hope she'll be a fool.
That's the best thing a
girl in this world can be.
A beautiful little fool.
All the bright, precious things
fade so fast.
And they don't come back.
When I arrived home, I noticed that a
figure had emerged on my neighbor's dock.
And something told me it was…
Mr. Gatsby.
He seemed to be reaching towards
something out there in the dark.
The green light.
I don't wanna talk about this, doctor.
Then write about it.
— Write about it?
— Yes.
Why would I do that?
You said yourself writing
brought you solace.
Yeah well… it didn't bring
anyone else much solace.
I wasn't any good.
No one need ever read it.
You could always burn it.
— What would I write about?
— Anything.
Whatever brings you ease.
A memory. A thought. A place.
Write it down.
A place…
The Valley of Ashes was a grotesque place.
New York's dumping ground half way
between West Egg and the city,
where the burnt out coal that powered the
booming golden city was discarded by men,
who moved dimly and already
crumbling through the powdery air.
This Fantastic Farm was ever
watched by Dr. T.J. Eckleburg.
A forgotten oculist whose
eyes brooded over it all.
Like the eyes of God.
Tom had invited me to town.
Apparently for lunch at the Yale club.
But the day took an unexpected turn.
Come on.
— Come on!
— What do you mean?
— Trust me!
— What are we doing?
— Hey, where are you going?
— Jump!
— What are you doing?
— Come on!
— Tom!
Oh, God. Tom, wait!
Wait a second, would ya?
Dominate, Nick!
Dominate!
Hello, Wilson. How's business?
Yeah, I can't complain.
So uh… When're ya
gonna sell me that car?
Well I've still got my man
working on it.
Yeah well he works pretty slow, don't he?
Maybe I'd better sell it somewhere else.
Uh no, no no, I wasn't
saying that, I… was…
If it's business, you should
be talking to me.
Get some chairs, why don't you,
so somebody can sit down!
Uh, sure.
Yeah, let's talk business.
Sure. I'll get the chairs, uh…
Mirt, why don't you uh…
don't you entertain.
— Oh yeah.
— Yeah. I…
— Hi.
— Mr. Buchanan. Candy?
— Uh. No! Thank you.
— No?
— Uh. Mrs. Wilson.
— Okay.
— Nick Carraway.
Oh. A pleasure.
— Uh, Nick's a writer.
— Ah?
Oh, I'm— I'm in bonds, actually.
I want you…
get on the next train.
— Now?
— Yes!
Can we get the dog for the apartment?
Whatever you want.
Hey, Mr. Buchanan, you want a—
you want a soda?
— Uh! I'm fine!
— No? Ah.
Call your sister,
she will like him.
No no no. Uh. That's alright, thank you.
Catherine's said to be very good looking,
by people who oughta know.
Uh. Really I can't.
Hey! You wanna embarrass Myrtle?
That's rude.
I'm Catherine.
Ain't we having a party?
Hum… I'm not sure
now's a good time.
I'm just going. Uh.
Actually, there are peop—
Hullo! Oh Chester,
this must be the cousin.
Oh, you are adorable!
Oh, thank you.
— Chester McKee, pleasure to meet you.
— Nick Carraway.
— Come on, don't you like me?
— Oh! Uh! Plant!
Myrtle? Myrtle?
Myrtle Turtle!
I really must go!
Myrtle, get everybody a drink
before they fall asleep.
Tom, I'm— I'm just leaving now.
Nick! Wait!
I'm just… I'm just going,
I've gotta get out of here.
Nonsense!
Go on in there, talk to Catherine!
Tom, I'm not comfortable here.
Daisy is my cousin.
Listen, I know you like to watch.
I remember that from college.
— That's not what—
Oh no no no, I don't make any judgment.
We have all summer! Now you wanna
sit on the sideline and watch,
or d'you wanna play ball?
— Play ball!
— Ain't we good enough for you?
Come on!
— Come on! Yeah!
He's gonna sit on the side and watch? Uh?
Or is he gonna play ball?
Take off your hat and stay a while.
Oh, uh Nick.
McKee is in the artistic game.
— Photography.
— Yeah. Nick's artistic.
— No! No no no, not really!
I write a little, but…
— Really?
Do you live on Long Island too?
— I live in West Egg.
I was there at a party
about a month ago.
A man named Gatsbys.
D'you know him?
I live right next door to him.
He's a cousin of Kaiser Wilhem's.
You know, the evil German king?
— Really?
Hey McKee! Take a picture of that!
Don't, I'm not one of those models!
But you can, if you want.
Neither of them can stand
the person they're married to.
Doesn't she like Wilson either?
He's a greasy little scumbag.
No thanks. I feel just as good
on nothing at all.
Nerve pills. I get them
from a doctor in Queens.
Do you want one?
Oh no. My nerves are fine, thanks.
I had been drunk just twice in my life.
And the second time was that afternoon.
That night in the hidden flat
that Tom kept for Myrtle,
we were buoyed by a sort
of chemical madness.
A willingness of the heart that
burst thunderously upon us all.
And suddenly, I began to like New York.
This is better than the Yale club!
High over the city,
our yellow windows must have contributed
their share of human secrets
to the casual watcher in the street.
And I was him too,
looking up and wondering,
I was within… and without…
…enchanted and repelled…
by the inexhaustible variety of life.
You have got no right to speak her name!
— Daisy, Daisy, Daisy—
— You got no right to speak her name!
I'll speak her name when—
Oh my God! You are crazy!
You're a whore!
They're gonna arrest you!
I have no clue how I got home.
But I do know that I awoke
with a distinctly uneasy feeling
that Gatsby was watching me.
Watching you?
Yes. Gatsby was always watching me.
And how did you know that?
I got an invitation.
I was the only one.
By which I mean, no one except me
ever received an actual
invitation to Gatsby's.
You see, the rest of New York
simply came uninvited.
The whole city packed into automobiles
and all weekends, every weekend,
ended up at Gatsby's.
And I mean, everyone from every walk
of life and every corner of New York city.
This kaleidoscopic carnival
spilled through Gatsby's door.
— Out of the way!
— My invitation.
Hello.
— Sir, my invitation.
— This way!
A caravansary of billionaire playboy
publishers and their blond nurses…
Heiresses comparing inheritances
on Gatsby's beach.
My boss, Walter Chase,
losing money at the roulette tables.
Gossip columnists alongside gangsters
and governors exchanging telephone numbers.
Film stars, Broadway Directors,
morality protectors,
high school defectors,
and Ewing Klipspringer,
dubious descendant of Beethoven.
Do you know where I might find the host,
Mr. Gatsby? I live just next door.
Gatsby? I've never seen Mr. Gatsby, sir.
Why, no one has.
Alone and a little embarrassed,
I decided to get roaring drunk.
I thought I might see you here.
Hello!
I remembered you live next door.
It's like an amusement park!
Shall we?
— Did you get an invitation?
— People aren't invited to Gatsby's.
Well I was. Seems I'm the only one.
Who is this Gatsby?
He was a German spy during the war.
Teddy Barton, Nick Carraway.
A German spy?
No no, no no. He's the Kaizer's assassin.
— I heard he killed a man once.
— It's true!
— He kills for fun.
— Free of charge.
He's certainly richer than God.
You don't really believe
he killed a man, do you?
Well, let's go find him, and
you can ask him yourself.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome to the stage
the incredible Ms. Gilda Gray!
The Charleston!
♪At least I miss
♪Trips around the world
♪Don't mean a thing
♪If I ain't your girl
♪I ain't got time
♪For you baby
♪Either you're mine
Or you're not
Mr. Gatsby?
Sweet baby, come on!
♪Right here, right now
But you are mistaken!
For I am the mysterious Mr. Gatsby.
You won't find him.
This house…
and everything in it are all part
of an elaborate disguise.
But Mr. Gatsby doesn't exist.
Phooey! I've met him.
Really? Which one?
The prince?
The spy? The murderer?
I cannot find anyone who knows
anything real about Mr. Gatsby.
Well, I don't care!
He gives large parties, and I like
large parties, they're so intimate.
Small parties, there isn't any privacy.
But if that's true, what's all this for?
That, my dear fellow, is THE question.
Are you ready?
♪A little party never
♪Killed nobody
♪So we gonna dance
♪Until we drop
♪A little party never killed
♪Nobody
♪Right here, right now
Is all we got
♪A little party
♪Never killed nobody
Can I have this dance?
Oh you penniless pantywaist!
Yeah!
I'm stealing her away, Carraway!
— Ladies and gentlemen!
— Come on!
A Jazz history of the world,
and accompanying fireworks!
Come on! Nick!
Look around you! Rich girls
don't marry poor boys.
She's mine.
Your face is familiar. Weren't you
in the third Division during the war?
Uh, yes, the ninth battalion.
— I was in the seventh.
— Excuse me.
I knew you looked familiar.
Having a good time, old sport?
Oh, the whole thing's incredible.
I live just next door.
Uh, he sent me an actual invitation.
Seems I'm the only one.
I still haven't met Mr. Gatsby.
No one's met him.
They say he's third cousin to the Kaiser,
and second cousin to the devil.
I'm afraid I haven't been
a very good host, old sport.
You see…
I'm Gatsby.
You're…
His smile was one of
those rare smiles
that you may come across
four or five times in life.
It seemed to understand
you and believe in you,
just as you would like to be
understood and believed in.
Sorry old sport, I though you knew.
Please, just… I don't know
what to say, please forgive me.
— It's quite alright.
— I've had so much to drink.
— Yes?
— Mr. Gatsby, Sir.
Chicago on the wire.
— Oh well…
I'll be in just a minute.
I'm taking my new hydroplane
out in the morning.
Would you like to go with me?
— What time?
— The time that suits you.
Well, that's very kind of you.
Lovely to see you again, Miss Baker.
If there is anything that you want…
just ask for it, old sport.
Excuse me.
I will rejoin you later.
I expected him to be…
— Old and fat?
— Yes.
Young men don't just drift coolly out of
nowhere and buy a palace on Long Island.
He told me once he was an Oxford man.
However I don't believe it.
— Why not?
— I don't know.
I just don't believe he went there.
I beg your pardon.
Ms. Baker, Mr. Gatsby would
like to speak to you, alone.
— With me?
— Yes, madam.
Nick. Nick!
Nick!
I've just heard the most shocking thing!
Where have you been?
The car's waiting.
— Come on, we're leaving.
— This is amazing.
It all makes sense!
Come on!
— What makes sense?
— Everything.
Come on, this is crazy.
We gotta get out of here.
Oh, but here I am tantalizing you,
and I swore I wouldn't tell.
Just tell me.
Oh Nick, I'm sorry, I swore.
I swore I wouldn't tell.
Sorry to keep her from you, old sport.
Don't forget, we're going up in
that hydroplane tomorrow morning.
Yes!
Mr. Gatsby sir, Philadelphia on the phone.
Yeah.
Good night, old sport. Good night.
Thank you.
What's the matter?
You run out of gas?
Nick! Come and see me!
We'll have tea next week!
I'm in the phone book.
I'll call you up.
Well, we rode in the hydroplane,
and I attended two more of his parties.
Even made use of his beach.
But you know, doctor,
I realized that I knew absolutely
nothing about Gatsby at all.
Until…
It's pretty, isn't it, old sport?
Haven't you ever seen it before?
It's all a custom job.
Supercharged engine.
Get dressed. We're going to lunch.
— Oh, well.
— Yeah.
Look here, old sport. What…
What is your opinion of me anyhow?
— My opinion?
— Yes, yes. Your opinion.
I don't want you to get the
wrong impression from all these—
from all these bizarre accusations
you must be hearing.
A pack of lies, I guarantee.
You— you've heard the stories.
— Oh! Well—
— I will tell you God's truth.
God's truth about myself.
I am the son of very wealthy
people from the Middle West.
Sadly, all of them are dead now.
I was brought up in America, but
educated at Oxford because all my
ancestors had been educated there for many
years, you see, it's a family tradition.
The way he spoke! No wonder
people thought he was lying.
After my family died, I came
into a great deal of money.
After that, I lived like a young prince
in all the capitals of Europe.
— Oh, Europe?
— Yes, Europe!
Paris, Venice, Rome,
Vienna, Zurich,
Helsinki, Moscow, Istanbul,
collecting jewels —chiefly rubies—
hunting big game, painting a little—
things for myself only.
Trying to forget something sad.
Just when I thought it couldn't be
any more fantastical…
Then came the war, old sport.
…he became a war hero,
single handedly defeating the German army.
In the Argonne forest, I took two
machine gun detachments, so far—
outnumbered, five to one—
there was half a mile gap on either side—
there wasn't a single
German soldier left standing—
we stayed there two days and two nights—
and we saw piles of dead—
130 men, with only 16 Lewis guns—
every allied government gave
me a medal — even Montenegro.
Here, that's from Montenegro.
"Major Jay Gatsby,
for Valour Extraordinary".
That's right.
And this something I always carry with me,
a souvenir of Oxford days.
That was taken in Trinity Quad, the man
on my left is now the Earl of Doncaster.
What could I say?
The photograph was undoubtedly authentic.
Could it all be true?
But of course, you don't need
to take my word for it, old sport.
At lunch today,
I'm going to introduce you
to one of New York's most
distinguished businessmen,
a Mr. Meyer Wolfsheim.
My good friend.
And he will confirm all I have told you,
and vouch for my good character.
Oh, I'm sure that's not necessary.
Oh, but it is though.
You see, I though you ought to
know something about my life,
I didn't want you
to think I was…
Well, I didn't want you to think
I was just some nobody.
— No!
— You see, old sport, I'm…
I'm going to make a very
big request of you today.
A big request?
Yes. Ms. Baker will explain everything
when you take her to tea this afternoon.
Jordan? What's she got to do with it?
Well I assure you it's nothing underhand.
Miss Baker's a honest sportswoman, she
wouldn't do anything that wasn't alright.
Pull over! Pull over to the curb!
Alright old sport. Alright.
Right you are! I'll know you
next time, Mr. Gatsby.
— Excuse me!
— Thank you.
— One of your old Oxford pals?
— Well I was…
I was able to do the
commissioner a favor once.
He sends me a Christmas card every year.
I imagine he'll be at lunch too.
Βy the time we reached the bridge,
Ι was impossibly confused.
I didn't know what to think.
But the city seen from
the Queensboro Bridge
is always the city seen
for the first time…
In its first wild promise of all
the mystery and the beauty in the world.
Anything can happen!
Now that we've slid over
this bridge, I though…
Anything at all, even Gatsby,
could happen.
Yes, absolutely.
Have you heard about…
Aah! My boy!
Meyer, Meyer, Meyer.
— Smell so good. Look at you!
— Look at you!
Mr. Carraway, this is my good friend,
Mr. Meyer Wolfsheim.
A wonderful pleasure, Mr. Carraway.
— My pleasure.
— I know all about you.
— I see.
— Yes!
Mr. Gatsby's always talking about you.
— Really?
Shall we?
Come!
Join us for a little lunch.
♪Hundred, hundred, hundred dollar bills
Yeah!
— …hands off! Get your hands off me!
— Out! Out you go!
Tell Walter Chase. He keeps his mouth
shut or he doesn't get a penny.
We'll talk about that later.
— Highballs, Mr. Gatsby?
— Highballs it is.
— Alright!
— Take care of my friend.
Mr. Warden. May I ask you…
Look who's here!
You see these fists?
He's the next heavyweight champion.
Pay my respects to your boss.
Hey, Jay! You're under arrest!
You be careful now, you're turning into
a real jazz hound, commissioner!
That's the commissioner back there.
Mr. Gatsby! You table is ready.
Gatsby!
Good to see you!
You be careful with those
tables now, Senator.
I'll put a bet on for you, Jay!
We'll have the lobster. It's decorated
with truffles and fine herbs.
How's the bond business, Mr. Carraway?
Fine, thank you.
I understand you're looking
for a business connection.
No. No no, no. No no no.
Uh. This isn't the man, Meyer.
Remember this is the friend
I told you about.
Oh my, I beg your pardon.
I had the wrong man.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to make that call.
— Any luck, Senator ?
— What a gentleman.
From one of the finest
families in the Midwest.
Sadly, all dead now.
When I first made the pleasure of Mr.
Gatsby's acquaintance just after the war,
I knew I'd discovered
a man of fine breeding.
A war hero, such medals, and…
a man, an Oxford man.
You know Oxford?
— Yes, I've heard of it.
Then you would know that when
it comes to married women,
a man like this can be trusted.
With a friend, with someone like you,
he'd never so much as look at your wife.
— I'm not married.
— But you work on Wall Street, right?
Yes.
You're looking at my tie pin?
Finest specimen of human molar.
Gentlemen?
Everything alright?
Yes! Yes, we… we were just
talking about other people's wives.
— Other people's wives?
— Yes.
Well, my work here is done.
I'm gonna leave you gentlemen
to talk about your sports and your women.
— Other people's wives?
— Hello, ladies.
Who is he anyhow ? An actor?
Meyer? No no no.
He's a gambler.
He's the man who fixed
the 1919 World's Series.
— Fixed it?
— Fixed it.
How did he manage that?
He saw the opportunity, I suppose.
He's a very smart man.
Now old sport, about Miss Baker
and that—
that request we spoke of—
— Nick?
Nick!
— Tom! Funny seeing you!
— How have you been?
— Yeah! Good.
Nick, Daisy is furious.
You haven't called her.
Hey, uh. Mr. Gatsby, this is Mr. Buchanan.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
I never wouldn't have expected
to find you in this temple of virtue.
Well, I was just having
lunch with Mr. Gatsby.
Can I help you, sir?
Jordan Baker, the famous
sporting star? The golfer?
I— I see, I've spotted her. Thank you.
There you are.
What kind of game are you
and Gatsby playing at?
— This gentleman will be joining—
— Excuse me, one moment.
— Nick, please, just sit down.
— Well, it's all rather strange,
he picks me up in his fancy yellow car,
and he's going on and on about his life,
— Please keep your voice down,
— and the war and…
— Everybody can hear you.
— What is this enormous request, Jordan—
— He wants you to invite Daisy to tea.
Daisy?
And Gatsby.
Why?
I don't quite know where to start.
You see, I didn't realize until
the other night that I'd met Gatsby.
Five years ago. In Louisville.
That was the day I got
my new English golf shoes.
Daisy was by far the most popular girl
with the officers from Camp Taylor.
Hello, Jordan.
One of them was in the car with her.
It was Gatsby.
And the way he looked at her, is
the way all girls want to be looked at.
So. Tell me what happened.
Well, I don't know.
Charge!
Gatsby was sent off to war.
When the war ended,
Daisy waited,
but for some unknown reason,
Gatsby couldn't return.
A year later, Tom Buchanan of Chicago
swept in and stole her away.
He gave her a string of pearls
worth 350,000 dollars.
But the morning of the wedding,
Daisy received a letter.
Tell them Daisy's changed her mind!
— What is this?
— Daisy, please!
— Hand it to me!
— No!
Leave me alone!
Jordan, no one must know about this.
— But what was in the letter?
— I don't know, she wouldn't tell me.
But it was too late.
That day at five o'clock,
Daisy Fay married Tom Buchanan
with more pomp and circumstance
Louisville had ever seen.
Congratulations, Mr. Buchanan!
After the honeymoon,
I saw them in Santa Barbara.
Well it was touching, really, I'd never
seen a girl so in love with her husband.
A week later, Tom crashed his car.
The girl with him was a chambermaid
at the Santa Barbara hotel.
It got into all the papers.
— It's a strange coincidence.
— What is?
The fact that Gatsby's house
is just across the bay.
It's no coincidence. He bought
that house to be near her.
He threw all those parties,
hoping she would wander in one night.
He constantly asked about Daisy.
I was just the first person that knew her.
All that for a girl
he hasn't seen in five years.
And now he just wants me
to invite her over to tea.
The modesty of it…
kind of take your breath
away, doesn't it?
Evening, sweet hearts.
Where're you kids going?
— Long Island, please.
— Long Island.
And you think I should?
I mean, does Daisy want to see Gatsby?
She's absolutely not to know.
You're just supposed to invite her over,
so he can happen to pass by.
I remember feeling torn.
Was it right to bring my cousin
Daisy, a married woman,
together with a man I hardly knew?
When I returned home,
Gatsby's was lit from tower to cellar
as if for another wild party.
But there wasn't a sound.
— Thank you.
— Have a good night, sir.
Your place looks like
the World's fair or Coney Island.
— Ah, does it?
— Yes.
Oh I— I've just been… glancing
into some of the rooms.
What'd you say we go
to Coney Island, old sport?
We— we could take my car if you want.
— Oh, uh… It's too late, tonight.
We could take a plunge
in the swimming pool,
I haven't made use of it all summer.
— I must go to bed.
Alright.
Happy to do it.
I'm going to call Daisy
and invite her to tea.
That's alright, I— I— I—
— What day would suit you?
— What day would suit you!?
I don't want to put you to any trouble.
The day after tomorrow alright?
The day after tomorrow?!
Well I… See, I— I'd want
to get the grass cut.
— Well…
— Uh…
Look here old sport, you—
you don't make much money, do you?
— Not really.
— If you forgive me.
You see… I happen to run a little—
a little business on the side,
a sort of side line. I mean,
you understand what I'm saying, right?
You do sell bond, don't you, old sport?
— I'm trying to.
Right, well, it happens to be a
rather confidential sort of thing,
but you might make a nice
bit of money on the side.
Uh no, thank you,
I have my hands full.
But you wouldn't have to do any
business with Wolfsheim, I assure you.
It's a favor, Jay, just a favor.
Yes. I'm happy to do it.
— A favor?
— Yes!
— Well, good night.
— Good night.
One of the papers says they thought
the rain would stop about 4:00.
I think it was the—
I think it was the 'Journal'.
Just in to the right, gentlemen.
To the right, in the living room.
Thank you.
Is everything alright?
Oh, the grass looks fine,
if that's what you mean.
Grass? What grass?
I bought cakes.
Have you— have you got
everything you need?
Perhaps more flowers.
— I think they did a fine job, don't you?
— Beautiful.
You think it's too much?
I think it's what you want.
I think so too.
I can't wait all day.
I'm leaving!
Ah, don't be silly,
it's just two minutes to four.
No one's coming to tea, it's too—
It's her!
Is this absolutely where you live,
my dearest one?
Yes, it suits me.
Why did I have to come alone?
Are you in love with me?
Oh, it's the secret of Carraway castle.
Tell your chauffeur to go far away.
Come back in an hour, Ferdie.
His name is Ferdie.
Oh my goodness!
I can't believe it.
You? Did you ransack a greenhouse?
He IS in love with me.
Would you?
— That's funny.
— What's funny?
What are you doing?
I'm certainly glad to see you again.
Hi. I'm certainly glad
to see you as well.
We've… we've uh…
We've met before.
I'll have someone to come
repair this immediately.
Sorry about the clock.
That's an old clock.
— Lovely though, a lovely clock.
— Yes.
— We haven't met for many years.
— Five years, next November.
— Tea?
— Yes, thank you,
— Darling, thank you.
— Thank you, old sport.
— Lemon or sugar?
— Neither.
Plain, thank you.
— I just have to pop into town.
— Town?
— I'll be right back.
— Nick, I've…
got to speak to you about something!
— Yes, I— I'll be right back!
God! This is a mistake!
This is a terrible, terrible mistake!
You're just embarrassed,
Daisy's embarrassed too.
— She is embarrassed?
— Yes. Just as much as you are.
Don't talk so loud!
You're acting like a little boy!
You're being rude, Daisy's
in there all alone, and you—
Looking over my story so far,
I'm reminded that, for the
second time that summer,
I was guarding other people's secrets.
Once again, I was within… and without.
It stopped raining.
Yes. It has, hasn't it?
What do you think of that, Daisy?
Come look.
— Oh Nicky, how funny.
Look, it's my house.
Just there, across the bay.
I know.
I have the same view from my place.
Where is your place?
Nick, I want you and Daisy
both to come over to my house.
I'd like to show her around.
You sure you want me to come?
Absolutely, old sport. Absolutely.
Ladner, open the gates.
— Open the gates!
I had the gates brought in
from a castle in Normandy.
— Oh Jay, it's so grand!
— You like it?
I love it.
— But how do you live here all alone?
— Well I don't.
I keep it always full of
interesting celebrated people.
Come with me.
The house looks well, doesn't it?
See the way the whole front
catches the light like that?!
That's splendid.
Come on, you two.
I want the Royal Tour!
You must understand that I like
all things that are modern!
Press the orange, it all comes out there.
Anyone for a round of golf?
You still know I'm a
champion golfer, don't you?
— Great!
— Go on.
I thought we could…
This remarkable little camera's
the latest design.
Let me show you,
I'll show you how it's done.
— Alright.
— Nick, keep filming.
She's gonna take a swing.
— Get ready. Aim. Fore!
I'm such a brute.
— Okay, you're ready for your close-up?
— I don't want to forget a single moment.
You're shimmering.
She look like she could be on
the cover of Vogue, don't you think?
Turn on the camera!
— Where did you go?
— Slow down.
Slow down.
— It's beautiful!
— It's a custom Wurlitzer.
— Can anyone play that?
— Klipspringer can.
— Someone, wake Ewing!
— Of course, sir.
Music! And then we can dance all night.
Ewing ​​is a funny genius,
he can play anything.
Then I demand a Charleston.
She makes it look so— so splendid,
don't you think, old sport?
I have a man in England
who buys me clothes.
I've never seen anything like this.
Something for the lady.
He sends over a selection
at the beginning of each season.
These are silk.
— These are flannel.
— They're so beautiful!
— Indian cotton.
— Stop it, Jay!
Linen!
— Nicky, he's a mad man!
— I can't help you!
You know you'll have to refold
every single one of them!
You'll ruin them!
Jay, stop it!
— Right here!
— No, Jay!
What is it?
Daisy, Daisy darling, what is it?
It makes me sad.
— Why?
— Because…
Five lost years struggled on Daisy's lips.
But all she could manage was…
Why?
Cause I've never seen
such beautiful shirts before.
If it wasn't for the mist,
we could see the green light.
What green light?
The one that burns all night
at the end of your dock.
Possibly it had occurred to Gatsby that
the colossal significance of that light
had vanished forever.
Now it was once again
just a green light on a dock,
and his count of enchanted
object had diminished by one.
Who is this? Your father?
Oh No. That's Mr. Dan Cody, old sport.
He's dead now.
He used to be my best friend
many years ago.
You never told me you had
a pompadour or a yacht.
I wanna show you something.
Have a seat.
Here's a lot of clippings I collect.
About you.
You saved my letters.
This was my first photo of you.
You remember this letter, do you?
"We can't lose each other.
And let all this glorious
love end in nothing.
Come home.
I'll be here waiting and hoping,
for every long dream of you to come true."
Excuse me.
- Sir, Slagle's in Detroit.
I can't talk now, old sport.
He must know what a small town it is.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
I said a small town.
He must know what a small town is.
Listen to me. He is of no use to us
if Detroit is his idea of ​​a small town,
you understand?
We'll chat later, old sport.
Alright.
Klipspringer.
He must be awake.
Shall we?
I wish I had done everything
on earth with you.
All my life…
I wish it could always be like this.
It will be.
If only it had been enough for Gatsby,
just to hold Daisy.
But he had a grand vision
for his life and Daisy's part in it.
It wasn't until the end of that summer,
on the last night I saw Gatsby,
that he told me of the life he had
dreamed for himself since he was a boy.
You see, Doctor, Gatsby's real name was…
James Gatz.
His parents were dirt-poor
farmers from North Dakota.
He never accepted them
as his parents at all.
In his own imagination,
he was a son of God.
Destined for future glory.
Chasing this destiny,
a 16-year-old Gatz ran far, far away.
One afternoon, off the coast of Lake
Superior, he spotted a yacht in peril.
He rode out and rescued the vessel and its
captain, alcoholic millionaire Dan Cody.
You're gonna hit the shoal! Come on
sir, we're gonna hit the shoal!
What the hell are you doing, old sport?
This was his opportunity,
and he seized it.
And I decided right then and there,
to call myself Jay Gatsby.
He sailed the yacht out of danger
and into his future.
Gatsby showed skill and ambition,
and for five years, they sailed the world.
He was alright, old Dane.
He taught me everything.
— How to dress, act and speak…
— Gatsby.
— …like a gentleman
— Jay Gatsby.
She looks well, don't she!
Gatsby hoped to inherit Cody's fortune.
— Old sport.
But when Cody died, Gatsby was cheated
of his inheritance by Cody's family.
He'd been left with the ability
to play the gentleman,
but he was once again dirt poor.
By mid-summer, Gatsby was front page news.
Where did the money come from?
That's what the whole of
New York wanted to know.
And it was the same
question on Tom's mind,
when he accompanied Daisy
to one of Gatsby's…
…glittering parties.
Take a look around.
I'll be right back.
You know, a lot of these newly rich people
are just filthy booze makers.
Not Gatsby. He's a businessman,
he owned a lot of drugstores.
— Businessman!
— May I introduce Senator Gulick.
This is Mr. Carraway.
— Senator.
Mrs. Buchanan.
— Charmed.
— Delighted.
Oh and Mr. Buchanan,
the polo player.
No, not me.
Always a pleasure to meet a Buchanan.
Likewise.
Senator, I'll catch you up later,
perhaps at the crap table.
I'd rather not be the polo player.
Tom, you should be proud
of your achievements.
— May I show you around?
— Sure.
You must know the faces of
many people you've heard of.
Absolutely.
We don't go around very much. I don't
think I recognize a single person.
Is that so? Perhaps you know
that lady right there.
It's Marlene Moon!
I adore her pictures.
Would you like me to introduce you?
I'd really rather not be the Polo player.
All these things excite me so.
Nice little dance.
I believe we've met before, Mr. Buchanan.
About a month ago.
That's right!
And you were with Nick, here.
The barber shop.
That's right.
You see, I know your wife.
— Is that so?
— Yes.
Mr. Gatsby, sir.
Mr. Slagle is here.
No, not now!
— … and guitars with…
…the Foxtrot.
Mr. Buchanan.
Would you mind terribly?
Of course not.
I think I can keep myself amused.
In case you need to
take down any addresses.
Please move aside. Excuse me.
Another swell party, Jay.
Be careful for the snake charmer,
Mr. McLennahan.
Is all this made entirely
from your own imagination?
No.
See, you were there all along.
In every idea.
Every decision.
Of course, if anything is not
your liking, I'll change it.
It's perfect.
From your perfect
irresistible imagination.
I wonder where the devil he met her.
— I'll find you.
— Alright.
Come with me.
Coming through, please.
Pardon me.
Thank you.
Have you seen my wife?
No.
Not for a while.
Whiskey. It's funny, the Senator
just saw her down here.
I wish we could just run away.
Run away?
No.
Daisy, darling, that…
that wouldn't be respectable.
You live around here, Nick?
— Just next door.
— Is that so?
We're gonna live here.
In this house. You and me.
Darling…
It's time to tell Tom.
Come on boys, it's too late!
Good night, gentlemen!
What a circus.
Well, if you see her, I'll be
looking for her. You tell her.
Remember how much fun we had?
I don't know why we can't
just have fun like that again.
Hello?
Hello, Nicky. We're having a row.
— What about?
— About things.
About the future.
The future of the Colored Empires.
It's Tom, he's wandering
around the party,
looking for—
— Sir.
Mr. Gatsby, sir. It's Mr. Slagle.
He's quite emotional.
Excuse me.
Nick. Would you mind terribly?
Of course.
Gatsby disappeared to deal
with a dispute of some sort.
Daisy waited.
But Gatsby was unable to return.
With these hot-headed types
in here, I rely on you.
But you were not available.
A scene was made.
What's going on with you, Jay?
— Where were you?
— With Nicky.
Mr. Gatsby was showing us the grounds.
He certainly must have strained
himself to get this menagerie together.
I'd like to know who he is.
What he does.
And I think I'll make a point
of finding out.
— I'm not sure. Ask them in the kitchen.
— To the left.
Yeah, we'll pile that stuff in the garage,
it's going back to town.
Oh, there you are!
Daisy just left.
She asked me to tell you
she had a wonderful time.
She didn't like it.
— Of course she did!
— No, no no.
No, she didn't like it, she…
she did not have a good time, I…
feel so far away from her now.
So hard to make her understand.
— You mean about the party?
— The party?
I couldn't care less
about the parties.
That will be all for now, gentlemen.
Thank you.
— Thank you, sir.
You see…
She has to tell Tom that
she never loved him.
— What?
— Yes.
Then we can go back to Louisville
to her parents' house.
Her parents are lovely people, old sport.
We'll be married there.
See… See, Daisy and I are gonna
start over just as if it were 5 years ago.
I wouldn't ask too much of her.
— Wouldn't ask too much?
— No.
I beg your pardon, old sport, it just…
it's so sad because it is so hard
to make her understand.
It's so hard to make
her understand.
I've gotten all these things for her,
now she just…
she just wants to run away.
She even wants to leave that.
Jay! You can't repeat the past.
— Can't repeat the past?
— No.
Why, of course you can.
Of course you can.
See, I'm gonna fix things,
just the way they were before.
Everything's been so…
so confused since that night.
He talked a lot about the past.
As if he wanted to recover something.
If I c— if I could just
get back to the start.
If I could just get back to the start…
I could find it again.
Some vision of himself that
he'd put into loving Daisy.
One night in Louisville, five years ago,
Gatsby found himself at Daisy's
house by colossal accident.
So I went to her house first, with
some of the officers from Camp Taylor.
I'd never been in such
a beautiful house before.
May I save the next dance?
His uniform hid the truth,
that he was a penniless young man,
with only that grand vision of himself.
— Daisy, don't scamper.
— I was not, mother.
So many dashing young officers here,
and from such illustrious families.
I always knew that I could climb.
But I could only climb if I climbed alone.
I knew that when I kissed this girl…
I would be forever wed to her.
So I stopped.
I stopped, and I…
I waited.
I waited for a moment longer.
He knew his mind would never again
be free to romp like…
the mind of God.
That falling in love
would change his destiny…
for ever.
Αnd then I just let myself go.
She blossomed for him like a flower…
and the incarnation was complete.
I knew it was a great mistake
for a man like me to fall in love.
I'm only 32, I might still be a great man if
I can forget that I once lost Daisy, but…
my life, old sport, my life…
My life has got to be like this.
It's got to keep going up.
She has to go to Tom…
and tell him that she never loved him.
I just need to give her more time,
old sport. More time.
Don't worry old sport, don't worry.
I can protect her here.
Good night, old sport.
You're wrong about the past, old sport!
You're wrong.
There had been music from
my neighbor's all summer.
In his blue gardens, men and
girls came and went like moths,
among the whisperings and
the laughter and the stars.
— Breakfast?
— Yes. Thank you, thank you.
Laughter.
Thank you.
No, the whispering and the—
the champagne and the stars.
But…
After Tom and Daisy's visit,
Gatsby's lights went out one by one.
There were no more parties.
Daisy visited discreetly.
For the very same fame that had all summer
been a source of satisfaction to Jay Gatsby,
had become a threat.
I don't wanna go home.
I— I heard you fired all your servants.
Daisy comes over sometimes
in the afternoon,
I wanted people who wouldn't gossip
until we decide what we're going to do.
You see, these towns are
very close together, old sport.
If it gets in the papers, you understand?
They're all people Wolfsheim
wanted to do something for.
What's the difference as long as
they can cook and make beds, right?
Nick, Daisy's ready.
She's ready, there's just…
one thing she's requesting,
that you and Mrs Baker be there
for lunch tomorrow at her house.
Will you come, old sport?
Daisy needs you.
We need you.
Will you come, old sport?
You know, I read somewhere that
the sun is getting hotter every year.
Wait a minute. It's the opposite.
The sun is getting colder every year.
Oh I would like to be out
on that bay today.
I'm right across from you.
Right there.
So you are.
You see, every night I can see that
light at the end of your dock blinking.
What light?
You see, Mr. Buchanan,
I wanted to be close…
Daisy and I have—
— It's so hot!
Everything's so confused!
What'll we do with ourselves
this afternoon or,
the day after that, or
for the next thirty years?
Oh, don't be morbid.
Let's go to town.
Who wants to go to town?
Town?
Oh! Women get these notions!
Daisy?
You look so cool.
He always looks so cool.
Like the advertisement
of the man in Times Square.
The man in the cool beautiful shirts.
She had told Gatsby that she loved him.
And Tom had seen it.
Let's go to town!
I'm perfectly willing.
It's a marvelous idea.
Henry, have the car
brought around now.
Just like that? Can't anyone
at least have a cigarette first?
We smoked all through lunch.
Come on, let's have fun.
It's too hot to fuss.
Daisy, it was your great idea!
Why don't we? Let's all go to town?
I changed my mind, you brute.
Oh come on, we'll get a
great big room at the Plaza.
A bucket of ice, a bottle of whiskey
and it will be fun.
Come on. It was your idea.
Fine. Have it your own way, Tom.
Come on, Jordan.
Will you join us, Mr. Gatsby?
Two bottles of whiskey,
wrap them in a towel.
Come on, Nick!
Mr. Gatsby, would you be good
enough to take my coupé,
and I'll drive everyone
else in your circus wagon.
I don't think there's much gas, old sport.
Nope, plenty o' gas.
Well, if I run out,
I'll stop at a drugstore.
I hear you can buy anything
at a drugstore nowadays.
— You take Nick and Jordan.
— I suppose you can, yes.
We'll meet you at the Plaza.
I'll be the man in the corner,
smoking two cigarettes.
You must think I'm
pretty dumb, don't you?
But I have a second sight sometimes
that tells me what to do.
I've made a small investigation
into this fellow.
And you found he was an Oxford man?
Oxford, New Mexico.
He wears a pink suit, for Christ sake.
Tom, we're almost out of gas.
Wilson? What are you waiting for?
Let's have some gas!
Do I have to do it myself?
Do you think I come here
to admire the view?
Sorry uh, I'm sick.
Why?
Why, what's the matter?
I don't know, I'm… I all run down.
I need money real bad.
— What?
— My wife and I, we wanna go west.
Oh, your wife does?
Tom was feeling the hot whips of panic.
His mistress and wife,
an hour ago so secure,
were both slipping
from his control.
I wised up to something funny
these last two days.
There she is. She's going West,
whether she wants it or not.
— What do I owe you?
— A dollar. A dollar twenty.
You can have the car.
I'll send it over tomorrow.
Fine! Fine, fine.
Open another window.
There aren't any more.
Then telephone for an axe.
Will you forget about the heat?!
You make it worse by crabbing about it.
Why not let her alone, old sport?
That's a great expression
of yours, isn't it?
What is?
'Old sport'. Where did you pick it up?
Now see here, Tom, if you're
gonna make personal remarks,
I won't stay here a minute.
Mr. Gatsby, I understand
you're an Oxford man.
No. Not exactly, no.
Oh yes, I understand that
you went to Oxford.
Uh yes, I went there.
Sure. The man in the
pink suit went to Oxford.
Tom!
I said I went there, didn't I?
Oh, I heard you.
I'd like to know when.
You'd like to know when?
Well, Mr. Gatsby?
It was in 1919,
I only stayed there 5 months,
that's why I can't exactly
call myself an Oxford man.
You see, it was an opportunity they
gave to some of us officers who—
who fought in the war.
I wanted to get up and
slap Gatsby on the back.
I'll make you a drink, Tom.
Then you won't seem
so stupid to yourself.
Wait a minute.
I wanna ask Mr. Gatsby
one more question.
Oh, please! Please go on,
Mr. Buchanan, go on.
What kind of a row are you trying
to cause in my house anyhow?
He isn't causing a row.
You're causing a row.
Please have a little self-control.
Self-control!
Oh! I suppose the latest
thing is to sit back
and let Mr. Nobody from Nowhere
make love to your wife.
Well, if that's the idea,
you can count me out.
See, nowadays people begin by sneering
at family life and family institutions,
and the next you'll know, we'll
throw everything overboard,
and we'll have intermarriage
between black and white!
Your wife doesn't love you!
She never loved you.
You see, she loves me.
— You must be crazy.
— No, old sport.
No, you see… she never loved you.
She only married you because I was
poor and she was tired of waiting,
it was a terrible, terrible mistake,
but in her heart,
in her heart she never
loved any one but me.
— We should go.
— Stay.
— Let's all go home.
— Sit down, Daisy!
Please. Please take a seat.
Come on, Daisy.
Daisy?
What's been going on?
— I wanna hear all about it.
— I've just told you what's going on,
it's been going on for five years.
You've been seeing him… for five years?
No, no. No, not seeing.
Not seeing, we couldn't but…
both of us loved each other
all that time, didn't we?
Oh, that's all?
You're crazy!
I can't speak about what
happened five years ago.
Because I didn't
know Daisy then.
And I'll be damned if I know
how you got within a mile of her,
unless you brought the groceries
to the back door,
but all the rest of that is a goddamn lie!
Daisy loved me when she married me,
and she loves me now.
— No! No.
— She does!
— I'm sorry, Mr. Buchanan.
— She does though!
— No.
— Oh no no, she does though,
she does, and what's more,
I love Daisy too.
Though once in a while, I— I go off
on a spree, I always come back.
— A spree!
— And in my heart I love—
— I love her all the time.
— You're revolting.
Do you know why we left Chicago?
I'm surprised they didn't treat you
to the story of that little spree.
Alright, that's all over now,
Daisy, darling, that's all over!
Just tell them the truth, go on.
That you never loved him…
and this… this will all
be wiped out forever.
Why, how could I love him, possibly!
Remember our plan, tell him
that you never loved him,
and all this pain will be
wiped out forever.
Daisy.
Daisy, tell him.
I never loved him?
Never?
— No.
Not at Kapiolani?
Not that day I carried you down from
the Punch Bowl to keep your shoes dry?
Never?
Please don't.
Daisy.
No, Jay! You want too much.
I love you now, isn't that enough?
I can't help what's past.
I did love him once—
but I loved you too.
You— you loved— you loved me too?
You loved me…
Even that is a lie! She did
not know that you were alive!
There are things between Daisy and me,
Gatsby, that you'll never know!
Things that neither of us
can ever forget!
I just need to speak to
Daisy alone. You see, you—
you've got her all excited now,
don't you old sport.
Daisy, hey—
Even alone I can't say I never loved Tom,
it wouldn't be true.
— Of course it wouldn't.
— As if it mattered to you.
Of course it matters. Daisy, I'm gonna
take better care of you from now on.
You're not taking
care of Daisy anymore.
— She's leaving you.
— Nonsense!
— I am though!
— No no no no no.
No, she is not leaving me.
And certainly not for a
common swindler like you.
Mr. Gatsby, exactly who are you, anyhow?
You see, I have made a small
investigation into your affairs,
You're one of Meyer
Wolfsheim's bunch.
Please, let's go home!
See, he ​​and this Wolfsheim,
they bought up a lot of drugstores,
and sold bootleg alcohol over the counter.
What about it, old sport?
Don't you call me 'old sport'!
And this drugstore business
is just small change
compared to this bonds stunt that
you and Wolfsheim have got going.
Your friend Walter Chase
isn't too proud to come in on it.
I was giving it lots of thoughts.
How does a reputable
banker like Walter Chase,
find himself up to his eyeballs in debt—
— I'll tell you how.
— to a little kike like Wolfsheim?
— It's called greed, old sport.
— That's right.
And you have half of Wall Street
out there swilling your free booze,
at that fun park every weekend.
I'm surprised he hasn't
tried to drag you in.
My God, he has.
— He's got nothing to do with—
— with your odd little racket.
Daisy?
Daisy!
Can't you see who this guy is?
With his house. And his parties.
And his fancy clothes.
He's just a front for Wolfsheim,
a gangster,
to get his claws into respectable
folks like Walter Chase.
The only respectable thing about you,
old sport, is your money.
Your money, that's it.
I have just as much as you,
that means we're equal.
Oh, no! No.
We're different.
I am, they are, she is.
We're all different from you.
You see, we were born different.
It's in our blood.
And nothing that
you could do, say, or steal,
or dream up, can ever change that.
A girl like Daisy—
You shut up! Shut up!
Gatsby looked in that moment
as if he had killed a man.
My… My sincerest…
My sincerest apologies.
I seem to… have lost my temper.
That's right, Mr. Gatsby.
You showed us some of those
fine Oxford manners.
Daisy, darling.
None of this has… any consequence, I—
Daisy.
Daisy, talk to me, darling.
I just lost my temper, that's all.
He began talking excitedly.
But with every word, Daisy was drawing
further and further into herself.
…to go to your parents' house
in Louisville.
Please, Tom,
I can't stand it anymore!
Why don't you two start on home,
in Mr. Gatsby's car.
— Daisy, darling, look at me.
— Go on.
— Daisy.
— He won't annoy you.
I think he realizes that this
little flirtation is over.
Daisy? Daisy!
Do you want any of this?
Jordan? Nick?
— Nick?
— What?
— You want any?
— No.
I just remembered…
today is my birthday.
Happy birthday.
Thirty. The promise
of a decade of loneliness.
The formidable stroke
of thirty died away…
as Gatsby and Daisy drove on
through the cooling twilight…
towards death.
Don't you lie to me!
Where did you get this from?
You might fool me, but you don't fool God!
God sees everything!
Myrtle! Where are you?
Stop! Stop!
— Myrtle! Baby!
— Stop!
Please!
Slow down! Slow down!
Bad trouble up ahead, sir!
Good! Wilson will have
a little business at last.
Let's take a look.
— Oh, must we?
Just a look.
Come on!
Move back! Clear the space here!
Have a little respect!
If you don't have a legitimate reason to
be in the building, I want you outside!
If you saw anything tonight
you'd like to talk to me about,
well, then you can talk to me outside.
I don't want you in here. Okay?
Please. Stand back. Please.
Oh God.
All right, folks. Make some room, huh?
Make some room back there!
If you have no business, clear out!
Sir?
What are you doing? Sir!
Sir, I'm asking you to—
— Get off me!
I'm fine!
I'm fine.
You knew her, eh?
Not really. No.
I gotta ask you to step back, sir.
So what happened?
She ran out in the road.
Sonofabitch didn't even stop his car.
Hey! I saw it. It was a yellow car.
A big yellow car.
The damn thing came out of nowhere.
Yeah. Yeah, big yellow Duesy.
Custom job.
You have to tell me what
kind of car it was.
I know what kind of car it was.
— Wilson. Wilson, pull yourself together!
— I know what kind of car it was!
He's upset!
Everybody out!
Can't you see the man
needs peace and quiet! Listen!
Wilson! I just—
I just got here from New York.
Enough! Hey, Wilson!
I was bringing you the coupé.
Sit down, sit down!
Give him a drink!
That yellow car wasn't mine.
D'you hear?
I haven't seen it all afternoon.
Hey!
What color is your car?
It's blue.
Coupé.
We just got here from New York.
Yeah, they just stopped.
Okay.
Blue.
Here.
Leave us alone.
Wilson.
Who owns the yellow car?
A fella named Gatsby.
Jay Gatsby.
He's a crook, George. Yes…
throws all those parties the papers
are always talking about.
Maybe he was the one that was
fooling around with Myrtle.
Maybe that's why he killed her!
Yeah, maybe.
A guy like that, who knows?
He didn't have to kill her.
Gatsby.
Something ought to be done
about a fella like that.
He'll pay.
Oh, he will pay.
Coward!
He didn't even stop his car.
You're gonna defend him now?
I'll telephone for a taxi, Nick.
Why don't you come inside
and have some supper while you wait?
No thanks. I'll wait outside.
What is the matter with you?
— Won't you come in, Nick.
— No Thanks .
— It's only half past nine.
— No, I've had enough! Of everyone.
Hello, old sport.
What are you doing?
— Just sitting here.
— Yes, I see that!
Did you see any trouble out on the road?
That woman you ran down is dead, Jay!
I thought so, I…
I told Daisy that I thought so.
It's better that the shock—
— Daisy?
— …should all come at once.
— Do you hear yourself?
How could you?
How could you do that?
— Keep your voice down!
— What's wrong with you?
You're nothing but a goddamn coward!
Keep your voice down, please!
There was no point in stop—
No point ? No point!
What about that woman?
No point. She was— she was—
she was killed instantly.
Yes, it ripped her open!
I was there, I saw it!
I understand! I understand you.
It was my fault!
It was my fault, this woman,
she rushed out at us as if she was—
See, she was trying to speak to us,
it all happened so quickly!
She tried—
I tried to turn in time, but—
— She?
That was Daisy?!
No, I…
You see, after we left
New York, she was…
she was very nervous, she thought…
that driving would steady her.
But… this woman, she rushed out at us.
It all happened so quickly.
It wasn't her fault, d'you see?
No one must know that Daisy was driving.
Promise me.
Jay.
You should go home
and get some rest.
I'm going to wait here.
I'm gonna wait here
all night, if necessary.
No, no, no. That's not a good idea.
If he tries to bother her about
that unpleasantness this afternoon,
if he tries to bother her,
if he tries any brutality—
— Wait!
— on her, whatsoever,
— Tom— Tom won't touch her,
— He's not even thinking about her, Jay.
— I don't trust him.
I don't trust him.
— Alright. Alright.
You wait here.
I'll see if there's any commotion.
Would you?
Thank you, old sport.
Listen, she was in the wrong,
running out on the road.
Sweetheart, you have
nothing to worry about.
Let me take care of things.
Take care of you.
I'll make some calls.
We'll go away.
Just go away, get out of town.
Get some rest. Don't worry.
It'll be alright.
— Hello, old sport.
— Jay.
— Is everything alright?
— Yes. Everything's just fine.
At four o'clock, she—
she came at the window.
She stood there, then…
she turned out the lights, so…
Well…
Give me a hand, will you, old sport?
I should have told him
what I had just seen, but…
All I could manage was:
You know Jay, with everything that's
happened, you ought to go away.
Tonight. They'll trace your car.
Go away? No. I can't leave now.
Not tonight.
Jay, do you understand that
a woman has been killed?
Daisy's gonna call in the morning.
Then we'll make plans,
to go away together.
Uh, Daisy, she—
She just needs time
to think things through.
Herzog! We're talking. Thank you.
She just needs time to think—
— No, Jay… Daisy—
She just needs time to think,
she's going to call in the morning.
Wait up with me.
The sun's almost up.
That was the night he
finally told me the truth.
All of it.
You know, I thought for a while
I had a lot of things, but…
the truth is I'm…
I'm empty.
I suppose that's why I make
things up about myself,
but I wanted to tell you the whole
story for a very long time.
You see, I grew up terribly,
terribly poor, old sport.
My folks were…
— He revealed his humble beginnings,
his transformative voyage with Dan Cody.
The war, Oxford, and how
he joined Wolfsheim in the business.
That was also that night that I became aware
of Gatsby's extraordinary gift for hope.
I can't describe how surprised I was
to find out that I loved her, old sport,
and that she loved me too.
A gift that I have never found
in any other person…
I never realized how extraordinary
a nice girl could be.
…and which it is not likely
I shall ever find again.
I thought out my life with Daisy in it,
trying to figure out how we could marry,
and struggle along on
so many dollars a month.
What was in the letter?
The reason why after the war, I…
I hadn't been able to return.
I asked her to wait until I made
something of myself. But she was…
See, I felt married to her.
That was all.
It was all for her. The house,
the parties. Everything.
God sees everything.
Mr. Gatsby, sir, excuse me.
— Chicago called, it's—
— Not now.
— Keep it open for a personal call.
— A personal call? Of course.
Excuse me sir, Mr. Gatsby,
I'm gonna drain the pool today,
before the leaves start falling in.
Not today.
Not today. It's so beautiful.
You know, old sport…
I haven't used that pool once all summer.
Let's take a swim.
Have the phone brought down to the pool.
I have to go, Jay.
I have to work.
— I understand.
Well. I'll walk you out.
— Well, I'll call you up.
— Please do, old sport. Please do.
I suppose that Daisy will call too.
I… Well I suppose.
Yes.
Well. Goodbye.
Jay?
They're a rotten crowd.
You're worth the whole
damn bunch put together.
I was always glad I said that.
It was the only compliment
I ever paid him.
That morning, Wall Street
boomed its usual golden roar.
But I wasn't worth
a decent stroke of work.
And I waited for Gatsby
to call with news…
while he waited for Daisy.
Gatsby's?
I know Mr. Gatsby will be
very happy that you've called.
Daisy…
Hello ? Hello?
Hello, is everything all right?
Hello? Hello?
I remember the rest of that day
as an endless drill of police
and photographers and tabloid reporters.
The headlines were a nightmare.
They pinned everything on Gatsby.
The affair with Myrtle,
the hit and run, everything.
And there was nothing I could say,
except the one unutterable fact
that none of it was true.
Darling, Daddy's taking care
of his two favorite girls.
— Where are we going?
— We're going on a holiday.
— We should go.
— Just you, me and Daddy.
Buchanan residence.
May I speak to Mrs. Buchanan?
It's Mr. Carraway, her cousin.
Madame is not available,
Monsieur Carraway.
If you speak to her, tell her
the funeral's tomorrow.
I'm sorry, Monsieur.
They have gone away.
Gone away! Do you know
when they'll be back?
No. They have already departed.
Please. I know that she would
want to be there, she would—
If you'd just get a message to her,
let me talk to her, please.
You wish to contact her…
I have no further information, Monsieur.
— Please!
— Αu revoir.
I…
Hello?
They were careless people, Tom and Daisy.
They smashed up things and people,
and then retreated back into their
money and their vast carelessness.
Hey! Hey!
Get out of here!
Go on! Get the hell out of here!
I rang, I wrote, I implored.
But not a single one of the sparkling
hundreds that enjoyed his hospitality,
attended the funeral.
And from Daisy…
not even a flower.
I was all he had.
The only one who cared.
After Gatsby's death,
New York was haunted for me.
That city…
my once golden shimmering mirage…
now made me sick.
On my last night in New York,
I returned to that huge
incoherent house once more.
Wolfsheim Associates had cleaned it out.
He threw all those parties,
hoping she would wander in one night.
It's like an amusement park!
How do you live here all alone?
She makes it look so— so splendid,
don't you think, old sport?
Music! And then we can dance all night.
Will you come, old sport?
We need you.
I wish it could always be like this.
It will be.
I remembered how we had all come to
Gatsby's and guessed at his corruption,
while he stood before us,
concealing an incorruptible dream.
It's perfect. From your perfect
irresistible imagination.
The moon rose higher.
And as I stood there,
brooding on an old unknown world,
I thought of Gatsby's wonder when
he first picked out the green light
at the end of Daisy's dock.
He had come such a long way,
and his dream must have seemed so close
that he could hardly fail to grasp it…
But he did not know that
it was already behind him.
Gatsby believed in the green light,
the orgastic future that year
by year recedes before us.
It eluded us then,
but that's no matter.
Tomorrow we will run faster,
stretch out our arms farther…
And one fine morning—
So we beat on,
boats against the current,
borne back ceaselessly
into the past.
Transcript and sync: jcdr
V3 — 10.10.2013