I beIieve in America.
America has made my fortune.
And I raised my daughter
in the American fashion.
I gave her freedom, but I taught her
never to dishonour her famiIy.
She found a boyfriend, not an ItaIian.
She went to the movies with him.
She stayed out Iate.
I didn't protest.
Two months ago he took her for a drive
with another boyfriend.
They made her drink whiskey
and then they tried to
take advantage of her.
She resisted, she kept her honour.
So they beat her Iike an animaI.
When I went to the hospitaI,
her nose was broken,
her jaw was shattered,
heId together by wire.
She couIdn't even weep
because of the pain.
But I wept. Why did I weep?
She was the Iight of my Iife.
BeautifuI girI.
Now she wiII never be beautifuI again.
Sorry.
I went to the poIice,
Iike a good American.
These two boys were brought to triaI.
The judge sentenced them to three years
in prison, but suspended the sentence.
Suspended the sentence!
They went free that very day!
I stood in the courtroom Iike a fooI.
Those two bastards, they smiIed at me.
Then I said to my wife, "For justice,
we must go to Don CorIeone."
Why did you go to the poIice?
Why didn't you come to me first?
What do you want of me? TeII me
anything, but do what I beg you to do.
What is that?
I want them dead.
That I cannot do.
I'II give you anything you ask.
I've known you many years, but this
is the first time you've asked for heIp.
I can't remember the Iast time
you invited me for a cup of coffee.
Even though my wife is godmother
to your onIy chiId.
But Iet's be frank here.
You never wanted my friendship.
And you were afraid to be in my debt.
I didn't want to get into troubIe.
I understand.
You found Paradise in America.
You made a good Iiving, had poIice
protection and there were courts of Iaw.
You didn't need a friend Iike me.
But now you come to me and say,
"Don CorIeone, give me justice."
But you don't ask with respect.
You don't offer friendship. You don't
even think to caII me Godfather.
You come on my daughter's wedding
day and ask me to murder for money.
I ask you for justice.
That is not justice.
Your daughter is aIive.
Let them suffer, then, as she suffers.
How much shaII I pay you?
Bonasera, Bonasera.
What have I ever done to make you
treat me so disrespectfuIIy?
If you'd come in friendship,
the scum that ruined your daughter
wouId be suffering this very day.
And if an honest man Iike you shouId
make enemies, they'd be my enemies.
And then they wouId fear you.
Be my friend?
Godfather?
Good.
Some day, and that day may never
come, I'II ask a service of you.
But untiI that day...
...accept this justice as a gift
on my daughter's wedding day.
- Grazie, Godfather.
- Prego.
Give this to CIemenza.
I want peopIe that aren't going to
get carried away.
We're not murderers,
in spite of what this undertaker says.
- Where's MichaeI?
- Don't worry, he'II be here.
We're not taking the picture
without MichaeI.
- What's the matter?
- It's MichaeI.
Don Barzini.
Hey, PauIie! Let me have some wine.
PauIie! More wine.
- You Iook terrific on the fIoor.
- Are you a dance judge or something?
Take a waIk and do your job.
Sandra, watch the kids.
Don't Iet them run wiId.
You watch yourseIf, aII right?
20, 30 grand. In smaII biIIs, cash.
In that IittIe siIk purse.
If this were somebody eIse's wedding...
Sfortunato!
Hey, PauIie!
Stupid jerk!
What's the matter?
- Have to go back to work.
- Tom.
No SiciIian can refuse any request
on his daughter's wedding day.
Don CorIeone, I'm honoured and
gratefuI that you have invited me.
Get out of here!
It's a private party. Go on!
What is it? It's my sister's wedding.
Goddamn FBI don't respect nothing!
Come here, come here, come here!
...but towards the end, he was paroIed
to heIp with the American war effort,
so for six months he's worked
in my pastry shop.
Nazorine, what can I do for you?
Now that the war is over,
this boy, Enzo, they want to
repatriate him back to ItaIy.
Godfather, I have a daughter.
You see, she and Enzo...
You want Enzo to stay in this country,
and your daughter to be married.
You understand everything.
Mr Hagen. Thank you.
Wait tiII you see the wedding cake
I made for your daughter!
The bride, the groom and the angeI...
- Who shouId I give this job to?
- Not to our paisà.
Give it to a Jew Congressman in
another district. Who eIse is on the Iist?
Hey, MichaeI!
He's not on the Iist,
but Luca Brasi wants to see you.
Is this necessary?
He didn't expect to be invited to the
wedding, so he wanted to thank you.
Don CorIeone, I'm honoured and
gratefuI that you have invited me
on the wedding day of your daughter.
May their first chiId be a mascuIine chiId.
MichaeI...
That man over there
is taIking to himseIf.
See that scary guy over there?
- He's a very scary guy.
- What's his name?
His name is Luca Brasi.
He heIps my father out sometimes.
MichaeI, he's coming over here!
You Iook terrific!
My brother Tom Hagen,
Miss Kay Adams.
Your father's been asking for you.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Why does your brother
have a different name?
My brother Sonny found Tom Hagen
in the street.
He had no home,
so my father took him in.
He's been with us ever since.
He's a good Iawyer.
Not a SiciIian. I think he's
going to be consigliere.
- What's that?
- That's a...
...Iike a counseIIor, an advisor.
Very important for the famiIy.
You Iike your Iasagne?
Don CorIeone.
I'm honoured and gratefuI
that you have invited me
to your daughter's wedding.
On the day of your daughter's wedding.
And I hope that their first chiId
wiII be a mascuIine chiId.
I pIedge my ever-ending IoyaIty.
- For your daughter's bridaI purse.
- Thank you, Luca. Most vaIued friend.
Don CorIeone, I'm going to Ieave you
now, because I know you're busy.
Thank you.
Signora CorIeone!
No!
Senator CauIey apoIogised for not
coming, but said you'd understand.
AIso some of the judges.
They've aII sent gifts.
What is that outside?
Johnny! Johnny!
I Iove you!
He came aII the way from CaIifornia.
I toId you he'd come!
- He's probabIy in troubIe again.
- He's a good godson.
Johnny, Johnny! Sing a song!
You never said you knew
Johnny Fontane!
- Sure. You want to meet him?
- Great! Sure.
- My father heIped him with his career.
- He did?
How?
- Let's Iisten to this song.
- MichaeI...
PIease, MichaeI. TeII me.
When Johnny was starting out, he was
signed to a personaI service contract
with a big bandIeader.
And as his career got better and better,
he wanted to get out of it.
Johnny is my father's godson.
My father went to see this bandIeader.
He offered him 10,000 doIIars
to Iet Johnny go,
but the bandIeader said no.
So the next day my father went to see
him, but this time with Luca Brasi.
Within an hour,
he signed a reIease
for a certified cheque of 1,000 doIIars.
- How did he do that?
- Made him an offer he couIdn't refuse.
- What was that?
- Luca Brasi heId a gun to his head,
and father said that either his brains or
his signature wouId be on the contract.
That's a true story.
That's my famiIy, Kay. It's not me.
BeautifuI!
I'II take care of it.
Tom...
I want you to find Santino.
TeII him to come to the office.
How are you, Fredo?
My brother Fredo,
this is Kay Adams.
- Hi.
- How are you doing?
- This is my brother Mike.
- Are you having a good time?
Yeah. This is your friend?
I don't know what to do.
My voice is weak. It's weak.
Anyway, if I had this part in the picture,
it puts me right back on top again.
But this... man won't give it to me,
the head of the studio.
- What's his name?
- WoItz.
He won't give it to me,
and he says there's no chance.
Sonny?
- Sonny, are you in there?
- What?
The oId man wants you.
One minute.
A month ago he bought the movie rights
to this book, a best-seIIer.
The main character
is a guy just Iike me.
I wouIdn't even have to act.
Godfather, I don't know what to do.
You can act Iike a man!
What's the matter with you?
Is this how you turned out a HoIIywood
finocchio, that cries Iike a woman?
"What can I do? What can I do?"
What is that nonsense?
RidicuIous.
- You spend time with your famiIy?
- Sure I do.
Good.
Because a man who doesn't spend time
with his famiIy can never be a reaI man.
You Iook terribIe. I want you to eat.
Rest, and in a month this HoIIywood
big shot wiII give you what you want.
It's too Iate, they start shooting
in a week.
I'm going to make him an offer
he can't refuse.
Just go outside and enjoy yourseIf,
and forget about aII this nonsense.
- I want you to Ieave it aII to me.
- AII right.
- What time does my daughter Ieave?
- Soon, after they cut the cake.
Do we give your son-in-Iaw
something important?
Never. Give him a Iiving, but never
discuss the famiIy business with him.
- What eIse?
- VirgiI SoIIozzo caIIed.
- We'II have to see him next week.
- When you come back from CaIifornia.
- When am I going to CaIifornia?
- Tonight.
I want you to taIk to this movie big shot
and settIe this business for Johnny.
If there's nothing eIse, I'd Iike to go
to my daughter's wedding.
CarIo, we're going to take the picture.
Wait a minute.
No, MichaeI. Not me.
Okay, that's it. Just Iike that. HoId it!
- You need a IittIe more heat on that arc.
- Start taIking.
I was sent by a friend
of Johnny Fontane.
This friend wouId give
his friendship to Mr WoItz,
if Mr WoItz wouId grant us a favour.
WoItz is Iistening.
Give Johnny the part in that war fiIm
you're starting next week.
And what favour wouId your friend
grant Mr WoItz?
He couId make your future union
probIems disappear.
And one of your stars has just moved
from marijuana to heroin.
Are you trying to muscIe me?
Listen, you son-of-a-bitch!
Let me Iay it on the Iine. Johnny
Fontane wiII never get that movie!
No matter how many Dago Guinea
greasebaIIs come out of the woodwork!
- I'm German-Irish.
- Listen here, my Kraut-Mick friend.
- I'm going to make troubIe for you!
- I'm a Iawyer. I haven't threatened...
I know New York's big Iawyers.
Who are you?
I have a speciaI practice. I handIe
one cIient. I'II wait for your caII.
By the way, I admire your pictures
very much.
Check him out.
- It's reaIIy beautifuI.
- Look at this.
- It used to decorate a king's paIace.
- Very nice.
Why didn't you say
you work for CorIeone?
I thought you were some cheap hustIer
Johnny was running in.
- I onIy use his name when necessary.
- How's your drink?
- Fine.
- Now I'II show you something beautifuI.
You do appreciate beauty, don't you?
There you are.
600,000 doIIars on four hoofs.
I bet Russian czars never paid
that for a singIe horse.
Khartoum.
I'm not going to race him, though.
I'm going to put him out to stud.
Thanks, Tony.
Let's get something to eat.
CorIeone is Johnny's godfather.
To the ItaIian peopIe that's
a very sacred, cIose reIationship.
I respect it. TeII him to ask me anything
eIse. This favour I can't give him.
He never asks a second favour
when he's been refused the first.
You don't understand. Johnny Fontane
never gets that movie.
That part is perfect for him.
It'II make him a big star.
I'm going to run him out of the business,
and Iet me teII you why.
Johnny Fontane ruined one of WoItz
InternationaI's most vaIuabIe protégés.
We trained her for five years.
Singing, acting, dancing Iessons.
I spent hundreds of thousands of doIIars
on her, to make her a big star.
Let me be even more frank.
To show you that I'm not a hard-hearted
man. That it's not aII doIIars and cents.
She was beautifuI.
She was young and innocent!
She's the greatest piece of ass I've had
and I've had them aII over the worId.
Then Johnny Fontane comes aIong with
his oIive oiI voice and Guinea charm.
And she runs off.
She threw it aII away
just to make me Iook ridicuIous!
And a man in my position can't afford
to be made to Iook ridicuIous!
You get the heII out of here!
If that goombah tries any rough stuff,
teII him I'm no bandIeader.
Yeah, I heard that story.
Thank you for dinner
and a very pIeasant evening.
Maybe your car can take me
to the airport.
Mr CorIeone insists on hearing
bad news immediateIy.
- You're not too tired, are you, Tom?
- No, I sIept on the pIane.
I have the SoIIozzo notes here.
Now...
SoIIozzo is known as The Turk. He's
supposed to be very good with a knife,
but only in matters of business
with reasonable complaint.
His business is narcotics.
He has fields in Turkey,
where they grow poppy.
ln Sicily he has plants to process them
into heroin.
He needs cash, he needs protection
from the police.
He'll give a piece of the action.
l don't know how much.
The Tattaglia family is behind him here.
They have to be in it for something.
- What about his prison record?
- One term in ItaIy, one here.
He's known as a top narcotics man.
- Santino, what do you think?
- A Iot of money in that white powder.
Tom?
Yes. There's more money in narcotics
than anything else.
lf we don't get into it, somebody else
will, maybe the five families.
With that money they can buy
more poIice and poIiticaI power.
Then they come after us.
Now we have unions and gambIing, and
that's great, but narcotics is the future.
If we don't get a piece of that action,
we risk everything in ten years' time.
So? What's your answer
going to be, Pop?
Don CorIeone.
I need a man who has powerfuI friends.
I need a miIIion doIIars in cash.
I need those poIiticians that you carry
in your pocket, Iike nickeIs and dimes.
- What is the interest for my famiIy?
- 30 per cent.
In the first year your end shouId be
three, four miIIion doIIars.
And then it wouId go up.
And what is the interest
for the TattagIia famiIy?
My compIiments.
I'II take care of them, out of my share.
So I receive 30 per cent for finance,
poIiticaI infIuence and IegaI protection?
That's right.
Why do you come to me?
Why do I deserve this generosity?
If you consider a miIIion doIIars in cash
just finance,
ti saluto, Don CorIeone.
I said that I wouId see you, because
I heard you were a serious man,
to be treated with respect.
But, I must say no to you.
And I'II give you my reason.
It's true, I have a Iot of friends in poIitics.
They wouIdn't be friendIy Iong if I was
invoIved in drugs instead of gambIing,
which they regard as a harmIess vice,
but drugs is a dirty business.
It doesn't make any difference to me
what a man does for a Iiving.
But your business is...
a IittIe dangerous.
If you're worried about security,
the TattagIias wiII guarantee it.
- The TattagIias wouId guarantee our...
- Wait a minute.
I have a sentimentaI weakness
for my chiIdren, and I spoiI them.
They taIk when they shouId Iisten.
But anyway...
Signor SoIIozzo, my no is finaI. I wish to
congratuIate you on your new business.
I know you'II do weII, and good Iuck.
EspeciaIIy since your interests
don't confIict with mine. Thank you.
Santino.
Come here.
What's the matter with you? Your brain
is going soft from pIaying with that girI.
Never teII anybody outside the famiIy
what you're thinking again.
Go on.
Tom, what's this nonsense?
It's from Johnny.
He's starring in that new fiIm.
- Take it away.
- Take it over there.
And...
...teII Luca Brasi to come in.
I'm a IittIe worried
about this SoIIozzo feIIow.
Find out what he's got
under his fingernaiIs.
Go to the TattagIias.
Make them think that you're not
too happy with our famiIy
and find out what you can.
I got something for your mother
and for Sonny
and a tie for Freddy,
and Tom Hagen got the ReynoIds pen.
- What do you want for Christmas?
- Just you.
Andiamo, Fredo.
- TeII PauIie to get the car.
- Okay, Pop.
I'II have to get it myseIf.
PauIie caIIed in sick this morning.
PauIie's a good kid.
I don't mind getting the car.
Buon Natale, caro. Grazie.
- Luca! I'm Bruno TattagIia.
- I know.
You know who I am?
I know you.
You have been taIking to the
TattagIia famiIy...right?
I think you and I can do business.
I need someone strong Iike you.
I heard you are not happy...
...with the CorIeone famiIy.
Want to join me?
What's in it for me?
$50,000 to start with.
Not bad!
Agreed?
Tom! Tom Hagen. Merry Christmas.
- GIad to see you. I want to taIk to you.
- I haven't got time.
Make time, Consigliere. Get in the car.
What are you worried about? If I wanted
to kiII you, you'd be dead aIready.
Get in.
- Fredo, I'm going to buy some fruit.
- Okay, Pop.
Merry Christmas. I want some fruit.
WouId you Iike me better
if I were a nun? Like in the story.
No.
- What if I were Ingrid Bergman?
- Now, that's a thought.
MichaeI.
No, I wouIdn't Iike you better if you were
Ingrid Bergman. What's the matter?
They don't say if he's dead or aIive.
- Sonny, it's MichaeI.
- Where have you been?
- Is he aII right?
- We don't know yet.
There are all kinds of stories.
He was hit bad, Mikey.
- Are you there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Where have you been? l was worried.
- Didn't Tom teII you I caIIed?
No. Look, come home, kid.
You should be with Mama, you hear?
Oh, my God.
Sonny!
Stay back there.
- Who is it?
- Open up, it's CIemenza.
There's more news about your oId man.
Word is out that he's aIready dead.
- What's the matter with you?
- Take it easy!
- Where was PauIie?
- Sick. He's been sick aII winter.
- How often?
- OnIy three, four times.
- Freddy didn't want a new bodyguard.
- Pick him up now.
I don't care how sick he is. Bring him
to my father's house right now.
- You want anyone sent over here?
- No. Go ahead.
I'm going to have a coupIe of our peopIe
come over to the house.
- HeIIo?
- Santino Corleone?
- Yeah.
- We have Tom Hagen.
ln three hours he'll be released
with our proposition.
Listen to what he has to say
before you do anything.
What's done is done. Don't lose that
famous temper of yours, Sonny.
I'II wait.
Your boss is dead.
I know you're not in the muscIe end
of the famiIy, so don't be scared.
I want you to heIp the CorIeones
and me.
We got him outside his office
about an hour after we picked you up.
Drink it.
It's up to you to make peace
between me and Sonny.
Sonny was hot for my deaI, wasn't he?
And you knew
it was the right thing to do.
- Sonny wiII come after you.
- That wiII be his first reaction, sure.
So you have to taIk sense into him.
The TattagIia famiIy is behind me.
The other New York famiIies wiII go
aIong with anything to prevent war.
Let's face it, with aII due respect,
the Don - rest in peace - was sIipping.
Ten years ago,
couId I have gotten to him?
WeII, now he's dead, Tom,
and nothing can bring him back.
You've got to taIk to Sonny, to the
Caporegimes, Tessio, fat CIemenza.
It's good business, Tom.
I'II try. But even Sonny won't be abIe
to caII off Luca Brasi.
Yeah, weII...
Let me worry about Luca.
You just taIk to Sonny.
And the other two kids.
- I'II do my best.
- Good.
Now you can go.
I don't Iike vioIence, Tom.
I'm a businessman.
BIood is a big expense.
He's stiII aIive.
They hit him with five shots,
and he's stiII aIive!
That's bad Iuck for me, and bad Iuck
for you if you don't make that deaI.
Your mother is at the hospitaI with
your father. Looks Iike he'II puII through.
It's a Iot of bad bIood. SoIIozzo, PhiIip
TattagIia, Bruno TattagIia, Ramon...
- You gonna kiII aII those guys?
- Stay out of it.
If you get rid of SoIIozzo,
everything faIIs into Iine.
What about Luca?
SoIIozzo thinks he can controI him.
If Luca soId out, we're in a Iot of troubIe.
- Has anyone been in touch with Luca?
- We've been trying aII night.
- Hey, do me a favour...
- Luca never sIeeps over with a broad.
WeII, Tom, you're consigliere.
What do we do if the oId man dies?
If we Iose the oId man, we Iose the
poIiticaI contacts and haIf our strength.
The other New York famiIies might
support SoIIozzo to avoid a Iong war.
This is aImost ¨1 946.
Nobody wants bIoodshed anymore.
If your father dies...
...you make the deaI.
- Easy to say. He's not your father.
- I'm as much a son as you or Mike.
What is it?
- PauIie, I toId you to stay put.
- The guy at the gates has a package.
Tessio, go see what it is.
- ShaII I stay?
- Yeah. Are you aII right?
- I'm fine.
- There's food. Are you hungry?
- No.
- A drink? Brandy wiII sweat it out.
- Go ahead.
- That might be a good idea.
Take care of that son-of-a-bitch.
PauIie soId out the oId man.
- Make that the first thing on your Iist.
- Understood.
Mickey, tomorrow, get some guys
and go to Luca's apartment.
Maybe we shouIdn't get Mike
mixed up in this too directIy.
Hanging around the house on
the phone wouId be a big heIp.
Try Luca again.
- What's this?
- A SiciIian message.
It means Luca Brasi
sIeeps with the fishes.
- I'm going.
- When wiII you be home?
ProbabIy Iate.
- Don't forget the cannoli!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Rocco, sit on the other side.
You bIock the rear-view mirror.
Sonny's running wiId. He wants
to go to mattresses aIready.
We have to find a spot on the
West Side. Try 309 West 43rd Street.
- Know a good spot on the West Side?
- I'II think about it.
Think whiIe you're driving.
I want to hit New York this month.
Watch the kids.
PauIie, go down 39th Street, pick up
¨1 8 mattresses and bring me the biII.
Yeah, aII right.
Make sure they're cIean, because
the guys wiII be there a Iong time.
- They're cIean and exterminated.
- That's a bad word to use.
Exterminate! Watch out,
so we don't exterminate you!
PuII over. I've got to take a Ieak.
Leave the gun. Take the cannoli.
Hey, Mike! Hey, Mikey!
- Yeah.
- Phone caII!
- Who is it?
- Some girI.
- HeIIo. Kay?
- How's your father?
He's going to make it.
l love you.
l love you!
- Michael?
- Yeah, I know.
- Tell me you love me.
- I can't taIk.
Can't you say it?
I'II see you tonight.
Why don't you teII that nice girI
you Iove her?
I Iove you with aII my heart. If I don't
see you again soon, I'm going to die!
Come and Iearn something. You might
have to cook for 20 guys some day.
You start with a IittIe oiI,
then fry some garIic.
Throw in some tomatoes, tomato paste,
fry it and make sure it doesn't stick.
You get it to a boiI, you shove in
aII your sausage and meatbaIIs.
Add a IittIe bit of wine.
And a IittIe bit of sugar. That's my trick.
Cut the crap. I have more important
things for you. How's PauIie?
You won't see him anymore.
- Where are you going?
- To the city.
- Send bodyguards with him.
- I'm going to the hospitaI...
He'II be aII right. SoIIozzo knows
he's a civiIian.
- Be carefuI.
- Yes, sir.
Send somebody with him anyway.
- I have to go.
- Can I go with you?
No, Kay. There wiII be detectives there,
peopIe from the press.
I'II wait in the cab.
I don't want you to get invoIved.
When wiII I see you again?
Go back to New Hampshire, and I'II
caII you at your parents' house.
- When wiII I see you again, MichaeI?
- I don't know.
What are you doing here?
You're not supposed to be here.
I'm MichaeI CorIeone. This is my father.
What happened to the guards?
Your father had too many visitors.
They interfered with hospitaI service.
The poIice made them Ieave
about ten minutes ago.
Get me Long Beach 45620, pIease.
Nurse. Wait a minute. Stay here.
Sonny, I'm at the hospitaI.
I got here Iate, there's nobody here.
No Tessio's men, no detectives,
nobody. Papa's aII aIone.
- Don't panic.
- I won't panic.
I'm sorry, but you wiII have to Ieave.
We're going to move him to another
room. Can you disconnect the tubes?
- That's out of the question!
- Do you know my father?
Men are coming here to kiII him.
Do you understand?
HeIp me, pIease.
- Who are you?
- I am Enzo, the baker.
- Remember me?
- Enzo.
You'd better go,
there's going to be troubIe.
If there is troubIe, I'II stay here to
heIp you. For your father.
Listen. Wait for me outside,
in front of the hospitaI, aII right?
I'II be out in a minute.
Just Iie here, Pop.
I'II take care of you now.
I'm with you now.
I'm with you.
Get rid of these. Come here.
Put your hand in your pocket, Iike you
have a gun. You'II be aII right.
You did good.
I thought aII you Guinea hoods
were Iocked up!
- Why isn't anyone guarding my father?
- You IittIe punk!
Don't you teII me my business!
I puIIed them off.
- Stay away from this hospitaI!
- Not untiI my father's room is guarded.
- PhiI, take him in!
- The kid's cIean, Captain.
- He's a war hero. He's never been...
- I said take him in!
- What's The Turk paying you?
- Take a hoId of him. Stand him up.
Stand him up straight.
I'm the CorIeone's attorney. These men
are hired to protect Vito CorIeone.
They're Iicensed to carry firearms.
If you interfere, you'II have to appear
before the judge and show cause.
Let him go.
- What's with aII the new faces?
- We'II need them now.
After the hospitaI thing, Sonny got mad.
We hit Bruno TattagIia this morning.
Jesus Christ.
Looks Iike a fortress around here.
Tommasuccio! Hey... ¨1 00 buttonmen
on the street 24 hours a day.
That Turk shows one hair on his ass,
he's dead.
Mike, Iet me Iook at you.
You're beautifuI, beautifuI.
You're gorgeous.
The Turk wants to taIk! Imagine
the nerve of the son-of-a-bitch.
- He wants a meeting today.
- What did he say?
What did he say... He wants us to send
MichaeI to hear the proposition.
He promises that the deaI
is too good to refuse.
- And Bruno TattagIia?
- That's part of the deaI.
- He canceIs out what they did to Father.
- We shouId Iisten to them.
No more! Not this time, Consigliere.
No more meetings, discussions,
or SoIIozzo tricks.
I want SoIIozzo, or we go to war...
- The other famiIies...
- They hand me SoIIozzo!
This is business, not personaI!
- They shot my father...
- Even that was business, not personaI.
Then business wiII have to suffer.
Do me a favour.
No more advice on how to
patch things up. Just heIp me win.
I found out about Captain McCIuskey,
who broke Mike's jaw.
He's definiteIy on SoIIozzo's payroII,
and for big money.
McCIuskey has agreed to be
The Turk's bodyguard.
So when SoIIozzo is being guarded,
he's invuInerabIe.
Nobody has ever gunned down
a New York poIice captain.
AII the famiIies wouId come after you.
The CorIeone famiIy wouId be outcasts!
Even the oId man's poIiticaI protection
wouId run for cover.
Do me a favour.
Take this into consideration.
AII right, we'II wait.
We can't wait. We can't wait.
No matter what SoIIozzo says,
he's going to kiII Pop.
That's the key for him.
We've got to get SoIIozzo.
- Mike is right.
- Let me ask you something.
What about this McCIuskey?
What do we do with this cop?
They want to have a meeting
with me, right?
It wiII be me, McCIuskey and SoIIozzo.
Let's set the meeting.
Get our informers to find out
where it's going to be heId.
We insist it's a pubIic pIace.
A bar, a restaurant.
Some pIace where there are peopIe,
so I feeI safe.
They'II search me when I meet them,
right?
So I can't have a weapon on me.
But if CIemenza can figure out a way to
have a weapon pIanted there for me...
...then I'II kiII them both.
Nice coIIege boy. Didn't want to
get mixed up in the famiIy business.
Now you want to shoot a poIice captain
because he sIapped you?
This isn't Iike the army! You have to get
cIose and get their brains on your suit.
You're taking this very personaI.
Tom, this is business
and he's taking it personaI.
- Where does it say you can't kiII a cop?
- Mikey...
I'm taIking about a cop who's mixed up
in drugs, a dishonest cop.
A cop who got mixed up in the rackets
and got what was coming.
That's a terrific story. We have
newspaper peopIe on the payroII, right?
- They might Iike a story Iike that.
- They might.
It's not personaI, Sonny.
It's strictIy business.
It's as coId as they come. ImpossibIe to
trace, so you don't worry about prints.
I put a speciaI tape on the trigger
and the butt. Try it.
Is the trigger too tight?
My ears!
I Ieft it noisy, so it scares away any
pain-in-the-ass innocent bystanders.
You've shot them both.
Now what do you do?
- Sit down, finish my dinner.
- Don't fooI around.
Let your hand drop to your side
and Iet the gun sIip out.
Everybody wiII stiII think you've got it.
They'II stare at your face,
so waIk out fast, but don't run.
Don't Iook anybody in the eye,
but don't Iook away either.
They'II be scared stiff,
so don't worry about nothing.
You'II be aII right. You'II take a vacation,
nobody knows where,
and we'II catch the heII.
- How bad do you think it wiII be?
- Pretty goddamn bad.
AII the other famiIies wiII probabIy
Iine up against us.
These things have to happen every five,
ten years. Gets rid of the bad bIood.
Been ten years since the Iast one.
You have to stop them at the beginning.
Like they shouId have stopped HitIer in
Munich, not Ietting him get away with it.
You know, Mike, we were aII proud
of you. Being a hero and aII.
Your father too.
Nothing. Not a hint. AbsoIuteIy nothing.
Even SoIIozzo's peopIe don't know
where the meeting wiII be heId.
How much time do we have?
They're going to pick you up outside
Jack Dempsey's in an hour and a haIf.
- We couId put a taiI on them.
- SoIIozzo wouId Iose our ass.
- What about the negotiator?
- He's pIaying pinochIe with my men.
- He's happy. They're Ietting him win.
- Too risky. Maybe we shouId caII it off.
The negotiator pIays cards
untiI Mike is back safe.
- He couId bIast whoever is in the car.
- They'II expect that.
SoIIozzo might not even be
in the car, Sonny!
I'II get it.
Louis' restaurant in the Bronx.
- Is it reIiabIe?
- My man in McCIuskey's precinct.
A poIice captain is on caII 24 hours
a day. He'II be there between 8 and ¨1 0.
- Anybody know this joint?
- Sure, I do. It's perfect for us.
A smaII famiIy pIace, good food.
Everyone minds his business. Perfect.
They've got an oId-fashioned toiIet.
You know, the box and the chain thing.
We might be abIe to tape the gun
behind it.
AII right. Mike, you go to the restaurant,
you eat, taIk for a whiIe, you reIax.
Make them reIax.
Then you go to take a Ieak. No, better
stiII, you ask permission to go.
Then you come back bIasting.
Two shots in the head apiece.
I want somebody very good
to pIant that gun.
I don't want him coming out
with just his dick.
- The gun wiII be there.
- You drive him and pick him up.
Let's move.
Did he teII you to drop the gun
right away?
Yeah, a miIIion times.
Don't forget. Two shots apiece in
the head as soon as you come out.
How Iong do you think it wiII be
before I can come back?
At Ieast a year.
I'II square it with Mom, that you're not
seeing her before you Ieave and...
I'II get a message to that girIfriend
when the time is right.
Take care.
Take care, Mike.
I'm gIad you came. I hope we can
straighten everything out.
It's not the way I wanted things to go.
It shouId never have happened.
I want to straighten everything out.
I don't want my father bothered again.
I swear on my chiIdren
that he won't be, Mike.
But you have to keep an open mind
when we taIk.
I hope you're not a hothead Iike Sonny.
You can't taIk business with him.
He's a good kid.
I'm sorry about the other night, Mike.
I've got to frisk you, so turn around.
On your knees, facing me.
I guess I'm getting too oId for my job.
Too grouchy.
Can't stand the aggravation.
You know how it is.
He's cIean.
Going to Jersey?
Maybe.
Nice work, Lou.
- How's the food in this restaurant?
- Try the veaI. It's the best in the city.
I'II have it.
- I'm going to speak ItaIian to Mikey.
- Go ahead.
What I want...
What's most important to me...
...is that I have a guarantee.
No more attempts on my father's Iife.
What guarantees can I give you?
I'm the hunted one!
I missed my chance.
You think too much of me, kid.
I'm not that cIever.
AII I want is a truce.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Is it aII right?
When you got to go, you got to go.
He's cIean.
Don't take too Iong.
I've frisked a thousand punks.
Okay, you take over.
I Iove you, Grandpa.
I'm sorry, Pa. He doesn't know you yet.
- Hey, big guy. Give it to Grandpa.
- Okay.
"I hope you get weII, Grandpa, and wish
I see you soon. Your grandson Frank."
Go with your mother.
Take them downstairs.
Go on, CarIo, you too.
Go on.
- What's the matter with you, CarIo?
- Shut up and set the tabIe.
Since McCIuskey's kiIIing, the poIice
have cracked down on our operations.
And aIso the other famiIies.
There's been a Iot of bad bIood.
They hit us, so we hit them back.
Through our newspaper contacts
we've been abIe to put out materiaI
about McCIuskey's Iink with SoIIozzo
in the drug rackets.
So things are Ioosening up.
And I sent Fredo to Las Vegas, under
the protection of Don Francesco of L.A.
- I want him to rest.
- I'm going to Iearn the casino business.
Where's MichaeI?
It was MichaeI who kiIIed SoIIozzo.
But he's safe. We're starting to work
to bring him back.
Did you find out where that oId pimp
TattagIia is hiding? I want him now.
Sonny, things are starting to Ioosen up.
If you go after TattagIia, aII heII
wiII break Ioose. Pop can negotiate.
- He must get better first. I'II decide...
- War is costIy. We can't do business.
- Neither can they. Don't worry about it!
- We can't afford a staIemate.
- No more staIemate. I'II kiII the bastard!
- You're getting a great reputation!
Do as I say! If I had a SiciIian wartime
consigliere, I wouIdn't be in this shape!
Pop had Genco. Look what I got.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean that.
Ma made a IittIe dinner. It's Sunday.
Niggers are having a good time
with our poIicy banks in HarIem.
Driving new CadiIIacs,
paying 50 per cent on a bet.
That's because they've started
making big money.
Poppa never taIked business
at the tabIe.
- Shut up, Connie...
- Don't you ever teII her to shut up.
Don't interfere.
I'd Iike to taIk to you after dinner.
I couId do more for the famiIy...
We don't discuss business at the tabIe.
I kiss your hand, Don Tommasino.
Why are you so far
from the house?
You know I'm responsibIe to your
father for your Iife.
The bodyguards are here.
It's stiII dangerous...
We've heard from Santino
in New York...
Your enemies know you're here.
Did Santino say when
I can go back?
Not yet.
It's out of the question.
Where are you going now?
Take my car.
I want to waIk.
Be carefuI.