THE GREY
Subtitle: Szaki & LaDa
A job at the end of the world.
A salary killer for a big
petroleum company.
I don't know why I did half
the things I've done,
but I know this is where I belong.
Surrounded by my own.
Ex-cons,
fugitives, drifters,
assholes.
Men unfit for mankind.
There's not a second goes by
when I'm not thinking of you in some way.
I want to see your face,
feel your hands in mine,
feel you against me.
But I know that will never be.
You left me,
and I can't get you back.
I move like I imagine the damned do,
cursed.
And I feel like it's only a matter of time.
I don't know why I'm writing this,
I don't know what can come of it.
I know I can't get you back.
I don't know why this has
happened to us.
I feel like it's me,
bad luck...
poison.
And I've stopped doing this
world any real good.
Once more into the fray.
Into the last good fight
I'll ever know.
Live...
and die on this day.
and die...
on this day.
Let’s go. Idents
and boarding passes please.
Please have them out
there’s a storm coming in
We gotta get this plane
off the tarmac.
Guys are fucking this up, let’s go.
Shit, sorry bro.
Sorry man, sorry.
It is as cold as this mother-
fucker has ever been, huh?
I ain't shitting either, man. I stripped down for
the shower and icicles are formed on my nuts.
I didn't even think that shit was possible.
- You got a girl back in Anchorage?
- No.
Oh, well. I got me a few.
Went out to get the scrape.
At least that’s what she told me.
She’s been hitting me up
for the money ever since.
I’m like: ”Bitch, we both fucked”
„I'll split it with you, whatever.„
I'am Flannery, by the way...
Todd.
- You're Aman, right?
- Ottway.
Oh, opps! Sorry bro. Ottway, yeah.
So, you blast critters for a living, huh?
You do some of that snipe issue.
What's the biggest piece of game
you've taken down? Like a kodiak?
You know, I saw that documentary
that asshole did. You know, the fag who loves bears...
Listen. Listen pal. I don't wanna talk.
I need some quiet. So I'm just
gonna put head back, okay?
Yeah, that's cool. That's cool.
- Sir, sir, I need you sit down, please.
- Yeah, I am sitting.
- You like that chick?
- No, I don’t. - Yeah, you do.
Just really never you can seriously say,
not only does it make you impotent
but it poisons you,
and it causes some skin rashes.
- No, it’s the opposite.
- Whatever.
Dude.
- Was it?
- Plus it tastes like shit.
Did you ever taste that?
You ever seen one?
- What's the other thing?
- …Not, not into it, not into it. Incontinent.
That reminds me of my childhood.
That was a true story,
a true story...
Fuck me...
- What was that?
- Shit...
Hey guys, do yourself a favor.
Don't do that head between your knees
crash position shit, if this fuck goes down.
Shut the fuck up!
Shut up!
- Shut the fuck up!
- Suck my dick!
Why would you even say that?
I'm just saying, I've seen
on Discovery channel,
this plane crashed, these people’s spines
went through the top of their skulls
cause they were all bent over
like fucking retards.
- Flannery, I’m gonna knock you the fuck out. Shut up!
- Who is friends with this guy?
- I was just saying.
- Shut the fuck up!
Whoever is closest should just fucking hit him.
Fucking guy, man! is he planning on flying out
of this shit anytime, or what?
Whooa you boys are sensitive.
Hey. There's ice on the
inside of the window.
What's going on?
- What happened?
- ...remain calm.
Tell the pilot to get on
and tell us what’s going on here.
Sir, you have to sit back
down to the seat.
Help! Help me out!
Help! Help!
Somebody help me!
Help me!
Help me, somebody!
Help! Somebody help me!
I got you!
- I got you!
- Oh, we fucking went down!
Oh my God! Oh my God!
That guy's cut in half!
Don't look! Don't look at it!
Don't look!
Look at me!
My hand's fucked, my legs fucked.
Aahh! Fuck!
- It’s good…It's good that it hurts.
- Is it good? - Yeah.
Oh, then I’m fucking fabulous.
- Are you bleeding anywhere else?
- I don't know, man, I can't tell.
- Listen, I'll be right back.
- Don't go, don't leave me!
- Where are you going? - Fuck
- Stay calm. It’s okay.
Oh, shit!
It's got to be okay.
There's some Vicodin in my bag.
- Hernandez, are you okay?
- I just gotta make a call to Vanessa.
I gotta make a quick call to
Vanessa. Just one call.
You're in shock, Hernandez.
But I need you to start over.
- What happened?
- The plane went down, man. We crashed.
Oh, no! No! No! That's bullshit!
That's fucking bullshit! I'm just asleep!
- We crashed.
I'm just sleeping! There's no way
that could have happened!
- What about the pilots?
- Pilots? What are you talking about?
The plane's gone, man!
It's in pieces. Look.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God!
This is so fucked up!
I can't fucking believe it.
- Are there lots of people dead?
- Yes.
But I need you to help me
find the one's that aren't.
- Can you walk?
- Yeah.
Oh, fuck!
I got you, allright, I got you.
- Too much blood!
- Fuck!
Fucking phone doesn't work!
I got this. I’m help.
You’re losing too much blood.
Fucking lose all this blood.
- Help him!
- Ottway, help him.
Wait!
It's can't be all coming outside.
Too much blood. This is
way too much blood. Oh! Fuck!
Help me. Help me, okay?
Something's wrong.
Something's really, really wrong here. Okay?
I don't feel right. I just... I just don't.
Help me. Okay? This doesn't...
- Look. - Something's wrong with me,
I know. Okay?
Aahh! I don't feel right.
Something feels wrong.
Listen. Listen.
You're gonna die,
that's what's happening.
What?
It's okay.
No. No. No. No.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
- Hold on.
- It's okay.
- Hold on, hold on, wait, wait, wait...
- Look at me. Sshh!
Hold on! Hold on!
Hold on! No!
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Look at me. Look at me.
Keep looking at me.
It's all right. It's alright.
Look. Look at me. Keep looking at me.
It's all right.
It'll slide over you.
It'll start to feel warm.
Nice and warm.
It'll move over you.
It's all right.
Let your thoughts go.
Hold the good things.
Hold the good things, yeah?
Who do you love?
Who do you love, Lew?
My girl, Rosie.
Is she your daughter?
Yes.
Let her take you then.
Let her take you.
It's okay. It's okay.
Did he just fucking die?
He's just fucking died, didn't he?
Oh, God!
- Did you...?
- Yeah.
- Did you feel him?
I felt him go.
Is this everyone?
Is this everyone who is still alive?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, I’m going cold.
One... two... three.
Seven, seven of us.
That we know of. Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
We fuck it.
You had to open your fat fucking mouth.
You had to keep talking. You had to put on us?
I didn't do shit.
Did I fucking crash us?
We need a fire.
Did I…I… I didn’t do shit.
We should gather up anything that'll burn.
Seats, luggage, any wood we can find.
- What are you doing?
- I said we need a fire.
It's about ten below and dropping.
So we don't die,
we build up a fire,
then we find food,
and at daybreak we figure out what
way is south and we start walking.
- Nobody is going to find us, not here.
- Somebody will find us.
- I mean, somebody will be fucking searching.
- They gotta know that plane went off the radar.
- Right!
- If they send fifty planes,
maybe they'll find us.
But they won't send fifty planes,
because it won't matter, because...
we won't have time to wait for the one
or two that they will send.
Wilburt doesn't give a fuck.
Nobody gives a shit about us.
You know how much payroll
they just pocketed in this crash?
If we don't move and work now,
we're all fucked.
Unless you wanna freeze to death,
cause that's the one thing that will come for you.
Hey asshole! I suggest
you get away from here!
A lot of wood...
It’s something to wear.
Don't.
Hey, careful with that,
she would kill us.
Fuck.
Oh, no.
- We gotta do something with the bodies.
- Fuck the bodies!
Fuck the bodies! Grab what burns,
or you're gonna be a body!
- Relax, Rambo. Relax.
- You fucking relax.
Telling me to relax.
- They're everywhere.
- I got a book!
It's called we're all fucked!
It's a best seller.
Here.
Oh, fuck!
- Hey man take it easy with that.
- Why?
Because I don't want to fuckin catch fire.
Hello?
I see you! I'm coming!
Jesus Christ!
Get out you motherfucker!
Who are they?
- You okay?
- You see him?
You okay?
- Come on man, we gotta get the fuck out of here.
- Don't stand, don't stand around.
What the hell was that?
- What's that?
- What the hell was that?
- I didn’t fucking see that.
- Coyotes? Huh?
- What's these shit?
- Fucking big.
They are big.
Maybe I'll turn into a wolfman now, huh?
Wait...
that shit's not real... right?
You mean you can't.
Ass-wipe, what do you think? Really?
I don't know, man.
I mean like Rabies, or whatever.
I didn't think the motherfucker
was gonna grow paws and teeth and shit.
Asshole.
You think there's more of them?
- Wolves?
- Maybe.
Yeah, most likely.
But we shouldn't be worried
about them right now,
we should be worrying about finding food.
- They're probably only passing through.
- Wait a minute.
Passing through as opposed to what?
Living here, hunting here.
Wolves have a territorial range of
over three hundred miles
and a killer range of thirty.
If we're close to their den,
and if we're within that radius,
then they'll come after us.
Well, how can we tell
if we're close?
We can't.
They might have just been feeding,
here's bodies everywhere.
I threatened them, they attacked.
What about the radius?
I mean, if we're in that, what,
they're gonna fight us?
- I thought wolves were scared of people.
- Not if we're near their den.
They're not scared of anything then.
What kind of wolves are they? I mean,
what do they call the ones that just eat plants and shit?
- Huh! They don't call them wolves.
- Herbivores, that's what you mean.
That's wishful thinking.
When did you come king shit
fucking animal expert all of a sudden?
They paid me to kill those things,
to keep them from killing you.
So it makes sense for me to know they're man eaters
and they don't give a shit about berries and shrubs.
There's blood in the air,
and there's death.
They know we're wounded,
they can smell it.
Hopefully they won't fuck with us.
We need to move these bodies out of here.
And then we've gotta find food.
Ah, check this fucking thing out.
Jesus, Diaz. Don't do that.
No, man. I saw one of these once.
It's got a beacon, you know? GPS.
Yeah.
Holy shit!
Holy shit, man! It works.
It's beeping!
This things can reach out like
forty thousand feet.
Yes, I think that's great
if that gives you hope.
- It's fucking heart warming.
- Very funny, bro.
Wow. That nice, my friend.
It's calfskin. It's very nice, not cheap.
And since you cocksuckers
didn't give us a holiday bonus,
- I'm gonna accept this on behalf of my homies.
- Put that back.
Put it back!
We're not looting dead bodies for swag.
You got lucky today, Ottway.
You should be lying there with them. Don't push it!
- I'm not gonna say it again!
- I'm a fucking take a big step back!
I'm gonna start beating the shit
out of you in the next five seconds,
and you're gonna swallow a lot of blood
for a fucking billfold!
I can't fucking stand guys like that.
These turn that into charcoal.
I'd say that we have about enough booze
for you guys to get drunk two more times.
- Fucking weird.
- After that then we’ll all be sober.
Jack makes me fight.
- Ladies, ladies...
- You like the white or brown?
How about some brown stuff?
No Tequila, sorry about that.
- It's all good. Thanks, papa.
- Where the fuck did you get that?
From that thing...
that server thing with wheels on it.
There's bunch of dead bodies all over, man.
You wanna make sure you know where that meat came from.
You know, it's like that movie where they start
taking chunks of frozen ass out of that guy.
- The plane crash, with that dude from training day? - Right.
It might be fucking funny as fuck.
How would you like
a dead ass on a stick?
And you thought like a severed dick
was hot dog, right? That's too fucking funny.
I wish some of the other dudes
would have lived.
Did you hear that?
Get up, get up!
Let's move. Go, go!
What the fuck is that?
What is it?
Everybody be cool.
Don't move.
- Jesus Christ!
- Stare right back them.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Why are they coming closer?
- Ah, fuck this shit! I'm getting back in the plane.
- Hendrick, God damn it! Don't move.
Look at the size of that fucking thing.
We'll take two hour shifts.
I'll start. You guys get some sleep.
Yeah. Like that shit's gonna happen.
Don't be afraid.
Hey!
Don’t drift out from us, Burke.
I’ll be allright
I'm not gonna sleep.
Motherfucker.
Where is my goddamn kid
when I need him?
Jesus Christ!
Oh, Jesus Christ.
No, no, no, no!
Fuck!
Man it's... fuck!
Oh, shit!
They ate him.
Jesus Christ!
Fuck, fuck!
They weren't eating him.
They were killing him.
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
How did we not hear them?
How many did it take to do that?
We could dig in, make some...
kind of a stand,
not much cover though.
Woh! Woh! What do you mean,
a stand?
Like fight those motherfucking giant things?
Are you out of your mind?
They'll get bold, start to come in for us.
Why would they?
- I mean, we're not harming them. It's not for food!
- We're a threat.
We don't belong here, that's it.
There's trees out there,
if we can get to that tree line,
they might back off.
If they see that we're leaving,
they might.
Fuck that! What they might do?
Bullshit!
What they might do?!
Are you fucking kidding me?
Hey, they pissed all over this place.
They mean to tag it.
We can't wait them out, we'll starve.
There's a lot of bad space between us
and that forest, but if we get there, then...
we could better defend ourselves.
Less exposed, I don't know.
Yeah. You don't know.
And nobody nominated you shit,
by the way.
It's getting to that point
in the evening, girls.
- Fucking heach is on.
- What the fuck you talking about?
Diaz, come on, man. You wouldn't last
five fucking minutes out here.
I survived that.
This ain't shit.
- I find a way through, with or without.
- Fuck it.
I'm gonna take whatever I can carry
and head into those trees.
You guys wanna join me,
then strip everything.
Fucking losers.
Hey!
We should collect all the wallets
for the families.
Wallets? Did I hear wallets?
Cause I carried a wallet.
Hendrick, do you mind carrying them?
Yeah, let's waste a little more time.
Even though the weather's about
to kick our ass.
You grab them wallets.
Fucking idiots!
To Hernandez.
Grab as many as you can.
Grab, as many as you can.
Waste as much fuckin' time as you can.
I'm gonna stay here
with my friend, Jack Daniels,
and waste some time of my own.
- Why don't you just fucking help us, man? Huh?
- Oh, I'm helping you. I'm helping you. I'm warming up, man!
You guys find any rubbish, save 'em.
- I don't know how long I'm gonna be out here with you fairies.
- Why don't you shut the fuck up?!
The key to survival, fellas.
Grab their wallets...
grab their wallets.
Hendrick.
Wait!
I feel like we should say something.
I mean, all these bodies, all these...
all these people that died,
it doesn't seem right to just walk away.
I don't know any official prayers,
so uh... I guess, uh...
God bless these men.
They were...
some of them, our friends.
and uh... we could be
lying here with them.
So, thank you for sparing us
and helping us.
Oh, and... keep that up, if you can.
Fuck!
Don't worry about me,
motherfuckers!
If any of you wanna run off into the trees,
that's cool too.
No! No! No! Ottway!
Help me!
Help...
Oh, fuck!
Flannery!
Get off him!
Jesus!
Flannery!
No.
Do you wanna say anything?
Come on. Let's keep moving.
There's nothing else we can do for him.
Those trees aren't getting
any fucking closer.
We're gonna be out here
in the dark with those things.
We have no idea if we're going
towards them or away from it, do we?
- Why didn't we just stay with the plane?
- Oh, come on.
- They would have surrounded us. - How the fuck
do we know if they're not doing that right now?!
Fucking genius.
- We're still better off in the trees.
- Yeah, we're better off.
- You tell that kid.
- Fuck.
What is that?
- Run!
- Go, go into the trees!
All this way!
Go, go, go!
- They are right on us.
- Don't stop running!
Wait, wait.
Don't look back!
Run!
They're flanking us!
Don't stop!
- Sam? Sam?
- They're all around us!
Need a fire to keep them off us.
Hurry!
Wood is wet.
Lets burn it, hurry!
Get that fucking thing lit.
- Come on!
- Come on, baby, come on!
Tell me that thing’s unbroke.
Just can't get it going that way.
Hurry!
OK, that's it. That's it.
It's going out...
Fuck!
- That's it. Come on.
- That’s fine.
It worked.
We start perimeter fires.
Let’s see these bastards before hey come…
What the fuck was that?
The alpha.
They went at him,
he put it down.
Whatever... whatever that challenge was,
the alpha put it down.
How are we gonna deal with this?
We kill them.
One at a time.
Tip the numbers.
That's what they're doing to us.
- What the hell are these for?
- I'll explain.
Fix them with electrical tape.
Talget, you got some, yeah?
In here somewhere.
Shot gun shell...
spear tip.
The tip has to drive into the primer
and set off the shell.
Secure them with these sticks
with the tape, simple.
Jab with them when
the wolf gets close.
Hit 'em hard,
gotta get real close.
It'll work,
it's like a bang stick.
A round discharges,
you pull it loose,
you still got something sharp
to create distance.
Unless you want to fist fight 'em.
There you go.
One shot a piece, guys.
Make 'em count. Burke.
Blacken the tips with in the fire, guys.
Makes them harder, stronger.
Really, boys?
This is what's come down too, huh?
This MacGyver bullshit?
Okay.
Good.
I appreciate a good laugh
as much as the next guy.
These things, they see well at night?
Jesus, can we talk
about something else, please?
Talget, you're carrying all that booze.
Let's break it out.
- I recommend rationing what we have.
- I recommend you kissin' my ass.
What, are you the booze police now?
You fucking guys, with your rules
and orders and bullshit.
Where are we?
Look around.
This is Fuck City,
population five and dwindling.
Two days, three maybe,
if we really pull our shit together.
Who's in charge of that right now?
This fucking guy?
The great white hunter,
with his jerry rigged
fucking wolf sticks.
Why are you constantly breaking balls
and bitching about everything?
Cause I wanna live, motherfucker.
Do you understand that?
I don't want some Timberwolf
shittin' me out on this mountain.
You're scared.
- What?
- You don't need all that nonsense,
all that chest puff bullshit.
What's wrong with being scared?
I'm not scared.
- You're not?
- No.
- I'm terrified.
- I can tell.
And not an ounce of shame in saying it.
I'm scared shitless.
That's because you're a punk.
I don't walk through this world
with fear in my heart.
You pick that up in the pen?
Somebody scribble that
in the day room wall?
You better take it easy,
motherfucker.
Talking tough means jackshit now.
You're not scared?
You're a fool.
Worse, you're a fucking liar.
I should have checked
your chin in the fuckin' plane.
Get up! Come on!
Get up, you big Irish fuck.
- You wanna knuckle up? Come on! Come on,
we don't have - Put that fucking knife down.
- Get the fuck off me!
- Put that knife away!
Shut up! Shut up.
You chicken shits make me sick.
Son of a bitch!
You got that kid, Flannery killed
and you're not gonna get me killed.
Put your fucking hands up. Let me show you
how this is done. Put your fucking hands up!
- Ah! You motherfucker!
- Cut this shit out!
Do you hear me?
Get up, get up, get up.
What the fuck?
What did it want?
You.
Diaz, please don't do that shit
to me again.
Allright?
No mas!
That was bullshit,
I'm sorry.
- Fuck you! Fuck!
- ...fuck?
Fuck!
Diaz, I think you got him. Yeah!
Oh! You Fuck!
I think I lost a nail. Ah!
Is that the big one?
That big fucker?
It's not the alpha,
It's an omega.
An outcast. They sent it in
to test you, Diaz.
That freak bitch!
Die, fucking bitch!
You fucking dog.
Let's get a large branch
sharpen the end of it,
shove it up in this thing's ass.
We're gonna cook that son of bitch.
And then we're gonna eat it.
Hey, wolf? Not so tough now, huh wolf?
- You want? Come on!
- No! - I've got it. - I've got it.
Is this the white meat
or dark meat?
- Dark...
- As black as bug.
Yeah?
And I know it tastes like shit, but guys,
it might be the last meat we'll get for a while.
It's grisly too.
- It tastes like shit, I know,
but eat it, guys. - Yeah.
It tastes like dog shit.
Then I'm much more
of a cat person really.
- Burke? - Yeah.
- Are you all right?
My head's a little off. I'm...
- Sit down, sit down.
- I feel a little dizzy.
- You think they're watching us?
- Oh, yeah. They're watching us.
You'll fuck with us,
we'll fuck with you.
You hear that?
You're not the animals!
We're the animals!
Come here you fucker!
Come here you puppy.
- Oh, yeah ...
- You're a twisted fuck.
You wrong for that,
that is wrong!
I'm not crazy.
I'm not fucking crazy. You fuck!
That's fucked up.
I mean, that's fucked up.
You tried to steal my fucking life?
Come on, you fuck!
You hear the bones cracking, Diaz.
Come on, that's enough.
Fucking mut! Come on.
Let him have this.
Little Fido here wants to go home.
He wants to see his brothers.
Jesus, he's crazy.
That's what I'm gonna do...
I'm gonna help him to get there.
Say goodbye boys.
Take it back, motherfucker!
We should keep moving.
These goddamn things are calling us out.
What the hell are you talking about, Talget?
Wolves are the only animal
that will seek revenge.
Hey, I don't wanna hear anymore
about fucking wolves
or you're gonna start
seeing them everywhere.
Burke, how are you doin'?
I can't breath.
I can't keep going.
Ottway, we can't keep going.
We can't stop.
Those things will be all over us.
We gotta keep going.
Ottway, Burke is hurting here, man.
This'll work.
It's a dead end!
They can't get in behind us.
They'll have to hit us from out front.
Let's build a fire.
That thing still workin'?
Up to forty thousand feet.
This shit has to save somebody
at some point, right?
I keep sittin' here thinkin',
even with all this stuff goin' on, that we hit
the ground at four hundred miles an hour,
and we made it.
Why would we go through
something like that, that crash,
if it wasn't meant to be?
Or ordained?
By who? The almighty?
That fucking fairy tale?
How's about good
old fashioned blind luck?
Flannery survived that crash,
so did Hernandez. It don't matter,
if they didn't give a fuck.
Dead is dead.
Where do you think
those boys are now?
Up in heaven?
Getting fit for wings?
No. I'll tell you where they are.
They're not, that's where.
They're no where.
They're gone.
Well, I don't believe it.
I do.
I wish I didn't. I really wish
I could believe in that stuff.
This is real. The cold.
That's real, the air in my lungs.
Those bastards, out there in the dark,
stalking us.
It's this world that I'm worried about,
Talget, not the next.
What about your faith?
What about it?
It's important.
Emma... is she with you guys?
It’s ok, big guy.
She was out the back house.
Speaking with her... she is...
She is, she is not here.
- She’s not here. Why don’t you…
- You tell her, that I am here...
Of course, yeah, just lie down, she is
coming. - That was good.
Yeah.
He's seeing things?
He's hallucinating, it's hypoxia.
Not enough oxygen is getting to his brain.
Hypoxia.
- Why don't the rest of us have it?
- Uh... it depends on the person.
Some people can't handle the altitude.
Who is Emma?
She was, his sister.
She died when he was a kid.
My daughter, Mary,
she's got really long hair,
almost down to her waist.
In fact it's the one rule,
my fucking ex respects, which is that
I'm the only one who cuts her hair.
She does this thing,
she'll come and hover over me,
I'll just be dead asleep,
and she'll start swinging
her head back and forth,
tickling me with her...
with her hair all in my face
and she'll be laughing like crazy.
Just... it's a certain type of laugh,
you know,
when a kid goes past
laughing to laughing like a...
Like they can't really breathe.
Sound more like an old man than a kid.
I miss the hell out of that kid.
Yeah.
You should. You know that?
Those facts of your life,
whatever they might be,
make you want that next minute more
than the last.
Make you fight for it.
I just wanna fuck one more time.
- You ruined my story. Motherfucker.
- No, man. - I'm telling a... - No, man.
I'm telling a nice little sweet story
about my daughter.
I don't mean to wreck your shit, bro.
I don't, I don't.
I just can't go out on that last piece of horrible
ass that I had. You know what I'm saying?
Fifty three year old hooker, half Eskimo.
You shouldn't talk about that.
She was 250-260, no shit.
The bitch gave me the clap
like it was gift wrapped.
No, no, no.
That ain't right.
No, I just didn't think that I would... I would punch
out and that would be my fucking swan song, right?
That alone is worth a fight.
That's worth a fight.
My uh... my dad was not without love.
But a cliched Irish motherfucker
when he wanted to be.
Drinker, brawler, all that stuff.
Never shed a tear,
it's a weakness everywhere.
But he had this thing for
poems, poetry.
Reading them, quoting them,
probably thought it rounded him off,
you know?
His way of apologizing I guess.
And there was one that hung over
the desk in his den.
It was only when I was
a lot older I realized
he'd written it.
It was untitled,
four lines.
I read it at his funeral.
Once more into the fray.
Into the last good fight I'll ever know.
Live and die on this day
Live and die on this day.
Storm clouds.
Blizzard?
A good bet.
Based on our luck.
It's our fucking luck.
Let's bundle Burke up
and dig in against these trees,
snow's deep enough.
I'm worried if we lose this fire,
we'll all freeze.
Burke, moving on.
Come on, Burke, wake up!
Burke! Wake up!
Listen, Burke, wake up!
Do you hear me?
Don't sleep, you hear me?
Burke, come on!
Wake up, Burke, Burke!
Burke, Burke! Wake up!
Wake up, wake up!
Wake up right now.
Wake...
Don't be afraid!
What is it?
Guys, get up, up!
Is it them?
Saw marks.
These trees have been logged.
That's water!
That sounds like a river.
You gotta be shittin' me!
The river must be a good size
if we can hear it all the way up here.
At least if we're following a river,
we got a better chance of finding shelter.
Who's climbing down that?
I can't. There's no way I can do that.
Well, we can't go back.
There's no way we can go back.
- Those trees though.
- What trees?
Them out there.
We got a tether of some kind, secure it
between here and there. We can climb down.
Guys, it's simple.
It's the wolves or those trees.
You're not talking about
jumping off the cliff?
It's an idea, I didn't say
it was a good one.
He's talking about jumping off the cliff.
This will wind up
being one of those wild stories
you tell at a party,
pretty girl on your lap.
- All right, are you ready?
- Yeah, why not?
Go get a good running start,
get a grip.
Now you'll free fall about thirty feet,
but it's gonna feel
like thirty thousand.
Is this supposed to pass for a pep talk?
When we feel this go taut,
we'll take up the slack
to stop you from hitting too hard.
When you get in there.
I'll figure it out.
If you gotta go, this is
a pretty cool way to go, bro.
Better a flying leap
than those fucking wolves, right?
I hope there's something down there.
Fuck!
Go, go, go, go...
Which one of you fuckers…
Pull me up!
Fuck! Pull me back!
Hendrick!
Hendrick, you in there?
Yeah! I'm all right!
Anyone with the nards to go first?
Talget?
Diaz?
I'll go.
Don't stay out there too long.
Hendrick! Make sure that thing is secure!
It's secure, but I don't know
how long it's gonna last!
Don't spend a lot of time out there!
You all right?
Yeah. You go.
What about your hand?
I'm all right.
Go ahead. Just haul me in
if anything goes wrong.
Yeah.
Just fucking hate heights, man.
Flips me out.
Well then you go,
I’ll stay and make sure...
No. I'm good. You cross, seriously.
Give me a minute to get my head around it.
All right, I’m through.
I’m across.
I'm coming!
All right!
I'm coming to cross now.
Okay.
Come on, you can do this.
You can do this.
Talget, you ready?
Talget, stop fucking around!
Move your ass!
Hey, baby girl.
I love you, daddy.
- Oh, God, no!
- Fucking killing him!
- No, no!
- Diaz don't.
They're killing him!
Talget!
They fucking took him!
No, no, no!
Fuck!
Talget!
They took him!
- They took him! Talget!
- They fucking took us!
They took him!
My knee!
My fucking knee!
They're just picking us off,
one by one.
I'm fucked. I'm fucked.
Ah! My knee!
- Let's get you up.
- I can't!
- I can’t… fuck.
Motherfucking things.
They're not gonna let us go,
are they?
What do you do?
Fuck it!
Forget it.
Whatever I had in the tank
I used back there.
I'm beat.
I just want to sit.
I just wanna...
stop this bullshit.
My fucking leg.
My ankle's fucked.
Diaz. Don't sit down.
Don't sit down.
I know, I know...
I don't wanna argue.
I just wanna rest.
I just had the clearest thought.
I'm done.
Come on, man. Up.
There could be a cabin down river,
right there.
That's a mile up at least, brother.
I can't walk that, man.
I can't walk fifty feet.
Fuck it.
I gave it a shot.
What the fuck, man?
Are you serious?
I really thought
this fucking watch would work.
Does it slide over you?
You told Lewenden back in the plane that it...
it slides over you.
Death.
That it was warm.
- Is that true?
- Yeah.
We carry him.
We put a litter together,
slide him down the banks.
I'm not going anywhere, Hendrick.
I don't want to.
I don't need to.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Is that it? You're just gonna sit there?
Is that what you want?
Yeah.
After what we survived?
That's exactly why.
What do I got waiting for me back there?
Gonna sit on a drill all day,
get drunk all night.
That's my life.
Turn around and look at that.
I feel like that's all for me.
How do I beat that?
When would it ever be better?
I can't explain it.
I don't have the words, brother.
My first name is John.
My first name is Pete.
Pete.
You look like a Pete.
John Ottway.
Of course that's your name.
Thank you, John.
Thank you.
Luck.
I'm not afraid.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
Where were you going that night?
That last night in camp,
at the bar?
You had your rifle,
you went out.
My shift.
No.
You worked that morning,
I remember.
I went out, yeah.
With your rifle.
Did you follow me?
No,
but I never thought
I'd see you alive again.
Back there with Diaz,
that look he had.
I've only seen it one other time,
on you,
that last night in camp.
It really doesn't matter now, does it?
No, I don't suppose it does.
Hendrick run, run!
Hendrick!
Hendrick, hold on!
Hang on!
What the fuck are you doing?!
Look at me!
Hold your breath!
Goddammit, hold your breath!
Jesus, please don't do this!
Do something.
You phony prick.
Fraudulent motherfucker.
Do something!
Come on! Prove it!
Fuck faith! Earn it!
Show me something real!
I need it now,
not later!
Now!
Show me and I'll believe in you
until the day I die!
I swear.
I'm calling on you!
Fuck it. I'll do it myself.
I'll do it myself.
A den.
It's a fucking den.
Don't be afraid.
Once more into the fray.
Into the last good fight I'll ever know.
Live and die on this day.
Live and die
on this day.
Subtitle: Szaki & LaDa
www.feliratok.info
www.hosszupuska.com