A case in point in anger's
ability to change us
is my mother.
My mother was always
the nicest person I ever knew.
She was the nicest, sweetest woman
than anyone who knew her ever knew.
Then things changed...
then she changed.
She got angry.
Good and angry.
Anger has turned my mother
into a very sad and bitter woman.
If she wasn't my mother,
I'd slap her.
I would.
I'd look her straight in the face and
tell her what I really think of her...
and then I'd run really fast
in the opposite direction.
- Are you eating?
- Yes.
I want you eating.
I mean it.
Okay.
You ladies
are old enough now,
I'm not gonna pull
any punches here.
He took his wallet...
and he left.
When he didn't come home
the other night,
you know,
I thought we got lucky
and he was just
in a car crash,
dead by the side of the road,
but the fact is,
he's run off with his little Swedish
secretary, who, oh, what a coincidence,
mysteriously left work three days ago
and moved back to Sweden!
But where did he go?
Have you spoken to him?
No, I haven't
spoken to him.
There is
very little to say.
He knows that. But I did cut off
all his goddamn credit cards.
Closed his checking
account, yeah.
See how long she sticks
around when he's broke.
Your father is a...
small man.
Very small.
I hope that's not an allusion
to the man's genitals
- 'cause that'd just be gross.
- Aw, dude,
- I was about to eat a string bean.
- Oh, my god...
Excuse me, excuse me.
Everything is not a joke.
I am talking.
And as
a jittery nation worries
about a counterstrike, we'll go to the
scene of the anthrax scare in Florida.
Sheesh.
Hey. Hey, Terry.
What do you want?
Well, I-I...
I wanted to talk
to you and Grey
about them building that
subdivision back there?
- Yeah?
- He's so, um...
He's so damned set
against it,
he hasn't even heard
the proposal.
Grey doesn't
live here anymore, Denny.
He doesn't exist.
Go away.
Officials tell us
that they are worried
about how to manage the fragile US-led
coalition in the days ahead,
but the facts
are already evident
from south Asia, to Africa,
to the Middle East.
Worldwide, thousands
of angry demonstrators
are taking to the streets
to protest US military...
The least he could have done
was taken this stupid jock with him.
There have been plenty
of protests in the world.
and I suspect...
Ugh.
What... what...
what do you mean,
"He doesn't exist"?
Oh.
Are you stoned?
- Yeah.
- Oh... Jesus.
What do you...
what do you mean,
"He... he doesn't exist"?
He's been messing around
with his assistant.
Go talk about it
on the radio.
No, I'm... I'm...
no, I'm-I'm... I'm-I'm be...
I'm being serious.
I need... I need to talk to him.
Um...
He left me.
- He left you?
- Mm. For Danken Shane
or whatever his
secretary's name is,
so Denny you can go ahead
and build your...
damn subdivision
back there...
I don't know,
whatever it is you want.
It was him who had
the problem with it, not me, okay?
- He left you?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hey, I'm sorry,
Terry.
You know, go ahead and build
your houses back there, Denny.
- He's gone. He won't stop...
- They're not my houses.
They're not.
I'm just, um...
I'm just the front man,
you know,
wave the
World Series ring.
They get the sales,
I'm getting a free lot out of it.
Ooh, a free lot.
- Hmm.
- It's something Shep set up.
He really left?
Really?
This is... true?
Yeah.
Hey, come on.
Just go away.
Hey. Well... ah... look,
let me come in.
Come on, if yo...
if you don't want,
I won't talk. I'll just sit there
and I'll drink with you.
There was a large mob...
of angry demonstrators
here today,
proving that a number
of people are willing to go and fight.
- The feeling is that...
- I got her to school.
Thank you.
You know I'm going back
to school in the morning,
you're gonna get her
yourself tomorrow.
Billy Edwards on my bus says
that when you get really drunk,
you get friendly and you sign baseballs
without bitching about it.
- He does?
- Yeah.
So, you got any
baseballs around?
No.
Why don't you run
down the street to my house.
I got a...
stack of boxes in my garage.
There's a key under my mat.
You grab one of those boxes.
You bring it back here.
One box.
Anything she makes...
I'm gonna split with her.
Buddy, Goddamn you!
Out!
What's the big deal? He wasn't licking
it more than three seconds.
The three second thing is for floors,
not dogs' mouths.
He spends all day
licking other dogs' asses.
Oh, let's just call
for take-out.
It's fine. You guys, it's good chicken.
It's fine.
Like you'd eat it?
You know the Zilwaukees'
Great Dane, "Mo'fo?"
You're licking
his asshole right now.
You know what,
that's really sick.
How's dinner coming?
Good.
We made your favorite.
- Chicken.
- Thank you.
Um, can you make an extra plate?
Denny's staying for dinner.
That was quick.
What was quick?
Denny?!
Please...
Give me more credit than that, Hadley.
He's a drunk.
You make a nice couple.
My life is falling apart
at this moment.
I expect some compassion
from you.
Now you go back up
to school tomorrow,
come back home
at Christmas break
and bust my hump
if you want to,
but right this minute, I want
the benefit of the doubt at every turn!
Are we clear?
Yes.
Thank you.
Mm, this looks good.
What kind of a dick-head
runs away
with his secretary?
That is lame.
Take a right,
make a left
at pathetic.
I think he's coming
back home.
Maybe not soon,
but... I do.
I think we should
call him.
And say what?
"Hey Dad, how's your
new life going so far?
I got an A
in interpretive dance."
He doesn't care about you, Emily.
Get real.
He lost his job, Hadley.
- What?
- Your father was about to be laid off.
He was told
a few months ago.
He was devastated.
He didn't want you girls to know it.
Okay? I think he
flipped out or something.
I read this article
on the internet.
Apparently, it's common.
They lose their jobs,
and they go nuts.
What do you want
from me?
It's the best
that I can come up with.
I don't want
anything from you.
Well, don't take it out on me, Hadley.
You aren't gonna have to be here.
You aren't gonna know
how empty this house is gonna be.
Well, if it makes you feel
any better, I hate him too.
Oh, does that mean
you hate me?
You are such a mental.
I have to go, okay?
All right.
I'll see you later,
okay?
Terry.
Hey.
Listen to my show
today, okay?
I'll mention you.
I'm gonna bring you up
as a drinking buddy
- I watched the invasion with.
- I don't want you to do that, Denny.
I know, but...
you don't have a choice.
Yeah, I do. I don't want to be
mentioned on the radio.
You don't want
to be mentioned?
- # She cried more, more, more! #
- No.
# With a rebel yell #
- # She cried more, more, more! #
- Okay.
Oh God.
Hey, come on!
Slow down!
- There's children playing here!
- Sorry, sorry, sorry!
- Sorry!
And now, once again,
Detroit's own legendary
Denny Davies.
Okay, it's the Denny Davies show.
and if you're
a regular listener,
and you've just tuned in, you know
that you haven't missed much.
And you know that's the beauty
of the show, right, Shep?
You can always just
jump right in here with us
- because...
- Because nothing ever happens.
Nothing ever
happens, exactly
Now what were we talking about
just before the commercial?
Oh yeah.
The invasion, right?
- See?
- Right?
- You still do have your memory.
- Yeah.
I know what people are saying.
Were you watching TV?
As a matter of fact,
I was watching it
with my drinking buddy
the very sweet,
the very tall
and absolutely sexy
Terry Ann Wolfmeyer.
But you...
but you know what?
- What?
- She doesn't want me to talk about her,
so I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not gonna talk about her.
Not gonna talk
about who?
- Terry Ann Wolfmeyer.
I get it. We're not even mentioning
Terry Ann Wolfmeyer's name.
- Nope.
- Is that the game that you're playing?
- Not even gonna bring her up.
- Terry Ann Wolfmeyer.
- You're getting no play.
- On 101 WRIF Detroit.
You're listening
to the Denny Davies show.
What I don't get, is how come
you won't talk about baseball?
With all they pay you every year,
what's with you not talking about base...
Hey, guess what,
guess what, pinhead?
They don't pay me
that much.
He just got flushed.
Okay, that's...
that's it for me folks,
the Poobah's up next,
Big Daddy Arthur P.
But I'll be with you tomorrow,
and you can all call in
give me hell, the radio equivalent
of dunking the clown...
into the water.
WRIF Detroit at 5:00...
That wasn't too bad,
was it, Shep?
Wasn't too... vicious?
No, you were mild today. You probably
only lost about 6 or 7,000 listeners.
You should feel really good
about yourself.
- WRIF or email the Poobah
at Arthur P...
Hey, but what was
all that about?
- All what?
- That whole thing about the woman
you watched the invasion
with? Who's she?
Just a girl.
Yeah, she's one
of the 20-year-olds, isn't she?
From the college thing.
The one I got you.
No.
No, she's not 20.
She's nowhere near 20.
In fact, look,
don't superimpose
your warped thinking
onto my life, okay?
I got enough problems.
Okay, well,
then while we're at it,
don't knock
my dating habits, okay?
'Cause they keep me young.
I happen to be a walking encyclopedia
of every boy-band that ever existed.
Trust me, you don't get that from dating
Arianna Huffington.
Did you, uh, find out about that, uh,
mall opening in Toledo?
- What it's price was?
- Yeah, $10,000.
$10,000 for you
to show up
for one-half an hour.
- You know, it must suck for you...
- You're going.
...not, uh, being me.
- Yeah, almost as much as it must suck
- actually being you.
- And now, your Rock 'n' Roll
- radio chaperone of Detroit...
- Go home.
Seriously. I've got a real
disc jockey to produce.
A die-hard drinking fan
with a serious football problem.
My impression of you
in about 15 minutes.
...WRIF Detroit.
That was said with love.
Where's Mom?
She's upstairs
taking a shower.
What are you working on?
What are you looking
in the want-ads for?
A job.
I need to work.
I'm not going to college.
Okay.
It's okay with me,
I guess.
Thank you.
- What are you gonna do?
- I want to be a reporter.
- A newscaster.
- Well, you have the face for it.
Oh. Are you staying
for dinner?
Depends.
If you're making any more
of that chicken, I am.
Here you go.
A little something
to get you into second gear.
What are you doing?
I wasn't looking,
relax.
Get out!
Jesus!
I get out, I'm taking
this drink with me.
Have you ever heard
of boundaries?
Okay, that's it.
I'm drinking them both.
Give me the drink.
I-I wasn't looking.
All right?
I, uh...
I didn't see much.
All right, well...
what are you doing here?
- What do you want?
- Well, little Emily invited me...
for dinner.
- She did?
- Yes, she did,
and I think you know
my position on free food.
Which one of you
recites Brownie?
Come on, your mother
told me once that one of you
recites Brownie,
beautifully.
Oh. Browning,
Elizabeth Barrett Browning
and I was telling you that...
um... Popeye,
a few years back
when you were like,
I don't know, nine or 10 or so.
I had her read Browning
and she used to
commit some
of the poems to memory
and recite them here
at the dinner table.
That's right.
That's what it was.
That sounds...
that sounds good.
I've never heard anything
like it before
but it...
it sounds fun.
To who?
To all of us,
if she can remember.
Popeye?
Can we do this tomorrow night
when I've had notice
and can make plans
to eat somewhere else?
I don't remember any
of them anyway.
I do.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Really?
Wow.
I'm impressed.
Good.
You should be.
What's so funny?
Nothing. Just...
You're just all...
I don't know...
very female.
I got her number in Sweden...
from Helen Trailer.
It forwards and I...
called last night.
It must've been the middle
of the night there.
It was Grey that answered.
I'm sure of it.
Yeah. I hung up
like a six-year-old.
Ah, he'll marry her.
I'd bet any money in the world.
What do you think
you'll do?
Eh, what can I do?
Well, you're set up,
right?
Right?
I mean Grey's got to be
pretty chunky
in the money department,
- plus, you have...
- I have, what?
Bills?
Responsibilities?
Four girls?
One that hates me,
two or three that are
leaning that way.
You can have your damn lots
back there, Denny.
I'm not here
for the lots.
Then leave.
Any other reason than that
for you to be here, frankly,
is just pitiful.
- Are you okay?
- No.
I'm a wreck.
She's gonna take us
to school.
You see women...
on TV, in the movies,
and they get left
or whatever.
You just wanna kick 'em,
they're so whiny.
Look at me.
I hate his guts.
I hate his guts for what he's done.
Oh.
He's a pig,
your dad.
Just a vile, selfish,
horrible pig,
but you know what?
I'm not gonna trash him
to you girls.
I'm not.
I hate him too.
I hate him so much.
I know you do, baby.
You're human.
How could you not?
# When your eyes
were open wide #
- All right. See you.
- # For the the last... #
Hey, hey, wait.
Who is that?
He's cute.
That's Gorden Reiner.
He's new.
He's from Chicago.
- Go meet him.
- Yeah.
I met him. He's not
interested in me.
All he likes to talk about
is bungee jumping.
Tell him you're
from a broken home.
- I'm serious.
- Should I?
Guys think things
like that are great.
Trust me.
I'm gonna use it.
Hi, Gorden.
Hey.
Did you know I'm
from a broken home?
Okay, bye.
Turn it down.
- Wolfmeyer residence
- Hey, beautiful.
It's Denny.
- Which one is this?
- It's Andy.
Bingo. You still
lookin' for work?
- I am.
- Well, I want you to come in tomorrow.
and see Shep Goodman
from my show.
He needs
a production assistant.
Denny, you're kidding me.
- You're amazing.
- Yeah...
well, you tell that
to your mom, we're even.
So you come in tomorrow, okay?
I'll set you two up.
Okay!
Thank you so much!
Oh my God.
I might get a job
working on Denny's show.
- Are you kidding me?
- No!
- That would be amazing!
- That would be so cool.
- Oh my God.
- What's up?
Denny just called.
She might get a job on his show.
Oh, really?
Denny just called here?
Yeah, I have an
interview tomorrow
for a job.
Wait, wait.
What about school?
I want a job.
I'm not going to college.
Wha... you're not going
to college?
No, I told Daddy and he wanted me
to wait to tell you, but now...
Oh, but now that he's off
screwing his assistant,
you think you can safely drop
the bomb on me, is that it?
No.
"No" is right.
You are going to college!
You know damn well
how I feel about this.
All four of you.
You're all goddamn going to college!
I don't have a job open.
It's that simple, Denny.
It's cut and dry.
This girl has something.
She does, Sheppy,
she's sharp.
She has class.
You could be hiring the next, um...
Diane Sawyer.
I don't have a job open.
I know you don't,
but you could do this
for me, right?
You could do this for me.
No, I can't.
Wanna know why?
- Yes, why?
- Okay, I'm gonna come in there.
I'm gonna tell you.
Hold on.
Jesus.
I'm going on
in a second here.
Because, my lord,
I'm too busy doing
other things
for you.
"My lord"?
# I'm looking for #
# A simple kind of life.
slow and easy #
- # A life that won't #
- Hi.
- # Bring me down #
- Um, I'm Andy Wolfmeyer,
I'm here to see
Shep Goodman about a job.
Um... Denny Davies
asked me to come in.
Oh, okay. Well, if you'd like
to take a seat over there.
- I'll let him know you're here.
- Okay, thank you.
No, you're not
understanding me,
- You're making this really...
- I found one!
I've got an opening.
Something's come up.
I found an opening.
- I'm on the phone.
- Okay.
If you want her to have
the job, I'll make it happen.
You'll just owe me, as usual.
I got the job.
What job?
With Denny, as a
production assistant.
Yes, what?
Are you looking
to get laid?
Is... is this
what's going on?
I mean, are-are you
looking for
another notch in your belt,
or... I don't know...
whatever it is you super
sports heroes call it.
I mean are you
looking to get lucky with me...
- to get me into bed?
- Uh, who's calling?
Be straight with me, Denny.
Be straight. Now, Grey always thought
you had an eye for me,
and I need you to be
really straight with me now.
Uh, okay. Um...
I do like you.
I always have.
Um...
You wanna have sex with me.
Is that it?
No! Uh, no, I mean...
um... well, uh...
yeah, if you're offering,
I guess.
Okay then.
I'll be right there.
Give me 10 minutes.
- Uh, ex... excuse me?
- Give me 10 minutes.
I'm not gonna do much with my face,
though, so don't expect much.
In fact,
keep the drapes shut.
I don't like a lot of light.
It's not very light in there, is it?
No, there, uh...
there's not a lot
of light here.
Okay, well,
have a drink.
Have a couple.
I don't want you to have
a real clear memory of this
when it's over, okay?
I'll see you soon.
Slow down!
- Slow down!
- Oh, please. Come on.
- There's children playing here!
- Ah, get over yourself!
There's children
playing here!
Hello?
I'm here!
Uh, Denny?
Denny?
I'm coming up!
Hello?
It's me.
Listen, um,
something came up.
I had a, uh...
I had a call.
They needed me right away
over at the station.
- Shep's in some kind of trouble.
- Oh, yeah.
- You are so full of shit.
- I'm not.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
I'm not and...
in fact, I'd like
a rain check.
It's not gonna happen.
This was like...
Halley's Comet.
It's not coming around
again for 57 years.
What the fuck
is Halley's Comet?
But this is the main
production booth
This is where you and I will be
doing a lot of working.
- Okay.
- Here, come on, I'll show you this.
this is the live
on-air studio. Arthur?
Say hello to my new
assistant Andy Wolfmeyer.
- Hello, Andy.
- This is Arthur Pennhallow.
- He's a big deal here in town.
- Yeah.
We're friends.
He idolizes me, actually.
The fuck I do.
- He does.
- Okay.
That was a joke. We're tight,
and we're good friends.
Okay.
So what is "Andy" short for?
"Andrea?"
- Yeah, "Andrea."
- Cool. See? I'm good with names.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll show you
up at the office now,
- where we work a lot up there, too.
- Okay.
Have you seen
an Emmy in person?
- You've won an Emmy?
- Couple.
Local, but who's counting?
Actually, I have three.
There's only two up there, 'cause one
I keep for the hotel room when I travel.
Wow.
Kids, hurry up!
You're gonna be late!
- How's your lunch, Gordon?
- It's good.
Did you ever see that documentary
on the Chicago Seven?
What about the one...
the one about
the Kent State killings?
- No.
- Something like...
six people were killed
by the cops,
there was
all this turmoil
and it got really ugly and just opened
up a lot of old wounds
between the police
and the people
of the area.
I'm from
a broken home also.
You are?
Hey, do you bungee jump?
- No.
- Well, I do.
I go up with my dad.
We drive up north
to Fenton Valley...
- and bungee jump off this huge crane.
- That sounds exciting.
Well, I read your letter.
Was it too mean?
I don't want it
to be mean.
Well, I mean I do,
but I don't.
Well, he's your father
and he's...
left you
at a very tough time.
I know and I want him to know
that it pisses me off he hasn't called.
Oh, he knows.
He's not talking to his brother
or his friends at work.
He knows what he's done.
Are you gonna call him?
Please?
This is stupid.
It's just a stupid game.
You said you have
his number.
This letter is good.
I mean, it's good for you
to get your feelings out.
Um...
I want you eating,
though.
You are dancing so much.
Do you think maybe
it's too much?
I know you have this out here.
Daddy built it for you,
- but you spend so much time out here.
- You're such a head case.
- What?
- Be happy for me.
Be proud! Shit!
You know? I'm focused!
What is your problem?
The only thing you're focused
on is drinking and Denny!
Be glad that I have
a dream!
I was just going to tell
you how proud I am of you.
That's the sad thing.
What?
Well,
I'm not going to now.
Not after that outburst.
Fine, I don't care.
I'm in the kitchen
making dinner,
and it wouldn't kill you
to come up and help.
Who knows? You may
get there just in time
to pull my head out
of the oven.
- Hello?
- What... what are you doing?
- Oh, making the girls' lunches.
- Good for you.
Yeah, what the hell. I'm going after
the Mother-of-the-year award.
See, um...
- You know what I was thinking?
- No.
Maybe it's been...
57 years.
- What are you talking about?
- Halley's Comet, you know?
By the way, it's, uh...
76 years, but I'll give you
that one, smarty pants.
Can I come over?
When?
Now.
- Now?
- Yeah, now.
- Did you hang up?
- Uh, not yet.
Good, then, um...
I'm coming over.
I am, so...
don't go hide
in the yard,
don't pull any
reciprocal crap.
Is that what you did that day?
You hid in the yard?
No, um...
You know what?
Delete that last line.
Look, um...
I'm coming over.
I am.
I'm coming now.
Hold it.
# Hold it! #
Wait, wait, wait.
- What is this?
- Your lunches.
- Our lunches?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you kidding?
- I make my own lunch.
You haven't done
it in years.
I'm back to basics.
What do you want?
- Bye.
- Have a good day!
No!
Oh, shit. Great.
Were you...
you taking off?
Hey. You're taking off,
just like that?
Yeah, I'm going to hide
in your yard.
Oh, come on, that's bullshit.
I was kidding.
- What are you doing?
- Step out.
Just step out.
- Are you stoned?
- Not at all.
- Not a bit.
- Well, you should be.
Listen, I, uh...
I know that you're fresh.
I know you're good and hurt
and I know that on some level,
this is way too soon...
- and not right.
- Yeah.
What's the other level?
I dial your number
10 times a day and hang up.
Come on!
Just a minute.
Goddamn, Terry, it's not like, you know,
it's not like I'm asking a lot.
It's just...
it's just...
I get it, okay?
I know who I am
for you.
I'm this guy that you sit
and you drink...
and you talk with.
- And now you want to fuck me.
- Well, you offered it.
That was before you hid
in your yard.
Well, I'm not hiding
in my yard, now am I?!
- Hey come on, lady!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Can that horn, now!
Jeez!
Not bad.
Thank you.
You wanna...
go back to my house?
I've seen your house.
I'll make the bed!
Let's go to my house.
Fine, let's go
to your house.
Oh, God.
Now that was
a real misstep.
Aw...
that was
a sweet thing to say.
God, what am I doing?
Why am I here?
You're here because
you're sad and lonely.
Desperate.
You need someone,
something,
anything to fill you.
Any...
- port in a storm.
- Mmm.
I asked why I
was here, not you.
What's my story?
Oh, your story is...
you're good
and bent out of shape.
Pissed off like
I've never seen a woman.
What?
Francis Wellard.
Timothy Westerburg.
Matthew Wintergarden.
Hadley Wolfmeyer!
Stephanie Winnington!
Nancy Woodside.
It's a special day
for her. So, just be nice.
- She's excited for you to meet him.
- Oh, really,
how excited can she be?
She's been seeing him for three years.
And she's in love?
She's in love?
- I'm just hearing about this today?
- Be nice!
It's not in my nature.
Why does she hate me so damn much?
She doesn't hate you,
she just thinks that he's stupid.
She thinks he's stupid?!
I thought she loved him.
No, she thinks
you'll think he's stupid.
Well, I won't think that.
That's my point.
She judges me so harshly.
I am her mother.
- Okay.
- I love her. I want her to be happy.
I mean, if she loves
this guy I'm gonna love...
- Okie dokie.
- Hi! Hi! Oh, baby!
Baby!
Oh God, I'm so proud
of you! I am!
I am so proud of you.
- Let me see your face.
- Mother.
A college graduate.
I'm so proud of you.
Your father doesn't know
what he's missing today.
I think he might.
Mm-mmm!
This is it.
This is life.
Mom?
- David. Hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
My parents are having lunch
at the Wheeler hotel.
- You're all invited.
- The Wheeler, really?
We'd... well, girls,
would you like that?
- We... we had lunch.
- Have it again.
Come on, I want us to go.
I want you to meet David's parents.
David you tell your folks
we'd absolutely love to join them, okay?
- Cool. Okay, see you later.
- See you later.
Bye.
Wow.
He is so handsome.
Nice and...
- intelligent.
- Mother.
Oh! He is, baby.
I can tell by looking at him.
He's incredibly
intelligent.
All right...
um...
there's something
you all should know.
You're pregnant
and you're getting married.
How did you know that?
Who told you that?
I guessed?
Really?
I guessed that?
I was right?
No, you've got
to be kidding me.
No, I'm... I'm not.
I'm getting married.
This is how I find out?
Through Popeye?
A 15-year-old?
- Don't be condescending...
- Close it!
You are a child.
What do you know?
Oh, that old chestnut.
You close it
as well, please.
Do his parents know?
Yes, they're ecstatic.
Oh, how long
have they been ecstatic?
You know what, can we just
go to the lunch please?
How long have they been
ecstatic, damn you, Hadley?!
I need a Bloody Mary as soon
as is humanly possible.
Hi. I'm Terry.
Oh. Gina.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- And this is David, my husband.
Oh, David Senior.
That's nice.
You're not Jews, obviously.
Oh, well I mean
not that that's a good or a bad thing.
That they don't
just name their children
after... okay,
that was horrible.
Um... these are
Hadley's sisters,
Emily, Andrea
and Popeye.
- Hi, girls.
- Hi.
Could we order you
a drink before lunch?
Oh, I'm set for now.
Thank you.
Um, I'll have the same.
Mmn. Mmn!
So, I understand we have something
to celebrate? Some good news, huh?
Oh, we're
very excited, Terry.
We are crazy about Hadley.
We really are.
I knew from the minute
I met her. I did.
- You did not.
- I did.
No, Mother, you didn't.
If she said she did,
she probably did!
Well, I was taken
for a surprise,
- but... but a happy one.
- Yeah, well, you and me both.
- Should we toast?
- Oh, yes. Let's do.
Well... to David
and Hadley.
- David and Hadley...
- Oh wait, wait, wait.
My glass is...
this is bad luck. Uh, waiter?
Mother, it's okay.
Here.
Oh.
Oh, just...
a little more.
Just...
Thank you.
So, shall we toast?
- May I?
- Please, do.
To David and Hadley.
A long and beautiful
partnership.
- Aww.
- Thanks.
The... mostly right now...
I'm sorry, David,
this is very emotional for me.
To my baby.
My first born,
my little Hadley-wadley.
Aww.
That's what we called her.
Hadley-wadley.
She was so loved
from the minute she was born.
Just an adorable
little thing.
She was... well,
she grew up too fast didn't she?
She grew up so fast
and had a mouth on her.
Mother!
When she was in her teens
she was her own little boss.
Mother!
And she would sometimes
just not come home...
All right, could we just toast, please?
Thank you.
Okay, baby.
We'll toast.
You have to
forgive me. Um...
you all had a chance
to process this,
and I'm just coming
on board, so to speak.
To Hadley-wadley.
Hadley-wadley.
Mmn.
Oh.
Oh!
Oh, no, no.
I'm done toasting.
I'm just ordering
another drink.
- It was horrible.
- Maybe it wasn't.
Maybe it wasn't
as bad as you thought.
No, it was horrible.
It was. I made an ass
of myself. I was like...
a public service film
against drinking.
Just...
yeah, I was an old lush.
Poor Hadley.
I feel so bad
for her, Denny.
Why are we going
out here?
I hate the way
I come off to my girls.
I just hate that I can't
control my emotions.
Oh God.
This is creepy.
This was all a farm
owned by the...
Firestone family
until the 50's.
This and the whole
subdivision.
It goes on a bit
about another eight acres.
Why are we out
here today?
I wanna do it.
- Out here?
- No.
Don't be an asshole.
I wanna sell
my part of it.
Just let your friends develop
the lots and tell them "Yes."
Tell them I don't need
the money, though.
If they think I need the money,
they'll play games with me.
- Do you?
- No.
Yes. No.
I don't know.
I'm in some trouble...
unless I officially
divorce the shitbox
which I refuse to do,
until at least he has
the balls to show his face.
I wanna give
the girls the money.
Just tell your friend Shep
I want to make the deal.
What?
Nothin'.
Good.
I'm going in.
This place is a clearinghouse
for Lime disease.
- Hey, this is cute.
- Shep...
- How are you, pal?
- I'm doing great.
I'm hanging with Andy,
how could I not be?
Hello, Terry.
Hadley...
Hadley's boyfriend.
Okay, okay.
- We're gonna go watch a movie.
- Isn't that sweet?
"The Bicycle Thief."
She's never seen "The Bicycle Thief."
He's a nut
for foreign cinema.
Anyone wanna join us?
Snuggle up on the couch?
Watch a classic?
I think we'll, uh,
probably pass.
Is it the subtitles?
You know me too well.
I do and it's a burden.
- I know him too well...
- Okay.
so it's a burden.
That's it.
Okay.
I cannot tell you how much
this thing disgusts me.
Oh, come on.
She's doing great at work.
Shep's got her producing
morning drive-time,
plus... I think
he really likes her.
Oh, the whole thing
just infuriates me.
That's probably half
the attraction.
What?
You know what.
Not another word.
The deep hatred that men
have felt for one another
through the ages has blossomed
into one chapter after another
of repression,
violence, hate, rape,
religious slang
and genocide.
I'm still working on it.
I need to fix the music.
It's my final
in television production.
You're really handsome,
Gorden.
Thanks.
I should go.
I really do have to go.
The power of stress
and naked anger
is seen over and over again
in the relationships
that exist between the male
and the female of our species.
Here, in rural Botswana,
an unfaithful tribeswoman
is brought to a field
by a group of locals
for a ritualized punishment
of beating and harassment.
Events quickly spiral out of control
for the tribesmen, though
as the woman's fury
becomes too great to contain
and the men are quickly forced
to flee for their safety.
Why am I not excited by it?
Um, because I don't think
any of these new age arts colleges
are really colleges.
Of course, it's a college.
What are you talking about?
Honey, I've been there.
I have.
I wanted to be a poet,
remember?
Just take arts courses
at Ann Arbor.
I don't want to go
to school in Ann Arbor.
No, of course you don't. It's what
I want you to do. Why would you?
Okay, four years learning
dance theory?
I have a theory about that.
It's not going to happen.
How's the show?
You enjoying it?
I wish you would
take me seriously.
Honey, I take you seriously.
I just don't think you have much
capacity for self-evaluation.
You know, you'd think
you'd be happy for me...
considering the way
your life turned out.
- The way your parents pushed you...
- To marry your father?
- Yeah.
- I'm not complaining.
They pushed me
to take life seriously...
not to live
in the clouds.
Do you have any idea
what a fucking idiot
you sound like
sometimes?
I love how you worry
that the letter
you sent to the parent
who deserted you is too mean,
and yet, to the one
who's here in the fight,
you have no problem
saying the most vile things.
Isn't that a tad odd?
Please finish setting
the table.
Fuck you!
Shep, wake up.
Wake up, wake up.
- Hey.
- Oh, it's 5:00.
Okay, 5:00. Just...
No, my mother's downstairs
we need to get up.
We need to get up right...
Ah, hello!
Okay, not now.
We need to get...
- No, we need to get up.
- And...
My...
G... God!
Wow.
That was weird, huh?
Yeah.
And according to a recent report,
the average male waist size
in the United States
has increased four sizes
in the last 10 years.
From 34 to 38.
See, here's my question.
When are they going to stop
calling it 'average? '
Just start calling it
what it is. "Fat ass!"
You have a fat ass!
Say something to her.
- Go in there.
- No.
- Do you mind if I do?
- Yes, I do mind.
Quite a bit.
All right.
Well...
Well what?
I didn't quite actually have the end
of that thought worked out.
It's late.
I think you should
go home, Denny.
I think it's going to be
nothing but trouble,
you staying here
tonight.
Well, if you want me
to leave, just say so.
That was a joke.
...English National
Ballet School
under the direction
of Katherine Wade
perform their highly
acclaimed production...
Can we talk?
Not now,
I have a stomachache.
Well, can I get
you anything?
No, but you can shut
the door.
I'm gay.
What?
No.
No, no, no.
You're not.
Yeah.
I am.
Are you lying to get out
of kissing me?
Have you ever
had gay sex?
What about sex
with a woman?
Look, you can't be gay
if you haven't tried it.
Or at least tried it
with a girl
to know that you don't
like it with girls.
No.
I like men,
because I'm gay.
I think you're lying.
I do, and I think
it's mean.
Have sex with me.
Just try it
and then, if you want to be gay,
you can be gay.
That's nice of you.
Hi. Um, I came
to apologize.
- Did you?
- I did.
I've been
a real shit to you.
Yes, you have.
What's this?
Well, I just want to do
something nice for you.
I want to clean
your house.
What if I don't want
my house cleaned?
Well, come on. Just don't be defensive
and shitty because I've been shitty.
- Let us in, okay?
- No. No.
No, come on. We're not gonna destroy
it, we're gonna clean it.
I don't want my house
cleaned, Terry, okay?
I just want you
to be nice to me, okay?
You know something?
What?
Nothing.
Right. Then move,
I'm coming in to clean.
These...
are all inventoried,
okay?
I know how many boxes
are here.
- And what does that mean?
- You know what it means.
I don't know
this crew.
You don't either.
This is why I don't like
people over.
I don't like too many people
knowing what I have here.
They're balls, Denny,
not gold bullion.
Yeah, well...
say what you want
but they keep me
in firewood.
I do what I have to do.
I'm not ashamed.
I didn't say
you should be.
Other...
Other guys
I played with, they, uh...
pulled car dealerships
out their asses, you know,
ran insurance companies
after they retired?
That wasn't me.
I get by, though.
You wanna have a drink?
You know me pretty well,
what do you think?
So what is it
about you and baseball?
Aw, come on, why don't you just
call in to the show
if you're gonna hit me
with that one.
Come on, really.
What are you so touchy about?
Nothing.
I'm just not sure
what they want from
me anymore, you know?
It was good.
It was grand.
Nice. Next.
It's over.
I don't want to talk
about it anymore.
And I realize
I'm a walking contradiction.
You know, hocking balls...
going to malls,
having my picture taken
in a room
full of fat fucks.
It's just...
you know, it's... I'm... I'm tired, okay?
- I'm just...
- Yeah, I know. Moving ahead is hard.
No, I don't
have a problem
with moving ahead.
You know what it is I like about going
over to your house, Terry?
I like how it smells.
Something's always cooking.
My house doesn't smell
like that.
And I don't even mind
going over there when there's tension,
and there's a... there's a fucking
lot of it, you know?
Somebody is always
mad at somebody.
Doors are slammin'.
Fur's flyin'.
Even when no one
is talkin', it's...
it's loud.
But at least
it's fucking real.
Believe me, this is not where I saw
my life going, okay?
This is not how
I would've drawn it.
But I'm okay
with all of it.
Well...
lucky me.
No.
Lucky me.
When I'm with you, Terry...
with your girls...
I feel like there's
a big chunk of my life
still left
to be played out.
And that's what
I want to talk about,
not... baseball.
I've had my heart broken
really badly, Denny.
I know.
It's not the kind
of thing that ever heals.
Yeah, it does. It heals.
It just heals funny.
You know, you more
or less walk...
with a limp.
Well, we'll...
we'll figure out a way
to be okay with that.
You know...
with the limp.
# Oh, she may be weary #
# And young girls,
they do get weary #
# Wearing that... #
# Mm-hmm. #
I'm showing.
I can't... I'm so pissed off
Well, you're not
showing that bad.
Another two weeks,
and we'd have to elope.
I have to go
get my bracelet.
I hate the fact that so many people
know she's pregnant.
Half of them, she's told.
I think she's actually
- proud of herself for this.
- What's the big deal?
She would have gotten
married anyway.
I know, sweetie,
she's a doll.
I just wish she could learn to keep
her goddamn mouth shut.
Hey.
- Do I look horrible?
- No.
- Tell me the truth.
- Are you kidding?
You... are...
a beautiful,
gorgeous bride.
- I am?
- Yes.
You are. You look
perfect in that dress.
Elegant and classy
and sexy and fresh
and your skin
looks great.
And your face is big and plump
and healthy-looking.
- Oh, I could just eat you up!
- My face is plump?
Oh, God.
No, I didn't...
- My...
- I didn't mean plump as in plump.
You said my face
looks plump.
No, I meant plump
like "adorable."
- Liar!
- I did! Sweetheart...
I have a fat face on my wedding day
and you... you know it!
You do not have a fat face, a plump
face, she didn't mean it, I swear.
- She just told me my face looked fat.
- Sweetheart... honey...
You're... wh... 10 minutes before my
wedding ceremony? That's just mean.
Well, what about all the beautiful things
that I said with that?
- Can we focus on those?
- Right, right, right.
- Nice fat face, Hadley. Go get married.
- Hadley! Ha...
Hadley...
Okay.
She'll be fine.
...what potential
the bonds of marriage hold for us.
To walk together
into the fog of the future.
Two partners, together...
in concert...
in tandem...
in holy matrimony.
Is any bond as sacred
as this one?
Is any promise
more permanent?
# Girl #
# You'll be a woman #
# Soon #
# I love you so much
can't count all the ways #
# I'd die for you girl
and all they can say is #
# "He's not your kind" #
# They never get tired
of putting me down #
# And I'll never know
when I come around #
# What I'm gonna find #
- # Don't let them make up your mind #
- Emily.
Would you like
to dance with me?
I don't think so. I have
a stomachache right now.
Oh, bullshit.
Come on.
- # You'll be a woman soon #
- Come on.
I don't... I don't want her
or any of them to judge me.
- # Please #
- Okay.
- # Come take my hand #
- I don't want them judging me either.
# Girl #
# You'll be a woman...
soon #
# Soon #
# You'll need a man #
# I've been misunderstood
for all of my life #
# But that's what they're sayin',
it cuts like a knife #
# "The boy's no good" #
# When I've finally found
what I'm looking for #
# If they get the chance,
they'll end it for sure #
# They surely would #
# Baby, I've done
all I could #
# Now, it's up
to you girl #
I'll have, um,
a coke, please.
Coke?
Not drinking today?
Okay, nice talking
to you.
# Have you heard
the news? #
# It's all over town,
if you ain't heard it boys #
- # You'd better sit down #
- What is your problem?
I don't have a problem.
I'm having a nice day.
Running around with young women half
your age. I mean, what is that about?
You manipulate young women,
use your power and title
to seduce them, and get them
to run around with you.
- Yeah, so?
- It makes me sick,
the thought of you
with my daughter.
Well, here's a tip.
Don't think about it.
Goddamn.
# Betty Lou's
getting out tonight #
# Betty Lou's getting
out tonight #
# Betty Lou's
getting out tonight #
# She was bad,
her mama got mad #
# But her mama
said it's all right #
Who should
I sleep with, Terry?
Women like you?
- # Betty Lou's getting out tonight #
- Your age? My age?
- I don't. You know why?
- # Betty Lou #
- 'Cause younger women are nice.
- # It's all true #
You take them out,
they're actually grateful.
- "Oh, look a steak. Yummy."
- # It's really true #
You go for a walk
after dinner
the air smells nice.
They say, "Thank you.
this was nice.
This was fun.
You're funny.
Tee hee."
What should I do, Terry?
Settle down and marry
some pissed off
thing like you?
I'd rather have someone
come over and do dental work
every day,
from my backside
up through my ass.
# Come on!
Play it, Betty Lou #
You gonna slap me
in the face again?
No, probably not.
# Oh, come on! #
# Have you heard
the news? #
# It's all over town #
# If you ain't heard it, boys,
you'd better sit down #
A vodka and orange
juice, please.
# Brace yourself now
and take a deep breath #
# Grab hold of something,
gotta hold on tight #
- # Betty Lou's getting out tonight #
- There you are.
# First heard the rumor
down on 12th and Main... #
- What did you just say to Shep?
- Nothing.
He left. He told me
he couldn't handle you anymore.
- What did you say?
- We had a heart to heart.
It was needed.
# Betty Lou's
getting out tonight#
# Betty Lou's getting
out tonight #
# Betty Lou's
getting out tonight #
- Dance with me.
- # She was bad, her mama got mad #
# But her mama
said it's all right #
# All the boys are getting
ready and right #
# Betty Lou's
getting out tonight #
# Betty Lou #
# It's all true #
# It's really true #
# Well what do you
think about that, boys? #
# Come on #
Mmm, no.
Yes? What?
Emily, what's up?
Hold... hold on.
Hold on.
It's... it's Emily.
She's in the hospital.
What? Baby?
- I should go with you.
- No.
- I should go with you, Terry.
That's a long drive
this time of night.
Oh, no. I need you to stay here
in case Popeye wakes up.
I don't want her
to be scared, okay?
I'll be fine.
# Can I help it
if I'm bolder? #
if I'm faithful? #
At this point,
I can't say much.
Could be an ulcer,
could be pancreatic.
I don't know.
I'm at a loss for tonight.
What?
You're at a loss?
She's in a lot of pain.
I had to put her out and let her sleep.
I can't do anything
until the morning.
Well, what are you
gonna do in the morning?
Actually, I won't be here
in the morning.
I'm at the end
of a long shift,
but tests will be taken and tomorrow
night, when I come back
- I'll look at them and we'll talk.
- Tomorrow night?
Yes.
And what if I want
a second opinion?
Well, I haven't given you
a first one yet.
And if I want
a second opinion?
It's 4:30 am.
I don't think you're going to get
a strong one.
Well, why would they
do something like that?
Because I didn't give
them candy, that's why.
Great. You're standing at the door
with a bowl of candy, why can't you...
Because I don't accept
15-year-old-girls
with no costume on.
If you don't have a costume on,
- you shouldn't be allowed...
- Who cares?!
They're just using
Halloween to get candy!
Who cares?! It's Halloween!
Just give them candy!
It's okay to use a holiday for your
own selfish purposes?!
Oh, so what?!
So you'd rather just have them
toiletpaper your house?
Well, I didn't know it was gonna
be "felony or treat!"
I don't... I didn't think that
trick extended to felony!
Why would it kill you just to give
'em a few pieces of candy?!
- I don't understand that!
- Because there's gotta be
some kind of cut-off!
Shouldn't there be for Halloween?
Bob, what is with you
and your cut-offs
and your shouldn't there be
and should there be... who cares?!
She's really sick.
And the worst thing
is they don't know what it is.
I mean, it could be
an ulcer, it could be thyroid.
It, uh...
She can't eat and...
you know,
it could be cancer.
It could be...
it could be so many things.
I don't know
what it is.
I don't know what it is.
Oh God.
Directory assistance.
Um, yes, operator.
I would like, um,
I'm looking for directory assistance
for Karlstad, Sweden.
You said
"Karlstad, Sweden?"
Yes, thank you.
Look at you
all alone in here.
I like it like this.
Did you call Daddy
to tell him?
Um...
No, I didn't.
I don't hate him.
I mean, you know,
I know that you do,
but I've, uh, been
thinking about it,
and I just don't.
- Did you talk to the doctor?
- Yes.
Did he tell you
it wasn't cancer?
Yes, he did.
Thank God.
He thinks that whatever it is
might be stress-related.
An ulcer, maybe.
He's very worried that you're under
too much stress, Emily.
- I'm not stressed.
- Yes, you are.
You are.
You're mad.
Mad at me.
Mad at Daddy.
I can see that
all the time.
You've got a cloud
over your head.
We need to get it
to go away.
Give you some air.
The doctor's
very worried, Emily.
- Maybe yoga.
- Stop it.
- I'm serious.
- Well, so am I.
You can't dance or exercise
your way out of this.
You need
to get better, Emily.
I can take a lot,
but I couldn't take
losing you.
Why is that funny?
Because you just don't seem
to care all that much about me,
unless, like now,
I'm sick.
That's not true.
That's just not true.
I adore you.
- You do?
- I do!
I don't see that.
Well, what can I say?
You're like everybody else
in my life
you need to pay
closer attention to me.
Okay.
How's the wind, Dad?
Fantastic!
Whoa! Yeah!
Far out!
Woo!
The only thing
I understand about this...
is the screaming.
Whoo! Hey, hey!
So, how does
this work now?
- You going next, Gorden?
- Hell no. He won't jump.
He's too scared.
He's a watcher.
- You're not gonna jump?
- No, he won't jump.
I'll go again,
unless you wanna take a shot.
Nope. Not me.
I'm a watcher too.
Are you gonna marry
my mother?
I don't know.
It's, um...
it's tough.
Your mom, she's...
she's tricky.
She didn't
used to be.
Ask anyone.
She was always sweet.
You should
marry her, Denny.
Would that make you happy?
It would, yeah.
Mmn.
So, uh...
your daughter
asked me
if I was going
to marry you, today.
Oh, please.
That's a cheap shot.
What do you mean?
She's, um...
she's adorable.
I know she is.
It wasn't
a cheap shot, Terry.
What?
Bringing up what...
bringing up what Popeye said.
It wasn't, um...
it wasn't a cheap shot.
I have enough problems
right now, Denny.
I don't need you
using my daughter as a pawn.
What are you
talking about?
I have a child incredibly
ill in the hospital.
Another one's sleeping with a pervert
that you brought into her life,
so I don't want to get
into something silly
like a cute talk
about a marriage
that we both know
would be doomed from the start,
so you know what
I'm talking about. Don't.
I don't wanna hear
what Popeye said, no.
I am so sick
of being your bitch.
I put up with your shit,
because I know how much pain you're in.
But it's enough!
It's a tall order
for a patient motherfucker,
and I am the farthest
thing from that
that you're ever
gonna lay eyes on.
...tomorrow.
- Denny? Can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah, I-I-I can
do this tomorrow.
Bad news.
You ready?
Management has
a bug up their ass.
Okay, they've been
getting a lot of calls.
I've been trying
to keep this from you,
but they want
to renegotiate.
Renegotiate what?
Come on,
you know what.
They want you
to talk baseball.
What?
Either that or they want
to take us off the air.
- Good gag.
- It's not a gag, Denny.
I wish it was a gag.
It's not a gag.
You either talk baseball,
or we go off the air next week.
- I don't wanna talk baseball.
- Big deal.
They didn't want to have a sports
talk show in the middle of a day
with an all-rock format,
but I talked them into it.
Guess what?
You're a baseball star.
That's what people want to hear
from you. Baseball talk.
Nobody wants to hear your cooking
and your stock tips, Denny.
I'm sorry,
but it's true.
Saturday. Baseball talk.
They may even promo it.
Okay, Arthur, you're on in 5, 4, 3, 2...
better yet, you're on. Go.
All right, 101 WRIF, Detroit's home
of rock 'n' roll...
You're not even
gonna talk to me?
Denny?
I called you
eight times today.
Denny.
Hey, come on.
I was in a bad mood, okay?
Denny?
I want you
to talk to me.
So, I brought
baby pictures.
Oh, I wish you'd
brought him.
He's with the nanny,
we needed a night off.
So it's done? They're gonna build
a subdivision back there?
Yeah, next month,
they break ground.
It's gonna change
the view.
The view
could use changing.
She's coming, okay?
Big smiles...
and compliments,
but normal though.
Everything's normal,
she looks great,
you're great.
Everything's calm.
- Calm and great.
- Yes, all of us.
Why don't you just put
some valium in her soup?
Don't test me tonight,
Hadley, I mean it.
I want her calm.
- Hey you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Look at you. You look beautiful.
No, you really do.
You look fantastic.
What?
So... David and I
have some news.
- We're pregnant again.
- Jesus.
Really? Wow.
You... are...
Well, you... you don't
look stressed out to me.
What do you know?
You're a child.
Wh... what do you mean you want
to end it? You're dumping me?
No, not really.
I just...
want us to move on...
- see other people.
- And continue seeing each other?
No, probably not.
So, you don't want
to sleep together anymore?
I mean, did I do something wrong,
'cause we were doing great.
I can't believe
we're hearing this.
Hey, don't turn around, man.
Just pretend we're in a meeting, okay.
Is this because
your mother detests me?
'Cause that's not a big deal.
A lot of people do.
I-I-I wouldn't have the things
that I have in my life
if people detesting me
was a big deal, 'cause it isn't.
It's not about my mother,
Shep, It's me.
Is it 'cause I've been
falling asleep lately?
Been, y-y-you know, quick,
whatever you're saying?
'Cause I'm tired,
but basically the sex is good, right?
I don't know.
Yeah, I guess.
You guess?
You make a lot of noise
and a lot of very odd sounds
for someone that guesses.
I guess I've just gotten
good at faking it.
I'm sorry.
Okay, look, I just
want to move on with my life.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
You know what?
It was inevitable.
Don't be sorry.
You're right.
It was bound to happen.
- Right?
- Yeah, I guess so.
Okay.
We gonna be able to
work together?
I mean... me producing
morning drive and you in the afternoons?
Yeah. Yeah,
it's gonna be fine.
- Okay.
- It's gonna be fine. It doesn't matter
'cause you're not gonna
be here that much longer anyway.
- What?
- This place is too small-time for you.
You're gonna be
long gone, real soon.
Now he's kissing
her ass, now?
Okay, I gotta get
back to work.
- All right? Okay.
- Go, go, go.
- Hello?
- Hey, come to the window.
What?
Come to the window.
I'm not a liar.
I really do bungee jump.
You are so stoned.
Yeah, I know.
Whoa!
Oh!
Gorden, shh.
Oh! Hold it.
Whoa! Whoa!
Don't worry about that.
Go to the back and start working.
All right, all right,
I got it.
Oh, hey.
Hello, Shep.
How are you?
I'm doin' good.
- You and Denny still not talkin'?
- No.
No, it's been awhile.
You know, it's been hard.
You know...
I'm not as bad as you
have me painted out to be, Terry.
Just so you know.
I promised myself
if I ever ran into you,
I would say that.
So there, I said it.
I should come over
some night with a bottle,
and you and I
should sit and talk.
- God...
- What?
What? You gave me that whole lecture
at Hadley's wedding.
- What lecture?
- About sleeping with women my own age.
You know, I'd love to sit
with you and talk to you
and give you my side
of that story.
You know, without
getting slapped around.
Oh, so you wanna come over
and sleep with me?
- Is that it, Shep?
- No, I didn't say that.
I said I'd like to have
a drink with you.
Hey, I'm not
drinking, okay?
Good, then we'll hang!
We'll hang...
or talk about you and Denny.
I mean, this is silly,
- you guys should be talking.
- It's silly, huh?
So you wanna tell me
how to live my life? Is that it?
Oh, God. Shep, you know, you were doing
better when you just wanted to screw me.
- What was that?!
- Hey...
you are a piece
of work. I gotta shop.
- Move back.
- Go.
Go.
- Shep!
Oh, Jeez!
Just for the record,
I never wanted to screw you!
Got it, got it.
Heavens to Murgatroids.
It's Denny Davies.
That promo's on disk two,
loaded and ready to go, Art.
You hit on Terry?
- What?
- You hit on Terry in a grocery store?
You guys are talking now.
That's good.
We are now. We're talking about
what an asshole you are.
Come on. I was talking
about something very innocent.
I was gonna pay
a little social call.
No, you wanted
to go over there with a bottle of wine.
You wanted to...
you wanted to screw her.
Screw her?
No, I didn't.
I wa... I was talking
about something very innocent.
Right out of "Gunsmoke."
This is the problem
with being a deviant,
everyone sees you
as so one-dimensional.
Don't... no, don't do your rap on me.
I know you.
You were hitting
on her.
I wasn't hitting on her, Den.
You're over-reacting.
Yeah, you were
and I'll tell you something else.
The whole Andy thing?
That was wrong.
It should have
never happened.
You had no business
being with her daughter.
I should've
said something. l...
- Go, Art.
- I don't know why I didn't.
Terry's right
to despise you.
She's right
to despise me?
What are you, a victim
of Stockholm Syndrome?
Come on. This is me.
Don't do this.
I knocked off
a great piece of ass...
What the fuck
are you doing?!
Shep, stop it!
Just stop it.
Okay, Arthur,
do your list...
and your promo and the give-away
Go right into the give-away.
You know what, Denny?
Everybody won here.
Okay? She went from being
a production assistant
to a producer in record time,
so you do the math.
I'll talk baseball.
I will...
but I don't want you producing
my show anymore, Shep.
I'm done with you.
I mean, I'll say what they want,
but you're off
of my show.
Now you want
to tell them
or should I?
Sorry, Arthur.
It's not your year,
is it, Sparky?
- Do you want me to dry your back?
- Jesus!
Oh, you scared
the hell out of me.
Oh!
You have no boundaries.
You have quite an ass,
know that?
What are you doing?
Have a drink?
No thanks.
Just, um... I'm not
drinking right now.
Do you want
to stay for dinner?
What do you think?
I didn't just come over
to see you naked.
You know,
been there, done that.
Gonna be late,
ladies!
Let's move!
Thanks for going
to this.
Oh, I know it means
a lot to you.
Mom, did you call him?
Did you ever call him?
No, I didn't.
And you know... you know,
I don't need to.
The doctor says
you're improving.
You're not wiggin' out
about this, are you? Stressing out?
Jeez.
Terry?
I don't mean to be the girl here,
but we're gonna be late.
People don't know
how to love.
They bite
rather than kiss,
and they slap
rather than stroke.
Maybe it's because they realize
how easy it is for love to go bad,
to become
suddenly impossible...
unworkable,
an exercise in futility.
So they avoid it
and seek solace in angst
and fear
and aggression,
which are always there
and readily available.
Or maybe sometimes...
they just don't have
all the facts.
In here?
Holy mother of shit.
What is it?
You'd better go back, okay?
Just...
- I'll be right there. Look... no, no.
- No, what is it?
We pulled this jacket up,
found a wallet.
Go back, Terry.
Look, I mean it, honey.
- I mean it. Go back, go back
- No, I don't wanna go back.
Terry, please.
- Give me the flashlight.
- Baby, no.
- No.
- Give it to me. Give it to me.
Give me the flashlight, Denny.
Give it to me!
It's an old water well.
All covered up.
He must have...
come out to walk
the property
and fallen through.
You guys sh-should
go call the police.
Oh my God.
Oh God.
...to honor...
...our sense of loss.
What is the price
we've paid?
we've paid for...
Anger and resentment
can stop you in your tracks.
That's what I know now.
It needs nothing
to burn but the air and the life
that it swallows
and smothers.
- What? What?
- Okay.
Whoa!
It's real, though...
the fury,
even when it isn't.
It can change you...
turn you...
mold you and shape you
into someone you're not.
The only upside
to anger, then...
is the person you become...
Good job.
...hopefully someone
that wakes up one day
and realizes they're
not afraid of its journey,
someone that knows
that the truth is, at best,
a partially told story.
That anger,
like growth,
comes in spurts
and fits
and in its wake,
leaves a new chance
at acceptance
and the promise
of calm.
Then again,
what do I know?
I'm only a child.
# How many roads
you've traveled #
# How many dreams
you've chased #
# Across sand
and sky and gravel #
# Looking for one
safe place, yeah #
# Yeah, yeah #
# One safe place, yeah #
# Will you make
a smoother landing #
# When you break
your fall from grace #
# Into the arms
of understanding #
# Looking for one
safe place? Yeah #
# Yeah, yeah #
# One safe place, yeah #
# Whoa, life
is trial by fire #
# And love's
the sweetest taste #
# And I pray
it lifts us higher #
# To one safe place, yeah #
# Yeah, yeah #
# One safe place, yeah #
# How many roads
we've traveled #
# How many dreams
we've chased #
# Across sand and sky
and gravel #
# Looking for one
safe place, yeah #
# Yeah, yeah #
# One safe place, yeah #
# Yeah, yeah. #