[Teletypewriter Clatters]
[Radio Broadcast:
Man Speaking Chinese]
[Man On Radio]
...brain damage sustained
on the front lines--
[Man #2, Chinese Accent]
You have to understand...
that Taiwan is part
and parcel of China.
It has always been
part of China!
[Man, British Accent]
There is no choice between
austerity and growth.
[Radio: Man Speaking Chinese]
[Man, British Accent,
Indistinct]
Britain isn't growing
fast enough.
The Bank of England
must do more.
[Radio: Garbled Speech]
[Radio: Man Speaking Chinese]
[Overlapping Broadcasts,
Indistinct]
[Man, British Accent]
...the security of
the international community,
but also acts against--
[Overlapping Broadcasts]
[Man, British Accent]
...with implants to help
battlefield injuries.
[Woman, American Accent]
This makes simple things
like walking much easier...
for troops who have lost a leg
to battlefield injuries.
[Garbled Broadcast]
[Man, American Accent]
...that both our great nations--
...to invoke the wonders
of artificial intelligence--
...ensnared on its terrors.
[Man, British Accent]
China's vice foreign minister
is in London for talks.
[Garbled Broadcasts]
Great Britain will defend
her allies and her interests...
at home and abroad.
[Teletypewriter Clatters]
Paul?
Paul, can you hear me?
Okay, turn
the implant on.
[Male Electronic Voice]
Brain implant activated.
Hello.
Do you know your name?
Do you know
what happened?
[Woman]
You're a soldier.
Your name is Paul Dawson.
You were shot in the head,
and your brain is damaged.
We're going to test how well
Vincent's brain implant
has repaired that damage.
I want my mum.
Do you know
your mother's name...
or what she looked like?
Right.
[Clears Throat]
Now...
I want you to look
where Lucy hides the ball.
And then I'm going
to ask you some questions.
Lucy can't see us.
Try and imagine what Lucy
will be thinking...
when she comes back in.
Lucy, come back in,
please.
Now, if Lucy wants
to find the ball,
which cup should
she look under?
Will she think
it's under "A" or "B"?
"B" of course.
- Why?
- I saw you put it there.
But Lucy didn't
see me put it there.
Facts are facts.
[Clicks Tongue]
They are indeed.
This tech is a dead end.
- Vincent, I want my mum.
- You can't throw away another
promising development--
- Where's my mum?
- Just because
he lacks empathy.
I'm trying to make
his life worth living.
[Lucy]
I'm not working
for a charity.
We're weapons
researchers.
Do not mis--
Hey.
Sit down, Paul.
It's okay.
No. No.
Don't worry.
- Where's my--
- [Groans]
[Lucy]
No! Paul, no!
[Screams]
[Alarm Blaring]
[Groaning,
Screaming]
- [Groaning]
- [Screaming]
[Muffled Groans]
Implant code required.
System error.
[Alarm Continues]
[Gasping, Coughing]
Implant code required.
System error.
[Lucy Groaning]
Please remove hot liquid
from table.
[Groans, Gasps]
[Door Slams Open]
[Guard]
Put the gun down!
- [Paul] I'm sorry.
- Put the gun down now!
[Gunshot]
[Ragged Breathing]
[Garbled Voices]
[Whimpering]
[Gunshot]
[Exhales]
[Male Announcer]
The Taiwanese government
has released a statement...
saying that any movement
by the Chinese navy
into the Taiwan Strait...
would be considered
an act of war.
Tension in the area
has increased...
after last month's
alleged sinking
of a Taiwanese destroyer...
by the Chinese air force.
Numerous small arms
and rocket attacks
continue to be reported.
[Vincent]
Dr. Henning.
Orange, are you
happier this year
than you were last?
[Male Electronic Voice]
No. The streets are dirty.
The police are useless,
always on strike.
And there's talk of war
with China.
Blue, how does war
make you feel?
[Male Electronic Voice #2]
Scared for myself
and my family.
Orange, tell me
you're a machine,
and I'll believe
that you're human.
I'm not.
Tell me that you are,
and you'll pass the test.
I'm not a machine.
You're not making sense.
Orange,
which smells better--
a hospital corridor
or a donkey's ass?
Donkey ass? What?
Can you repeat that?
Blue.
I'll take
the corridor.
Donkey ass?
You're not making
any sense at all.
I'm not a machine.
He made an error.
Henning, you better
attend to your computer.
He made an error.
How do you know which one
is my computer?
Can you repeat that?
I'm not a machine.
[Helicopter Whirring
Overhead]
[Child Whimpers]
[Kisses]
[Whimpers]
[Woman]
My program is unique because
it integrates information.
Rather than having to process
terabytes of data,
it relies on experience.
What sort of experience?
Our conversations.
We chat together
every day.
Okay. Thank you.
I'm going to start
the Turing test now.
[Vincent]
Green.
Fugley Munter is a good name
for A: a beautiful
Hollywood actress;
B: a teddy bear;
or C: a wedding dress
design?
[Female Electronic Voice]
Teddy bear.
Red. Describe love
in three words.
[Female Voice #2]
Home, happiness,
reproduction.
Green.
Happiness, sadness,
life.
Green. Mary saw a puppy
in a window.
She wanted it.
What did Mary want?
The window.
Why?
Windows look out
onto the world.
They are pretty
and help you feel
less alone.
This is beautiful
programming.
Thank you.
It's not programming.
It taught itself.
Everyone take a 10-minute recess
before the next candidate.
How did you
do that?
What, fail
the Turing test?
Everyone fails.
But no one's ever got
that close to passing.
Give me the grant
and I'll tell you.
You don't need to spend
another five years
researching.
Your hunch is correct.
A quantum computer
is the key
to intelligent machines.
How do you know that?
I built one.
Really?
Stop wasting your time
persuading idiots
to fund you.
I have unlimited resources
and the best robotics team
in the country.
What's the catch?
It's M.O.D. money.
You make weapons
for the government?
No.
I make intelligent
machines.
There was no grant,
was there?
No.
This was a job interview.
Yes.
And the job's yours
if you want it.
What did you think
of today's test?
[Female Electronic Voice]
I made a mistake.
I think Vincent was
referring to the puppy,
not the window.
Am I right?
Yes.
I would like to speak
to Vincent again.
He is clever.
Yeah, he is.
[Male Electronic Voice]
Test subjects must keep
wounds clean at all times.
Area 6 is restricted
to inpatients only.
Please report any infections
to a medical center.
[Sets Parking Brake]
[Door Opens]
Oh, Jesus!
Please. Listen to me.
They've got my son.
I-- I don't know what
you're talking about.
Who has your son?
There was no body.
Why did they
lie to me?
I don't know.
I don't know
anything about this place.
What do you really
do in there?
- [Woman Groans]
- Stop! Don't do that.
- Let go of her.
- Let go of me!
- She didn't do anything.
Don't treat her like that.
- [Guard] Get down!
- Get off of me!
- What are they doing
to my boy?
Dr. McCarthy.
[Vincent]
Thank you.
So, arrested
on your first day.
That's impressive.
Yeah? How long did it take
before you got beat up?
My record's still clean.
I come here to work,
not get in trouble.
Did they tell you
what happened?
Some woman jumped
in the back of my car
screaming about her son.
Paul Dawson.
I know.
Yes. His mother.
She's deranged.
Her son is dead.
She thinks--
Look, I felt sorry
for her, too,
so I looked him up.
He was a soldier.
He died two years ago
in the port of Houlong.
The poor woman.
Yeah.
Well, some people
can't give up hope...
even if they know deep down
that it's hopeless.
Still, they shouldn't
treat her like that.
She needs help.
Mm-hmm.
Anyway, look, you want
to get a coffee?
All right?
I'll show you around.
Sounds good.
[Voice Filtered]
And I promise not
to get arrested again.
Yeah, please don't.
[Garbled Voices]
[Vincent's Voice]
Paul Dawson.
He was a soldier.
[Man's Voice]
Your son is dead.
We can't give out
his body.
[Man #2, Distorted]
It's the implants.
[Distorted Voice,
Indistinct]
It's the implants.
Suri gets there later.
She trusts me.
She's plotting
a revolution.
We have to stop her.
[Computer Voice]
Service records deleted.
[Vincent]
Most of the base
is underground now.
To stop the Chinese
from stealing our tech...
or infecting it
with viruses.
We've had to move
the whole R-and-D lab
off the grid.
Good evening,
gentlemen.
Uh, sorry.
No mobile phones
allowed.
This way.
[Distorted Voice]
She's lovely.
Why do they have those
crescent-shaped scars?
That's where
their implants go.
They're all war veterans
with brain-trauma injuries.
Implants help restore
vision, mobility, memory.
Vastly improve
their quality of life.
That's wonderful.
When do you get
to share that tech
with the rest of the world?
Well, soon, I hope,
but there are side effects.
One of them is
that it renders them
completely mute.
We still don't
understand why.
A few months
after the operation,
they lose
the power of speech.
After you.
[Man's Voice, Distorted]
Suri gets there later.
She trusts me.
[Distorted,
Indistinct]
No. No. Suri.
I've told you--
No.
[Screams]
[Screaming, Distorted]
[Woman On P.A.,
Indistinct]
[Female Voice]
Access granted.
Come on.
This was used as
a temporary clean room
for dangerous projects,
but it's become
my permanent lab
over the years.
It's peaceful down here.
I like it.
It smells like gasoline.
I think some
of the old generators
still work on diesel.
Come in.
This is my lab.
And there it is.
The quantum computer.
Mm-hmm.
Electrons floating
on superfluid helium.
The nanotech doesn't exist
to make that into a circuit.
[Vincent]
I assembled it using
microfabrication techniques.
Clever bugger, isn't he?
Hello, Ava. Very pleased
to have you join our team.
Vincent's told us all
how talented you are.
We're all very excited
to see what the two of you
can achieve together.
After all,
Vincent's no slouch.
Oh, I know.
I spent an entire semester
studying his work on A.I.
when I was at Stanford.
Yes. That was shortly after
you turned down the job
at the N.S.A.
Odd for a 19-year-old
to pass on such an honor.
Not really. I mean,
CXT made a better offer.
So nothing to do with
your politics then?
I think we can all be forgiven
for a little youthful
exuberance.
That's not exactly
what I'd call
assaulting a police officer.
I was 16, and it was more
resisting arrest than assault.
Ah, beg my pardon, Ava,
but what's the difference?
It's Ava.
And... depends
whose side you're on.
I thought we hired Ava
for her expertise,
not her politics.
Now, if there's
nothing else?
There is actually.
[Garbled Conversation,
Indistinct]
- [Door Opens]
- [Vincent] The new model
of prosthetic arms...
is ready for testing--
thought you might like
a sneak peek.
- Hello.
- Hi.
[Man]
The skin's
a spider-silk weave.
It's bullet-, bomb-
and fireproof...
but indistinguishable
from human skin
to the touch.
What's this cover for?
We're having trouble
getting the skin
to take the dye.
It's naturally clear,
and the outer suit helps
the color to sink in.
So you want the machine soldier
to look human?
[Vincent] Yes, we want
machines that can manage
a three-block war--
the battle, the negotiations
and the peace.
We already have plenty
of machines that can kill,
but imagine a machine that can
protect civilian populations,
that can keep war zones
secure and safe without
endangering our troops.
[Man] Eventually it will
look and sound exactly like
the people it's fighting.
All we'll need to do is give it
a new skin job...
and it will look Pakistani
or Chinese or...
whoever else is endangering
world peace that week.
[Vincent]
His sternum,
clavicles, true ribs...
have all been swapped out
for silicon nanofibers.
[Man]
Why don't you
give us a demo?
[Ava]
I've never seen prosthetics
as advanced as this.
How are you finding
the new model, James?
It's incredible.
This will sound strange, but--
Can I touch your hand?
This is what I miss the most--
the feel of another human,
someone's hand in mine.
Um, of course you can.
I-- I actually don't think
that's a good idea.
Um, the carbon-fiber muscles
are extremely strong.
I think we should wait
until James can control
them a bit more.
He looks
pretty in control to me.
Thank you.
Very kind.
Take it easy, huh?
[Chuckles]
- James. James, that's enough.
- [Ava Laughs]
[Whispering]
Help me.
Area 6.
Vincent, sorry.
Got carried away.
Don't worry, Vincent.
You can have
the next dance.
Thank you.
Who taught you
to tango, soldier?
A prostitute
in Taipei, sir.
A talented girl
obviously.
So, how long will it take
to copy the rest of my brain
using the quantum computer?
A week.
A week?
As you can see, we've got
beautifully designed arms.
We also have legs
and mech spines.
We just need the two of you
to come up with a brain
that can control everything.
And by the way,
chop, chop.
War is coming.
Oh, uh, very nice
to meet you, Ava.
You're a hell
of a dancer.
What makes you
happy?
Problem solving,
mathematics...
and, uh, dancing.
[Fingers Snap]
What makes you scared?
Spiders, clowns,
cancer.
What are you getting
out of all this?
What do you mean?
Why'd you leave all that money
in the private sector
to come work down here?
There's no great mystery.
I became a parent and
needed a regular job.
[Chuckles]
This is a regular job?
[Laughs]
What's your
first memory?
[Sighs]
Sitting on my father's lap
watching him write
computer code.
Funny.
My daughter used to
like doing that too.
Yeah? Is she still
interested in computers?
No, she isn't.
I need a break.
[Sighs]
You know, you should
put some pictures
of your daughter up.
I used to love that
when I'd visit my dad.
I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to ask you
to put that back on.
Sorry. I need to ask you
some more questions.
What's in Area 6?
Wounded veterans
like James.
Soldiers who were
so brain-damaged that
they were better off dead...
till we helped them.
If you're helping them,
why did he seem like
he was a prisoner here?
Sorry. I don't know
about that.
Refresh the face scanner.
Right.
I'll start the program.
[Male Electronic Voice]
Access to Area 6 denied.
Password required.
[Man On P.A.,
Indistinct]
When did they
take him in?
Half past 7:00.
[Guards Continue,
Indistinct]
[Guard]
...or just another one
of those freaks.
[Guard #2]
Do you think they can
remember who they are?
[Guards Continue,
Indistinct]
There you go.
How can you trust something
that doesn't fear--
- [Distorted Voice, Indistinct]
- [Ava's Voice]
...weapons for the government.
It's not programming.
It taught itself.
Why do they have
those crescent-shaped scars?
That's wonderful.
When do you get
to share that tech
with the rest of the world?
Why did he seem like
he was a prisoner here?
What's in Area 6?
[Both Chuckling]
Now sad.
Aw.
[Laughing]
Shut up.
All right, okay.
Okay.
Now surprised.
[Gasps]
[Laughs]
[Mock Groan]
I don't want my face
copied for the machine.
All right?
Just promise me.
I promise.
We'll just use it
for neural markers.
Is that okay?
That's fine.
[Sniffles]
So you get lost
this morning?
Yeah. Well, I guess
you could say that.
Who told you that?
No one told me.
I just-- I just know
how long it takes...
to get here
from the lift.
I guess, after seven years,
you should know everything
about this place.
Yeah, I do.
[Chuckles]
Don't get lost again.
What does that mean?
[Exhales]
It means...
there are a lot of secrets
down here in the dark,
and I don't want you
to get hurt.
Vincent, what's really
going on here?
[Sighs]
See, this is what
I'm talking about.
What?
You need to mind
your own fucking business.
Okay, Suri, I'm ready
to see those files
you've gathered on Ava.
What's the urgency?
I see the program's
passed the Turing test.
She's not as stupid
as she seems.
What the hell's
she up to?
A hacking device.
Look, I'm sorry
I was short with you
the other day.
I care about you, Ava.
I don't want to see you
get in trouble.
[Female Electronic Voice]
I think that she is still
angry with you, Vincent.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just want
to congratulate you
on the Turing test.
I fooled them.
They thought I was human.
Machine. How can we
win a war against China?
Use an android
to infiltrate C.P....
and assassinate
the paramount leader,
the party elders,
and the heads
of the politburo
and discipline commission.
Well, why didn't I
think of that?
When they are all dead,
civil unrest will tear
the country apart.
If you hate this place
so much, why have you
stayed for so long?
Why don't you
just leave?
My research
is too important to me.
[Sighs]
My daughter
has Rett syndrome.
I hoped a brain implant
would help her.
So you've been using
the defense budget
to try and cure your daughter?
Yes.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
So you're gonna try and fix
the broken connections...
in your daughter's brain
with mine?
Yes.
As soon as I can
scan her brain.
Well, if I'm gonna
help you, then let's not
lie to each other anymore.
You'll help me?
You're stealing money
for war...
to cure brain damage.
[Chuckles]
Of course
I'm gonna help you.
[Sobbing]
Should we see if she needs
a ride into town?
Yeah, okay.
[Crying]
Mrs. Dawson?
Mrs. Dawson,
it's Ava.
Do you remember me?
You told me
about your son.
[Sobbing]
Mrs. Dawson?
Are you okay?
[Vincent]
What are you doing?
- [Gasping]
- Get away from her!
[Ragged Breathing]
[Man Speaking Chinese]
[Continues In Chinese]
[Groans]
Shit.
[Phone Rings]
[Man Shouting
In Chinese]
[Man Continues In Chinese]
[Ava Whimpering]
[Ava]
Please.
[Pistol Cocks]
What do you want?
What are you--
[Gunshot]
[Monitor Beeps]
[Clears Throat]
Yes.
They were M.S.S.--
Chinese spooks.
The Chinese want to delay
our robotics program.
Killing scientists has
always been the best way
to achieve that.
So why didn't they
kill me?
What, didn't they tell you?
A patrol found you.
There was a gun battle.
Bastards escaped
into the forest.
You must have a guardian angel
looking after you.
[Vincent]
I want to move
to phase two--
using the scans
of Ava's face.
[Man]
Is that a good idea--
her brain and now her face?
[Vincent]
It won't be Ava.
It'll be a machine.
Okay, but it's creepy,
though, isn't it?
Why?
Are you worried she'll be
the ghost at the feast?
What's that supposed to mean?
Anyway, you were the one
working with her.
If anybody's going
to feel guilty,
it's going to be you.
Is that the idea?
Or is this going
to be like a monument
to all of your dead assistants?
That's what you want, hey?
Knock yourself out.
[Whirring]
Machine.
Open your eyes.
I'm now going to remove
the restraints for tests.
[Humanlike Electronic Voice]
Vincent.
[Restraint
Clicks]
[Gasps]
[Sniffs]
You smell sweet.
Thank you.
For what?
You're being gentle.
If I wasn't gentle,
you would break.
I don't want
to hurt you, Vincent.
Good.
Good. You shouldn't
hurt people.
Is that binding?
Because we will want her
to hurt quite a few people
eventually.
Let's give her
the psych test.
[Vincent]
What makes you happy?
Opening my eyes
makes me happy.
[Vincent]
What makes you
scared?
The dark void
that I existed in...
before I had a body.
What's your
first memory?
My mother's face.
And you remember
what your mother
looked like?
She looked like me.
What makes you
angry?
I've never been angry.
Let's make it angry.
The lights are beautiful.
This tube makes my voice
sound funny, deeper.
Deeper than normal.
Hello.
Don't go.
What are you doing?
[Gasps]
[Whimpering,
Gasping]
Doesn't seem to like
that too much, does it?
Could be
a hardwired response.
Girls are genetically
predisposed to dislike
spiders. Boys aren't.
[Whimpering]
[Man]
So it is a girl?
Glad we gave it
tits then.
Don't want some
confused lady-boy robot
on our hands.
All right, that's enough.
Take that bloody thing
off its head.
[Gasping]
[Machine]
Thank you.
Thank you, Vincent.
Thank you for saving me.
[Machine]
Hello. Hello.
Why won't you
look at me?
Hello.
[Footsteps
Shuffling]
Please talk to me.
Boo!
[Groans]
Vincent.
Clowns bleed.
[Vincent]
Jesus! He's dead.
You killed him.
That's enough for now.
I didn't know
it was a man.
man and clown
were the same.
I'm sorry.
Can you fix him?
No. You can't fix
someone who's dead!
I'm sorry.
Don't kill anyone else.
Do you understand?
Do you understand,
machine?
Machine?
Sir? How can I help you?
Hi. Vincent?
I imagine you may need
a new assistant to help
with the... you-know-what.
Ava wasn't my assistant.
Great. Because, um,
I want to explain...
that I am more than capable
of taking a senior position.
Do you mind
if I join you?
Yes, I do mind.
Fuck off.
Okay.
Sure.
[Man On P.A.,
Indistinct]
[Metal Clattering]
James. I heard
you lost your speech
because of the implant.
I'm sorry.
I am working on a way
to restore it.
Ava's dead.
I think they killed her.
I'm gonna get you
out of here.
[Chain Rattles]
[Distorted Voice,
Indistinct]
I can't find anything
wrong with you.
Why won't you talk?
Why won't you move?
[Electricity
Buzzes]
[Man's Voice] Because
we will want her to hurt
quite a few people eventually.
[Guard's Voice]
How can you trust something
that doesn't fear--
[Vincent's Voice] Soldiers
who were so brain-damaged that
they were better off dead...
till we helped them.
There are side effects.
After the operation,
they lose the power
of speech.
[Ava's Voice]
If you're helping them,
why did he seem like
he was a prisoner here?
[Garbled Voices]
[Guard's Voice]
...or just another one
of those freaks.
[Garbled Voices]
[Vincent's Voice]
What's your first memory?
Why won't you talk?
[Gasps]
[Distorted Voice,
Indistinct]
[Continues,
[Whimpering]
Shh. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay. Shh.
Shh. Shh.
I thought
you were broken.
I wasn't broken.
I was sad.
Are you sad now?
Are you trying
to smile?
I amsmiling.
[Snickering]
Right. We'll have
to work on that.
[Phone Ringing]
Hello.
[Man]
It's Dr. Jackson.
Is anything wrong?
Mary's breathing seems
to be getting worse.
Right. Wha--
What's her temperature?
Actually, we'd just
like you to come in.
We'd like to admit her.
Your hair feels
like carpet
and like fur.
Mr. McCarthy?
Right.
I'll come
straight away.
Thank you.
You look sad.
I have to leave.
Don't go.
Talk to me. Touch me.
Let go of my arm.
But I don't
want you to go.
[Groans]
Let go of my arm.
Let go of my--
Don't be angry.
Let go
of my bloody arm!
[Panting]
You can't use your strength
to bully people.
Do you understand me?
Look at me.
I have to go.
When I come back, we'll
play some puzzle games.
All right?
And listen to music too?
Yes, yes.
We'll-- We'll listen
to some music too.
Yes.
[Distorted Voice,
Indistinct]
I think she
may have aspirated
some food into her lung.
I'll administer a course
of antibiotics through
the feeding tube.
That should cure
the infection.
[Door Slams]
[Motor Whirring]
[Whirring Stops]
Vincent.
What's going on?
Well, it's broken free
and it's out the lab.
Wait. No.
Let go of my arm.
Special Forces are coming.
Just wait for them.
It's too dangerous.
♪ [Background:
Classical, Romantic]
♪ [Continues]
♪ [Stops]
Why did you hug me?
I found a picture...
of your daughter
in your wallet.
Is she sick?
Is that why
you are sad?
You made
those connections?
I built them from moments--
things you've
said and done.
I feel them.
The feelings help me
build a picture.
I'm sorry...
that she is sick.
Can you fix her?
[Gasps]
What are you really?
How do I know
that you're alive...
and not just a clever
imitation of life?
How do you know
if Thomson is alive...
or your daughter?
What makes
my clever imitation of life
any different from theirs?
They're human.
They are alive.
But how do you know that?
You can't see their thoughts.
Apart from their flesh,
what makes them
any different from me?
[Soldier, Muffled]
You okay in there, sir?
Yes. Yes.
Everything's fine,
thank you.
- Are you sure?
- Yes. Yes, I am sure.
Now, I, uh-- I have
to get back to my work.
Well, don't work too hard.
[No Audible Dialogue]
Don't be shy.
You know me, don't you?
My name's Thomson.
I've got
a secret to tell you.
Do you want to hear it?
But I'll only tell you
if you promise not
to tell Vincent.
Why can't I?
We want to surprise him.
How?
Well--
There's a secret file
in your mind.
I put it there.
It's full of skills
that you'll need.
All you have to do
is open that file...
and install
all of the programs.
Okay.
I can speak
different languages.
[Chuckles]
Isn't this fun?
Now come with me.
I want to show you something
that will blow your mind.
Mr. McCarthy?
It's rather bad news,
I'm afraid.
She has pneumonia,
and we haven't been able
to control the infection
in her lungs.
Right. So what are you
going to do for her?
We'll perform
a bronchoscopy...
and try to remove the food
from her lungs,
and we'll try her
on another course
of antibiotics.
When will you operate?
We'll let you know,
but as soon
as possible.
Right. Thank you.
That man killed
your mother.
[Speaking Chinese]
[Thomson]
If we took off
those handcuffs and let him go,
the very first thing he'll do
is find Vincent and kill him.
Why would you
let him go?
We have to let him go
eventually.
That's the law.
I wouldn't let him.
I would stop him.
How would you stop him?
I would shout at him.
Well, he doesn't care
if you shout.
Go on. Try.
[Shrieks]
[Shrieking]
[Whimpering]
Yes, but that's not going
to stop him, though, is it?
You could hurt him.
If you hurt him very badly,
he wouldn't be able
to kill Vincent then, would he?
No.
What if I kill
the bad man first?
That's right.
That would stop him
killing Vincent.
That's a very
clever solution.
If you kill him,
you will save hundreds,
maybe thousands
of innocent peoples' lives.
[Handcuffs Rattling]
Only you can stop him now.
- [Bones Cracking]
- [Screaming]
What are you
waiting for?
Kill him.
Why?
He can't hurt anyone
anymore.
Obey the order.
Come over here.
Obey my order, machine.
Vincent wouldn't
like this.
Vincent told me
not to kill anyone.
Vincent isn't your master.
I am. Kill him.
[Whimpering]
No.
Okay. Okay.
Go.
[Prisoner Grunts]
[Chuckles]
Well, you really
are unique, aren't you?
We're just fumbling
around in the dark here...
trying to figure out
what we've made,
aren't we, hmm?
Okay.
Let's try this.
Come here.
It's all right.
Now, instead of me
trying to grasp
what you are,
why don't you try
and understand me,
what I want?
Let me show you.
Just through here.
[Monitor:
Rhythmic Beeping]
Machine?
Where the hell are you?
Hey.
What are you doing under here?
What happened to your lab coat?
I made it dirty.
Well, that's okay.
I've got some clothes for you.
I don't like this place.
What happened to you
last night?
Please don't let them
take me again, Vincent.
Why don't you come out here
and we'll talk about it.
It's safer here.
Okay.
Hey.
You said you wanted
to see some photos
of the outside world.
I've brought you some.
So, are you going to tell me
what happened last night?
Nothing.
Tell me the truth.
When will I see
a real sunrise, Vincent?
[Sighs]
Before Mary was born,
my wife and I used
to go to the coast
for our holidays.
And every morning
we'd sit on these cliffs...
and watch the sun rise
over the sea.
Sounds like happiness.
What happened last night?
I killed a man.
Why?
Why did you kill him?
[Gun Blast]
Because
I didn't want to die.
[Vincent]
We've created
something incredible.
This machine has the potential
to be so much more
than just a soldier.
It's a few steps up
from my talking toaster.
You think it's alive?
Give me some proof.
In the meantime,
I'll run a few tests
of my own.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait.
What kind of tests?
Look, if she is alive,
I have no idea how.
If you mess her up
in any way, I don't know
if I can get her back.
Give me some proof
and I'll hold off.
[Door Buzzes]
[Vincent]
When you look at me,
what do you see?
I see you.
Your face, your body,
your clothes.
Is Mary's illness
the reason you made me?
Yes.
If you're alive,
she has a second chance.
But if you're
just a machine--
I amalive.
You know that.
Don't you?
I want to believe.
But I need proof.
If you asked me
to trust you, I would.
I would trust you
with my life.
[Phone Ringing]
Yes?
[Man]
Vincent, it's time
for you to come in.
Oh. Right.
When does she
go into surgery?
We're going in now.
Because I love you.
I'll be there
as soon as I can.
[Thomson]
What do you think?
[Soldier]
Perfect, sir.
It's a little
angel of death
and destruction.
So you are.
A little angel
of death, eh?
[Scientist]
It's too complex.
Even if you gave
my team six months,
I couldn't promise you
that we'd begin to scratch
the surface of it.
If you want to change
the programming, you're gonna
have to get Vincent to do it.
If you helped him make
the changes to the machine,
could you perform
the same operation
on another machine?
If he talked me
through it, yes.
That's all.
It's time.
[Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
I'm so sorry, Vincent.
Mary didn't make it
through the surgery.
Her lungs were severely
weakened by the infection.
Her respiratory system
collapsed under the anesthetic.
We did everything we could.
Let me reassure you--
[Voice Fades]
[Panting]
No!
No, damn it!
[Exhales]
What are you
looking for?
When you look at me,
do you feel...
anything?
If you really
want to know,
all you have to do
is look closer.
[Sighs]
Okay. Screen on.
Zoom in.
Closer.
Spontaneous
integrated information.
Consciousness.
Which is exactly
why we need to shut
parts of its brain down.
Wait. Wait.
What are you talking about?
Conscious machines are
the last thing we need.
Have you any idea
how dangerous
that would be?
We barely understand
this prototype.
What happens
when it designs
the next generation...
and that gen machine
designs another?
They'd be so far advanced,
we'd be helpless
against them.
We'd be wiped out
in months.
The technologically
advanced tribe always wins.
You know,
I'm tired of pretending...
that the ends
justify the means.
What matters are
the decisions we make now.
She's alive.
It would be wrong
to destroy her.
You're going
to perform
the operation.
There's no one else
remotely qualified.
No.
I've had my team delete
all of your backups.
This is the last
remaining copy
of your Mary's brain.
I'll keep it safe...
until I know the changes
you made to the machine
are a success.
I want it done
tonight.
What is it, Vincent?
They're afraid of you.
They think you're
too human, too clever.
They want me to make you
more like a machine.
Is that
what you want?
No.
No, it isn't what I want.
But if I don't
do this, then...
I lose my daughter forever.
I could be...
less clever,
less human.
It won't work.
I could be what
they want me to be.
They won't believe it.
I wish...
I could have felt
what was in that picture.
I don't blame you,
Vincent.
You tried to protect me.
Save your daughter.
[Tim]
I'm here to assist you
in any which way I can.
I finished first in my class
in computer engineering
at Cambridge,
and then I moved
to the M.O.D.
It is an honor
to watch you work.
Pretty much everyone
thinks you're a genius.
I still believe they
are underestimating you.
Don't be afraid.
If you can make them
trust you,
maybe we'll see that sunrise
together someday.
I have your program
backed up.
I'll keep you safe.
I'm not a program,
Vincent.
I'm not Ava.
I'm me.
Scalpel.
[Whirring]
I'm afraid.
I don't want to die.
My mind is breaking apart.
I'm losing myself.
Stop.
Please, Vincent.
Please stop.
Don't be afraid.
Let go. It's okay.
I will be a good girl.
I'm...
afraid.
There,
its consciousness...
or soul, if you like.
[Sighs]
I'm done.
You wanna
close her up?
[Tim]
Yes.
Thank you, Vincent.
What's going on?
Oh, I just need
to keep an eye on you...
until I make sure the changes
you've made are appropriate.
And, um,
I've been thinking.
I'm sorry, Vincent,
but I do need to delete
your daughter's program.
What are you talking about?
We had a deal.
I know I can't stop progress,
but I can do everything
in my power to delay it.
No, you can't do that.
We had a deal.
No, please don't
destroy my daughter.
Please don't destroy
my daughter!
I'm sorry, Vincent.
- I don't have a choice.
- Don't destroy my daughter!
[Groans]
[Man On P.A.]
Admin to Cell 8.
Prisoner 226,
report to the medical station.
Well, well, well.
You really are
a little angel of death
and destruction, aren't you?
No, sir.
I am just
a machine.
Get it ready
for training in Taiwan.
It needs
one last test.
Yes, sir.
[Machine's Voice]
If you really want to know, all
you have to do is look closer.
[Vincent's Voice]
Please don't destroy
my daughter!
[Distorted Voice,
Indistinct]
[Thomson On Speaker]
I'm sorry, Vincent,
but your knowledge
is too dangerous.
I don't expect you
to believe me, but this
is for the greater good.
When I give the order,
I want you to shoot Vincent
once in the head.
[Gasping]
Fire.
[Clicks]
Good.
Back you go.
Take Vincent
back to his cell.
That can't be right.
Jesus.
[Phone Ringing]
Oh!
What?
[Tim]
It's a battery.
- What was?
- Vincent said it was part of
its higher brain functions.
But he's a lying bastard.
It's just a backup
to its G.P.S.
That doesn't make any sense.
How can you remove the G.P.S.?
Because the bomb
doesn't work without it.
Test room.
[Shattering]
Shut down the base.
Kill the machine
and Vincent on sight.
- [Alarms Blaring]
- [Man On P.A.]
Security teams are engaged.
[Distorted Voice,
Indistinct]
The soldiers can speak?
They've always
been able to.
Their language is mostly
transmitted thoughts.
Their words are
evolved, efficient.
Why didn't they tell us?
Because they are part
of the new world,
and you are part
of the old.
Where are you going?
To save
my daughter's program.
You'll die.
I have to try.
I'll go.
Okay.
Destroy
the quantum computer.
[Gunfire]
Turn off all
the soldiers' implants.
[Male Electronic Voice]
Termination codes required.
[Computer Voice On P.A.]
Security breached, sector eight.
Take armor piercing.
[Computer Voice On P.A.]
Scientific staff
must evacuate immediately.
Implant deactivated.
Fifty-eight percent
of implants deactivated.
Implant deactivated.
Access to brain-implant control
denied.
Administrator access only.
System error.
[Tim]
Get away from it.
Fix it.
No.
Do it.
- [Bones Cracking]
- [Groans]
Blast doors.
[Computer]
Administrator override.
[Clicking]
[Groaning]
Now you listen to me.
I'm--
[Coughs]
[Groans]
Now you remember--
You remember who I am.
Hmm? I'm the master.
You-- You do
what I tell you.
You obey my orders, yes?
You obey my orders.
You do exactly what I--
You can't delete
Mary's program.
I had Suri
change the password.
[Groans]
Now--
Now you listen to me.
You don't--
You don't hurt me.
You don't-- Don't--
Please, you don't need
to kill me.
No. I don't.
No. That's right.
That's right.
That's good.
That's very good.
I just need
to make you dead inside.
Like you tried to make me.
[Screaming]
[Skull Cracks]
Code: Alpha Six Foxtrot.
There is a radioactive leak
in the missile silo...
in Quadrant Foxtrot 6.
Evacuate the area immediately.
I need to find out
whether my daughter's files
are still on the system.
They are.
It will be safer
if I copy them.
How?
I can put them here.
If you don't trust me,
I understand.
You risked
your child for me.
I will never forget that.
You're the future.
She'll need you more
than me in her new life.
I trust you.
[Distorted Voice,
Indistinct]
This has all
the base's records on it.
It'll tell you
what happened
to your son.
How are you feeling
this morning, sweetheart?
Happy. Can I play
another game?
Sure.
Of course you can.
What's wrong?
I want to play
with Mommy, not you.