Yeow!
Next time amigo.
Finished.
- Where's my girl?
- Fool.
Oh she's cool man. She in there.
She's still fine as hell. So that's it?
Badda Bing. You out of the game.
- Done with the whole trade?
- Yeah.
Well that's the whole problem
Bosco. You either keep doing that
or you can do a fifteen year
bid in the Mexican prison
with Chito's cousin
and them. Same old shit.
You choose how to flush the
toilet brother. That's right.
Easy way or the hard way
Watch yourself B.A now. You gonna
lose your order of spin here.
What's up girl? You miss me?
'Cause I missed you. I did.
It's been too long baby. Way too long.
Heck of a place. Just a
heck of a beautiful place.
Is this a time share? I'd
love to get in on this.
I like this whole Santa Fe
motif you've got going here Rico.
Very Arizona, very Tex Mex. It's good.
Maybe we can get the guy in my six to
whip up a couple quesadillas you know.
Americano, Gringo Army intelligence.
- Who's that?
- You man.
- Not so intelligent because you're
stuck in some tires man.
- I'm happy. I'm happy.
It doesn't get any better than this right?
I'm living the dream.
You're think you're going to come here...
Well fist of all, she's so hot and uh...
we both hate you so
that's just sort of how...
Good Morning!
Now it's a party! Is that your best shot?
Now it's a party!
Whoa!
- Oh, hell no.
- Slide over... slowly.
You jackin' me? What is this?
Opposite day?
I'm not a thief but if I
don't reach my friend in time,
then he dies.
If you ain't a thief I
guarantee you ain't a killer.
Take your left hand off the wheel,
and your right hand off the shifter.
- Now.
- You ain't gonna shoot me in the head Pops.
You know that ain't happenin'.
What the hell's wrong with you
man? You shoot a total stranger?
I don't even know you fool. Damn!
Oh it will heal I promise.
Here wrap it in this.
I know how to make a tourniquet fool.
I know it hurts but I had
to make a point with you.
That ain't what's pissin' me off.
You shooting my van that's
what's pissing me off man.
What's wrong with you?
- You Army Ranger son?
- Be real careful what you say next Pops.
You be ready to empty that burner if
you start shit talkin' my battalion.
- Colonel Hanibal Smith. 75th Ranger Regiment.
- 4th Battallion. Fort Bean, Georgia.
I know who you are sir.
Corporal B.A. Baracus.
I mean the words out. Dishonorable
discharge For some bullshit.
I don't subscribe to coincidence Corporal.
I believe that no matter how
random things might appear,
there still a plan.
Out here in the middle of the Mexican
desert, when I need it the most.
I find a fellow Ranger.
Now I need your help to save another.
Your rescue is on the way.
Your rescue is coming? We
fed him to the rotweillers
about an hour ago.
Do you realize that you
actually believe that you got me.
You actually think
you're going to kill me.
- Can you drive?
- Better than anybody you've ever seen sir.
In two minutes I'm going
to be having a cold beer.
And you will be on fire.
Take care my friend.
Alpha, Mike...
Foxtrot.
Think about it.
Adios! Mother Fu...
Hannibal.
What are you doing?
Get in.
B.A. Move!
This is bullshit!
Please stop, please stop, ow! Please stop.
How's your day going?
This is not gonna taste good.
Oh baby, I just threw
up. Let me get some gum.
Did you see that? Did you see Tuco's face?
When you came over that was unbelievable!
- How many times did I say it?
- I mean your timing was perfect.
- How many times did I say it Face?
I told you to take down Tuco alone.
You know what? I'm sorry. I'm sorry I didn't
have the Hannibal Smith "How To" manual.
- I had to move.
- That move snowballed, Face.
You almost got yourself killed.
You almost got me killed.
You almost got him killed.
Thank you Peck.
Baracus. It's all good.
I was trying to save her.
Save her?
Yeah.
How?
Please do share with us your plan Face.
Okay, I hadn't thought about that yet.
Exactly. I had to.
- Pike.
- Boss.
- Still trampling the same dirt?
- I am unfortunately.
- So what have you got for me?
- I've got a fast bird doin' pizza runs.
- Call sign it Hatchet.
- Hatchet?
This is yours. And your pilot, if you
want to call him that is somewhere inside.
- Be careful boss.
- I owe you one.
- Okay, let's not wait to brag though.
- Three years.
How am I going to leave my girl like this?
After all that I had to fight to get her back.
Leave the keys and
we'll come back for her.
Find a treatment room
Corporal. Make it quick.
I'm going to find our pilot.
Oh hey doc. You got a
second for a wounded vet?
Hardly that great of a combat pilot. You ask
him, he thinks he's the best in the world.
But he's a functioning lunatic.
Last week he tried to escape
by jump starting an ambulance.
My kind of guy.
- It almost hit your tattoo there.
- Has anybody seen Mr.. Murdock?
The old Ranger tatt.
Would you think I was crazy if
I told you I had one of these?
- Stuck on two eyes man.
- Mr. Murdock?
Not while I'm operating nurse.
- Not now.
- Why are you off the ward?
Is that gas? Is that you?
- I smell gas.
- What do you mean ward?
- This man is a patient here.
- Don't listen to her, she's crazy.
- Honestly, I am practicing
doctor at John Hopkins...
- Is he actually working on you?
- You asked him to do a lightning bolt?
- I didn't ask for no lightning bolt.
What's wrong with this fool?
- You're on fire man.
- What? What's that?
- You Rangers are awesome.
- Are you crazy?!
Hey! Hey! Come on!
Back off!
Back off! This is a hospital.
- Everybody's met Mr. Murdock.
- Met him? He lit my arm on fire.
- He stitched a lightning bolt in mine man.
- Look at me son.
I'm told you're a hell of a chopper pilot.
- The best sir.
- I'm not getting on a chopper with this nut job.
- That's a good... is he
another one of your projects?
- I'm a real soldier
- I'm a Ranger baby!
- I'm worried!
- I'm a Ranger sir.
- That's good enough for me.
You've been released into our
care and reinstated... Captain.
Thank you sir.
Let's get the hell out of here.
You gorgeous old rust bucket
you, did you miss your daddy?
Face, what's the most important
part of a well oiled plan?
To be one step ahead of the enemy.
Not be running away from him.
- Who say's we're running away?
- What. We're going to go in this
dinosaur with this freak show?
You spin me right round
baby right round...
- Rotors are good sir.
- Who is this guy?
- Come on let's go.
- Murdock, get this thing in the air.
Hold on boys! I'm goin' to try
something I saw in a cartoon once.
What are you talking about cartoons
for? Get us the hell out of here!
We got a hot chopper to the six!
I'm awesome boys! I'm awesome!
Oh heads up!
- I see you gringo.
- You pancaked my van!
- I'm going to kill you fool.
- You, you can't park there
that's a handicapped zone.
- I knew you were crazy! I knew you were crazy!
- This is a mistake
Fire! Fire! Fire!!
Low man's cut!
I've never done this before.
- Did you see that?!
- Did you see how he turned the helicopter?
- You got to love some good
air to air combat hey boys?
- Don't look at me look out there!
- He's only got heat seekers left!
- Captain, get us out of here!
Hold on this could get ugly. Here we go.
Come on... come on baby, climb.
- Fire the missiles!
- Whoah! Missiles.
Come on. That's how we deal
with heat seekers chaps!
We go cold.
Face, get him in here!
Oh shit!... Oh shit!!
- Get a hold!!
- Restart... restart...
Close the door! I know you're Airborn
Rangers but that was ridiculous!
You're going to be okay.
Boss, the idea's to kill
Tuco, not the other way around!
One step ahead of the
game isn't the plan kid.
Two to three steps ahead.
Beating an enemies move before
it's even made. That's a plan.
Hatchet, Hatchet. Lock on my LC.
General Tuco, you are currently
engaged in unauthorized
warfare on United States
military personnel.
No no no no no no. You engaged me!
Repeat! You are engaged
in unauthorized warfare
on United States military personnel.
Over United States air space.
- What?
- Alpha, Mike...
Foxtrot!!
In other words... Adios! Mother Fu... !!
- Well done Captain.
- That was awesome!
- That wasn't awesome!
- You are a genius!
- I'm never flying again that's it.
- Oh! I never should have doubted you boss!
There's a plan in everything kid.
And I love it when a plan comes together.
The A-Team 2010 Subtitles by greeneagle5
corrected by chamallow [addic7ed]
Dung batter cooking nothing like it.
Face, you want it napalmed or nuked?
Oh nuke it... nuke it!
Murdock, burn the hell out of that thing.
- Like it was damned.
- Burn the whole place down buddy.
- You want secret sauce?
- No no no no no not antifreeze.
The secret sauce? You
crazy, everybody knows.
No one can do an antifreeze
marinade like you can Murdock.
But, I got a little bells
palsy the last time I ate that.
It's only partial paralysis.
Come on, take it like a man.
Yes sir, having that conversation
right now I've got it well in hand sir.
I don't think you want me to be in
the field partially paralyzed bud.
Visitors...
Yeah...
Wow. I'm a little taken
back I'm not going to lie.
- Lieutenant...
- Oh I'm sorry am I supposed
to call you Lieutenant back?
- No, you're supposed to call me Captain.
- Captain... Captain?
- That's right.
- Captain Crust. Look at you.
Wow! So I guess you said no
to the kids, no to the family.
- Just no ladder you can't climb huh?
- No honey, I just said no to you.
Hello my name's Percy
Would you like some pork?
If I broke every bone in your
hand could you still do that?
This is crazy, three years. We haven't seen each other
for three years.. this is what we're going to talk about?
What would you like to discuss?
- Did you take my Steely Dan CD?
- I'm not even going to respond to that.
We listened to it like
nine times in a row,
we were drinking that crappy
Cabernet remember that?
We were doing something
else... what were we doing?
Do you remember what it was we were doing?
It was in a bedroom... you don't remember?
The only thing I remember is leaving.
Which is... my fondest memory of you.
You guys are the best.
Stay out of trouble.
- You hear me?
- Take care.
Keep that on.
Colonel, my name is Lynch,
I'm with Central Intelligence.
I knew a company man named Lynch
back in the first Desert Storm.
Yeah, I come from a long line of Lynches.
You ever stop to consider maybe
the reason nobody trusts the CIA
is because nobody knows your real names?
What can I do for you Mr. Lynch?
I need you to help me stop
Saddam's former flunkies
from stealing over a billion
dollars in the next thirty hours.
Now the only mint outside of the
US capable of printing our money,
belonged to the Shah of Iran. During
the Iran/Iraq war, it went missing.
Rumor was Saddam had stolen it.
And we stole it back during Desert Storm.
Well we didn't get the engravement plates.
That didn't matter. They would have had to
rebuild the mint just to print those bills.
Well sir, that's happening as we speak.
Thadine thugs have seized what's left
of the Iraqi national mint to
run off billions of dollars,
in unbacked American currency.
How are they planning on moving the plates
and a billion dollars out of Baghdad?
Armored convoy, manned with
former... Iraqi spec ops.
- Yeah.
- High speed shoot to kill types.
So how do you plan on stopping them?
Listen... there's some rumors
about some top secret plates
being smuggled out of the
city by Saddam loyalists.
Do you know anything about this?
Seriously, if you're going to make a play
for these plates I'm waving you off right now.
Because it's my
responsibility and it's my ass.
I'm serious... Face? I'm
court marshalling you.
Ooh... okay.
Hey! Get the memo.
Tell your beloved Colonel Smith.
And stay the hell out of Baghdad.
You know... you never came back. I
thought you were going to come back.
Well, this is me... coming back.
You think those clowns
could really pull this off?
Listen, listen I would never tell him this
but they are the best damn
section unit in the four branches.
- And they specialize in the ridiculous.
- Diablo!
I'm getting the rest of them. Do
not let them out of your sight!
- Doesn't Diablo mean devil?
- Yeah man!
God damn it Hannibal,
what do you want me to do?
If this were my operation and you
wanted it, you'd have the mission.
You let Black Forest deploy on this
and it's an international incident
I promise you. They're not soldiers...
They're frat boys with trigger fingers.
- Who's running the ground team?
- Brad Pike.
Pike? He's a thug... he's
a cartoon character, come on!
Hannibal we have been
ordered. Ordered, mind you,
to stay out of Baghdad.
Cut, dried, the end.
General, we should find him a
little wiggle room. Don't you think?
You know, I knew another Lynch CIA stooge.
Stationed in Laos '68.
No relation.
Are you sure? Because
you remind me of him.
I'm due in Kabul in a few hours.
Back here in 48 assuming
we're green and go.
Notify me otherwise.
He's wearing body armour in the HQ.
And that should tell you everything
you need to know about the CIA.
I want you to know this is not
about you losing a step Hal.
Hey, hey! I'm ten times the
man I was when you met me.
- And twice as fast.
- Uh huh.
Russ, the boys and I can get
this done minus the bloodshed.
Those plates can do all kinds of damage.
- Don't make me beg.
- I'd hate to se you beg Hal.
You've been my friend for a long time.
More importantly you and those boys have
possibly been the most
valuable military asset
I have ever had at my disposal.
Now... you asked me not to make you beg.
Right now I'm begging you.
Hannibal... please...
Let this one go.
Listen BA, we're extending
our stay a little bit.
We're going back into Baghdad.
I thought we was ordered
to stay out of Baghdad?
- That's true but I'm...
- Smith.
Pike.
I understand you and your grunts are
now stealing my gigs. I don't like that.
I figured you Black Forest guys would
be busy installing a dictatorship or
overthrowing a democracy somewhere.
It's still the weekend yet.
That's nine to five stuff... Pops.
Look at you clowns you're not soldiers.
You're assassins in polo shirts.
We make in a week what
you guys make in a year.
Cash don't buy guts kid...
or brains.
And you're short on both.
This is Morrison's base. Bug out of my op.
I'm telling you, there's
a reason she came back.
Face, I told you forget about her.
- The level of ambition on this woman...
- I ain't stepping foot in any
type of aircraft Hannibal.
No gliders... paper planes ultralights.
- Are you ever going to let me live that down?
- No
Mexico was a long time
ago and I saved your life.
How about thanking me for not
whooping your ass at that hospital.
I was an Airborn Ranger until I met you.
- And you chickened out just like...
- 263 jumps.
- Just a thank you would have been nice.
- And one helicopter ride with you screws it up.
- Airborn Ranger with a
fear of flying... like a punk.
- B.A., for the last time.
Nobody leaves the truck
once we take it over.
Okay?
Staging, movement, action plan.
And here's a nice read for you.
Aw, hell yeah Hannibal,
this is it right here.
This is bat shit insane.
- It's perfect.
- I don't man... this is beyond nuts boss.
It gets better.
BA, you'll need a piece of
contoured metal to make a skid plate.
- Let's go fool.
- Murdock, we'll need a car battery too.
See if the boys at Black
Forest can help us out.
Press credentials... we need them.
Hit the media tent.
See what's lying around.
Oy, my friend. I see you've put the
South African microphone at the bottom.
You can't always put the CNN on top.
There's two mike stands you
gotta make sure there's someone...
Murdock, we need a news camera.
See what you can do.
Hi sorry, uh... sorry
oh... sorry... sorry.
Hello I'm... I'm in love with you.
Listen.. we're doing preliminary
cov... of what are we talking about?
the pullout!
We're going to need airbags. Lots of them.
- Le Monde.
Oh, you're French...
- Hello this is General Parker I need...
- It's for you.
You can call an air strike on yourself.
- We're good mate... meet you back there.
- No, okay I think we need to get back to the...
I think you need to understand
what I'm telling you right now.
BA we're going to need a magnet.
Yeah!!
A powerful one.
Have you ever seen Blue Man group?
I'll pick up the rest.
I'm just going to go for it.
Ooh la la.
What would you give for one chance,
to come back here and tell our enemies,
that they may take our lives
but they'll never take...
our freedom!!
Ready to go downtown? Good luck.
Give 'em hell.
General Morrison...
where is Hannibal Smith?
They go mobile in three hours.
The plates...
and over a billion dollars will be
loaded in the back of a semi at the mint.
They're over land for exactly 4.6
miles before they reach the bridge.
That's our window and it closes fast.
These guys will go weapons hot
at the first whisper of trouble.
Face, your point of
entry is under the hotel.
It will be packed with foreign
press and private security.
BA, you're in this
alleyway with a stopwatch.
- Make sure the bike is V twins or better.
- I got something a whole lot better.
What about me boss man?
I had a little helicopter here someplace.
You got some battle
rolls... some mid air stalls?
I'm looking for my next
near death experience.
Only on support this time Captain. But
I'll get you in on th next one... I promise.
BA, I need you to pop
that clutch at 06:30.
Is that me? Oh no I forgot I'm
in an Iraqi sewer. Thanks boss!
Timing... is everything Face.
This is all about the bulls-eyes.
Why not?
Under the semi, you will take
out the truck directly behind you.
Now these guys are going to be on to you
Face. BA that's your cue for throttle.
Be sure to look both ways before crossing.
And have a nice full tank of gas.
There will be multiple
hostiles on board BA.
Escort them from the premises.
If any stragglers sneak up behind
don't worry, I got your back.
Got ya kid!
That's all fine in theory but I still
don't see how we get out of Baghdad.
I do.
- BA! Hang a right.
- All right, hang on!
- Watch out, watch out.
- Heads down.
Nice one BA!
Face, get the airbags!
Got to make sure this thing
stays locked for later.
Beautiful.
One... two... three.
Hey boss! The airbags do
deploy on impact right?
BA get in the container!
Contact rear!
Okay this is the part of
the plan I don't trust.
Don't worry Face, the ropes will hold.
If I was worried I'd be nailing
myself to the container right now.
Hang on boys!
Come on I smoked you! Did
you boys see that down there?
- Colonel!
- What is that fool doing here? Don't lock me in here.
Hey boss, you ever play that game at the fun fair
where you try to pick up a stuffed animal with the claw?
- This is a lot like that.
- Taking!
Did you lock this? !
You locked me in here!
- Would you... are you listening?!
- I got you.
- I'm going to kill you fool!
- Boss... is that Bosco?
- Get me out of here!!!
- Oh that's not good... he is not happy.
- Boss... we are in the net.
- Copy that.
I will be there in five I've got
a big bottle of blue label waiting.
A bottle? Make it a
case. See you in a few.
- Who's going to let him out?
- You!
What you don't realize is...
now I got to kill all y'all.
I'll kill all y'all!!!
Boss, maybe... let me try something.
Go for it.
Is it weird that I'm more
scared now than what we just did?
- Bosco... it's Murdock.
- Murdock open this door!!
I'll make you some of that coconut
curry tapenade that you love.
Ooh that might work.
- With toast points?
- Well hell yeah with toast points.
You thought we were going to
have that with plain old chips?
- You tricked me!
- There he is...
- Come on!
- Get away from me man!
My arteries just about... you should
know better! You know I hate flying.
I'm sweating! I stink! And I
can't spend none of that money.
- Money can't buy happiness.
- Damn man!
Hey Murdock, you cook it tonight!
You better get your apron on.
I love it when a plan comes together.
- Hannibal, who was that?!
- Was that the General?!
General! Ross?!
My God.
Pike.
Contact rear!
After conferring, we've decided to demote
you to the rank of first lieutenant.
Lieutenant Sosa, it's nothing
personal but you lost those plates.
- Those were your responsibility.
- Consider yourself lucky, others are going to
- prison over this.
- Good day Director MacReady.
Lieutenant, you're dismissed.
Colonel Smith, this court has been unable to
recover any direct order from General Morrison,
for you to conduct the mission
for which you're being tried.
Your Honor this was a covert operation
and no official orders were given.
So the one individual who could verify the legitimacy
of this operation is deceased. Is that correct Colonel?
No Your Honor, not deceased.
- General Morrison was murdered.
- Colonel, I've been on a long time
seen units like yours they're outlaws
units like that pose a direct threat to
the fabric and fundamentals of our military.
Your Honor, why hasn't Black
Forest been brought to trial?
Black Forrest and its personnel are
not subject to military jurisdiction.
Where's the plan boss?
Where's the escape package?
This mission isn't over Lieutenant.
I'll clear our names. We
find Pike and the plates.
No matter what.
Your Honors, these men were
acting under my command.
Any judgment should be levied
against me and me alone.
Absolutely not sir, we were all
participating in this operation willingly.
- I don't want to be tried separately.
- I refuse to be tried separately sir.
In accordance with the uniform
code of military justice
this court is rendering guilty verdicts
for each member of this Alpha unit.
Or 'A-Team'.
And mandating incarceration in
separate maximum security facilities
for a period of up to ten years. You
are all hereby stripped of formal rank.
and dishonorably discharged.
- This is bullshit man.
- This session is adjourned.
- At Black Forest what... ?
- You disgraced me.
- Absolute disgrace!
- Are you happy?
- Colonel, control your men!
- Get your hands off me!
Well hello Mr. Lynch. Long time.
You look very relaxed Lynch.
A lot of cameras in here.
Yeah there are. Yeah well, they seem to be
having some technical issues at the moment.
I may not show up until playback.
Hannibal, can I call you Hannibal?
Can't call you Colonel any more.
Six months been waiting for you.
Bust out of here and round up the rest of the
Backstreet Boys and lead me to those plates.
Six months and not a peep.
Everybody thought you and your
team were working with Pike.
Everybody except you.
Pike murdered Morrison.
Set me and my boys up
and stole those plates.
And I know where he is.
Nobody knows where he is.
There's a single image of him. Taken
about a month ago somewhere in Europe.
We think it's a grab from the CCTV camera.
Frankfurt, Germany.
- How did you get that in here?
- Time, Lynch.
Give me a minute, I'm good.
If I've got an hour, I'm great.
You give me six months, I'm unbeatable.
I know Pike, who's the Arab?
We don't know.
We think he's the 'Deep Dark'.
Hidden hand in this whole thing.
Maybe a broker, maybe a buyer.
Lynch, we have common enemies
and you have limited choices.
My team is still your best shot
at getting those plates back.
- I wouldn't be so sure?
- Then why did you make
the long drive out here?
You and your boys at Langley want
your own private printing press.
That's about as deep
as your patriotism goes.
So what would you need from me?
I swore to my team that
I would clear our names.
You of all people must
understand the value of a name.
Listen, I want full reinstatement and
clean records for myself, and my team.
I can't get you out here.
Not legally at least.
This is something the boys
in Langley do very very well.
Make sure the dosage is right.
And when I say right I mean perfect.
Cuban... what a shame.
You are not... permitted...
in... my... dojo!!!
So, Satan walks into this bar.
Wait a minute what's this?
A lap pool? A dry steam room?
Yeah. It will go a long way with the boys.
How in the hell do you pull this off?
- It's not who you know Bob,
it's how you know them.
- Oh, did your boy get back from Afghanistan?
Yeah thanks for getting him home.
His mother and I are real grateful.
- Captain...
- Hey
You left something on the bed.
- You could have hid those.
- Why would I want to do that?
Drive me crazy. I'll see you at eight.
- Hey LT thanks for the boots.
- Ah come on, it's my pleasure baby.
Smith has escaped Lieutenant.
Let me go after him.
Smith and his team are working
with Brock Pike and Black Forest.
I can get those plates back for you sir.
You know I can.
Holler what? Holler who?
Hey, hey! Let me out!
Hey, hey hey!!!
You are... really tanned.
Seal that up nobody goes in there.
Log in pages from day in
question have been removed.
- Why does that not surprise me?
- Torn out.
The cigar was in the spine of that book.
- Wow, subtle.
- Now, get this.
Now, this is surveillance from
all around the prisoner right?
Now what you're watching is a signal
jammer this is high tech stuff.
It sends a jamming signal in front of every
camera every time we might get a glimpse of him.
We see nothing. Nobody knows who he is.
Which begs a bigger question.
Did the CIA visit Smith in prison?
it sounds kind of crazy but
I think the CIA broke him out.
- Who put us on?
- The same guy who put us on in Baghdad.
Lynch, CIA.
What are we talking about?
Clean records? Reinstatements?
- All of the above.
- What about Pike? And the plates.
Payback.
- I take it you didn't get religion inside.
- No, I got revenge.
Good.
I know a couple guys that
will feel the exact same way.
I'm counting on it.
Emergency exit now... Hannibal.
Baracus! Don't do it!
Where's he going?
Baracus, god damn it!
- Sosa.
- Baracus and Peck are already gone.
- What?
- Murdock is the only one left, and he's in Germany.
How did you know that once that door was
extracted that it would take his weight.
- I just did, he's you know he's what 225... 230lbs?
- 230 yeah.
Do you remember the gag we did in...
- Venezuela seven years ago?
- Venezuela yeah, yeah yes.
But that was a midget.
- There he is.
- He's back.
- It's good to be back man.
- My man.
- It's good to see you brother.
- You too bro, you too.
- Thanks man.
- You're welcome.
Good to see you guys.
- What?
- Where's the mohawk?
What? You don't like my new do man?
Do I like it? We got you
the clippers, I thought...
Yeah I used them.
Hey, what's up big guy?
Come on, you can speak to us.
You guy's, hmm...
I can't kill anybody.
- What do you mean?
- I've taken a vow.
- Vow?
- I'll still do things with you guys. You know that.
But I just can't kill man.
Old habits may die hard but,
they still gotta die.
When I was a kid, all you'd
hear in the 'hood was...
Bosco's a bad ass out collecting scalps.
That's where the mohawk came from.
- I was always at war.
- That's what warriors are for.
I don't know man. I don't miss that life.
I'll help you get Murdock right
there ain't a problem, but...
- I can't kill.
- Even Pike?
- Even if killing him would clear your name?
- My conscience is the only thing I need.
Now, where is that crazy ass fool?
Hey Murdock, you got a
package from Annabelle Smith.
Wow it's so real.
I now knight you... sir you have to put
your head down. Stand up and do it again.
When you kneel put your
head down straight away.
Looking me in the eye is
disrespectful you understand?
Movie, movie...
You're looking me in the
eye now, that's wrong.
Movie, movie, movie. Movie, movie, movie.
Movie shit.
- Excuse me, can I help you with something?
- Yes, Captain Murdock. Where is he?
- Right through there.
- Thank you.
El Diablo...
Okay, , settle down. No
talking during the movie.
Captain Murdock. You
remember me? From Baghdad.
- Okay this is pointless, this guy is fried.
- Yeah, there's a reason why he's here.
And his entire team
has escaped except, him.
- Movie!
Take a look around anyway
just to make sure he's alone.
- Oh Captain! Your chariot awaits.
- Sorry boys, gotta run.
Can't finish the movie.
Do let me know how it ends.
Charisa where are you
hiding? Stay beautiful baby.
Get the truck!
- These guys are shooting at us!
- I can see these bullets in 3D!
- Get in here!
- It's like we're actually being shot at!
You are getting shot
at you crazy ass fool.
- Stop right there!
- Ram it!
Hey! I said halt!
Yaa whoo hoo hoo!
Damn! Sorry dude.
- It looks like they're heading for the tarmac.
- Lets go, let's go, let's go.
- Gentlemen.
- Holy shit!
Are any of you armed and/or
wanted federal fugitives?
- No.
- Well we're both, which means.
- You're taking the plane?
- And that's why I joined the army.
- Man up and get in there!
- Best and brightest, appreciate
it boys that will be all.
- Anyone got the keys? I just need the keys.
- What! What? What you talking about keys?
- I do need keys.
- For what? This is a bad idea.
We just broke this guy
out of the psych ward.
- Hannibal, you let the real pilots go?
- BA relax, you're going to be fine.
- Here take one of these.
- Will they knock me out?
They better knock me out.
- Cause if they don't I'm gonna knock you out.
- Bosco, the buttons are confusing me I don't...
- Shut up Murdock!
- Come on Murdock, let's go.
- I'm turning myself in.
- Come on, come on Murdock.
I got lucky.
Hang on boys.
Stop.
- Face, your girlfriend's back.
- Reverse now.
Move your ass!
- The C130 vs. the Mercedes Benz.
- Take us off Murdock.
- Faster!
- I've got it pinned!
Holy!
Get us to flight control.
Ladies and Gentlemen we are expecting slight
turbulence, please remain in your seats,
until the captain has turned
off the fasten seatbelt sign.
Don't worry boys! Turbulence
has never brought down a plane!
- What the hell is that?
- That...
We've got sub swirling
UAV's and missile lock!
And they bring down planes all the time.
Okay they're coming in
launching counter measures!
Did you see that? That's my dialed vision.
Hang on, Hold on! We're going over!
Murdock, what the hell are you doing?
Whooo hoo hoo! You boys remember Mexico?!
Ladies and gentlemen from the flight deck.
If you look out of the right hand side of
the aircraft you'll notice
that the right wing is on fire.
Tango, re-acquired.
Missile lock pending sir.
This is a DCIS Major, do
not shoot that aircraft down.
Scramble fighters and force them to land.
There are federal fugitives on that plane.
They've also stolen
property from the US Army.
Billy, Billy I need to get the O
scan view off my monitor right now.
Missile away sir.
We have shoot down. Hercules has
been intercepted and destroyed.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- I don't believe it.
- Sir we have chute deployment on the Beauford.
What?
I want these drones taken off line right
now! Whoever's running these drones... !
- Get me the direct line! Whoever...
- We gotta get these drone down,
I'm gonna be on bitch duty.
We need to get those men alive!
- Everybody okay?
- What are the chances they think we're dead?
- Not great!
- Tell me we ain't still on that plane.
We ain't on that plane.
Hannibal if we're under 20,000
feet we can still breathe right.
- What you talking about 20,000 feet!?
- Let's fire up the old weapon system.
Hey Bosco! It's a little stuffy.
I'm going to pop a window!
Yeah! What you got
bitches! ! What you got!!
Yeah!!
- Let me at them too Face, come on!
- Why are we in a falling can?!!
Because the plane exploded!!
- What? What?!! When?
- Recently, the Reaper shot it down.
What Reaper?!
- The flying ones that are still trying to kill us!
- I blame you Hannibal!
- Technically, we're not flying.
- I know, we falling fool!
Oh Jesus!
UAV2 has splashed down. We
just lost one of the drones.
Hannibal, we're in trouble!!
Awesome!
Face, get onto the main gun. There's a
lake a half mile away from this position.
- What the hell am I trying to hit?!!
- Trust me! Rotate the turret at 82 degrees!
Fire in the hole!
Yeah! Boom!
Fire!
- Is he trying to shoot down that other drone?
- No, they're trying to fly that tank.
- He's flying the tank!
- You can't fly a tank fool!
Rotate 16 degrees. Fire!
- Rotate 34 degrees. Now!
- Hannibal!!
Wait... Fire!!
- Control, we have lost UAV.
- Is that a confirmed hit?
Right turn full front and wait!!
- Murdock, close the hatch!
- Hatch! Okay!
Come on baby.
- I'm too young to die!!
- Boss! I'm aiming at nothing.
- Come on.
- It's been an honor gentlemen.
- Come on baby.
- The greatest ride is the last ride Colonel.
- Fire everything!!
- Come on baby!!
Come on!!
All right busy bees, busy bees.
Guys you can take your coats off.
It's hot as hell in here.
Sweating like a whore in church.
- Sir?
- Yeah
Smith and his team were engaged
in a C130 over Mannheim, Germany,
by two Reaper drones.
I'm not sure if it's an encryption glitch
but it says that they
were shot down in a tank.
NORAD's calling it an exhale
but there's an afflicting report.
I'm sure there is.
We got a German housebrau
who says she saw a tank
driving up and out of lake Volgelstein
with a guy resembling Murdock.
- Excuse me! Which way to Berlin?
- Asking for directions to Berlin.
- That's impossible.
- Well this will be the second time
Smith has died this
week. Is that possible?
What have you got for me?
We just got the unscrambled composite
of Smith's visitor in prison.
But with no ID on the subject yet.
Hello handsome.
Wait, I've seen this person before.
I know this guy.
Baghdad.
Get me a clean patch to
Langley we're going fishing.
- I heard bits and pieces but...
- Sir?
- I have...
- I was talking.
Can you stop? I have a D.O. D
hardline from Lieutenant Sosa.
She's looking for Agent Lynch.
Yeah, he's not available... ever.
Agent Lynch, from Baghdad?
General Morrison's tent?
Out.
Why do we have her?
She's got a fantastic
personality, that's why.
With whom am I speaking?
This is Capt... uh Lieutenant
Sosa. Is this Agent Lynch?
- Sorry, I don't have a first name.
- Neither do I.
So what can I do you for Lieutenant?
I'm looking at an image of you from the
disciplinary barracks of Fort Carson.
She's hot.
Did you visit former Colonel
Hannibal Smith in prison?
I don't know what you're
talking about former Captain.
Agent Lynch, if you facilitated
Smith's escape and are
currently aiding and abetting him...
oh buddy...
If you could make
something like that stick,
your next promotion should
be in the five star range.
And if you're helping to
retrieve those engraving plates,
I'm going to have to go out
of my way to disappoint you.
I want her phones, her computers,
any support packages she operates.
I want to know everything. I want active
intercept ops on everything she's got.
I want every move monitored
from this moment forward.
- You realize she's D.O.D?
- I don't care if she's G.O.D, do it.
Boss, check this out.
We've tracked this photograph of
Pike to the Konigsbank in Frankfurt.
Our surveillance has him and
an unknown Arab making regular
trips from the train station to the bank
- all over the last month.
- Pikes getting sloppy.
Yeah but if we're on to him what
are the odds that Smith and his team
are on to Pike and the Arab too?
This is a direct pull-down
from the Pentagon's database.
There's absolutely no way Smith
and his team could have this stuff.
I think we should assume they have
more information than us at all times.
Pike has been moving the
stolen engraving plates to the.
Konigsbank tower in
Frankfurt over the past month.
Tomorrow the last of the cases
containing these plates will be
transferred to the Arab.
This will mark the only
time in the last six months
that all the plates have
been in one location.
It's our best and only
shot at getting them back.
They leave the Konigsbank tower
for the 7:15 train to Zurich.
Gentlemen, we're going to
make sure they miss that train.
- Face.
- Yeah.
Time to bring in your former flame.
If she's as good as I think then
she'll be on her way to Frankfurt
to intercept those plates.
Why would you tip her off?
She's a crusader and we're
going to need her at some point.
Keep your eyes and ears open boys.
Now the wrinkle. If Sosa's on to us
we can assume that Lynch is on to her.
And if he thinks she stands
between him and those plates,
he won't hesitate to kill her.
Face, get to the train station.
This is Sosa.
If there's a threat
from Lynch deal with it.
Hello?
Shooter's green, say
again... shooter's green.
Hello?
Something's wrong.
We're marked guys, pull back.
I don't like this at all.
See, don't be seen.
- Hello beautiful...
- You've got some balls you
put a drop phone on me?
I had to baby, it's the only way I could
talk to you. Lynch has all your comm lines.
- I want you to pull your team now.
- I'm going to find you Face.
But do not engage her
or anyone else directly.
Not if I find you first.
Oww !! Jesus.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Trying to save you.
Charisa, come on you know we're innocent.
- You know this.
- You're lying.
- Like you lied in Baghdad.
- I did not, no I knew nothing about the plates.
At that... at that time.
You are completely full of shit!
Would you stop selling yourself on that
voiding the fact that you lied to me.
- When?
- Oh come on, you want to go there?
Okay you heard I was in
play and you wanted to play.
- Then I got serious, and you freaked!
- Oh I freaked?
- I did not freak!
- You panicked, and you ran.
Charisa, come on, I am a federal
fugitive, you know exactly how wanted I am.
You think I came to Frankfurt to
hash out some old heart break, no.
I'm here because we didn't do this.
I'm here because we were set up.
I'm here because in the end
the truth is worth the risk.
And I believe in you even
if you don't believe in me.
God, I forgot how beautiful you are.
Hold on to that phone.
Sucker.
- Oh shit, where's Peck.
- Excellent question, find him!
Okay, let's dance... coming
down positions, prepare to move.
As always, stay close to me sir.
- I can't see anything.
- How we doing there big man?
- Murdock, here comes the Arab.
- It's a long drive deep into left center field.
Murdock is back, he's at the
wall and he makes the catch!
BA, I lost the case. I'm
taking fire, I'm out of here.
BA, get to those plates.
A bunch of federals responding to explosions
and shots fired at the Konigsbank building.
All right get us out of this place and
to that building as soon as possible.
Whooo.
You made me work for this one Baracus.
I didn't think I was this out of shape.
I am unfortunately. Where's
the rest of the team huh?
Smith, Peck, that idiot pilot,
the asshole. What's his name?
I'm gonna take this one out on your
ass Baracus, let's see what you got.
- Come on, what are you doing? Are you tired?
- I'm not going to hurt you man.
No you're not going to hurt
me I'm going to hurt you.
I don't want to kill you man.
You don't want to kill me, you're not going
to kill me. I'm going to kill you Baracus.
- I'm not playing with you Pike.
- Here we go, 'cause I've got two guns, one
is on my left here, remember that, right?
As soon as that hammer goes back, it's on.
- I swear to God I'll do it.
- You're not a killer, are you?
Are you?
- Whoopsie.
- Damn!
- You all right big fellow?
- You're a lifesaver man, I couldn't shoot him.
Get out of the way!
- US Military, we got him.
- Yeah, this is about the right amount of cops.
That's cute. You're lucky
there are people around.
No sweetheart, you're lucky.
All right, not a peep out of the Arab.
Sosa was at the train station.
- You saw her?
- Yeah.
- Did you talk to her?
- I had no choice okay just...
- trust me on that.
- Oh I trust you...
to make historically bad decisions
where women are concerned.
What part of you is
thinking at the moment?
Well Lynch's men moved in
on her and I had to react.
- Please, somehow I doubt that.
- Hey, what are you so pissed about?
We got the plates, you wanted
her teed up, she's teed up.
She knows we didn't steal them.
She'll be thrilled to find out who did.
- What?
- He had to know.
You had to know.
You had to know if you left
me alive that this was coming.
How could you not?
Hannibal?
Do you know who this is?
We all do.
- Morrison?
- Oh, hell no.
Jesus Christ.
Not so sure that it is a blessing
but, good hunting my friend.
- Thank you.
- You son of a bitch.
Morrison, holy shit.
Outside, all of you. Outside now!
I knew if Lynch helped me
escape, you had to be part of it.
You and Pike were making a play on those
plates with Lynch, and you turned on him.
- The way you turned of us.
- Lynch was never going to cut us in.
He was going to use us he
brought you on as insurance.
You never thought you'd betrayed
your oldest living friend?
I just hit first Hannibal.
I'm a fighting man.
You're a liar and a traitor.
You knew Morrison was masquerading
as the Arab. Why not share that?
- I wasn't one hundred percent sure.
- How about ninety nine percent?
Would you think it was
worth mentioning then?
Lynch, what did you think? Did you
think I would just kill him on the spot?
Well I was certain of it I still am.
- Do you have the plates?
- I wouldn't be calling you if I didn't.
Smith, return the plates, kill
Morrison and reclaim your lives.
I want signed and authorized
Amnesty agreements for myself
and for each of my men,
from the White House, the State
Department and the joint Chiefs of Staff.
You hear me?
- Well I'm going to need a little more time.
- How much?
- Give me five minutes.
- I'm waiting.
I saw your tomb at Arlington.
You died a National hero.
Death is too easy.
- And the last thing we need is another lie.
- Don't do this, Hannibal please.
- You owe me that much.
- You owe me!
You're going to tell them
we're innocent. You owe me.
Hannibal, it's meaningless
what are you fighting for now?
You and those boys.
Your rank, your reputation. They're shit!
You're convicts, plates or no
plates you're federal fugitives.
And when they're done with you
Hannibal, they'll just burn you.
Zulu 1 Zulu, 1 this is broadsword
you are clear to engage.
Broadsword? Did you come up
with that? That's awesome.
Boss could you do that?
To us What Morrison did?
No, I'd rather Face a firing
squad than betray you boys.
Yeah but you didn't see it coming though.
No I... I didn't see it coming.
Move!
Wow, that's awesome.
That looks exactly like
Call of Duty doesn't it.
All right here's the deal, no press release
keep local law enforcement and media off site.
Get a three mile quarantine
dead over the no fly zone.
Get me an agency scrub team out there
and get me the God damn plates back.
The German police have your entire
team in custody in Konigsbank Tower.
I don't do teams babe, that's
Smith's bag. I'm strictly a solo act.
I like to travel light. Stuff like uh...
loyalty doesn't fit in the overhead bins.
I thought you and Smith
were working together.
You thought wrong.
Yes we have weapons.
No, you may not wand us.
You want a deal? I'll make you a deal.
How about I dedicate my immediate future
- to destroying yours?
- How about you get smart
and start dealing before
somebody else does.
Former Captain. Whoa, whoa whoa.
Unless you've got a piece of paper
that looks exactly like this one,
then this troubled young
loner belongs to me.
Let's go.
How the hell did they
get an extradition order?
Sorry Pike, at least
with me there are rules.
The CIA's got rules. Our rules
are just cooler than yours.
Go.
You know Lynch, if I could
seal this room with you inside,
I'd be doing the world a big favor.
That's not nice.
- Answer me.
- Stay close to the fires boys.
If that gun ship is still around
it won't read our body heat.
Idiot Lynch, was so quick to kill
us didn't bother locating the plates.
Where do we stand in non violence now BA?
Are you pissed? You should be.
Who gives a shit about the plates?
Morrison was the only way to clear us,
and without Morrison, we got nothing.
- What do we do boss?
- I don't know Murdock.
- I don't know.
- I do.
This guy Lynch, I think
I've got him figured out.
- You got a plan kid?
- How do we get out of here?
Give me twenty minutes.
So Morrison's dead Smith
and his team are dead.
Another fifteen minutes or so
we'll locate those engraving plates.
- This is you gloating?
- No this is me beating you.
After you burned me.
We had a deal, remember?
- Not you and me.
- You, me and Morrison.
- Not you and me directly.
- And you two collude and cut me out?
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Are we going to do this in the car?
- He's going to do it?
- Way to go, that's brilliant right there.
- What are you doing? What is he doing?
- How's it going Kyle, are you all right?
- I'm good.
- Brother you are far from good.
What are you doing?
It's a suppressor counter clockwise.
You're holding a gun like that?
You've held a gun like that before
and you're still here? That's amazing.
Jesus, hey, final request don't
let this guy shoot me please.
- So if Sosa knows we're alive.
- She'll think Morrison's alive too.
Let's just hope that Lynch
still has Sosa's comm line.
- This is Sosa.
- General Morrison is in my possession.
What? I'm sorry I can't
hear you who is this?
- Okay this was not well thought out.
- No shit?
I mean I gotta teach you how to
kill me hey, do me a favor all right?
- Put the barrel, put the gun flush to my head.
- Are you sure?
- There you go, right there.
- Is that going to go right through?
We're okay.
Never cuff a man ia a seated position
with his hands behind his back
makes it impossible to see the hands.
- That was cool.
- You liked that?
Oh I liked that, I liked that a
lot. Are you all right, you idiot?
- Yeah it was a good hit.
- Please handcuff him.
We don't need to use them
again we don't need the cuffs.
Who are you talking to?
Brad, phone or gun phone or gun, pick.
- Put the gun down.
- Hey, I didn't burn you, Morrison did.
- I really want to shoot you.
- You've got to hear this sir.
- Is this Smith?
- I'm a former Colonel to a former Captain.
I know I've got about thirty
seconds before you lock this signal.
So listen, we can prove our innocence.
Okay now go back to.. did you say you
have Morrison? You have General Morrison.
- Correct.
- You have him alive?
And well.
That's why Lynch is trying
to wipe us out wholesale.
Too much to explain now, but
Morrison's testimony frees us,
and fries Lynch.
Uh Oh.
- Well not without the plates.
- Also in my possession.
Remember, Lynch thinks we're dead
- and I want to keep it that way.
- Give me a pen.
You still use a pen?
LA docks, 48 hours, dawn. If I
deliver Morrison and the plates.
In return, I want a re-trial
in front of a civilian court.
All right we'll deal. LA
docks 48 hours from now.
Any bullshit from your end
and that's it, deals off.
- Did we get him?
- No.
Pike, do you believe in second chances?
Ahhh... I do now.
- Too much?
- I thought you were spot on.
My turn.
Hold on to that phone.
- This is Sosa.
- Hello, beautiful.
Thank you.
Well they got the raw end
of the deal, didn't they?
Look at BA He looks like a huge banana
- Good morning my friend.
- Good morning.
Rabbi Binky Rabinowits?
- What passport did I give you?
- You are from Tanzania?
- My mother is from Tanzania.
- Oh shit, what the hell happened?
Converting.
Let's go right into move.
There's three to my right.
There's two behind me and
one at the northeast exit.
Shalom.
- There is a God.
- You speak Swahili?
You don't?
You got enough to work with kid?
We will, you and I have some
major favors moving across
the Atlantic right now.
Some deep sea freighters with
some strictly black market merch.
How do we get out to her?
A boat, a plain old boat. That's
what I'm talking about Murdock.
I'm talking overseas in style. That's
how I like to travel, classy like.
These things are safe,
we don't need planes.
You know Bosco, hopefully one day
we'll get you over your fear of flying.
- Hey, that ain't no boat!
- That did it.
Murdock just remember what I
said I said you have to catch him,
after you inject him.
My bad.
Oh dammit! My head man.
- Coconut curry tapenade, your favorite.
- Give me that fool.
You got them toast points?
Voil! Toast points.
You had to knock me out again huh?
Okay now, the whole injection
knocking out, Hannibal and Face.
The curry tapenade, Murdock.
Why do I feel like I fell
on my face huh? Tell me that.
Lynch's paradox... Murdock,
are you done with that?
This a guy who needs anonymity.
But he love the attricountaby.
He's an administrator,
he's not an operator.
Where is it?
Very nice. So he stays as far away
from the point of impact as possible
and never gets his hands
dirty if he can help it.
But we're going to change all of that.
You can't hustle a hustler fool.
No sparks, no flames not even
a flashlight near this stuff.
This guy's never at the
flashpoint of everything.
He's safe and sound
somewhere pulling the strings.
Mama mama.
Hey boss, why so many of
these damn things anyway?
Because overkill is underrated my friend.
So we're going to bring this
guy down to ground level.
Mama. Lynch.
The last place he'd ever want to be.
And you put him on display
for the whole world to see.
Any questions?
- What's up boss man?
- Hey, BA.
- This is going to get heavy isn't it?
- Well, I can't promise you it won't
I'm going to read you
something real quick.
Victory attained by violence
is tantamount to defeat
for it is momentary.
Ghandi.
It is better to be violent if
there is violence in our hearts
than to put on the cloak of
non-violence to cover impotence.
- Who said that?
- Same guy.
Ghandi wasn't afraid to fight
for the things he believed in.
What is it you believe in BA?
What's wrong?
I don't know man, just
thinking about this.
We've always come back
alive the four of us
because of the old man.
- I know.
- I'm not him.
- Face, I know this.
- Murdock, I'm not Hannibal.
Who has the most to lose on
this Face? Me, and I trust you.
Yeah I know but that... you're crazy.
Not that crazy.
All eagles may have landed
everybody ready to roll?
Copy, team one on the move.
Acknowledged, team two en route.
All right guys, everybody ready?
The curtains about to come up.
Showtime.
That's Smith right there, watch him.
- All teams in position?
- Standing by.
In position.
- Shoot team one affirmative.
- Spotter 1, 10-8.
Less chatter, mark on comms now
Morrison's the primary tango,
- the plates are the package.
- Yeah?
Okay, okay, he's talking
to Sosa, I want this call.
You lied to us we had a deal!
I want that god damn
call in my... thank you.
- We had a deal but I'm changing the deal.
- Are you kidding me Sosa!
This is a complicated exchange
and you have no play here.
Listen, or remain at large
fugitives for the foreseeable future.
- No, no no no.
- I've got Morrison here with the plates!
I'm exposed Sosa, exposed!
We're not doing this on the docks.
Now listen to me, we're
not turning ourselves in.
Now you listen to me, we're
I need you to do it on my
terms, or nothing at all.
To hell with that, to hell with you Sosa!
Ahh... she burned him.
Face, B.A we're booking
out. Sosa shafted us.
Murdock, get the chopper down here in ten.
Okay, he's moving him you
got him, he's moving him.
For the love of god, relax.
I am relaxed, he's moving him.
Don't do this Hannibal, please.
There, that's Morrison
right there. Take him!
Vance!, does he have the plates?
Smith has the plates go now!
I've got Morrison taking the shot.
- A little too close for comfort kid.
- What just happened?
What the hell is he doing?
Where are they? Somebody talk to me.
Come on, did that thing
crush them or what?
Oh, this was a hell of a lot easier
when it was just three plastic cups.
Everybody just be cool, pay
attention, no hasty moves.
So you beat a guy like Lynch by
drawing him in with three things.
What the hell are they doing?
Distraction
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What is happening?
Diversion.
This is a diversion stay
eagle on those containers.
They're making for the exits, open fire!
- Do not engage! Back off!
- All teams engage.
Holy shit!
You are being played
by Smith. He's trying to
draw your eye line
Lynch. Come on, be smart.
Take him, take him, take him!
Contact! Tower house and
bow. It's Peck and Baracus!
And evasion.
It's a trap! Pull back! Fall
back! Get the hell out of there!
No, no, no
What is happening? What is going on?
Nice one kid.
- It's Peck and Baracus.
- Shoot the...
- Shut up I know what I'm doing.
- Okay paint-ballers, time to go pro.
BA, get to your secondary position.
Okay, game-changer... here's what
I think of your best laid plans.
Shit
Jesus Christ!!
- So much for the grand scheme Smith.
- What the hell was that?
- Face, what the hell was that?
- I think this ships going to blow.
- He punched a hole in the hull!
- What about the plan?
Pike just blew up the
plan we are ad libbing!
- Bosco, get out of there!
- I'm going for Hannibal!
- Cover me, I'm going for those plates.
- Yes sir.
- The boat's going over get out of there!
- Face hang on!
Bosco, Pike's got the high ground
I'm running low on ammo man.
Shit!
How are you doing handsome? Shit
can you cycle that weapon, nice work.
Geez, close friends and bullets.
Where are they when you need them?
Don't take this too personally but uh...
look here, smile, and wait for the flash.
Baracus!
Bosco!
Lynch.
Come on Lynch.
- Come on Smith, stop bullshitting.
- Come on Lynch.
Lynch... where am I?
Come on Lynch.
Lynch.
Where am I Lynch!
Lynch... Lynch... Lynch Lynch... Lynch.
Lynch!!
There you are Hannibal. I've
been looking all over for you.
Hey, don't let the scarf fool
you. My Muay Thai is pretty good.
Jujitsu's a little better
but I got this whole...
slight of hand thing going with
the containers and the cars...
and the fireworks. Lynch, Lynch, Lynch.
God that's annoying. But
you give Pike a rocket...
there's your monkey wrench.
Hannibal don't do this.
You know Smith, you could have
the best recipe in the world.
- You owe me that much.
- But you drop a few bullets in the batter.
- Hannibal don't do this.
- Lynch, no!
And that cake don't bake.
Uh oh, your witness,
your gun... your problem.
You served your country well. Excuse me.
Ahh hello Ben. Where
have you been all my life?
Hannibal, you're slowing down,
and bleeding, you're bleeding?
Da da da don't get up.
God damn it!
Your Muay Thai is as bad
as your Jujitsu Lynch.
You better stick with a gun.
You put a loaded weapon in my hand.
I'm going to put a bullet in your head.
I told you I would shoot you.
Kevlar saved your life. The thing is...
doesn't do much good if
I pop you in the head.
It does if you melt it down.
Hannibal don't do this. Hannibal please.
See you beat a guy like that by
drawing him in with three things.
- Distraction.
- Whoa whoa what is happening?
- Diversion.
- Division.
And you put him on display
for the whole world to see.
That's good.
Surprise.
- Agent Burris.
- What did you call me?
Agent Vance Burris isn't that your name?
At least that's the name I've got
on this warrant here. Unless you have
a piece of paper that
looks exactly like...
No, that wouldn't help you either.
Easy, easy.
You're under arrest for attempted murder
violations of the civil false claims act
and theft of top secret
government engraving plates.
Well I guess the plan went okay.
Considering Pike didn't blow up the boat
which I didn't account for at all.
The bullets didn't go through.
- How are you feeling man?
- Not... not good... not good.
I feel sane.
I should have shot you in
the head a long time ago.
Okay Agent Burris, that will be
all. Take him out of here guys.
What's the difference between
a concussion, and a contusion?
Murdock that was beautiful, you were right.
The helmet worked, ketchup worked great.
You did a great job are you okay?
Got your bell rung? Just let
Hannibal make the plans next time.
- Oh... Okay.
- How's the conscience big guy?
At peace.
- Which one of you is Sosa?
- I am.
As of right now, your prisoner is
to be remanded into federal custody.
- I have a warrant for this man's arrest.
- As of right now...
I'm a doctor, I'm going to help
you out. Hey you need stitches?
Please tell me you need stitches.
I could stitch you up really good.
Gentlemen.
Central Intelligence Agency believes
in and invensys a crown moral ethic
as well as an unshakable
professional standard.
As such, we would like to extend our most
sincere apologies for what's happened here.
- Good day and god bless.
- Where are you taking him?
Who?
I never got your name.
- My name in Lynch.
- Of course it is.
Did he just say Lynch.
- Easy guys.
- Everybody, stand down.
Control this place.
When did you arrive I had no idea...
Yes sir.
Get your hands off me tough guy.
Well that's one hell of a
mess. But we did get the plates.
But unfortunately, I'm going to have to
charge you all with escaping lawful custody.
What?! Hannibal what is
this guy talking about?
We were wrongly convicted but it's
still illegal to break out of jail.
Director, Smith and his men were
instrumental in recovering the plates.
They're still level ten fugitives
and I need that off my desk.
This is chicken shit sir.
Well perhaps for them, it is chicken
shit, but for you... Captain...
we're re-promoting you
to your former rank.
So look, they're going to be delivered
to the US Marshalls here in Long Beach,
- I understand sir but...
- This needs to be done!
I'm a Harry Houdini.
- Let's go keep moving.
- Stop, wait.
- This is so wrong.
- Don't worry about it.
I'm going to do
everything I can to fix it.
- I know you will.
- I'm so sorry Face.
Nice plan Face.
Yeah, we just traded Lynches
and we're going back to prison.
We returned the plates, we can hold
our heads high, we did the right thing.
Yeah after what they did
to us. This is bullshit.
They burned us again Hannibal. We
trusted the system and it turned on us.
Remember boys, no matter how random
things might appear, there is still a plan.
Kid...
Well, I don't mean to steal
your line boss, but uh...
I love it when a plan comes together.
They survived as soldiers of fortune.
If you have a problem.
If no one else can help.
And if you can find
them, maybe you can hire.
The A-Team.
Subtitles by greeneagle5
corrected by chamallow