The world of investing.
Can be a jungle.
Bulls, bears, danger at every turn.
That's why we at Stratton Oakmont.
Pride ourself on being the best.
Trained professionals.
To guide you through
the financial wilderness.
Stratton Oakmont..
Stability, integrity, pride.
1, 2, 3!
[ALL CHEERING]
Twenty five grand to the first
cocksucker to nail a bullseye!
come on! Let's go!
One, two, three!
My name is Jordan Belfort.
Not him, me.
That's right.
I'm a former member of the middle
class raised by two accountants
in a tiny apartment in Bayside, Queens.
The year I turned 26, as the
head of my own brokerage firm,
I make 49 million dollars.
Which really pissed me off because
it was three shy of a million a week.
No, no, my Ferrari was white
like Don Johnson's in Miami Vice.
Not red.
See that humongous estate down
there?
That's my house.
My wife, Naomi.
The Duchess of Bay Ridge, Brooklyn,
a former model and Miller Lite girl.
Yeah, she was the one loop my
cock in the mouth in the Ferrari.
So put your dick back in your pants.
In addition to Naomi and my two perfect kids,
I own a mansion, private jet,
six cars, three horses, two
vacation homes and a 170 foot yacht.
I also gamble like a degenerate, I drink like a
fish, I fuck hookers maybe five-six times a week.
I have three different Federal
agencies looking to indict me.
- Yeah, baby..
- Oh, yeah.
And I love drugs.
Okay..
- Oh, yeah..
- One more.
- Oh, you like it?
- Yeah.
Later that night..
Pull up! Pull up! We're gonna
crash! For christ sake!
Come on!
Just relax!
Oh.. Fuck..
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm alright.
- Alright, good.
- Good job.
Good..
You got in there save, alright?
- Until next time, brother.
- Until next time.
Yup, on a daily basis I consume
enough drugs to sedate Manhattan.
Long Island, and Queens.
For a month.
Oke, Mr. Jordan.
I take Quaaludes, 10-15 times a day,
for my back pain.
I had the role to stay focus.
Xanax to take the eye pot ot mellow me out,
Cocaine to wake me back up again,
and morphine, well..
Because it's awesome.
Good morning, Lycon.
But of all the drugs under God's blue heaven,
there's one that's my absolute favorite.
See? Enough of this
shit'll make you invincible.
Able to conquer the world.
And eviscerate you enemies.
And I'm not talking about this.
I'm talking about this.
The money doesn'tjust buy you a better life.
Better food, better car, better person.
It's also makes you a better person.
You can give generously to the
church or the political party
of your choice. You can save
the fucking spotted owl with money.
I always wanted to be rich.
So let me go back.
I'm 22 years old, newly married,
and already a money crisis little shit.
So what do I do?
I go to the one place on earth
that befit my high-minded ambitions..
You are lower than fucking pond scum.
You got problem with that?
Jordan?
- No, no problem at all.
- Good!
Because that's it what you are.
Pond scum.
You job is ''Connector'', which means
that you'll be dialing the
phone over 500 times a day.
Trying to connect me with
wealthy business owners.
And until you pass your Series 7,
that's all you gonna be fucking doing.
Sit. Sit!
Just so you know, last year
I made over $ 300.000.
The other guy you'll be
working for, he made over a million.
A million dollars? I can only imagine
what a douchebag that guy must be.
- Jordan Belfort? Mark Hanna.
- Yeah, sir.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- And you as well,
I see you already meet the village asshole.
Smile and dial.
And don't pick up your
fucking head until one.
Hey, fuck him.
I'm the senior broker here,
dia isjust a worthless piker.
Why don't you blow me, Hanna?
I heard you really pitched a stock
in yourjob interview.
I had to do something to stand out, right, sir?
I fucking love that!
- Lunch, today.
- Ya, alright.
Oh, we don't start dinning at 9:30, because
our clients, they're already answering the phone.
3, 2, 1!
Let's fuck!
You want to know what money's sound like?
Go to the trading floor on wall street.
Fuck this shit that, cunt, cock, asshole.
I couldn't believe how this
guys talk to each other.
I was hooked within seconds.
It was like mainlining adrenaline.
Fuck face! Look where
you start at today, huh?
Motherfucker, you can't get anywhere,
and at 40..
- Pick up the cock sucking phone!
- Yes, sir.
- Market has been raise well.
You are such a fucking dougchebag, Hanna.
We don't give to shit about
how technology work.
Because all we care about is
getting fucking rich!
- Solid!
- Jordan Belfort
I got it!
Time to play the tape!
Wow! a 20.000 Microsoft!
Go in the hole!
Come on! It's alive, it's alive.
I want you to hold on, that is hot.
Here! In, in! Shut that
motherfucker! Shut it! Shut it!
Salut!
Tootski?
Oh, no, no thank you, thou.
Mr. Hanna, what can I bring for
you on this glorious afternoon?
Well, Hactor heres the game plan.
You gonna bring us two absolut
martinis, you know how I like em.
Straight up, and then precisely seven and a half
minute after that you gonna bring us two more,
And then two more after that every 5
minutes until one of us passes the fuck out.
An excellent strategy, sir.
Oh, I'm good with water for now, thou.
Thank you.
It's her first day on
wall street.
Give him time..
Thank you. Thank you.
Mr. Hanna, you're able to drugs
during the day and still function?
And still do yourjob?
Well, how the fuck else would you
do these job?
Cocaine and hookers, my friends.
Right..
I got to say, I'm incredibly excited
to be a part of your firm, I mean..
- Your.. The clients you have were absolutly..
- Talked the clients.
Your only responsibility is
to put meat on the table.
You got a girlfriend?
I'm new married, I have a wife,
his name Theresa. She cut hair.
- Congratulation.
- Thank you.
Think about Theresa.
Named a game, move the money from your
clients pocket.
into your pocket.
Right. But if you can make the clients
money, at the same time, isn't that
advantageous everyone, correct?
No, okay, number one rule of wall street.
Nobody.. Okay, if you Warren Buffet or Jimmy
Buffet, nobody knows.
If a stock's going up, down
orsideways fucking in circle,
At least of all stock brokers, right?
It's all in ''Furgazy''.
you know what Furgazy is?
Yeah, ''Furgazy''..
It's a fake..
Yeah, Furgazy, it's
fegazy, it's a wuzzy, it's..
Fairy dust, it doesn't exist.
It's never landed, that is no matter,
it's not on the elemental charge.
It's not fucking real! Alright?
Alright.
Stay with me.
We don't create shit.
We don't build anything.
- No.
- So, if you got a client.
who brought a stock at 8,
and now it's at 16.
He is all fucking happy, he is
want to cash it, and liquidate.
Take his fucking money and run home.
You don't let them do that.
- Okay.
- Because that would make it real.
- Right.
- Now, what do you do?
You got another brainer idea.
The special idea.
Another situation, another stock,
to reinvested his earning in this stock.
And he will, every single time.
As they're fucking addicted.
And you just keep doing this,
again, and again, and again.
Meanwhile, he think,
he is getting shit rich.
Which he's is, on papper.
But you and me, the brokers?
We taking the whole hot cash.
The via commision, motherfucker!
Right!
That's incredible, sir.
I can't tell you how excited I am.
You should be.
There is two keys, to success,
in broker business.
First of all..
- You gotta stay relax..
- Yeah.
- You jerk off?
- Do I jerk off? Yeah.
Yeah, I jerk off, yeah.
How many time a week?
Like, 3-4 time, maybe..
Gotta pump those numbers out, those
are rookie numbers in this racket.
I, myself, I jerk off, at least twice a day.
- Wow!
- Once in the morning.
Right after I work out,
and then once right after the lunch.
Really?
Well, I want to,
that's not the way I do it.
I do it, because I fucking need to.
Think about you doing with numbers,
all day long.
Desk more point, high frequensy, bang-bang.
Fucking digits kick, kick, kick,
and all very asidick above the shoulders.
Right?
You can't go weeks the people out.
Right? You got to feed the gizz
to keep the blood flowing.
And keep the ryhtme below the belt.
Done.
This is not a tip, this is
a perscription. Trust me.
If you don't, you'll fall out the balance.
Glicth your differasion,
and the tip fuck over.
Or more shit.
I've seen this happen.
In blood.
- No, I don't want blooded, sir.
- No.
- No you don't. Ya.
- I in for a long run, you know?
- Implusion are ugly.
- Ya.
Pop off to the bathroom,
work on that anytime you can.
And when you get really good at it.
You'll be fucking stroking it,
and you'll be thinking about money.
Second key.
To success.
In this rackets, is this little
baby right here, it's called Cocaine.
Right.
It'll keep you sharp between the ears.
You'll also got your finger dial faster.
And guess what.
That's good for me.
Yes, sir.
- Revolution, you follow?
- Revolution.
Keep the client on the fairys will.
And it goes, the park is open 24/7365.
Every decade, every goddamn century.
That's it.
Named the game.
How tickity?
Mmm... Thank you.
Come on.
With combine of dominator
Keep that for me.
# The CEO
# Had the money comes in
# The pray comes down.
# Going down to Broadway.
# It's a one way street.
# Which is a way I go.
For the next six months I got to know
in and out of Wall Street.
Earning shit money, as I
gear up, to take my series 7.
Ow! Oh God!
That was..
Then I was an licensed brooker at last.
Ready to make my fotune.
My first day as a future
master of the universe.
October 19, 1987.
I've X on 86 from six month ago.
Today is draining to 36 in the half.
Mr. Buns! Mr..
They called it, The black monday.
No shit, by 4 PM, the market
has dropped 508 poin.
The biggest plomits since the crash of 29.
I know you family,
you know mine!
No, I don't know, from fucking
country are you or shit.
Let them do what they want fucking do.
Our market are out.
Sir, this is not something you want to sale!
You know what happened?
A fucking Tsunami.
Yeah, I.. Yes, I will talk to your wife.
You not answering the phone,
alot of people gonna be calling you.
Trying to get your dirty laundy.
You don't know what's going on here.
I know, I know.
Holy fucking shit.
Unbelieveable..
My first shity day as a brooker.
Within a month, L.F. Rothschild, an institution
since 1899, closed it's doors.
Wall street did swallow me up,
and shit me right back out again.
We can pawn our engagement ring.
If we needed to.
- Baby..
- Beside that is mine..
- If we need to, I'm just saying.. Okay.
- You listen to me..
You're not pawning anything, okay?
- Okay.
- What I always tell you?
You going to be a millionaire.
That's right, okay? So let me look,
I'll find something.
- How about this?
- What?
''Nobody beats the wiz''
Electronic store, stock boy.
What'd you think?
You not gonna work at that place.
- Yeah, but you know, you start off..
- Jordan, you're gonna be miserable at that place.
If you go there.
It's sales, it work a way out,
I'd be a gentleman.
You're not gonna be stock boy.
- Why not?
- Because you are a Stock brooker.
Do you understand there is nobody
hiring stock brooker right now?
You understand that?
Okay?
Ah, this place is.
- What?
- What those say?
Stock brookers.
- Long Island, stock brookers at Long island?
- Yeah. Yes..
Hei, I'm.. I'm looking for investor center.
That us, you want to invest?
No, investors center,
I'm looking for investors center?
Yeah, yeah, that's us, hey.
That's us, this is it.
This is it.
- Oh..
- I'm Dwayne.
- You Dwayne?
- Yeah.
Alright, Dwayne, we spooked on the phone.
I'm Jordan Belfort.
I'm a Brooker from Rothschild.
- from New York.
- Yes. Yeah, have a seat. How are you?
- You know we have..
- We spooken at phone are they, right?
Two hours ago.
Right, yeah.
Well, that because they ignore the stock.
Of course you never have it,
that's what it's mean.
It's said share!
It's 3 dollar! You cheat fuck!
So where your Quotrons?
- Quotrons?
- Yeah, the computers.
No, no, we don't need computers here,
we just write it up in the pink sheet here.
- Pink Sheet?
- Yeah, the peny stock.
You know, the company that can't
listed in NASDAQ, but they had the capital.
They share traded here.
Peny stocks?
Yeah, this one, Aerotyne,
it's a really interesting..
- Aerotyne..
- Aerotyne, yeah.
- Aerotyne, huh? Yeah.
Really hot stuff right now.
- Yeah?
- You know it'sjust a couple brothers
making radar tech out of their garage.
They are at Dubuque.
Maybe it's a Microwave.
I'm not sure, but if you
called the company mainline.
Their mom, Dorothy answers,
and she is so sweet.
A company?
I actually don't know what else.. I don't
know anything else about them other then that.
6 cent a share?
Oh, come on, who's buy this crap?
Well, I mean, honesly mostly schmucks.
Postman, there is always postman.
Plumbers, em they see our ads in the
back of a Hustler and popular mechanic.
And our ads actually said that
we can make them rich quick.
- Hustler?
- Yeah.
- You know the girly magazine?
- Yeah, yeah.
Nudie mags.
- Alot?
- Yeah.
We helping them financial the houses and we're
helping them buy their wife a diamond ring.
And a boat, maybe.
Is this.. is this.. a.. Is this stuff regulated?
Or you guys.. What are you guys doing here?
Sort of..
Sort of?
Jesus Christ, the speard of this are huge.
Yeah, and that's the poin,
that's.. What your name again?
My name..
Jordan Belfort.
Jordan, what do you get
from that Blue Chip stock?
I make 1 percent.
Well, I didn't make 1 percent.
Pink sheets is 50.
It's 50 percent?
50 percent commission?
- Yeah.
- For what?
It's our market price services.
So if I sells stock at $ 10.000,
my commission is $ 5.000?
If you sell $ 10.000 worth on this stock, I
will personaly give you a blow job for free.
And I hope it's happens.
Hallo, John, how are you doing today?
You mailed my company a post card
for a few week back.
requesting information on Peny stock
that had huge upside potential?
With very little down side risks.
Is that ringing a bell?
Oh, yeah, I interesting on that.
Okay, great.
Well, the reason for the call today, John, is..
Something just come across my desk,
John, it is a packs is the best thing
I've seen in all last 6 month.
If you have 60 seconds, I'll like to share
the idea with you, you got minute?
- Say it, I really interesting on that.
- Name of the company..
Aerotyne International, it is
a cutting edge high tech firm,
Out of the midwest.
Awaiting imminent path approvall
On a next generation of radar detectors that had
both huge military and survilliance application.
Now, right now, John, the stock trade
over the count of 10 cent a share.
And by the way, John.
Our analysis indicated it can go
way hack of lot higher than that.
Your profit, on a mare $ 6.000 investment,
would be up to $ 60.000.
- Jesus! That's my Mortage, man.
- Exactly.
You could pay off your mortage.
This stock would be safe, right?
John, one thing I can promise you,
even in this market.
Is that I never asked my
clients to judge me on my wins
I asked them to judge me on my loses,
becuase I have so few.
And in the case of Aerotyne.
Based on every technical
factor out there, John.
We're looking at the grandslam homerun.
Okay, let's do it.
I'll do $ 4.000.
$ 4.000, that'll be $ 40.000 share, John.
Let me lock in that trade right now,
and get back to my secretary
with exact information,
sound good, John?
- Yeah, that's sound good.
- Great.
Hei, John, thank you for
your vote of confidence.
And welcome to the Investor Center.
- Yeah, thanks alot, man.
- Bye-bye.
How'd you fucking do that?
Just like that I made 2 grand.
The other guys looked at me like
I just discovered 5.
Great! Even better!
I'm selling garbage to garbageman.
And making cash hand over the fish.
the only problem you can have
is you can't buy more.
Boom shoot!
So I was salling them shit.
Way to go!
The way I looked at it.
Their money was better off from my pocket.
I knew how to spend it better.
Excuse me.
It's that your car at lot?
Yeah.
- It's a nice ride.
- Thanks, man.
Donnie Asoff.
- Hei, Jordan Belfort, nice to meet you.
- How are you doing?
- Yeah.
- You know, actually I see that car around.
I seen it around alot.
- Well, you don't happen..
- Yeah, I think we living in the same building
- No shit?
- Yeah, yeah.
- 12 floor? 4 floor.
- Yeah, 12 floor. What floor you at?
- Oh.. Right.
- two little kids?
Ugly wife.
What you do, bro?
What is.. What you mean, what I do?
For work, what you do?
I'm stock brooker.
A stock brooker?
Yeah.
- Childern furniture.
- Oh, good for you.
It's alright.
You make alot of money?
Yeah, I do alright for myself.
I'm trying to put it together,
your fucking nice car..
We living in the same building,
I'm just.. I'm not..
Understand how much money you make?
I don't know, $ 70.000 in the last month.
You fucking kidding.
Get fuck out of here..
I'm serious.
Yeah, now, I'm serious too..
Seriously, how much money you make?
But I'm already told you..
$ 70.000. Well, technically,
$ 72.000 in the last month.
Something like that.
You make 72 grand in a month?
Yeah..
I'd tell you what.
You show me a phase up of
the 72.000 dollars.
I'll quit my job right now,
and I will work for you.
Hei, Paulie, what's up?
No, yeah, yeah, everything is fine.
Hei, listen, I quit.
And he did quit hisjob.
Ya, yeah, I know..
Which I thought it was little wierd,
I mean, I just meet this fucking guy.
Don't tell fucking Susan,
It's not her business.
And there is another thing about him too,
like his phosphorescent white teeth
Wife? I gotta fucking deal with you wife?
and the fact that he wore horn rims
with clear lensesjust to look more Waspy.
Then with these rumors
I've heard some stupid shit,
I don't know..
Look, I don't want to bring it out.
This isjust stupid.
It's was with me?
You know, people say shit, I don't know,
I didn't listen to them talk.
What they say?
It's about this shit you moving with
you cousin, or something like that.
I didn't really listen to it.
- It doesn't make sense.
- It's not like that.
No..
It's not like that.
What I mean, like married you
cousin and some stupid shit,
You know?
Yeah, my wife, yeah.
My wife is my cousin, whatever..
It's not like what you are thinking
of what happen, you know..
- Is she like your first cousin or she..
- Yeah, no, her.. her father..
Is brother of my mom.
It's not like, you know,
look, we grow up together.
And she grow up hot, you know, she is fucking grow
up hot, and all my friend was trying to fuck her.
You know.. And I will not gonna let somebody,
you know, like these asshole fuck my cousin.
So you know, I just do the cousin thing.
Like, I not let them in, I'm not gonna let
someone else fuck my cousin.
You know, if anyone gonna fuck
my cousin it is gonna be me.
I had it respect, you know?
No, I get it. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, you not afraid, like, the whole
kid thing, right?
- Like, that's are..
- We are having kids right?
- Yeah.
- No, we have 2 kids.
And I don't mean, I don't want to get personal.
Like are they really okay?
No, they are not
retarded or anything like that.
But there is a big chance, right?
Yeah, no, yeah, there is like 60%%, you know,
60-65%% chance the kids gonna be fucking retarded.
- Or whatever that is.
- That is really shit out of me, buddy.
Alright, look, man.
Alot can happen
to having a kid, and whatever your have to take
the risk wether you fucking your cousin or not.
- What if you, what if something like that happen?
- I basically, you know..
If the kid is retarded, I would
take him drive out to the country.
And just like, you know, open the door
and I say, you free now.
You know? Like, run free.
You know?
You can't do that, you fucker.
- Itu buruk sekali, kau tahu itu..
- Tidak.
You right, you look like a fuck. But no,
we will taking to like some institution or
somewhere that have angle, you know.
rise the kid or whatever.
You know what? If you happy,
God bless you, buddy.
No, I not fucking happy, no one
married just fucking happy.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that, buddy.
Listen, I really, you know..
I really appriciate this fucking
job, and I'm really enjoy it.
- I'm really happy with what you are doing.
- Actually I got you a present.
- You got me a present?
- I got you something, yeah.
You're fucking sweet.
Yeah, it's back there.
- What you mean?
- We all must go back there.
- Are this wrapped out or something?
- Yes, it's wrapped out, Yeah.
I don't get it.
We can do at our fucking car, come on.
Now your turn.
I'm not fucking doing this!
You gotta be fucking lost your mind!
What the problem?
No, no one is hear this, bro!
Come here! This isjust some crack, bro!
- I will not doing this!
- this is look like a small crack.
- It's more then fucking crack for me, bro!
- One in.
- One in that's it.
- Alright.
Let's rock.
Ya, smoke it, man.
Wow!
Wow..
Let's go, Don..
We gotta get out of here, buddy.
We gotta get out of here,
let's go fucking more!
Let's run like a fucking
lion and tiger are in back!
Let's run! Let's fucking run!
Let's fucking run! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
You reach Frank Best's Otobody.
We're closed right now,
so please leave us some messages.
Hallo, my name is Jordan Belfort.
And my partner and I are very interested,
we think we could your garage.
Donnie and I were going out on our own.
And the first thing we needed was brookers.
Guys who sales experience.
So I recruit some of my home town boys.
Sea Otter, who sold meat and weed.
Chester, who sold tires and weed.
And robbie, who sold anything
he could get his hand on.
Mostly weed.
Hey, can you get some ketchup? Okay?
This is Brad.
And Brad is the guy I really wanted.
But he didn't go along with us.
He is already making so much money saling
quilenty become que lew king of basesack.
Got a pussy right there, or what?
- Hey, man, of couse..
- Maybe I gonna check you out here, sometimes.
I got much.
I got much, you know I mean?
Hey, Zip! Tell sister I was asking about it.
Would you bring me a pair of paddys,
next time you come through?
Yeah, man, but she said she didn't
want to talk with you anymore, man.
Go fuck out of here.
Hey, mom, we got chicken or what?
Mom!
You listening?
It's easier then you think.
Every person you had on phone, they want to
get rich, and they want get rich quickly.
They don't want something for nothing.
Yeah, there is one time, that I
was selling a pot, on this Amish dude,
You know this guy, he got like a beard..
And look like all mustache..
Some bullshit, well, he says..
That he only want to make a furniture.
- I don't understand.
- Kau must be get it.
What the fuck you're talking about?
While from your promoting mouth with nothing,
but you just said that
everybody wants to get rich.
- Holy fuck, you did just say it.
- You just say that.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Yeah, I mean like Buddhas.
They don't give a shit about money,
they're wrappen sheet.
They did buying shit.
I'm not talking about Buddhas
or Amish.
I'm talking about normal people, working class
everyday, people everyone wants to get rich.
- Do I like crazy?
- There is no such thing as Amish Buddha.
- So, don't say fucking shit.
- No.
Hey, can I have a beer?
I didn't say Amish Buddha.
Do you guys didn't want to make some money?
- No, I want to make it.
- I can find one who want money.
I want to make some fucking money, okay?
I can sell anything.
Should I sell this two con friends full in non and
get them so horney so they can fucking each other?
That's the attidude, you can sell anything?
Sell me this fucking pen, right here,
You can sell anything, right? Sell that.
Go ahead, sell me a pen.
Can I finish eating first?
I needed that.
Brad, show them how it's done.
Come on.
Sell me that pen. watch it. Go on.
You want me sell this fucking pen?
That's my boy right there.
This pen.
Fucking sell anything.
Well, do me a favor, why don't write
your name down at that napkin for me?
I don't have a pen.
Exactly. Supplying demands, my friend.
What he saying is creating
urgent needs.
to get the people want to buy this stuff.
We make them something they
need, you know what I mean?
That the thing.
All nuns are lesbians.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Yeah, think about it.
Think, what people can do,
so they just stop..
It's been 4 time,
Give me 4 times..
- She still didn't aware that!
- There she isjust coming.
Oh, look, I know this guys
weren't like Harvard or MBA's
Robbie the pin head took 5
years to finish highschool.
Otter, didn't even graduade.
Chaster the creep chinaman, though
jitjitsu was in Israel.
The smartest from a bunch,
was Nicky Kascov.
He actually went to law school.
I called him, Rugred, because
of his piece of shit hair piece.
Still give them to me,
young, hungry, and stupid.
And in no time, I'm make them rich.
Oh, my God.
- Jordan that..
- You like it, baby?
Ya, I mean, it's beautiful.
They're not the biggest stone in the world,
but I promised they're really high quality.
It beautiful.. I..
That so beautiful..
Yeah, why?
- What?
- I know that look..
- What is it? Go ahead..
- I don't know.. It's you know..
This stock that this company..
They're.. They're like crappy companies.
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay.
Yeah, they're terrible.
Don't worry about it, I've told you,
what I'm doing is completely legal.
Yeah, I know, but they're still not
gonna making more money, thou, right?
Well, sometime they do, sometimes they don't.
You know, how it goes.
Well, won't you feel better if you
sell this to rich people
who making fortune from their money?
Of course.
But rich people
didn't buy penny stocks.
They're just don't.
Why not?
Because they're too smart.
That's why not.
I mean, what person that collage education.
Will trust this bunch of jerkoff.
Tell him to call back!
- We have 5 fucking grand on, right now.
- Hey!
But what if they didn't sound like
a bunch of jerkoff?
What if I can teach them how
to sell to the people with money.
Real money.
So I decided to reinvented the company.
Gentleman, welcome to Stratton Oakmont.
Your snuke now be targeting the
wealthies 1 %% of Americans.
Talking about wealths here.
Mobby fucking Dicks!
And with this scripts, which
is now it's your new harpoon!
I'm gonna teach each and everyone of you,
to be like a captain fucking Ahab.
Get it? Huh?
Captain who?
Captain Ahab.
- From.. Book, you mother fucker!
- Book, you mother fucker!
From the book!
Turn your fucking brain on!
- Fuck you!
- Listen to this.
We're new company.
With a new name.
A company, that our clients can believe in.
A company that our clients can trusted.
A firm whoes roots,
are so deeply in betting on wall street.
That our very founders..
Sale over of the mail flower.
And chizel the name Stratton Oakmont
right into a fucking rock!
You got it?
What are we gonna do are these.
First we pitch them Dysney, TNT, IBM.
Blue Chip Stock's exclusively.
Companies this people know.
Once we sucked them in.
We unload the dark shit.
The pink sheets. The penny stocks.
Where we make the money.
50 %% commission, baby.
Now the key to making money
in this situation like this.
Is the position of yourself
now before the settlement.
Because the time we read it
on the wall streetjournal.
It's already too late.
And you wait.
You wait.
And whoever speak first.
Loses.
Sorry, I.. I appriciate the call..
I really had to give this some thought.
And go talk to my wife about it.
Em, can I call you back?
They don't know, right?
They got to think about.
They are gonna talk to his fucking
wife, to the fucking tooth fairy.
The point is doesn't matter
what the fuck they say.
The only real objection of what
they have is they don't trust you guys.
Why should they trust you,
I mean, looked at you.
You're bunch of slazy salesman, right?
So, what do you say?
You mean, you tell me, that if I put you in.
Kau need to call by the 7,
and you out at the 32.
Texas instrument at 11,
dan took you out at 47?
You are still at 16,
and too you out of 41.
You would going to say to me right now, Chester,
take me up a vew thousand share of dysney.
On the spot, right now.
- Come on..
- You're not sleep, Kevin, honestly, seriously?
I.. I don't know you.
You.. You call phone me.
You're total stranger.
I'm complete agree with you,
you don't know me, I don't know you.
Let me introduce myself to you,
My name is Otter.
- Robbie.
- Chester.
I'm senior vice-president in Stratton Oakmont.
And I planned to being on of the top brookers
at my firm in the next year.
And I not gonna get there by being
below of standard.
I won't say that, you sound like..
You sound like sincerely guy.
Because I'm gonna make you rich,
and it's not gonna make you poor.
But what Stratton will do in it's serving
is bend the mark for future busines, Kevin.
You feel comfortable with me now, Scotty?
And then you'll know, for sure, that you
finally found the brooker on wall street
That you can trusted.
And who can consitetly make you money.
Sound fair enough?
[MOUTHING]
Fuck you!
You know, yeah..
You..
I gotta say, I'm pretty impressed.
What do you... I don't know,
what do you thinking?
Kevin, you give me one shot here
on the blue chips stock like Kodak.
And believe me, Kevin, the
only problem you're gonna have,
is that you didn't buy more, sounds fair enough?
Shit, well...
Ah... My wife might divorce me,
but yeah, let's do it. Oh, yeah.
Excellent choice, Kevin, how
much you wanna go for this time?
- Let's do $5.000 dollars or something...
- We'll try $8.000, Kevin.
- Alright, let's do $10.000. You wanna do that?
- $10.000?
Excellent choice, Kevin let me
lock-in that trade right now...
and get back to you in a few minutes
for an exact confirmation, Kevin.
- And welcome to Stratton Oakmont.
- Thanks, man, I'm gonna have a beer, alright.
It's fun.
- Take it easy, Kev.
- Hey, yeah, thanks Jordan, thanks a lot.
Get the fuck out, motherfucker!
What a fucking idiot.
The one thing I know about
in this world is airlines,
Cruise air lines is the future
of air lines, get in now...
My name is Nicky Koskoff...
Chester Ming...
and I'm a Senior Vice
President for Stratton Oakmont.
Julia, I'm so, so, so sorry for your loss.
Just say I'm wrong, and the stock goes down...
I make you in the words of my grandfather,
God rests his soul in a shit tons of money.
You're gettin' in on fucking sunlight before
there was fucking sunlight, do you understand?
$80.000.
And $25.000.
That's very intelligent decision, I'm
gonna transfer you to my field associate.
Rhonda? Rhonda!
I'm gonna put you through to Andrea.
Does anybody fucking see Rhonda?
Everybody have a good week?
And the mark $28.700,000 in gross
commisions, all from pink sheet stock, boys!
And to celebrate with our weekly active debatery.
I have offered our lovely sales
assistant, Danielle Harrison here...
$10.000 dollars to shave her fucking head!
Do you want this?
Do you want this!
Let's get the party started!
Scalp! Scalp! Scalp! Scalp!
FYI boys, Danielle promised to use her $10.000
for breast implant, she already got C cups,
but now she wants fucking double D!
Is this a great fucking comedy or what?
This is the place to be the wild!
Done it! Blow the roof of this motherfucker!
Do it!
Word about us spread through out Wallstreet.
Even to places I didn't wanted to.
Wasn't long before Forbes Magazine, the flagship
of Wallstreet call to do a profile on me.
Let me ask you, how do you see
the future, for Stratton Oakmont?
We'll work...
- Diversification.
- Sounds good.
Thank you so much, I have more
than enough, I appreciate your time.
- Fantastic!
- Can we get a quick picture?
A total fucking hatchetjob.
This knitting little twad! Look at this!
''The Wolf of Wallstreet,'' they call me. Look!
- Your hair looks good. Yeah.
- My hair looks good.
Jordan Belfort...
(pushing dicey stock)
sounding like a kind of ''Twisted
Robin Hood,'' who takes from the rich...
and gives to himself and his merry little
band of brokers. Read that, read it.
Listen, there is no such thing
as bad publicity, sweet heart.
- Big article, babe.
- Jordan, you look great.
You're in a huge magazine.
The fucking deal I will.
Mr. Belfort! Just give me a chance!
Mr. Belfort! Excuse me, excuse me, Sir!
[CROWD]
Shut the fuck up!
What's all this?
It's the Forbes article, they
all want to work for you now.
Hey! What did I say?
Hey! You want a job, you talk to me!
- Mr. Belfort!
- Forbes make me a superstar.
Everyday, dozens of money craze
kids be the path to my door.
If we hired them, they drop
straight outta college overnight...
and spent whatever allowance they had
on a new suit from our Stratton taylor.
Are you fucking serious right now?
I mean we were literally putting
clothes on these kids backs,
And here comes thisjerk off snffing around.
But you know, everytime
someone rises up in this world,
there's always gonna be some
asshole trying to drag him down.
Within months we doubled in size
and move into even bigger offices.
It was a mad house.
A greed fest, with equal parts,
cocaine, testoterone and body fluids.
Yeah!
It got so bad, I had to declare the office a
fuck free zone between the hours of 9 and 7.
But I'm counting even that didn't enough.
Actually the madness started
on our very first day.
When one of our brokers Ben
Jenner, christens the elevator,
by getting a blowjob from a sales assistant.
Her name was Pam and her credit,
she did have this amazing technique,
with this wild, twist and jerk motion.
By the month later, Donnie
and I decided to double team...
on a saturday afternoon while our wives
were out shopping for Christmas dresses..
Eventually Ben marriage,
that which was pretty amazing,
considering she blew every
single guy in the office.
He ain't got the present and
killed himself 3 years later.
Anyway I hired my Dad, Max to
maintain order as The Enforcer.
Stratton very own Gestapo.
We called him ''Mad Max. '' because
of his hair trigger temper.
Which could be set off by something as
obnoxious as a ringing telephone.
Who the fuck has the Goddamn ball to
call this house on a tuesday night?
Goddamn it!
You're gonna missed it!
Oh, please, tell me something I don't know!
I wait all wek for The fucking Equalizer!
And I have to fucking... Hello?
But as soon as he picked up the phone...
Jean? How are you Jean?
He defect his weird British accent.
Why, yeah, Jean, that would be great. Cherio!
It was absolutely bizarre.
Fucking half wit!
- And hang up and then he's Mad Max all over again
- You missed it!
Damn!
What, tell me what happened, what happened?
Well, he discovered it was the Mother's sister.
Who's he? Who?
- Tell me who he is?
- The main guy.
- You know who the main guy,
- The main guy...
it was his Mother sister, she showed up dead.
Of course, Mad Max didn't have to know
everything we were doing at Stratton.
Then there's a big target and we...
They get lunge at the target, they stick.
There's a bulls eye and the
bulls eye a dollar sign,
whoever gets close to the dollar
sign gets the most points.
I so full of this shit of
this little fucking thing.
Yeah, you have to hear yourself talk.
So, if he gets hurt, what happens?
Yeah, we're gonna a get fucking knock.
I don't think he's gonna get hurt, they're like...
They got like super human strenght.
I think he's gonna be fine.
You can't look him right in the eyes.
You can't look him at in the eye?
That's a fact, I saw it on PBS.
They get confuse, their they wires get cross.
You gotta look like, the chin Like it's looks like
I'm looking at you, but I'm looking at your chin.
I feel like you addressing me
right now, but you're not, are you?
They're like The Monalisa, they find eye
contact, like wherever you standing in the room,
the minute they lock in, you know.
No, but there is a limit to
what we could do with them.
I mean, we're allowed to throw shit at em'.
We allowed to throw food, bananas...
I know crack button.
But, for example, what I wouldn't do
is maybe like tell the police cock out.
and like to get some of the girls
to, you know... Fun or shit like that.
- That would be... That's unacceptable.
- I mean we can, let's keep that in our pocket.
But this guy is more about
thrown, thrown at the dartboard?
Correct, yes, yes.
The thing is this is their gift, okay?
They're built to be thrown like a long dart.
They're top heavy like a long
dart, so they're built for accuracy.
Oh, My God, this is...
Can we bowl with this guy?
That's his fucking brother, Robbie.
He brothers the bowling ball.
The brother you put a skateboard on,
strapped him onto a skateboard.
you toss him down on alley at some pins.
No shit, that's intersesting.
- Can we get that guy?
- We can get, we'll get that guy too.
But it says here, this guy will show his cock.
Yeah, instead of going up, yeah.
They are very armory, by the way, so you
gotta be very careful with these little guys.
Safety first, safety is first, alright?
I want somebody with a fucking tranquilizer
gun, ready to knock this fucker out.
- Do we want to get like a...
- Mace tasers gun.
A pellet gun manybe? Just like the...
No, pellet gun, is gonna hurt him,
I just want him out, knocked out cold
I say we stick with the loophole, right, okay?
We don't considered him a human,
we just considered it an act.
I think we're in the clear, like a flying,
you know a lot of those guys died.
but they never sued anybody.
The important thing, you
guys gotta keep in mind is...
is that these things gossip,
they get together and they gossip.
- It's a good point.
- And the last thing that we need is...
them getting together and then saying ''Oh,
listen, they made fun of us'' like...
- like, it's gonna make Stratton look bad.
- That's why I love you.
You think of shit like that.
That is a come in?
We treat itjust like one of us, okay?
One of us, we're gonna treat them like one of us!
We accept that one of us, we're
gonna treat them like one of us!
Jordan!
Your Dad's coming, something
about The American Express bill?
- Hey, can you get him outta here? I'm not...
- Yeah, lick my toe.
No, I'm serious, get...
Fuck! Okay, guys, act like we're working on stuff.
Okay, he's coming, he's coming.
Make some shit off.
I think we're short at visor...
$430.000 dollars in one month, Jordy, huh?
Four hundred and fucking thirty thousand
fucking dollars in one fucking month!
Good morning, they're businness expenses, relax!
Business expenses? Jordy, look what you got here!
- What?
- Look at this,
$26.000 dollars for one fucking dinner!
Okay, no, no, no this could be explained.
Dad, we had client, we have the Visa client.
Right, the porter house from Argentina.
The expensive champagne and
wine, we have to buy champagne...
And you go it all the fucking sides.
Tel him about the sides order.
- I ordered the sides, so...
- Sides?
Sides? $26.000 dollars, worth the sides?
What are this sides? That cures cancer?
This sides did cure cancer, that's the
problem, that's why they were expensive.
- Shut the fuck up!
- I'm serious...
- I know...
- Stop!
EJ Entertainment, what the
fuck is EJ Entertainment?
Well, that's a...
- Jordan what's EJ entertainment?
- How I describe this...
- It's a fucking prostitution ring, Jordy!
- I know.
- That's what it is!
- That's... That is what it is.
That's the perfect decription for it!
It is what it is, but none
of this were charge to me,
This is all of them.
Oh, that was all of us.
It wasn't me though, fucking
explain the shit to him!
These all of your fucking charges right here!
You guys, The IRS, they
allow for T&A, it's fine.
- T&A, T&A?
- Yeah, I said T&E.
- No, no you said T&A.
- No, I didn't.
- Yeah you did, you say T&A!
- When did I say that?
It's T&E, alright?
I know you're upset about the dinner and that
make sense because we did spend too much money.
But I said T&E...
Don't tell me what you
said, I heard what you said.
- I...
- Dad, he said T&A.
- Yeah, he said T&A.
- Yeah, absolutely no question. I heard it.
Jordan, I'm trying too...
- I'm fucking sweating.
- I'm getting this close.
- Dad, relax!
- I'm getting this close!
That's what I'm saying, why you open up more, Max?
He's gonna fucking kill you.
Why do you hold it in? Max, why do you hold it in?
That's it, that's it! Get the fuck out!
- No, no, no, no!
- Hold on!
Get out asshole!
- What kind of hooker takes credit card?
- A rich one!
At Stratton, there were 3 kinds of hookers,
the blue chips, top of the line, model material.
They cost between $300-$500 and you had to
wear a condom unless you gave them a hefty tip.
Which of course I always did.
Then came the Nasdaq, who are pretty not great.
They cost between $200 and $300 bucks.
Finally there were the pink sheets skanks.
They cost about $100 or less.
And if you didn't wear a condom, you have
to get a pennicilin shot the next day...
and pray your dick didn't fall off.
Not that we didn't fuck them too.
Believe me, we did.
Aw! I slip this thing again.
I know what it is, you know too much...
with EJ Entertainment.
- Pops...
- How are things at home?
Well, not the best, she just doesn't...
You know what I'm saying?
It's like this smell, a smell, there's attraction
thing and after a while itjust kinda fades away.
- Yeah, well it supposed to fade away.
- Supposed to?
- That's marriage, you know...
- That so...
- Your Mother and I we've been
married a long long time. - I know
What do you think? We, we, we...
jumpin' into bed every 2 minutes?
- It doesn't work that way.
- I love her to death, I want to stay married, but
It's crazy out there, some of these
girls. You should see them, oh my God.
They're fucking... The things they doing
now, Pops, I mean it's on a whole new level.
- Really?
- And they're all shaved too.
Get outta here!
- All shaved and nice.
- Are you kidding me?
- Yeah, bald as a China doll.
- No bush? No bush?
- No bush, I know...
- Oh, My God.
All of the sudden like, one week...
- Nobody had anything down there anymore.
- It's a new world.
- They bald from the eyebrows down.
- Wow.
- Nothing, not a stitches, like lasers.
- Wow. New world.
I was born too... Too early.
I've never been a fan of the bush to be honest.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I don't mind it.
Dad, I don't want you
stressin' out about any of this.
How can I not get stressed out? Look at
the knuckle heads you got working for you.
I know they're knuckle head, but I need
them to want to live like me, you get it?
To live like me.
Jordy, one of these days, the
chickens are gonna come home to roost.
You looking at me like I'm crazy.
Crazy? This is obscene.
It was obscene, in the normal world.
I mean who the fuck wanted to live there?
The party are fucking cast off!
We got planes up here, that's gonna take
this company into the fucking stratosphere!
Wolf! Wolf! Wolf!
Fuck Lynch, fuck them!
Why should they be taking all of our
fucking money all the fucking time?
That's why we became underrun.
It was our next big move, finding
companies to take public, IPO's.
It was the only way this Wallstreet pricks...
would ever stop thinking of us
as some shit kick a bucket shot.
We got an unclip international.
See we're a little different, we like to get as
fucked up as possible during our businness powers.
in order to stimulate our free flowing ideas.
Which is why we're popping
this ludes like they were M&M's.
You mad...
We own the fucking company...
We own the company...
Don't know what a ludes is?
I'll tell you.
Wait, wait, wait...
Looks like those ludes are working
their magic on Donnie, right now.
The Quaalude or lude as it commonly referred to,
was first synthetize in 1951 by an
Indian doctor, that's not feathers.
as a sedative and was prescribed to
stressed out house wife with sleep disorders.
But pretty soon, someone figured out that if you
resist the urges to sleep forjust 15 minutes...
you got a prety kick ass high from it.
Didn't take long for people to
start abusing ludes of course.
And in 1982 The U.S Government scheduled
one of them along with the rest of the world.
Which meant there's only a
finite amount of this things left.
No shit, you can't even buy them
anymore, you people all shit out of luck.
- Steve Madden...
- Steve Madden.
- Steve...
- Steve.
You remember those ads?
Those giant headed girls with the bug eyes,
wearing those big clunky shoes?
- My friend from school, Steve Madden.
- His friend from school, Steve Madden.
Steve Madden was the name
in women shoes at the moment...
and all of Wallstreet was begging
to take his company public.
Go ahead, what is it?
- Except, guess who grew up with them?
- Women shoes!
Women shoes.
My very own Vice President.
Diamond Donnie Azoff.
- Madden... Steve...
- Steve.
Jordy, Jordy, Jordy, Jordy... You
better come check this fucking chic' out.
Look at this, look there.
- That was hot.
- That girl, if she was my sister,
I would let that girl give me fucking 8.
Can the wolf handle it?
She's hot!
Christy...
Jordan, this is my friend, Naomi.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Naomi.
Naomi, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, you got an awesome place here.
I don't think I've ever been
in a house this big before.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
There's a beautiful beach out there,
I could take you there...
Blair Hollingsword.
Hi, Blair, nice to meet you.
- Your name is Blair, right?
- Yeah.
- You like to jetski?
- No, never done it before.
- You neverjetski in your life?
- No, I never on a jetski.
- You never been on a jetski?
- No, I haven't.
How many times you gonna ask
her, if she's never on a jetski?
I don't know, I might ask
her a couple more times.
Okay...
- Hi, I'm Hildy, nice to meet you.
- Hi.
Jordan, Teressa need your help.
Yeah, I'll be there in couple of minutes.
Just tell her I'll be there in couple of minutes.
Why don't you tell your wife that?
How am I gonna do that? While
I'm having a conversation...
You know what? I think we should get going.
Wait, wait, where you guys going?
We gotta go, we got to other parties.
- No, no, yeah stay for a drink.
- We can stay for a drink.
No, no, we got to other parties
we supposed to get to, so...
Why don't you let her stay for a while?
- Let her stay for a while, what's the big deal?
- Perfect...
- You like champagne?
- I do.
Donnie, what the fuck are you doing?
You gonna have to excuse my friend, he gets...
- Get the fuck outta here!
- Jordan, you gotta fuck her, she so hot!
Fuck you Donnie, let him finish
it Hildy, that's fucking rude.
So, Bay Ridge. That's near Staten Island, right?
Brooklyn across The Verrazano bridge.
- Southern island territory.
- That's right.
You mean gulge, go to Verrazano
bridge and see the plank.
Right, so I presumed you're Italian?
On my Dad side, I'm also Dutch,
German, English, I'm a mutt.
- You're a mutt?
- Yeah, I still have family over there, in London.
My Aunt Emma, she's the
best, very British you know?
- She's a classy lady.
- That explains it then.
Explains what?
Explains you, I mean you're Duchess, right?
The Duchess of Bay Ridge.
Excuse me, can I get a straw, please?
Thank you.
So, I was a little surprise
you ask Christy for my number.
Why is that?
Aren't you married?
Well, yeah, but what? Married
people can't have friends?
We're gonna be friends?
Yeah. You don't wanna be my friend?
We're not gonna be friends.
And then I worked on my designs.
I have an entire an entire line of
lingerie, camisoles, bustiers, panties.
She designs woman panties too? Oh, My God!
Come on Jordan, think of a
way to get up to her apartment.
You want to come up for some tea or something?
Tea? Yeah, like hot tea?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah, sounds nice, yeah.
Tea, fuck yeah I wanna come up for tea.
Like rosehips or something like that.
This is Rocky.
- Who is this? say hi, Rocky.
- Hi, sweet heart.
- Okay. - Why don't you light a fire or
something, I'll be right out.
- Yeah, fire, yeah.
- Sure.
I like your painting, it's uh...
God, help me how do I fuck this girl?
- Are you alright?
- Yeah, yeah I just try to light the fire in here.
That's it, that's it! You leave and
don't get involved, go home to your wife.
As you can probably guess, I
fuck her Goddamn brains out!
Oh, Jesus Lord!
For 11 seconds.
- Did you just cum?
- Oh, yeah I just came.
- Did you? Did you cum?
- No.
No?
Okay, I'm still hard, just give me a second.
- Sure.
- Yeah...
Come on, come on...
Hold me, oh yeah... Oh yeah...
- Oh, God!
- Fuck off, Rocky!
- Do you have biscuits or something like that?
- It's okay.
- Just keep going.
- Rocky, go play.
Gom play Rocky, go, go...
- You're crazy.
- I couldn't get enough.
I mean her pussy was like heroin to me.
And it wasn'tjust about the sex
either, Naomi and I got along.
I mean we... We had similiar interest in shits.
- Ctulthu train, huh?
- Oh, yeah...
I'm gonna get it...
What's going on down there, huh?
Shit!
You! Get out of the fucking car!
You son of a bitch!
Fuck!
Relax, sweet heart, relax...
- Son of a fucking bitch!
- Okay, okay, babe, stop now!
- Please!
- Bitch!
- What do you doing? I thought you're in...
- With the whore from that party?
- Jesus Christ!
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
I thought you're at the fucking beach!
i didn't know you were here.
That's who you fucking been?
With that fucking whore from the party?
What are you doing here? I
thought you were at the beach!
How could you do this to me?
- Sweetie, come on!
- I don't know who the fuck are you Jordan.
You're like a completely different fucking person.
I made a mistake, I don't know
what to tell you, babe, I...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Is that what you want?
Do you love her?
Answer me.
I felt horrible.
3 days later I filed for a divorce
and move Naomi into the apartment.
Say what you will, but the Duchess did have style.
She brought in an decorator,
feng shui the whole place,
she even hired a gay butler.
This guy was smart, sophisticated,
professional, I mean really, really great.
- Jasmine? - Yes, Sir, I try to stump
you this evening, really good.
Very good, great nose.
Except for that one time.
Oh, My God!
Oh, hey...
Is it wednesday already?
What the fuck? That is fuck up!
He must thought we still at The
Hamptons this weekend, you know?
- Where are they doing it, sweet heart?
In the bed room? - They were everywhere!
There were 2 guys over there on
the table, there are more over here.
- There were 4 right here.
- Oh, God! Are you fucking serious?
Right there? Why didn't you tell me, sweetie?
Baby, that worst.
After they're left they checked the apartment.
Right, what? What is it, baby? What?
- Where's my money?
- I don't know where your money...
zWhere's my fucking money, where is it?
I don't know where your money is
Mr. Belfort, I didn't do anything.
- You don't know where my money is? - He's
lying Jordan, he's lying to his fucking teeth.
Let's start from the beginning!
Let's start from the beginning, right?
- You invited some friends over, right?
- Yes.
One thing led to another, things got outta hand,
We understand that, we do blow all the time, we
fucking degenerates us, so look at us, right?
My money were stolen from my
apartment, right from my socks drawer, alright?
Like I say, I don't know where your money is.
Just start from the beginning, who came over?
It's a normal day, I knew
you coming home the next day,
so everything will be fine, it will be cleaned up.
I got a little high at breakfast, I
got a little happy and made some eggs.
had a little bit ice cream, and then I
say, who do I know who likes ice cream.
- My friend Rudy, so I call Rudy.
- Who's Rudy?
- Yeah, who's Rudy?
You know who Rudy is, come on.
- He know who Rudy is?
- Who the fuck is Rudy?
- I don't know anyone named Rudy.
- You know, last month, The Lollipop club.
You know who Rudy was.
You know Rudy?
I don't know about, fucking know anyone...
What do you mean?
- So he went to The Lollipop club?
- Oh, he was at The Lollipop club for sure.
On the stage aquintance with everybody.
I got fucked up, I like the dance, I don't
know... Maybe I met them, maybe i didn't.
I meet a lot of fucking people.
- $20.000 dollars was stolen from my fucking
sock drawer! - What are you saying?
All my girlfriends know that!
I don't know who Rudy is, what the fuck!
You little faggot friend, Rudy,
take my shit, did he? Answer me!
Okay, now I get it, now I get why I'm...
This is a gay thing.
- Oh!
- I see all of you.
This is because you're a fag?
My cousin is a fucking faggot and I go on
vacation with him and his boyfriend! I love faggot
You're like being charged, right?
I will not be stolen from, you get that?
I fucking like gay people, I don't like you!
You should hire a fucking Mexican
like I hired in my fucking house.
Shit!
You fucking!
Talk, you fuck, talk!
I'm gonna drop you, you fucking!
Where is it?
Chester and Toby, they
went all yakuza on Nicholas.
You know, they got crazy.
I really appreciate your help.
I had to call the copsjust to
keep them from killing the poor guy.
I gave them each $2.000 bucks and
told them what Nicholas have done.
They naked his ass.
It's not like I care about the $50.000 anyway.
I was making that much almost everyday
through one rat hole or another.
A rat hole, is a friend, like Brad here.
Who held stock in his name for me.
How are you doing? Goodbye...
I drive the price up, then he'd sells
and kick most of the profit back to...
you guessed it, me!
All cash, none of it's on the books.
A big no no of course in the eyes of the law.
Enter our new security attorney, Manny Riskin.
$700 bucks an hour to be the voice of doom.
You pissed up the SEC's leg, you
end up with your tits in the ringer.
Do not worry about it, I
have The SEC under control.
What the fuck are these imbeciles doing?
Hey, what are you doing? Hey!
We got The SEC in here!
The Security of Exchange Comission
sent 2 lawyers down to review our files.
So I set them up in our conference room.
And I had it bugged and the air conditioning
turn up so high that it felt like antartica there.
- Is it always this cold in here?
- I don't know.
Then, while they were looking
for a smoking gun in that room,
I was gonna fire off a bazooka
here, offering up our latest IPO.
An IPO is an initial public offering,
It's a first time a stock is offered
for sales to the general population.
Now as the firm taking the company
public, we set the initial sales price...
then sold those shares right back to our friends.
Yet... Look, You're not gonna
following what I'm saying anyway, right?
That's okay, that doesn't matter.
The real question is this, was all this legal?
Absolutely fucking not.
We will making more money
than we knew what to do with.
And what do you do when you making
more money than you knew what to do with?
Oh, My God.
Will you marry me?
Is that a yes?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- Yeah.
I held my bchelor party
at The Mirage in Las Vegas.
They flight there alone was a buck and all.
One last blow out fior the God
before I settle down for good.
A hundred staff, 50 hookers plus
50 more waiting once we landed.
All in drugs, I mean I tell you, up
plane was like a pharmacy with wings.
All told, that we came
across nearly 2 million bucks.
Including the cost of
refurbishing the entire 28 floor.
Kiss the bride.
Ah, but the wedding was
something out of a fairy tale.
With Naomi, my Duchess.
Meet her handsome Duke in the Bahamas ocean club.
Of course after the bachelor party, me,
The Duke needed a few pennicilin shots,
so we could safely consumate the marriage.
I'm Barry Klineman, filming the wedding.
A few words, huh? For your son.
Jordan, remember what I told you, it
involves your penis and her vagina...
and you know what to do, Jordy.
Oh, My God! Aunt Emma?
Auntie, you came!
Jordan, Jordan!
Look who came, it's Aunt Emma!
- Aunt Emma, hey, how are you doing?
- Jordan, how are you?
Glad you came, pleasure to
finally meet you in person.
You're not too sassy.
I... I was.
I live through the 60's my dear...
Enjoy the day.
She wants to meet you, I didn't even know.
- Just one more step.
- Where are we going?
Keep your eyes closed, 1, 2, 3!
- What is this?
- It's your wedding present.
- What?
- It's your wedding present, sweetheart.
What?
- Are you serious?
- I'm serious.
A fucking yacht?
Millionnaires, whose ship come in,
A pricy pleasure boat offer the most fun of love.
It's no coincidence that it's 150 feet
of green hull is the color of passion.
And cast away!
Oh, My God, baby!
- I think you're like it?
- You're crazy!
- You like it?
- Yes!
For 3 weeks we sailed The
Naomi through the Carribean,
eventually taking our home to Long
Island where we bought a house.
7 acres on the gold coast of Long Island,
the most expensive real estate of the world.
With maids, cook, landscape, as you name it.
We even had 2 guards who works
in shift, both named Rocko.
''18 months later. ''
It was heaven in earth.
Wake up you piece of shit!
Who is Venice, huh?
- Who? Who?
- Who?
What are you a fucking owl? Who is she?
- I don't know what the,
- Some hooker you fuck last night?
What the fuck are you talking about?
No, no way baby, no!
You're calling her name in your sleep!
Are you out of your fucking mind?
I don't even know who Venice is.
What the fuck does that even mean? Venice!
That's the Stupidest shit I ever hear
in my fucking life!
Venice, Venice baby where are you?
Venice, Venice!
Where did you go?
[ GROANING ]
Oh baby, oh you can play rough, huh?
- Oh, jesus christ!
- Relax.
I like it, I like it..
Aw, wolfie, wolfie, wolfie!
- Wolfie?
- Yeah, it's my safe word baby, it's my safe word
- I don't give a fuck about your safe word!
- Oh come on!
Shut the fuck up!
[ SCREAMING ]
Shut up, you little bitch!
Ah! Your fucking dirty little birdy!
[ SCREAMING ]
That's right, that's right, I forgot.
Forget it babe, Donnie and I were investing in the
condominium complex in Venice, that's why this all
is confusing!
- You were investing in Italy?
- Not Italy, California.
- California?
- Yeah!
You're lying piece of shit!
- Duchess, baby.
- Don't you fucking duchess me!
- Don't you duchess me!
- Okay, I am sorry.
Do you really think that I don't know
what you're up to?
- You're father now, Jordan.
- Yeah.
You're father now, and yet you still acting
like an infant!
God damn it! Baby, you know, you got really
anger issues!
- You got so many emotional problem..
- Who was the one who threw in here..
At three in the morning on that stupid helicopter?
And woke up Skylar.
- That was you.
- Skylar, that fucking bullshit!
Does it matter to you, that I just hit that
driving range, sided with bermuda grass..
- Oh, My God, bermuda Grass.
- You fucking ridiculous!
No, you didn't research the whole thing, and
you with the fucking gold course!
Oh my God, you had the deal with the golf
course people too!
What a great tragedy, honey, oh My God.
You probably had to pay them in cash,
with you hand, what a fucking burns!
And actually do some work besides swiping
my fucking credit card all day, huh?
'Cause I can't keep tracking you profession,
honey!
'Cause last month you're one connoisseur..
And now you aspiring landscape architect,
let me get that right?
- Fuck you!
- No, no fucking dare throw that fucking
water at me!
Don't you fucking dare!
All right, honey?
And we can just, we can talk this on, all right?
Just use our words, you know..
Communicating, okay?
Come one sweetheart, talk to me.
Stop flexing your muscle Jordan, you look
like a fucking imbecile.
Babe, come on, you should feel..
...should feel happy you gotta husband
who's in such a great shape like this, huh?
Come here, come on give me a kiss, you look
so beautiful right now, come on.
- Kiss you?
- You look so beautiful..
- Yeah, give me one..
Fuck you!
Ah, yes, my morning ritual.
First I'd get up and fight with Naomi about
whatever is I did the night before,
Next was a steam so I could sweat out the
drugs that still in my system..
Then I assess the damage.
Drowned out my eyeball, take my back pill
to get the day started,
Then seek to make up with Naomi.
Good morning daddy.
Where's my kiss?
Hey, sweetheart..
Could daddy get a kiss from
both of you little girls?
Oh no, no, daddy doesn't even get to touch
mommy, for a very very very long time
Daddy is really sorry about what he said
in the other room, he didn't mean any of it.
Daddy shouldn't waste his time.
And from now on, it's gonna be nothing but short,
short skirt around the house.
And you know something else, daddy..
Mommy isjust so sick
and tired wearing panties
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
In fact, she is decided to throw them
all away.
So take a good look daddy,
You gonna be seeing all of this
around the house.
Yeah, mommy.
But no touching.
- What's wrong daddy?
- oh, baby..
God..
Look at this shit.
Okay, mommy likes to play game with daddy.
Mommy..
Have you ever notice anything odd about
Mr. Fuzzybear over there?
His eyes seems to be a little bit odd, don't they?
Yeah, there's something little bit different
about his eyes.
Yes, I think it's true,
say hi mommy!
Say Hi to Rocco and Rocco,
say hi.
Are you fellas see that, huh?
Of all the fucking days, she chooses today
to give me blue balls.
I mean today was the biggest day
in Stratton history..
And I needed to be thinking straight.
Jordan, welcome!
Steve here yet?
This was the day that we launch the Steve
Madden IPO.
Should be around here,
everyone are rallied, excited..
Everything had to run tight, and had
to be perfect.
What the fuck is that kid doing?
What is he doing?
The biggest IPO in the firm's history,
what the fuck is he doing?
Is he.. is he wearing a bowtie?
Hi, How are you doing?
Good.
Are you cleaning the fish bowl?
- I just, I had a minute and I..
- You gotta minute, and today you need to clean
the wish bowl? today?
I have finished my paperwork, and I was
thought that I just have couple minutes.
Okay, nice to meet you.
On the issue day!
You cocksucker! Why the fuck in the issue day?!
This is what you do?!
Hey, everybody, listen up!
This is what happen when you fuck with
your pet on the Issue day!
Take your little bowtie, get your
shit, and get the fuck outta my office.
You understand?
Get the fuck out!
Everybody on port! We are here
to make money, everybody on port
The real wolf pit, which
is exactly how I liked it
Jordan, When I came to lobby I caught a genius.
Enter, Steve Madden.
Red hot ladies footwear impressario.
And thanks to Donnie, we were taking
this company public
Stratton Oakmont was crawling at the
primordial Oz.
Pawn Scam no more.
That's why they gotta see your face.
Get them fired up so they push the
shit outta this stack, okay?
Not only that, Donnie and I secretly own
85%% Steve Madden's shoes.
Which illegally speaking was a big no, no.
But we get filthy fucking rich
of our troops got behind it.
Ourjob was to get them worked up.
But not too worked up.
Hello, for those who don't know me, I uhhh,
my name is Steve Madden.
- Yeah we know who you are.
- Your name is on the bucks.
The shoe, show them the shoe,
show them the shoe.
Okay, yeah, anyway, you know,
this shoe..
This pretty cool, this is the Mary Lou
Which is really the shoe who put me on the map,
without her, I wouldn't be here.
- It's a fat girl shoe.
- Believe it or not..
Believe it or not, though, Mary Loui is actually
the same as the Mary Jane but it's black Leather.
Got back! Come on, will you, will you!
All right, let's give it up for Steve Madden, and
his awesome Mary Lou, hold that up, hold that up.
Hold that up proud, all right!
Give him rioting applause!
- You guys gotta that on your system, huh?
- Yeah!
You're having good afternoon or what?
I want to take a moment to tell you why Steve
here is so absolutely off the fucking wall.
Is because this man is a creative genius.
This ability, this gift that Steve has..
.. goes beyond just, spotting the hottest shoe
trends.
Steve's power is that he creates trends.
You understand?
Oddest like Steve come along once every Decade,
I am talking George Romany, Gianni Versace,
Coco Schnell..
Izalora!
Steve come over here for second.
I don't think you're all realized.
That Steve Madden is the hottest person in the
winning shoe industry with orders going through
the roof of every departmen store in North America
We have him here at our office!
We should thank our fucking lucky
star, this man is here.
We should be on our hands in knees right
now, getting ready to suck this guy off!
Like this! Ok? I want to suck
you off, Steve!
Everyone is going to suck you off.
This is our golden ticket into the
fucking chocolate factory right here.
And I want to meet Louis Vodka Wonka,
okay?
And I want to meet with the fucking
Oompa Loompa like this!
All right, get off this fucking stage,
get out of here.
All right, I want you to focus
for a second.
See those little black boxes?
They call it telephone, I'm gonna let you in on
a little secret about this telephone.
It not gonna dial themselves, okay?
Without you, they just worthless
hungs of plastics.
Like a loaded M-16 without a trained marine
to pull the trigger.
And in the case of the Telephone,
It's up to each and every one of you..
My hightly trained Strattonites,
my killers who will not take no for an answer.
My fucking warriors.
Who'll not hang up the phone.
until their client either buys or
fucking die!
Let me tell you something.
There is no nobility in poverty.
I've been a rich man, and I've been a poor man,
and I choose to rich every fucking time!
'Coz at least as a rich man, when I have to face
my problems, I show up in the back of the limo..
Wearing $ 2000 suite, and $ 14000
gold fucking watch.
Good boys, get him up! Hit him!
Fuck off from me!
If there anyone here thinks I am superficial
of materialistic..
Go get a job in fucking McDonalds, 'cause
that's where you fucking belong!
But before you depart this room
full of winners..
I want you to take a good look at the
person next you, go on.
'Cause sometime in not so distant future..
You know, you pulled out to a red light and
you beat-up old fucking Pinto, and that person
gonna be pulling up right along side you..
In the brand new Porsche.
With their beautiful wife by their side,
who's got big full up juiced tits.
And who will you be next to?
Some disgusting wildebeast with 3 days of razor
stubble in a sleeveless moo-moo, crammed in the
next you with a carload of groceries from the
.. fucking price club!
And that's who you're gonna be sitting next to!
So you listen to me and you
listen well.
Are you behind on you credit card bills?
Good, pick up the
phone and start dialing!
Is the landlord ready to evict you? Good!
Pick up the phone, and start dialling!
Is your girlfriend think you're fucking
worthless loser? Good!
Pick up the phone and
start dialling!
I want you to deal with your problems
by becoming rich!
All you have to do today!
Is pick up the phone.
And speak the words that I have taught you.
And I will make you richer than the most
powerfull CEO in the United States.
I want you to go out there..
And I want you to ram Steve Madden's stock down
to your clients throats..
Till they fucking chokes on it.
Till they choke on it and the buy a hundred
thousands shares, that's what I want to do!
You need ferocious!
You be relentless!
You'll be telephone fucking terrorist
Now let's start this motherfucker
rolling around!
[ MUSIC ]
At one PM, we opened the stock for sale
at 4 dollar and 15 cent a share
By 01:03, it was over $18.
Even the big wallstreet firms were buying.
From the 2 million shares offered for sale, a
million belong to me held in phony accounts by my
ratholes.
Now, once the price hit the high teens..
You know what? Who gives this
shit? As always, the point is this.
$ 22.000.000 in 3 fucking hours!
Can you believe it?
I get love this-
Crazy account!
Call for you! Berry Kleinman
on the phone from Future Video?
- Who?
- I don't know, he shoot your wedding,
he said it's urgent.
Urgent? Who the fuck is Berry Kleinman?
Oh my God, you want to marry me?
You're in love with me?
Yeah, go fuck your cousin.
Berry, what's up?
- Listen, uh, I got this Subpoena..
- Subpoena? What are you talking about?
The FBI, they want to copy of your
wedding video.
Fucking FBI? Are you fucking kidding me?
Listen to me, his name is Denham, he is an
agent within the New York Office.
What is his problem? He's a boyscout!
Thinks you're fucking Gordon Gecko!
What does he want from my wedding video?
It's like invasion to my privacy.
You know what I am saying? It's like..
It's intrusive!, you know..
He's got picture of your whole inner
fucking circle
Pictures, name of the people, he is do what
is he wants to do, exactly what is he do.
Look at your self, he's try to rattle you,
he's try to rattle your old lady..
So she nagging you to turns become
a fucking witness.
Oh, so he wants me to rat on my self, he wants
me to give information about my..
- What your solution?
- The good fucking news, is I know everybody
down town.
I called the justice department, the DEA, nobody
even know you fucking exist. So calm down!
- They don't know I exist?
- No.
That's Good.
- But you.. you know who is he, right?
- Yeah.
So if I just want to get some more information,
just find out what he know, you can.. you can go
his house, go to his house
right, tap his phone, a little bit bug him..
you could get some information
You don't fuck with these guys like this.
You don't fuck with him like that, what do
nuts or something?
What do you fucking do? What did I pay you for?
I have a fucking PI license, you know?
I am making living at this, I am not
a cop anymore.
- They'll take my fucking license away from me,
all right? - Okay.
Okay, if I can't do that, can I just
can I get the guy a call?
- Why? Is that..
- Jordan, Jordan..
Do me a favor, the only one who
call this guy is your lawyer.
- Allright, okay..
- What would you do?
I told you, whatever the fuck you say to him, he's
gonna use against you, don't you understand?!
He is smart, you dumb
- I am not allowing call-
- Are we fucking talking tonite or you gonna
or you gonna get you wipe..
The last time you took this fucking pills, you
put your head and fucking like a maniac, now
pick it up!
All right.
Okay, I won't call him.
Hey fellas, come on board, plank's
around there.
Welcome.
Huh, what a nice day.
Hey, welcome aboard
Jordan, welcome to the Naomi,
nice to meet you.
- Agent Denham, this is agent Hughes.
- Hi, how are you?
Now, I'll introduce you..
This Nicole, Heidi, come on,
don't be shy..
Why do you guys shy for?
Don't be scared..
These are friends of Stratton.
- It's a pleasure.
- Hello.
- Come on..
- Your message said that..
You want to speak privately.
Right, I do want to speak privately.
Give us some minute, hey ladies?
- Let me know if I can get you anything.
- We'd be happy to help.
You guys hungry? Want some to eat? We got some
pasta, shrimp, lobster. I got whiskey and kind
of Booze..
You know what, the biro doesn't allow us
to drink while at sea.
Duh, I forgot, of course.
Ever been on one of these before?
A boat?
Learned to sail when I was six
No shit? Is that right? All right.
I mean, one like this.
The whole front extended so it fit
the chopter up there.
You see that?
Any way, this is for you.
It's uh, a complete list of every person
who was at my wedding..
Yeah, I understand you want the whole wedding
video, figured this would help the whole process,
right?
- There you go.
- Look..
My point is that I know you're investigating
Stratton..
But for the life of me,
I can't figure it out why
I know we are little unorthodox, we are little
loud in the way we do things, we gotta understand
with the new guys on the block..
You know, trying to make an impression, but..
Now I want you to understand, we don't..
do anything Illegal, whatsoever.
You could talk to the SEC, there were at my
office 15 times for the last 6 month..
I mean I got nothing to hide.
Well, you know the SEC is civil right regulatory
agency, we pursue criminal activity.
Exactly, you go after real criminals..
Makes me wonder what.. what the hell are you
doing sticking me for?
What is the thing that we did? or do?
I don't get it.
Well, I.. Jordan I can't discuss
ongoing investigations.
No, I get that, No I understand.
With that said, this case got dumped on
my desk.
- Did it?
- You know, by higher up who..
needs to make a show looking in and the
new company on the block..
- Loud guy..
- I got pressing and anything..
And then I ended up be in the
smuch who does the local, exactly.
Itjust, you know, bothers me..
We are the new guy..
Where the one with bank there
in Wallstreet?
Oh man, you should see what's going on the
bigger firms, I mean I know all the information.
It's true, Goldman, Lehmann Brothers, Merryl,
collateralized debt obligation..
Internet stock bullshit? I mean, it's a fucking
travesty.
I mean I can take you step by step, to what
exactly is occuring, you know..
All you have to do is ask.
It's exactly what I want to hear.
- Hmm.
- I don't see why a little sitdown like this, can
be profitable for the both.
- It should, right, it should profitable.
- It should.
Look, I am gonna give my personal line, 5
days a week, you just call me, feel free.
- I'll do that.
- Great.
Are you sure you guys don't want some to
drink? I mean, you're not hungry? Nothing?
- Nothing?
- Oh no.
No.
Mind if I ask you, and if you dont want to get
too personal, just tell me to shut up at anytime.
Did you try to get your broker's license
at one time?
Isn't that right? When you trying to take
a step at wallstreet?
- No?
- Who have been told it to you?
- Who the fuck you've been talking to?
- Why you investigating me..
Hei, you see what I mean?
You ever think about what would happen
if you're, you know, stay in the course.
You know what? When I ridin' home on the subway,
and my balls are fucking sweating, I'm wearing the
same suit 3 days in a row,
Yeah, you bet I do, I've thought about it before.
Who wouldn't rite?
Yeah, who fucking wouldn't?
I mean, what do you.. another personal question,
no need to answer if you don't like..
No, that's all right, Jordan.
Whattaya pull in? 50? 60'k?
something like that?
A year? Low part?
Let's put it this way.
You get a free hand gun when you
sign up for the biro.
No, but it is fucking pisses me off, you know.
When you think about the people that build
this country, hardworking people like you..
You know, fire fighters, teachers,
FBI agent..
End of the day you guys get fucking skin-the-life
financially, fucking makes me angry.
That's the one thing about Wall street, in this
market is, for me..
I feel it's good to give back, you know,
There's situation where I can..
make those situations better for people.
You know what I mean.
Opportunity is everything.
Exactly.
Take for example I got this one
kid, right?
He went to school for environmental
science something like that..
He was bogged down by students loan,
turns out, his mother needed triple bypass surgery
- Right, horrible situation.
- Sure.
We got them minute, the market, the right time,
choose the right stock, we gave him the right
guidance..
Bom, overnight, change his entire life..
You know, He gotta put his mother into
the best hospital in New York City.
It didn't work out for her, she passed
away unfortunately, but..
We gave him that opportunity,
you know what I am saying?
Itjust about sending up the right team and
then overnight your life can change.
What if.. what is.. what is the intern to make
a deal like that?
Oh that's the situation.
I mean, that particular trade,
and one trade.
North of half a million dollar.
And I do that for anybody, you know, anybody
that needs the proper guidance.
Can you say that again? Just the
way you said it.
Just the same way.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- No..
- Oh come on, you know what I am talking about.
- No, I don't know..
Say this, I think Jordan just did..
- If I am not mistake
- No.
- You just tried to bribe a federal agent.
- Oh, technically I didn't.
I didn't bribe anybody, technically, I didn't.
No, according to US criminal code, there needs to
be exact dollar to give for the exchange services.
that would not hold up on the court of law..
No, no, no, that's the truth, but..
- I want to tell you this.
- Yeah.
The same gentlemen that told me that you try to
get your brokers license also told me that you're
straight arrow.
- You ran a security check on me?
- Well..
Sail on the boat, fit for Bond villain,
sometimes you need to play the part, right?
I think it's time you both get the fuck
off my boat, what do you say?
You know Jordan, I'll tell you something.
- Most of the wallstreetjackasses that I bust..
- Yeah.
They're.. they were the man for born.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Their father is douchebag, just like the
fathers before them
But you..
- You got this all way on your own.
- Did I?
- Good for you, little man.
- Little man?
- Good for you.
- Me, the little man?
Let me tell you something.
No, let me tell you something else.
Honestly, I am not bullshit here, this is one of
the nicest boat I've ever been on,
- I got tell you this.
- I bet it is.
And you know what I just thinking too?
what a fucking hero that I am gonna
back at the office..
When the bureau seizes this fucking boat,
because I am being fucked this, fuck, fuck..
It's beautiful, and you got the beautiful
girls there.
- It's wonderful.
- Okay, get the fuck off my boat.
I am sure we'll be seeing each other
real soon.
I am sure, good luck on that subway ride home,
and your miserable ugly fucking wife
I am gonna have Heidi lick some caviar off
my balls in the mean time..
Hey, you guys want to take some lobsters
for your ride home.
Fucking miserable bricks, I know you can't
afford 'em, fucking cheap fuck.
Fuck those people.
Hey fellas, look what I found in my pocket!
Your salary, right here!
You know what I call 'em?
Fun coupon.
See that?
The fun coupon.
What's hon? What the fuck is in switzerland?
Swiss fucking bank, that's what.
He was ask couple of time.
I had to hide my money.
Enter Rugrat.
He knew this Swiss Banker from law school.
But he was in Geneva, and there's no way I was
gonna make that flight sober.
So I knew if I took my drugs right
I could sleep to the entire flight.
But I had to take them just right.
At 4 PM I pooped a few more ludes,
which is start kicking in by the time I
finished my sales meeting. My dingle face.
By dinner, I popped a few more, on top
of some coctail and valium too.
My slur phase
By eight thirty, I took a few more ludes..
I am pretty much lost all my motor skill.
This was the drool face.
And by ten, I didn't know who or what
the fuck I was.
The Amnesia phase.
And boarded to the plane just before
midnight.
- Ah look at you, you're so beautiful.
- Excuse me..
It's his sleeping pills, he's all right,
he's all right.
- May I ask your boarding pass, sir?
- We have the boarding pass.
Jesus Christ, I am so sleepy.
Hey, relax!
Oh my God, you got your hand
on my fucking cock!
Get in chair, this guy is touching
my dick again.
- You got his hand on his dick?
- You gotta stop doing that..
...in public space.
Take it off.
I heard there's treasure map under this..
- Excuse me sir.
- I know miss.
Please sit down..
- Watch him.
- Go back to your seat please.
- What are you upset about?
- Please go back to your seat.
I had been have to call the taxing.
Please sir, please, sit down.
- Please,Sit down!
- Okay, okay, I am going!
- Stop!
- We apologize, we are going to sleep ma'am.
We're sleeping as you question.
Fasten your seatbelt, sir.
- okay.
- We cannot take off if you haven't
fasten your seatbelt.
Sit down, fasten it, I can do it for you.
- What?
- I will do it for you.
- Okay.
- You gotta speak english..
We don't understand this languages, mam..
I will help him fasten his seatbelt..
I am not a fucking idiot.
Sit back, sit back!
There you go, yeah there you go!
- Hilfa!
Jesus christ, fuck.
Donnie, this isn't funny, you
must untie me, buddy.
I can't untie you.
The captain tied you up, he almost
fucking teasing you.
- Why?
You were screaming at the people.
You are on the floor, like rolling
around and shit.
- You called the captain the ''N'' word.
- I called the captain the ''N'' word?
- Yeah, he was very upset.
- Really?
- Luckyly we're in the first class.
- Oh jesus.
Jesus christ, I think you have a fucking
drug problem!
- Where the ludes?
- There're at my ass, don't worry about it.
I got it.
Thank god.
Jesus Christ, what we gonna do when we
get to Switzerland buddy? This is bad.
I think this belt are get on my chest,
I can't breathe, come on do something to calm me
down, please?
Okay, Shut the fuck off, shut the fuck off.
- Oh please?
- Okay, sshh
That's good.
Go to sleep.
- Harder buddy.
- You're all right.
We're all love you..
Shut the fuck off!
Mr. Belfort, you're free go.
Really?
- Hi, Donnie.
- Yeah?
When we get up there, try not to act like
yourself, okay, let's make you even ass hole
version Donnie, all right?
- Why phone and call me to come for?
- Hey listen.
The only reason you sitting in this limo and not
a Swiss dale 'cause you're my friend,
- Ok?
- Hilfa!
- We're here, here, we're here.
- I am more calm down, come on.
Jordan Belfort, at last..
Nicholas has told me so much about you.
- Jordan, Jean Jacques Saurel.
- Pleasure to make your acquiantes.
Nice to meet you.
You understand what we're talking?
Oh, ok.
- Couch, for desk.
- I don't understand, I am sorry.
I am curious about your
bank secrecy laws here.
Wait, yes, excuse me Jordan.
- Swiss custom, we require 10 minutes of bla bla.
- Chit chat.
Chit chat thank you, before business
can be discussed.
Yeah.
Of course, let's get down to it.
What would you like to know?
Under what circumstances would you be obligated
to cooperate with the FBI or..
US justice department investigations,
for example?
Ca depend.
- Ca depend?
- Yeah.
Ca depend on what exactly?
Whether America plans to invade
Switzerland in upcoming month.
- So you want check the tank are rolling down
the Ru de La Croix? - Yes, Ru de La Croix
- Ah, Croix!
- Yeah, Croix
Not Croix, not even Ru de La Croix, Croix
This is what we used to do back in law school,
Champagne - Champagna.
- Yeah.
- yeah yeah, french fries or Frittes.
And kind uh..
- That kind of stuff.
- That's right.
What I'm asking you, Swiss dick,
is are you going to fuck me over?
I understand perfectly,
you American shit.
The only way the Banque Real de
Geneve would cooperate with a
foreign legal body
is if the crime being pursued
is also a crime in Switzerland.
But there are very few Swiss laws
which applied to your ''practises''
from a financial standpoint.
You are now in heaven.
See, I told you he was fantastic, right?
If the US Justice Department
sent us as subpoena,
it will become a,
um.. papier-toillette.
- We will wipe our ass with it.
- [LAUGHING]
Unless, of course, it was an
investigation into stock fraud
which is a crime here in
Switzerland, if I'm correct.
Then there would have to be co-operation,
on your part, if I'm not mistaken.
Yes. Yes, we would
Assuming the account is under your name.
If it were another name
- of friends, I get my..
- Cousin.
Cousin, absolutely no.
- Relative.
- Yeah.
Was that yodeling I just heard or..
Did you just say what
I thought he said?
Yes. Yes.
He's telling me to use a fucking
rathole.
But the US rathole would never get
into Switzerland with all that money.
What I needed was a rathole with a
European passport.
[MUSIC]
- Jordan.
- Hey.
- How's my favourite aunt?
- Welcome, was the traffic terrible?
Oh, no, not at all.
Jordan, Come on in
Thank God, aunt Emma didn't
need too much convincing.
Turned out the British weren't
too different from the Swiss.
Money talks and bullshit takes the bus.
How do you say ''rathole'' in British?
.. If you gettin' any trouble whatsoever,
I'll come for it immediately,
I'll say that I duped you.
And I promise.
Risk is what keeps us
young, isn't it darling?
Sometimes I wonder,
if you let money get
the best of you, my love,
among other substances.
Ooh.. [LAUGHING]
Is that obvious, huh?
It's chilly darling,
you're sweating bullets.
What can I say, I'm um..
I'm a drug addict.
I'm not really am, I, I mean..
Coccain, pills,
whatever it is, I'll fuckin' do it.
That's the truth.
I am.. I am sex addict too.
Well there are worse things to be
addicted to than sex. [LAUGHING]
Jesus, why am I telling you all this?
I am sorry.
Because I'm very easy to talk to
You are. You are easy to talk to.
That's about it, it's..
It'sjust my job, you know, it's uh..
All these people depending on me, tens of
millions of dollars at stake, you know, it's..
Sometimes I feel like I've bitten
off more than I can chew, you know?
You're a man with large appetites.
yeah.
Is she fuckin' hittin' on me?
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
Suppose I put that on myself though, right?
My decision.
It is hard, though..
Hard to learn to control the
anxiety, sometimes, you know?
You know, to..
Learn to relax, and let go, and..
To release the tension.
She is hittin' on me. [LAUGHING]
Holy shit.
I got to release the tension.
Suppose we, uh.. We
all just need to learn.
Learn to do what comes
naturally in life, you know?
Is he fucking hitting on me?
Stability, dear. Family.
You take care of my nice, my love.
I'll take care of everything over here.
Deal.
Hold on! There you go!
[GROANING]
[SCREAMING]
We had, literally, a fuck load of money.
Aunt Emma could never
carry all this by herself.
So I thought to myself, who
else has European passport?
Okay Brad, you're making
this too fuckin' tight.
Now, Brad, as a successful drug dealer,
spent his winters in the south of France,
which is where he met his wife, Chantelle.
A striper of Slovenian origin,
born in, of all places, Switzerland.
Well, this is fucked.
Oh, no, shit!
- Like this will take a, like, 50 trips.
- I know.
Yeah, a suicide work.
But, how about her family? Right?
I mean, they all got
Swiss's passport, right?
I mean, she's got parents,
she's got a brother.
Right, brother's got a wife,
that's five fuckin' people.
Six, seven trips, boom, right?
They're all fuckin' Swiss and it was like,
''what are you doing?'', they could do that.
At least I have a family,
you crooked nose fuck!
Hey, hey, uh, don't
forget about my money.
- I'm sorry, what was that?
- Hey, I forgot to tell you
- he's got some, he's got some money.
- My money.
- Yeah, a couple mill comin' in like a week.
- Yeah.
And when it gets here, I'll give
you a call, you come pick it up.
You give me a call?
When it gets here, I'll give you
a call, and you come pick it up.
Well, we don't fuckin'
work for you, man!
Shh..
Sweetheart, you have my
money taped to your tits.
Okay? Technically you do work for me.
Hey, Jordan, we're gonna need to talk.
If I fuckin' do this, I'm telling
you right now, I ain't goin' to him.
Okay? I'm not a fuckin' schwas, I
don't do fuckin' pick-ups, alright?
- But listen to me, when this thing placed,
- I'm gonna take care of everything.
and I fuckin' say, and you
tell that fuckin' piece of shit.
- If he comes correct.
- I will.
If he comes in, I'll fuckin' loopy and fucked up.
I swear to God, I'm a mash that douchebag's teeth.
I hear that, who's fucking cheating?
- Who's fuckin' cheating?!
- Look, may I asking..
I put the money on that
fuckin' table, not you!
I'm the reason we
have this fuckin' deal!
- I have a gun, you fucking idiot!
- What the fuck this gun.
I already told you this.
You know what? You're a fuckin' pill
deal, I got five more just like you, bro!
Keep talking, you piece of shit!
Do you know what? You dress like shit!
- So, fuck you!
- Fuck you, motherfucker!
- Jesus!
- Like that faggot. Who's the faggot?
- Enough with your shit!
- You okay?
Hey pal!
The next day, aunt Emma flew to Geneve.
Two million in cash in her carry on.
Which in a big picture was
a drop in the Swiss bucket.
'Cause the following month,
over the course of six roundtrips,
Chantelle's family and friends smugglin'
over 20 millon in cash without even a hiccup.
- Shred it.
- And by the way..
- Here they are.
- Excellent!
- And I have some more.
- Really?
- Here.
- Oh, thank you.
- And here.
- Welcome.
[LAUGHING] Welcome?
- And yeah, like four bags of it.
- Ooh.
Are you Swiss-Slovakian
or Swiss-Slovenian?
- Slovenian. Yes.
- Slovenian? Okay.
- So you're blonde?
- Oh, stop that.
Shit.
Put the fuckin' car
parked, you dumb idiot!
Yeah, close the briefcase.
One fuckin' day, one fuckin' day
you couldn't keep it together?
I was fucked up, Brad.
- You're fuckin' kidding me!
- Fucked up.
- It's a joke!
- It's a joke?
- I'm sober.
- Jesus fucking Christ.
- It's a fuckin' joke. I'm not stupid.
- Are you fuckin' stupid?
- You fuckin' drivin' you like a fuckin' maniac.
- Do you know what..
- You know the attention that fuckin' draws?
- You know what, I'm not stupid.
- I'm smart.
- Smart?
- I make million dollar deal.
- That's right.
We smart important people, unlike you.
People who don't sucker punch
people when they're scared, okay?
- I'm scared?
- And by the way,
- I haven't got an apology for that.
- One apology, okay.
I check my fuckin' messages everyday
- when I come home from work
- Did you?
- my answering machine
- You didn't got one, huh?
zero! I got a blinking light
because I don't have shit from you!
- Yeah right. You know, you got a big
fuckin' mouth! - I got my wife, I got my wife
checking the messages every 45
minutes, calling the office say,
has Brad apologize? Is there any
apology message on the machine?
- Alright, do you know what..
- I don't have jack shit.
- You know what? That's not how you treat me.
- Yeah, you got a big fuckin' mouth. You know
I'm not gonna give you a fuckin'
pass, just give me the case.
- Oh, you're not gonna give me a pass?
- Get out of here.
Look, it's a figure fuckin' speech.
- Oh my God, the Emperor of Foxville
- Just give me the fuckin' case
came down from Foxville
to give me a pass!
Hey, what are the citizens of Foxville
doing at the day when the Emperor's gone?
- I'm begging you.
- Is it, is it mayhem?
Or people looting and raping?
What all the little fuckhead doing?
- Why are you here?
- You go fuck yourself!
- You fuckin', alright, alright.
- Hey, you fuck the back up!
I'm fuckin' saying!
That if I ever cross you in my
life, if you come at me again,
- Just fuckin' keep it down.
- You know what?
I got it. I don't want to be avoiding
anything, but I think you like, like..
- Like, when you come at me,
- What the fuck?
- 'cause you look at me.
- what's the matter with you?
I just know I just noticed like,
you have like a fuckin', like..
- Stop that talk!
- You might twinkle.
You have like a twinkle, were
you trying to kiss me, bro?
- Jesus fuckin' Christ..
- Bro, you're trying..
- I'm.. What's with you?
- I have like a, I don't know, I just..
- I said that homophobic thing..
- Baiklah.
- You're just not the one for me, pal.
- Okay.
You know what I mean? It's not,
it's not about that for me, you know?
- You understand?
- I've heard enough, please.
I'm begging, give me the fuckin' case.
- Okay?
- I gonna give you the case.
- Gve me the case. What's that?
- You gotta do me one favour.
You gotta take this case,
you gotta drive straight home, you know.
I need you to open up the briefcase,
and you take out every single dollar,
don't leave one dollar inside the briefcase.
I want you to have it all neatly
organized outside the briefcase,
and you to take it,
I need you to shove it right up your
wife's Slatvian cunt, you understand?
- My fuckin' wife?
- Fuckin' chill!
- [GROANING] Chill, bro!
- You motherfuckin' piece of shit!
- How about that?
- Let go, let go! Come on. Fuck!
[SIREN]
Motherfucker! You fuckin' dick!
Stop! Don't move! Don't move,
I'm gonna fire your fuckin' leg!
I'm gonna fire you in your fuckin' leg!
Drop the case, put your hands in the air!
Get that!
[SCREAMING]
Get on your knees, sir!
Get down on your knees!
Motherfucker!
Fuck! Jesus!
Mother fucker!
Jordan!
Do I have a surprise for you.
20 real lemons.
Retired pharmacist friend of mine,
it been in his safe for 15 years.
You fuckin' kiddin' me? Lemons?
- [LAUGHING]
- They're gonna knock us out off our fuckin' head.
When it comes to quaalude, the
lemon 714 was the holygrail.
- Can you believe it?
- Oh my God..
I thought they were like a myth.
Three times as powerful as
anything available today.
- Look at these babies.
- Boy Donnie really knew how to celebrate.
He said he was saving these for a special
occasion, like a birthday, or being clapfree.
Or, my money arriving
safely in Switzerland.
We're gonna die!
[PUKE]
So that night, I cleared my schedule,
and I rid my body of anything
that could fuck with my high.
It was celebration time.
Okay.
We start off with one, see how it'll go?
My guy says all we need is one.
Here we go.
- Salute.
- Cheers.
Maybe if I pull it
again, it will go down.
Steve,Steve! I gotta get outta here.
No! I think I got it figured out.
It must be one pull for
up, and two pull for down.
Okay.
You feel anything?
No.
Been thirty five minutes.
Maybe we built up a tolerance
after all these years, huh?
Hm..
This is bullshit!
My metabolism is pumped
out, I can't feel shit!
They're old, I think
they lost the potency?
Huh?
Check the bottle!
January '81
They're fuckin' duds.
- Fuck!
- Let's take a..
- Take two more each.
- Yeah.
Jordan!
You're up, babe?
What are you two retards doing?
We're workin' out, honey.
Well, Bo Dietl's on the phone.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay?
Hey! Bo, what's going on?
Jordan, listen to me clearly.
I can not talk to you in this
phone, and I have to talk with you.
We're gonna get outta
here. What's going on?
Listen to me, leave the
fuckin' house, Jordan!
And then call me from a payphone.
This is not a fuckin' joke, Jordan.
Yeah, yeah. Ya.
- Shit!
- What's.. What he said?
I don't know what the fuck
is going on, I gotta go!
Is everything okay, Jordan?
The closest payphone I can get to
is at the Brookvile Contry Club.
It was a real WASP stronghold.
Just a mile down the road from my house.
Hey Bo, what's up? It's me, what's going
on? I'm at the payphone, what's going on?
Listen to me carefully.
Please, your little friend
here, Brad, your little buddy,
he's in jail.
He.. What the fuck he's in
jail for? What did he do?
I don't know what he did.
My friend in Long Island told me he got
picked up in some fuckin' shopping mall,
- he got locked up..
- Wait, did you say a shopping mall?
- Yeah, yeah.
- He, he was with Donnie
he was supposed to deliver some money,
and that fuckin' fat piece of shit.
- I'm gonna go and fuckin' kill him.
- Jordan, Jordan, Jordan. Listen to me!
Don't go! Listen to me.
That guy, Denham, that FBI agent guy,
somebody told me, he's got your phone
tapped. Your ofice and your home.
- Don't talk on that motherfuckin' phone!
- Okay. Fuck! I got it, I got it.
I got it, I got it.
Jordan.
You didn't try to bribe this
fuckin' FBI agent, did you?
No, I didn't try to
bribe that FBI agent.
You think I'm that fuckin'stupid? No!
What the fuck you said?
I can't understand.
Say that again!
I said I won't, I know what
my feeling with this FBI agent.
What the fuck are you saying?
- I said..
- Are you fuckin' high?
Are you kidding me? I
don't wanna see more FBI!
Jordan! Are you fuckin' high?
Jordan, do me a favour.
Stay where you are,
don't get behind the wheel of the car,
I'll be there in a
moment to pick you up.
Jordan, Jordan!
After 15 years in storage,
the lemons had developed a delayed fuse.
It took 90 minutes for this little
fuckers to kick in, but once they did..
Pow!
I mean, I'd skipped the tingle phase
and went straight to the drool phase.
Tell me where you are, don't fuckin'..
This little bastard was so strong,
I discovered a whole new phase.
The cerebral palsy phase.
Come on, stand up.
Oke, walking's out.
I think, think what else is there?
Yes!
I can crawl, I can crawl like Skylar.
Fuck!
The kid makes it look so goddamn easy.
Think, you motherfucker, think.
Yes!
I got it!
I've got it!
I can roll.
I can roll!
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[SHOUTING]
Jordan?
Oh Jesus. Where are you?
I'm at the Country Club.
What?
I'm at the Country Club!
I don't know what the fuck are you
saying, but you need to get home!
Donnie is out of control.
He's on the other line
with some Swiss guy,
- I don't know..
- What?!
Get him off the phone!
I can't understand you.
What the fuck are you saying, Jordan?
Can you just get home? Hurry.
Oh my God!
Oh my God..
I was less than a mile from home.
I drove as slow as I fuckin' could.
I think Jello move faster.
I just couldn't give him two million.
I'm gonna be a little late.
You ate two million?
Million!
Get off the phone, get off
the fuckin' phone, idiot!
- [CAR HORN]
- Get out of the way, asshole!
- Hello?
- Too late..
- And it's..
- You hate two million?
No, you don't hate two million, Donnie.
By some miracle, I made it home alive.
Not a scratch on me or the car.
Is that so?
Jordan?
Oh Jesus fucking Christ!
What did you take?
What is wrong with you?
Jordan!
It's fuckin' good, right?
- What the fuck are you saying?
- You fucked up.
- What were you saying?
- Get off the phone!
Get off the fuckin' phone!
What the fuck, Jordan?
You're doing this in the
house, I hope you know that!
You fucking doing this in the house!
- You two are fucking funny friends!
- Get off the phone!
- Jesus, Jordan!
- The FBI!
- Get off the phone!
- I buy the phone!
Get off the phone!
- Give me the phone!
- [SCREAMING]
Come on. We're gonna
go upstairs, alright?
Get off the phone!
Fuck you!
- What's wrong?
- What you did?
- You piece of shit!
- What?
What?
Brad!
Huh?!
You fuckin' asshole!
Gimme the phone.
What did you do?
You piece of shit!
- What the fuck I did wrong?
- Fuck you!
I wanna fuckin' do it!
I wanna fuckin' kill you!
I'll get you!
What the fuck happen?
Oh, shit!
Jordan? Jordan, are you alright?
Donnie? Donnie?!
Donnie is not breathing!
Oh, fuck! I don't know what to do!
Jordan, I don't know what the
fuck to do, I can't help him!
What are we gonna do, Jordan?
Oh my God, I think he's choked, Jordan.
Do something!
- Oh God, help me!
- I got you!
He's not breathing, Jordan.
You got to do something!
- Oh shit!
- Oh my God!
Oh my God..
I got you!
Here!
Get in me!
[GROANING]
Step aside! Oh my God!
Oh God!
Move aside, baby!
Oh, God..
Look at me! Come on!
Come on, come on!
Jordan, he's not breathing,
you got to do something!
Jordan, he's a father, he's
got fucking kids, do something!
Yeah! Yeah.
Jordan, you gotta get over
here, tell me what I'm doing.
Oh fucking God, get over here, call 911!
[SCREAMING]
You alright?
Are you alright?
Mr. Belfort?
Why the fuck you are here? Fuck.
Sir?
We need to ask you some questions.
You fuckin' kidding me? Fuck you!
Come on, get up!
Well, get the fuck outta my house!
- Let's go! Come on! Get up!
- I've been here all night.
- Let's go!
- I've been sitting here all night.
- What the fuck are you talkin'?
- Wait a minute, why you taking him?
- The fuck are you doing?
- Let's go!
Why you taking him?
- Tell him!
- We got no warn.
You just come up and
peep a house like this!
- I'm just talkin'..
- Did you drive your car that night
Mr. Belfort?
Well.
Wow!
Maybe I hadn't made at home okay.
Get out of the fuckin' way!
Fuck! Fucker!
Did you drive..
That car, tonight?
- Yeah..
- Yeah?
Right.
I'm a family man. Family man. Honey!
It was a miracle I wasn't killed.
More, you know, that I
didn't kill anybody else.
The cops took me in for questioning,
but they couldn't charge ne.
They had no proof I was even behind the wheel.
Meanwhile, Brad did three months in jail for
contempt because he wouldn't let Donnie out.
The result? I was scot free.
But I had eyes on me like never before.
You're a lucky man, Jordan.
You're lucky be alive,
let alone not in jail.
No, I don't believe in luck, right?
But it's time.
Please, let me call
the SEC and cut a deal,
before your luck runs out.
Wave to daddy!
Hey! Hey, sweetie.
- [LAUGHING]
- You're doing great, sweetie.
You're doing so great.
What kind of terms that
we do talking about, if I..
- You know..
- I don't know
you know you plead guilty to
handful of securities violation.
Stock manipulation, high pressure sales
tactics, ticky-tack shit like that, you know?
Pay a couple million dollars in fine,
in exchange, SEC fucks
off till the end of time.
And Stratton, what happen to Stratton?
I mean that you,
there's no way, I mean..
You gotta walk away, right?
- Let Donnie be in charge.
- Alright, Donnie.
And the FBI is another
animal, completely.
They still be pursuing you
for criminal wrongdoing.
However, with you
stepping down voluntarily,
my guess is, that your best friend, agent Denham,
will be standing around with his dick in his hand.
Jordan.
Wh.. What do you have to think about?
Yo.. You beat them!
You won!
God knows you'll never
have to work again.
What you're gonna do? Spend the rest of
your life in jail? Is that what you want?
- No.
- Okay!
Okay. You got all the
money in the world.
You need everybody else's money?
- Of course not.
- Well?
- You know I built it.
- I know you built it!
You built it, so now preserved it!
[CLAPPING]
You know..
Five years ago, when I started
Stratton Oakmont with Donnie Azoff,
I knew the day would eventually
come where I'd have to be moving on.
And it's trully with a heavy
heart, that I'm here to say that..
That, that that day is finally here.
[SHOCKED]
I wanna, I wanna thank you all for your
years of loyalty and admiration, but uh,
the point is this.
Under Donnie's keadership, along with
Nicky Koskoff and Robbie Feinberg,
moving into key management posisitions,
this place really is, it's gonna be better
than ever. That I promise you, okay?
This is Ellis Island, you people.
Okay, who you are, or where you
from, where do your relatives came
over, from the fuckin' Mayflower,
or the inner tube from Haiti.
This, right here, is the land of
opportunity, Stratton Oakmont, is America!
[CHEERING]
- All of you know Kimmie Belzer, right?
- Yes, we do.
Fuck you!
Come on, Kimmie.
Which you probably didn't know is,
Kimmie was one of the first brokers
here, one of the Stratton's original 20.
And most of you met Kimmie the beautiful
sophisticated woman that she is today.
A woman that wears
3000 dollar Armani suits.
Drives brand new Mercedes Benz.
A woman who, who spends her winters
in Bahamas and her summers in Hamptons.
That's not the Kimmie that I met.
The Kimmie that I met didn't
have two nickels to rub together.
She was a single mom on the balls of
her ass with an eight year old son.
Okay? She was three
months behind on her rent.
And when se came to me
and ask me for a job,
she asked for 5000 dollar advance just..
Just so she could pay her son's tuition.
And what I do, Kimmie?
Go on, tell them.
You wrote me a check..
For 25.000 dollars.
That's right.
Thank you.
And you know why that is?
That's because I believed in you.
It's because I believed in you, Kimmie.
Just like I believe in each
and everyone of you here today.
- I fuckin' love you, Jordan. I fuckin' love you.
- I fuckin' love you.
- I love you.
- I fuckin' love you too!
I fuckin' love you too!
And I love all of you!
I love all of you, from
the bottom of my heart.
- I love you, Jordan!
- I mean it!
It's a shame, you know, 'cause..
For years I've been telling you guys,
never to take ''no'' for an answer, right?
In order to keep pushin' and
to never hang up the phone,
until you get what you want.
Because you all deserve it.
You know this fuckin' deal
that I'm about to sign..
barring me from the securities
industry, barring me from Stratton..
My home..
The fuck is that? You know?
I tell you what it is. It's..
It's me taking ''no''
for an answer, you know?
It's them, them selling me,
not the other way around. It's..
It's me being a
hypocrite, is what it is.
So..
You know what?
I'm not leaving.
I'm not fucking leaving!
[CHEERING]
The show goes on.
This is my home.
They gonna need a fucking wrecking
ball to take me outta here!
They gonna need to send a national
guard or fucking SWAT team,
'cause I ain't going nowhere.
Fuck them!
[HUMMING]
[SHOUTING]
Jordan! Jordan!
Jordan, get back here!
Hey!
Give.. Give me that!
What a trouble in the jungle, for Christ sake!
How did he, muffle
truffle you, huh, richman?
Turn the offer, trust
Welch on the order of SEC.
He is back in the ocean, happy hunting.
[MUSIC]
It was our time to party big.
And just as Brad was
released from jail too.
I apologize, even offered to
pay him for his time in the can.
But he said no.
The day he was out,
he didn't want any part of us.
Sad thing was, two years later,
he was dead.
Massive heart attack, at 35.
Same age Mulshock died.
Not that they, have a hell
of a lot in common, but,
anyway, I don't know
why that came to mind.
Within days, subpoena started flying.
Notices to produce documents,
deposititions, you name it.
Donnie couldn't drink water fast enough.
You now say it's coming
was to get me a subpoena.
Here's how we do a subpoena
to substracting our funds.
Fuck you USA, Fuck you!
Fuck you, Fuck you..
[CHEERING]
Jordan Belfort.
Olden, that's a nice name.
Thank you very much for that.
What kind a name is that?
That is my name.
I do not recall that.
I do not recall that, okay?
Mr. Ming, thank you for coming in today.
Is it okay if I grab some danish?
- Can I have a danish?
- No, no, go.
They interogated everybody.
I got a low blood sugar,
that were I thinking.
I went on for months, it was
a total fucking harassment.
But not a single Strattonite cracked.
Gladys Carrera.
- Doesn't ring a bell.
- Sorry, I have no recomendation of that.
- No.
- No idea.
I don't recall that transaction,
do you guys have any milk?
Absolutely not.
By end of this, you called so many times,
I just thought you might remember that.
I don't remember that.
- Would you re.. remember any of those?
- I do not recall any of that.
- This Abdul..
- I do not re.. No I don't recall.
It was a long phonecall, I just wanna
review if you have any memory of that.
Okey, you know we've talked to several
of the employee at this firm and nobody
can recall anything about this thieft man IPO.
It's.. I think it's odd.
- Do you recall?
- Carnage Cooperation?
- You do, you do recall it?
- No I don't recall that at all.
Excuse me, I have to ask,
is that your real hair?
Are you gonna say anything about that?
- Will you never comment on my hair, is that
how we're doing? - I just asking about that.
Is this personal question?
I wondering why you
wearing something like that.
I'm sure I don't recall what happened.
Can I get you anything else gentlemen?
Yes sweetheart I have rare condition which require
me to drink one of those every 15 minutes, please.
We were specifically adviced
not to leave the country.
So, we took our wives to Italy.
We figure that we were safer working from
over the seas, giving orders to Rugrat.
Nobody could arrest us.
And nobody could prove I was still
running Stratton from a yacht.
Hey, Rugrats bonjour, you
bomheaded eagle, how you doing?
Donnie, Donnie listen,
we have a problem okay?
Your friend Steve Madden
is unloading shares.
What do you say? Who told you that?
- What is going on?
- He's doing it, Donnie.
He says, he says Steve
Madden is unloading shit.
Who told you that? That's bullshit.
- Gimme that goddamn phone, just..
- Don't!
- Ruggie, what's going on?
- He doesn't know what's going on..
Jordan look, I'm watching the screen and
huge chunk to Steve Madden is being sold, okay.
It's not coming from us,
so it's gonna be Steve.
He's the only person
with that many shares.
Donnie, call me back, alright.
Donnie, your little friend is
trying fuck me, you know that?
Your little friend trying to fuck me
right now. Get him on the phone now.
Even though I own 85%% of
Steve-Cock-Sucking-Motherfucker-Madden-Shoe.
The shares were in his fucking name.
This motherfucker knew I was in trouble with
the fed and he was try to take advantage.
Donnie come on talk to me man,
how do you wanna play this?
Ruggie, I want you to get all
client on the phone right now
and having start selling Steve Madden we gonna
try make that fucking price down, do you hear me?
Shut the fuck up, this is your
fucking friend from highschool.
They will fuckin' freak me, they're gonna
fuck with me and gonna turn this entire
company to a penny stock, you hear me?
- You got it?
- Yes, I got it.
Don't startjumping into conclusion
before we know what is going on.
Capitan!
Hang up your phones,
everybody! Hang up..
Turn the boat away, we're going home!
Baby, baby, what happened?
Sweetheart what's going on?
I am uhh..
- Just wait, I can't..
- Baby, baby, baby..
What is going on? Why are you crying?
- She's dead.
- Who?
I just got a call from my cousin, Betty,
- Yeah?
- Aunt Emma's dead.
- You fucking kidding me?
- No.
You serious? Oh my
God, baby, that's, fuck!
Oh sweetheart thatjust fucking..
Fucking heart attack, boom, snap, gone.
Shuffled off her mortal coil and twenty
million dollars stock in a Swiss bank account.
She was fine.
- Oh God, baby oh God, that so fucking terrible.
- You know, she's not that old.
It is terrible to you. Your aunt was such an
elegant, attractive woman. My condolences to you.
Yes, yes we absolutely devastated, thank
you, thank you so much, for your condolences.
Now where is that leave us in regard to her
account exactly, does it going to probate or what?
Don't worry Jordan, not to worry,
your aunt before she died, signed a
document naming you as her successor.
She did.
Fantastic, well that's a good news.
Well, not as of yet.
Wait, wait.. what is it means, not as of yet?
No [SPEAKING FRENCH]
I, I can't seem to hear you
I must have bad reception.
Aren't you speaking English?
Now.. Fast, very fast.
Fast, I have to get to Switzerland now.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
Speak English, fucking speak English!
- Hey, hey.. quiet, okay?
- Okay.
Take your suit, take your dick
okay, and move your ass, please.
Okay, move my ass.
I gotta say these Swiss were
some sneaky motherfuckers.
Within minutes he had set me up with a
forger who could fake aunt Emma's signature.
You American Shit.
I just had to get there by
tomorrow or lose 25 million dollars.
- We're going to Monaco.
- Monaco? Now?
Yes baby we're going to Monaco
so we can go to Switzerland, okay?
But her auntjust die.
I realize that but i have bussiness in
Switzerland i need to go Switzerland right now.
Bottom line, sorry.
- We got to get to London.
- Why?
- The funeral.
- Yeah, but babe look, look.
I love your aunt, more than anyone
in the entire world i really did.
but she is dead now sweaty, she's
dead and she's not going anywhere.
She still be dead by the
time we get to London, okay.
- Captain Ted.
- Captain Ted, we go to Monaco, Monaco now, okay.
- Monaco right?
- We go to Monaco.
So we can drive to Switzerland so we dont need
to stamp up passport take care of business here.
We'll drive back to Monaco, take a flight
over to London to catch the funeral
be in the New york meet with him in
three business days it's a fucking plan.
I'm just wanna to inform you out
there here. Might run into some chop.
Chop? We can fucking handle chop
right, i mean it's 170 foot yacht.
No, no, we're not going anywhere
unless he said it's safe, alright.
- It's safe.
- Don't worry about the chop.
- You don't know shit about chop.
- Oww, really.
- And you two? You fucking expert on this?
- I'll chop your fucking credit cards.
Chop is fine, trust me chop is
fine, is chop fine Captain Ted?
Yeah, i mean if we take it slow.
Ya, we gonna take it slow.
It's a little uncomfortable
but tell me it's safe.
It's gonna be safe, because.. I mean we'll have
to batten down the hatches and we secured the deck
We're looking a few, maybe a few broken dishes.
Few broken dishes, what a few broken dishes.
Is that sound fucking awesome or what.
- Oww, not really.
- We're gonna fucking fun time.
Let's go to fuckin monaco now.
Let's fucking move let's go.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Hold on.
What the fuck is going on here?
The jet ski jus went overboard.
Jesus Christ, hold on okay.
The waves were 20 feet high building,
turn around go to that fucking way.
- We can't
- Go.
We'll get broad sided and it's game over.
I am a master diver, you hear that
I am a master diver, no
one is gonna fucking die.
I got you.. Trust me okay, i love you.
I love you, just hold on tight.
Tight.
Hold on, baby.
Donnie.
Donnie,
- What?
- hold on baby?
Get the fucking ludes!
I don't wanna die trying, i do love
that shit up to but i'm so scared.
I fucked up, i fucked up so bad.
- Get the ludes, downstairs
- What do you say?
Get the ludes.
I can't go down, They're below deck!
There's like three feet of water down there!
I will not die sobber, get those fuckin ludes.
- Okay, okay.
- Go!
- Where he's going?
- Don't know baby.
Donnie, he fucking crazy.
Jesus Christ.
Hold on, get away from the
window, we'll gonna blown away.
Mayday! This is Captain Ted Beecham
aboard the Yacht Naomi! This is a Mayday!
I got them, i got them.
Give me to me.
What you're gonna do right now.
This is a fucking may day.
[SCREAMING]
[MUSIK]
[CHOPPER SOUND]
Nice thing about getting rescued by Italians..
.. That they feed you,
make you drink red wine.
And you get to dance.
[EXPLOSION]
Did you see that?
That was the plane I
sent to come get us.
I shit you not, it exploded when a seagull
flew into the engine, three people killed.
You want a sign from God,
After all this I finally got the message.
New dream, of becoming financially indepedent.
But struggle every month just to pay your bills.
Would you like to own a home like this?
Who can barely afford to pay your rent.
My name is Jordan Belfort.
And there is no secret to well creation.
No matter who you are. No
matter where you came from.
You too can become finacially
independent in just a matter of months.
All you need is strategy.
When i was 24 years old, i made a decision.
Not to survive, but to thrive.
At first i didn't feel like
deals like this were possible.
But we have the house, and we
have 30 thousand dollar profit.
I certainly beleive now.
I think about it for second.
If you dont have guts to attend Jordan Belfort
Straight line perssuasion system seminar.
Then how do you, expect to make any money.
You wanna be a millionaire some day.
Have some guts make a decision.
Jordan belforth said work for
me because i work hard for it.
And if it doesn't work for you it's because
you lazy, you should get a job at Mcdonalds.
There is nobody holding you
back from financial freedom.
And there is nobody stoping
you from making millions.
Don't you sit in a home or the life
you dreamed will fly right pass.
I change all these people's
live and i can change yours too.
So come to my seminar, the
life of your dream is only..
- You're under arrest
- You've got to be joking..
- Don't kidding, hey.
- Turn that Camera off.
You fuckin, you fucking cocksucker.
Fuck you!
What the fuck you doing?
you fucking pieces of shit.
Hei Jordan let me give you a little legal advice.
Shut up, fuck off.
(FBI, New York)
Jordan Belfort.
I cleaned on my act, i did rehab.
I'm a Tv personality.
I'm sobber for 2 years, and this happens.
Rugrat goes and get busted down in Miami.
And Guess who the fuck with? Saurel.
- You gonna beat me? I know your country.
- No!
What the fucking odds? There had to
be ten thousand Swiss bankers in Geneva.
and Rugrat is the one dumb enough
to get himself arrested on U.S. soil.
I know.
[CRYING]
Even more fucked was he got busted for
shit that had nothing to do with me.
And nothing to fucking do with me.
Something about laundering drug money, to
offshore boat racing to a guy name Rocky aoki.
You know the founder of Benihana.
Benihana?
Beni Fucking hana.
Beni 'fucking' hana,why, why god.
Why would You be so cruel as to choose a chain
of fucking Hibachi Restaurants to take me down?
Long story, short Saurel ratted me out, but
not before he ratted out Brad's wife Chantalle.
Who turns out he been fuckin
everytime she went to Switzel.
No, no, no
Alright
One count engaging in conspiracy
to commit securities fraud.
Two counts securities fraud.
One count engaging in Conspiracy
to commit money laundering.
21 counts money laundering.
1 count of obstruction of justice.
Bail has set at 10 million dollars.
What up?
Rocky, how you doin?
- Wooff..
- I'm not a fucking dog.
Yeah, it's getting old to crap to
start to shit in the house again.
- Me too.
- Come here buddy.
- Good to see you pal.
- Me too.
How you doing brother?
You know, shitty pal.
But i'm hanging in there.
Piece of jewelry, check that out.
Can't leave the house, you know.
Sun to get cub and fiber already.
Fuckin Rugrat.
That wig-wearin'faggot I can't believe
that fucking guy were'nt killed..
When he got out, i want
to show on his desks.
Irresponsble prick.
I'll tell you one thing.
That you never eat Benihana again.
I don't care who's birthday it is.
What is that Naomi actually doing?
She right in the house there, say
hi she probably won't wave you back.
Naomi, sweetheart.
What's up her ass, was she mad at me?
No you know.
Probably had to mortgage
the house to make bail.
Probably ended sell a thing in
order pay for all my lawyers.
It's been a night mare
buddy, i tell you the truth.
What do you gonna do right.
Anyway how is Stratton that
more important how is morale?
You piss of cause he have
to make money legally now?
Jordan.
I got the founding partners together.
Talk to them about everything and..
I got you.
How much you got me?
The house, money, don't
worry about it i got you.
I love you buddy. You
know i do it for you right.
- I'll kiss you.
- Alright, enough, enough.
- You wanna beer, pal?
- What do you drink?
We got this non-alcoholic shit.
- What is that?
- It's non alcoholic beer.
It's got no alchohol.
- Is it beer?
- Ya, with no alchohol.
But you drink enough and you
drink a lot to get you fucked up.
No, it's no alchoholic fucking point.
I'm not a scientist, i dont get fuck target
but I can get you a beer, if you want..
I know, but i don't drink, you remember.
- I'm not drink anymore.
- Are you wanna go inside.
And blow some lime and baking powder..
Can't imagine ever not
enjoyed geting fucked up.
- Yeah.
- I loved it.
But i've been sobber.
Fucking sucks.
- Boring right.
- So boring.
Like kill myself.
There is a term and we dont like to
use it unless circumtances dictate..
.. I think they do dictate in this case and
term is Grenada, have you ever heard Grenada.
No i haven't.
Grenada very interesting because it is a small
island nation that was invaded by the United
States of America 1983 have 9000 people.
And essentially means is.
This case is unloseable.
So, you know, come in we can have our dick
hanging out of our pants, nobody gives a fuck.
I'm gonna win.
You Sir.
Are was known.
As a Grenada.
You're looking at real prison time.
Money laundering can get you as much 20 years.
And, our case gonna be stronger, if we
caught your shed and cash your mattress,.
Oh that right.
Hei Jordan.
Jordan, You're rotting away in
jail, 2 your kids get out the college.
That's not our ambition here.
There's other people involve in this too.
We think, they need to see
their day in courts as well.
Why do I sense there's
an offer in the air?
He's got good sense.
What are you, Craskin?
Full cooperation, he provides us with the
comprehensive list of all coconspirators spanning
the last seven years and he agrees to wear a wire.
- Did you just say wear a wire?
- A wire.
Wow, wow, is that means, you
want me to rat, is that it?
No, i want you to cooperate.
- No, you want me to rat.
- Yes, we want you to rat.
That fucking exactly what
we want you to do, to rat.
How is Christy's party?
- Fine.
- Good.
Babe, i've spoke to the lawyers again today.
There is some really really great news.
Turns out you completely
off the hook, honey.
I know that already.
Right, exactly, you never did
anything wrong in first place right?
It turns out, all the FBI really
wants for me is to a coorperate.
You know.. turns out i have so much information
about the stock market and the Wallstreet..
That i could save the government years of
heartache not to mention countless dollars.
It gets even better babe.
Because if i do to sign cooperate, i might
only be looking at 4 short years.
How much case, we could start
fresh maybe sell the house.
And any fine that i have to pay
wouldn't due till i serve term.
So, we still have plenty
money left over, you know.
You think, of course bug me out a little
bit is this whole idea for doing it.
Give an information about my friends.
Ohh, like he said, ther is
no friend on Wallstrett right.
Right.
It's exactly silver lining to that
too honey because they said eventually.
Eventually everyone gonna have to
give an information on this case.
So at the end of the day, might
not even a factor, you know.
- Well, that's a good news, right.
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm really happy for you.
What do you mean you happy for me?
- You should be happy for the both of us right?
- Yeah right.
Alright.
Come here baby.
- Gimme a kiss, sweetheart.
- Jordan.
- Let's make love. Please.
- No.
Jordan stop it! No!
Jordan stop it.
I Fucking hate you Jordan.
- Get off me.
- Ohh Baby don't do that.
You know how much i love you right.
Stop that sweetie, please.
You want to fuck me Jordan?
You want to fuck me?
Good, go ahead, go ahead and fucked me.
I want you to fuck me real hard.
I want you to fuck me like
its a last fucking time.
- Come babe, cause i need you to come for me baby.
- Oh i like that.
Come for me baby, i need you to
come for me like its a last fucking time.
Come baby.
Ohh, baby that was so fucking great.
That was a last time.
What do you mean baby?
I mean that was a
last time we had a sex.
What are you talking about.
I want to divorce.
What do you mean, you want a divorce? What
is that suppose to mean you want a divorce.
Get off me! i want a divorce.
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- I don't love you any more Jordan.
You don't love me.
You don't love me anymore huh?
Well it'sjust fucking convinience for
you, now i'm under federal indigement
with electronic brace around my ankle.
Now you decide you don't fucking
love me anymore, is that right?
No, no.
What kind a person are you? Tell me.
- You married me.
- What the fuck is that suppose to mean.
Jordan, this is how it's gonna go,
i'm gonna take the custody of the kids.
If you agree to divorce right now,
i will allow you to take shift, okay
Don't try to fight it.
It will save us both a lot of money
and i got a felling you gonna need it.
You're not taking my kids,
sweetheart, you hear me.
I already talk to lawyer, he said if
you get convicted, i've got a good
chance to getting custody.
I got news for you, you're not fucking
taking my children you vicious fucking conman.
Fuck you! You fucking bitch.
You're not fucking taking my
goddamn fucking kids, you hear me.
Fuck you! You're not takin my fuckin kids.
Fuckin bitch.
Fuckin whore.
Fucking bitch, piece of shit, fuckin whore.
Look at yourself Jordan.
Sick.
- You're a sick man
- Fuck you.
I've told you not taking my
fucking kids, you fucking..
You think i will let my kids near you.
Look at yourself.
You know what my lawyer said.
My lawyer said that you're
gonna prison for 20 years Jordan.
20 fucking years, you never
gonna see the kids again.
- You think i'm not gonna see my kids again?
- No, i'm not letting you near my kids.
You don't get understand
what i fucking tell you, huh?
Don't you fucking touch her.
Don't you fucking touch me.
Sweetheart.. you gonna
go with daddy alright.
You cool right, you're with daddy.
Don't you fucking touch her Jordan.
I swear i will fucking kill you!
Alright baby.
Daddy will go little trip
together okay, litle trip together.
Get the key
There you go. Go inside,
put your seat belt on, okay.
Here you go, get your legs in.
I'll take her with me.
I'll told you i'll taking her
with me. You fucking bitch.
You're not gonna stop me.
Little trip.
Don't don't
Get the hell out of here.
Close the door.
Mommy!
- Get out of here.
- Open the fucking door.
No!
Naomi!
- Mommy!
- honey, It's okay.
You're alright.
It's alright.
What's the matter with you.
You alright.
Paragraph one
The defendant shall plead guilty to all counts
of the indictment currently pending against him
in the United States District Court
for the Eastern District of New York
Paragraph 2
Talk normally.
The defendant shall participate
in undercover activities
Breath normally
wearing a recording device also known a wire
After 5 minutes you'll forget you having on.
Conjungtion of the investigation..
Paragraph 4.
The defendant must not commit or
attempted to commit any further crime.
Please.
Let me just sign the fucking
thing, alright, thank you.
- Just here?
- That will be good.
Thank you.
It, wasnt even a choice.
For the next 6 hour i came up with the list.
Friends, enemies, business associates dan anybody
you ever known me or taking so much as a stock tip
[CHEERING]
First name on the list.
was Donnie.
George do you know how good it
is to have yo back in this office.
It's not to say when you
gone, it's sad, you understand.
I fucking stiff mad now.
I can't
I can't even think about it you know.
Everytime i think about them my blood boils.
- I can't even say his name.
- I know.
You know, this is disgusting.
I grew up with these guys.
He betrayed me like that?
Do you have a.
Ever Get back, too, about um..
But um.. Account.
( Don't Incriminate
yourself i'm wearing a wire)
You remember was like 4-5 miles
or something like that right.
It was supposed a take back 4-5 million, was it?
Actually i was... I was fucked up Jordan.
Yeah right, it's stupid.
If he calls you, you make
sure you contacts me, okay?
- Of course.
- Yeah.
Are you gonna eat last piece, of your tail.
It's all yours.
I'll take it this.
So, what else is
Tell me and everything.
You know.. how it is,
she hate my fucking guts.
How she, good
She still alive, so, my life fucked you know.
No.
[KNOCKING DOOR]
Mr. Jordan.
Mr Jordan You got a visitor.
What?
You got a visitor.
I need you to get dress.
What the fuck is going on.
You going to jail.
- I will get some clothes
- We'll give you hand with that.
Okay.
[MUSIC]
FBI, every body sit down,
put your hands.. Shut up.
I gave up everyone.
And in returned i got 3 years some
hell hole in nevada i never hear of.
Like my pops mad maxx said.
Chicken come home to roast.
I wanna fucked that meat.
Mr belfort has distinguished
himself in terms of his cooperation.
Mr belfort has helped the governmet went
conviction of over 2 dozen serious offenders.
And help them recover millions of dollars he
made available for restritution to their victims.
The sentence of the court should
be 36 months in federal prison.
Please remain the offended.
I'm Sorry.
Stratton Oakmont Belfort sentenced.
I'm not ashamed to admit it.
When we arrive at the prison.
It was absolutely terrified.
Belfort on your feet.
But i ended have been.
See, for brief leading moment.
I forgot i was rich.
And i lived in the place
where everything was for sale.
When you like to learn how to sell it.
To live In some bad motherfucker in my life, look
at that rockstar, professional athlete, gangstars.
I'm telling you some real bad
mother fucker but this guy.
my good friends Mr Jordan Belfort is this
single badass motherfucker i have ever met.
So i want you right now, to give a warm
aucland new zealand welcome for my good friend
And The world greatest sales
trainer Mr Jordan Belfort.
[CLAPING]
Thank you.
Sell me this pen.
It's a amazing pen.
For professionals.
Sell me this pen.
It's a nice pen you can use the pen to right
down both from your lifes so you can remember..
Sell me this pen.
Well.. This pen works and
i personally love this pen..
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com