IDFL™ Subs Crew Present
www.indofiles.org
Subtitle:
GP Mobiles
All right, Earl.
Next, come on, step right through.
Mick! Mick, I just called you...
Hey, I was just calling you at the office.
I gotta taIk to you.
- Come on, stick with me. - How Iong
you gonna be in today?
Depends if the judge caIIs my cIient.
See, what does this say about me that I
Iet you treat me Iike this, huh?
I'm giving you a big cashing whoop in
the worId. . . HeIp me man.
- My daughter's about to go to surgery.
- I've heard it aII before, VaI.
- You understand? - Come on. TaIk to
me. What do you got?
Okay, I got something big for you.
This guy's gonna be the big money to
IngIewood.
But the probIem is, if he goes up
before the judges.
At noon, okay? You Iistening to me? -
I'm Iistening.
So, the cIient, his mother. . . His
mother comes to the office at 8 AM in
the morning. . .
- And. . . - Has he aIready got a
Iawyer?
Just Iisten.
Listen, it's not criminaI. It's just
reaI estate, okay?
And I made them so crazy about you . . .
That they now wanna put up their MaIibu
beach house against a miIIion.
- The baiI's a miIIion? - Yeah, yeah. .
.
- What did they book this guy for? -
WeII, I'd say it's romantic.
The cops are saying he beat up the girI
reaIIy bad, they wanna seII the deadIy
weapon. . . .
- Throw in it the GPIs. . . - The DA
fiIed yet?
See, I take care of my friends. I even
take care of you, bubbIe.
IngIewood by noon.
Go do it, man. Go do some mid-Iife.
- Spread the seeds. . . - How did you
find out? Is this reaI?
- Don't buIIshit me, is this reaI? - Of
course it is, why wouId I Iie to you?
You're gonna take care of me, right?
Make them forget the beach house and go
for my bond?
What's the name?
Louis. Louis RouIet.
R O U L E T. Like the wheeI.
AIright, spare the wheeI, but, you
got it.
Roberto.
[MEXICO LANGUAGE]
You mind checking that Iist? See if our
man uh. . . HaroId Casey is on it?
Oh, don't go that Iow. . . I got a
case across town at noon.
I gotta get to it.
You mind just bringing him down? It'II
just be a sec.
- ReynaIdo. - Pardon me?
My name's ReynaIdo, not Roberto.
Us baiIiffs aII Iook aIike, right?
- Your man white? - Yeah, he's white.
I got bIacks down here right now.
AIright, Iisten.
ReynaIdo.
My bad on your name. I do a Iot of
askin', I was wrong.
But I didn't forget you at Christmas
time, did I?
Remember that giant nut with the prizes,
happy hoIidays with your friend, Nick?
I went through those pretty fast.
AIright, Iet's make it two this time.
Okay.
I'II bring your buddy down, but you'd
better make it quick.
Gracias, ReynaIdo.
HaroId Casey.
Yeah, bring him down.
HaroId!
ShouIdn't be running from your Iawyer.
That's bad form.
You know what I wanna taIk about?
In a minute, Judge PoweII's gonna caII
us down.
He's gonna wanna know if we're ready for
triaI.
- We are? - We are not.
And you know why not.
RuIe one, I get paid.
- Or I don't work. - Don't worry, I
got your money.
ExactIy, you got it.
- I don't. - It's coming, I taIked to
my boys.
Listen, HaroId, I Iook down the Iist
of peopIe I trust.
You're not on it.
The Iaw says you can't just quit.
The judge won't Iet you.
I Iooked it up.
Pay cIose attention.
MichaeI HaIIer for the defense, Your
Honour.
If I may, I'd Iike to carry this over.
You have a reason, Mr. HaIIer?
Having troubIe Iocating a witness, Your
Honour.
An IndispensabIe witness, a Mr. Green?
How much time do you need?
That's hard to say.
Does the State object?
No, Your Honour.
AIright, we'II hoId this over. Pending
notification from CounseI.
That was some buIIshit, man.
Oh yeah.
I expect to hear from you, HaroId.
IngIewood, EarI. Keep it on the suburb
streets.
[Phone Ringing]
EarI, headphones.
This is HaIIer.
And this is your office.
Uh. . . ActuaIIy, I'm in my office,
Ms. Lorna. I'm on my way to IngIewood.
Listen, jot down and remind me to give
ReynaIdo. . .
The baiIiff over at San Fernando, $200
for Christmas, aIright?
Got it. Hey, did VaI reach you about
his customer?
Yeah, 'I got something big for you,
Mick!'
Everytime. Any other caIIs?
No, just some odds and ends.
PDUI's, they just recruited some house
members. Oh. . .
GIoria Larson caIIed from county
Iock-up.
She got popped again?
The usuaI with compIications.
Coccaine possession. First appearance
is right after Iunch.
TeII her, I'II try.
So, I was thinking, boss, you know,
uh. . .
When you get your Iicence back, Why not
maybe uh. . . you know, Iike a stay-on.
- Like permanent things on me, you
know? - I got my Iicence back 3 months
ago, EarI.
Hey, boss. Want me to do something
about that?
'Cos I can.
Uh. . . keep doing what you're doing.
Boss?
AIright.
PuII over up here.
CounciIor.
- Eddie. - How's it hangin'?
Oh, a IittIe to the Ieft, my man. How
about you?
Not bad.
Your car's a IittIe messy.
Yeah, maid didn't come 'tiI Tuesday.
What can I do for you, big man?
Our boy, HaroId caIIed from the Pens,
said you're staIIing his case 'tiI you
see some more 'green'.
I don't get paid, I don't work.
We paid you, $5, 000.
That's Iong gone, Eddie.
Look, I couId teII you, the haIf of it
went to an aeriaI photo expert.
He's gonna bIow the State's case by
showing that the DEA vioIated the air
space. . .
Over HaroId's farm by fIying too Iow.
I can aIso teII you that I gotta fIy
that guy in from New York City . . .
Get him to testify, put him up in a
hoteI, and aII that kind of stuff.
But you don't need to know that.
AII you need to know is that we had a
deaI.
It's time to refiII the tank.
What? Another 5 grand?
Ten. He wants to fIy business.
He wants first cIass hoteI.
And we want HaroId back on the farm.
- He's our best farmer, you know what I
mean? - I don't.
And I don't want to.
Now, Iook.
Either pay me.
Or go with the pubIic defender.
He won't know much about air space,
but. . .
Aren't you gonna count it?
I just did.
Keep that rubber on the road, Eddie.
Let's roII, EarI.
So, this expert fIying from New York.
You want me to pick him up at the
airport?
There's nobody coming in.
The best camera experts in the worId are
right here in HoIIywood.
Nice, you know what?
You wouId've done aIright on the
streets.
Shit. . . What do you think I am,
EarI?
Louis RouIet?
Yes.
I'm MichaeI HaIIer.
Mr. HaIIer. Our guy caIIed you because
I need someone.
This whoIe thing is a set-up.
I made a mistake with that woman and she
was setting me up. . .
Keep your voice down, hear me?
Don't say anything about the case,
untiI I get you out on baiI.
I understand your famiIy Iawyer's in
court?
Yes, his name's CeciI Dobbs.
- He's here somewhere. - I'II find him.
TeII me about yourseIf.
- How oId are you? - 32.
Ties to community? Did you grow up here?
Yeah, BeverIy HiIIs. Went to USC.
Work for my mother's business.
What about your father?
He died when I was 2.
How much did you make Iast year, Louis?
The taxes said $600, 000.
I want a Iawyer too.
My name's CorIiss. Who's this?
- You got a card on you? - Listen,
buddy, they have a Iawyer for you out
there.
Right now, I need you to back away and
give us a IittIe space.
Can you do that, paI?
I'm backing, boss.
Here we go. AII good.
There we go.
Now, Iisten, they've uh. . .
Put some heavy charges on you, Louis.
The DA's probabIy gonna ask for no baiI.
- No baiI? - I said they're gonna ask
for it.
When was the Iast time you were
arrested?
- Never. - So, if I check your record.
. .
You'd find parking tickets.
Are you gonna get me out of here?
I'm gonna try, Louis.
Are you the prosecutor who used to have
the RouIet's case?
HaIIer.
Son of a bitch.
RuIes are ruIes.
I wanted this one. Okay, okay, I'II
go quIetIy.
But after today's hearing, if you don't
object. . .
Depends.
You going for no baiI?
That won't change with the prosecutor.
Not after what your guy did.
If he didn't?
Sure 'if'.
BaiIey picked him in her home with bIood
aII over him.
I Iove it when you get sarcastic.
Can I see the arrest report?
You get it from whomever takes over.
No favours on this one.
How's HayIey today?
She's good.
Good.
I'II pick her up the usuaI time on
Saturday.
Because of the seriousness of the
offence. . .
The financiaI resources of the accused.
. .
The State requests no baiI.
Your Honour, there's no way the State
can cIaim that my cIient is a fIight
risk.
- He's not. - With resources Iike this
man has, fIight is aIways risk.
- Are there any priors? - No, Your
Honour.
Then, I'm gonna reduce the risk of
fIight by ordering him to a tracer
ankIet. . .
And I'm gonna set baiI at $1 miIIion.
- Judge, have you seen the photo? - Ms.
McPherson, the baiI is set.
Thank you, Judge.
Mick, feeIing Iike to thank me and
speak good of me? 'Cos this one's gonna
be the money, I'm teIIing you.
- We'II see, we'II see. - This is the
Iawyer right there, CeciI Dobbs.
Hey, Mick, don't forget our deaI.
. . . He's here now. I'II taIk to you
Iater.
- CeciI Dobbs. - Mr. HaIIer.
Depressing to see the boy caught up in
that kettIe caII.
The boy?
I represent the famiIy for a Iong time.
Listen, my advice is, Iet VaI fix you
up the bond.
And you, take the boy home.
WeII, we were thinking of putting up
property.
There's the Windsors beach house.
Mother's name is Windsor?
Her second husband's name.
He's dead now.
Assessing the house couId take days.
Trust me, you don't want the boy in the
cIean CIeveIand that Iong.
So, tap VaI. Take Louis to your
office. . .
I'II meet you there at 4.
Here, Iet me give you my business card.
Oh boy.
Media?
Yeah, that'II be on us.
Mrs. Windsor's sensitive about the
press.
I guess there's much we can do about
that.
We'II see.
Say, Bob!
Come here. Come here.
Saw you fiIming in there. What's your
name?
Name's Rob GiIIan. They caII me
'Sticks'.
Sticks, you freeIancing on this?
Yeah, your cIient's got profiIe,
figure I'II seII to IocaI news.
- How much? - How much what?
How much they pay you for what you shot
in there?
Uh. . . That depends.
7. . . 750?
How about we take it off your hands. . .
For 8? No?
Too short?
AIright, Iet's make it a grand.
- DeaI? - It's yours.
- So, I can expense this, right? - Of
course.
AbsoIuteIy.
Thank you, Sticks.
Thank you.
You know, Mr. HaIIer. . . You weren't
my choice.
Bet I wasn't.
Firms Iike yours must have some heavy
hitters on caII.
We do, but Louis insisted.
FrankIy, I've never heard of you.
But uh. . . Maybe I shouId have.
Did you say I was Louis' choice?
Yes, he read about a case you had.
I need a hundred grand upfront.
Working at $550 an hour. . .
Another hundred if we go to triaI.
The motion goes pass a week.
AppeaIs, we start over.
I take it that's no probIem?
- No. - See you at 4.
Where are we heading now?
We gotta go and meet Sticks at Jim's.
- The same spot? - Hm-hm.
AIright.
There he is.
There we go.
Eight for me, two for you.
- Thanks, Sticks. - Anytime.
- Hm-hm. . . - Hey, hey, my tape!
You don't Iook good, girI.
Thanks.
Something new?
Booked on possession of coke?
PIus the usuaI.
I know, it's dumb, it's. . .
A guy paid me with it and I had it on me
when I went to the next.
And the next was a cop?
Yeah.
Look, can't you get me one of those. .
.
Rehab pIaces that get you straight?
We did a pre-chiId rehab Iast time. The
DA's never gonna go for it again.
- You may have to do some jaiI time,
GIoria. - I can't.
Yes you can. Yes. . . You can.
Hey. . . They have programs in jaiI too.
Look, you've had a Iong run.
Maybe after this you'II get a Iife.
Yeah.
Housewife of the year. That's me.
Maybe I can turn some tricks for the
PTA.
- It's not funny. - I'd Iike to see
that.
AIright, aIright, give it to me.
AIright, I uh. . .
I did a guy at the TraveIIer's at Santa
Monica.
A guy who paid you with coke instead of
money?
Yeah, and he had a show of coke in
there, I saw it.
- You know him? - No.
He reached me from my website. He was
uh. . .
He's Mexican or something.
Did you screen him?
Oh, I screened them aII.
Okay, with what? His driver's Iicence?
His passport. It was uh. . .
His name uh. . .
- His name's Hector. - Hector what?
- Um. . . - What's his Iast name?
Think, GIoria, think.
Hector Arande Moya's what you get if you
run a trace.
He's a fugitive from a the grand jury
down in FIorida.
The DA wants him for drug trafficking.
And LesIie, they want him a Iot.
And your girI's Iooking to trade?
She gives you his hoteI and room number.
- She'II aIso testify on the coke? - No,
Iocation onIy.
You guys take it from there.
My best guess is that Hector hasn't
checked out yet.
And in exchange?
You drop aII charges, aII she does is a
pre-chiId rehab.
The faciIity at the USC Med wouId be
nice.
Or I can take it to the Feds.
They'II cut this deaI in a minute.
AIright, you fucking asshoIe.
After you.
- You'd go head first? - I'd give it a
shot if I was gonna do it.
- Why? - Star points.
You're so vain, nobody cares if you
kiII yourseIf.
It'II Iook cooI. What do you think the
Iast thing that'd go through your mind
wouId be?
Your asshoIe.
Mr. HaIIer.
Louis, good morning.
- Thank you. - It's just a start.
This is Frank Levin. Frank's my
investigator.
- Louis RouIet. - Good to meet you.
We're in here.
Got a. . . tracer ankIet.
A present from your friend, VaI
VaIenzueIa by the order of the court.
As if I'd go any pIace before this
thing's over.
GentIemen, weIcome.
- Mr. Dobbs. - Mr. HaIIer.
Good to see you. This is Frank Levin.
Mr. Levin is my investigator. His fees
are in addition to mine.
Of course.
GentIemen, this is Mary Windsor. She's
Louis' mother.
- Mr. HaIIer. - Mrs. Windsor.
- PIeasure to meet you. - How do you
do?
Fine, thank you. This is Frank Levin,
my investigator.
How do you do?
The charges against my son are
ridicuIous.
So is that woman.
Here's a cheque for you, Mr. HaIIer.
This is going to have to come from your
son, Mrs. Windsor.
You can give him the money, he can
write the cheque.
But it must come from him.
He's my cIient.
And I have to be cIear from the start.
I can't thank you enough for being here.
SincereIy, it's good to know that
you're gonna be there.
When we need you.
But not now? Is that it?
No, ma'am. The DA can make you testify
about what you hear.
Attorney priviIedge does not cover you.
I'II see you at home.
She's not used to being toId what to do.
I can beIieve that.
So, how fast can I go to triaI?
I want this behind me.
Are you sure?
You can stretch it out and enjoy your
freedom.
- Most cIients choose to. . . - GuiIty.
. . cIients, you mean.
Okay, then I insist on going to triaI
right away.
Or perhaps, it never goes to triaI at
aII?
My firm can bring uh. . .
ConsiderabIe infIuence to Bear.
Oh, don't kid yourseIf, CeciI.
There's no way the State's dropping
these charges.
As a matter of fact, they've aIready
upped them to the negotiating position.
There won't be any negotiating.
No pIea bargain, no nothing.
I'm not going to jaiI for something I
didn't do.
I'm innocent.
And if there is a triaI, I wanna take
the stand and teII the jury. . .
That I'm innocent.
Now, if that's a probIem, we can part
company right now.
Time to teII me what happened.
I was having a drink at The Association.
The Association? The bar on 6th Street?
The one with a Iot of young women?
Right. Good for pick-ups.
What's the fiIe say about the girI,
Frank?
Uh. . . Regina Campo.
Known as Reggie, 26 years oId.
Part time actress, part time office
temp.
And hoping to retire after suing my
cIient.
Did you know her before Iast night,
Louis?
No. I've seen her around, but. . .
We never spoke. She was aIways with
another guy.
Last night too.
I got it that she wasn't into her date.
She brushed by me on her way to the
bathroom.
She basicaIIy just Iaid her address on
me, on a napkin.
She said she couId get rid of him by 10.
Do you stiII have it? What she wrote
down?
No, I didn't keep the napkin.
Check the fiIe. See if the poIice
report has any of this.
Frank here has aIready worked us a
IittIe miracIe.
He uh. . . happened to score us a copy
of the discovery fiIe.
Everything the DA has.
They wouId have had to turn it over
eventuaIIy, but it wouId've taken a
whiIe.
No, they don't have the other guy.
They don't even have the bar.
So, what? AII they've got is Louis
shows up at her apartment. . .
And she gets beaten?
That is such buIIshit.
Just keep teIIing me your story.
Okay.
I got there earIy.
And uh, waited untiI he came out.
Did you see what he was driving?
A bIue mustang.
AIright, so he comes out, you go in?
She saw it was me.
And opened the door.
Uh. . . the haIIway was tight.
So I had to. . . waIk pass her, you
know. . .
She cIosed the door.
So my back was to her and um. . .
That was it.
- What was it? - She hit me with
something.
I got down. . . And verything got bIack
fast.
Show me where she hit you.
Right here.
StiII hurts.
And that bIow knocked you out?
Next I know, 2 faggots were sitting on
me. HoIding me down.
PoIice report has it, it's the a
homosexuaI coupIe from across the haII.
Like I said, faggots.
I stand corrected. Faggot coupIe from
across the haII.
Go on, Louis.
I was stiII foggy when the cops came.
My name's officer MaxweII, I'd Iike to
ask you a few questions.
- Can you teII me your name, pIease? -
Reggie Campo.
- Do you know this gentIeman? You met
him before? - No!
That's when I saw she'd set me up.
- Set it up, how? - She put bIood on my
hand.
My Ieft hand.
He said he was gonna rape me.
And kiII me.
And then he said he was gonna come back
here and rape me again.
You said she Ieft her door open a crack.
Did you happen to see her face?
Not aII of it.
MainIy her eye.
Wait, her Ieft eye?
- Yes. - AIright, so she aIready had
the injuries to the right side of her
face. . .
She opens the door. . .
ConceaIs that from him.
And as he enters, she . . . she
cIobbers him.
So, our case is what?
She beat herseIf up?
If she aIready had the injuries. . .
She either did just that or she had a
boyfriend do it.
She must have. I mean, she saw Louis'
Maserati. . . His watch.
It's known the famiIy has money.
I weigh you shouId be fiIing in civiI
court the moment this is over.
Let's hear the poIice report.
How's Reggie teIIing?
Okay, according to the victim. . .
She was home aIone when the suspect
presented himseIf at the door. . .
As someone she knew.
Upon Ietting him in, she was
immediateIy struck.
Does it say, he knocked her down?
Yes, there was a struggIe that
continued from the haIIway to the
stairs.
He heId the victim by the neck. . .
And forced her down. Suspect maintained
the position. . . .
Behind her. . .
HoIding a knife against the Ieft side of
her throat.
That's not my knife.
His prints aII here, Frank?
WeII, stands to reason, if she put
bIood on his hand. . .
She put his prints on the knife.
I just toId you though, that isn't my
knife.
Keep taIking Frank.
As Ms. Campo ran for the stairs. . .
They fought and she kept the intruder
backwards.
ReaIising her attacker had her cornered
she fought free and . . .
Reached a nearby bottIe of vodka.
And that's when she cIogged him.
That's her story.
Those are aII Iies.
Look, if everything she's saying is a
Iie. . .
Then, this is going to be the easiest
case, ever.
But you swear, it's aII Iies?
AII of it?
Are you sure there's not anything. . .
That you're not teIIing me?
Nothing.
Why did he choose you, Mick?
Rich kid, spoiIed as shit . . . Never
heard the word 'no'. . . .
Yeah, but the damn thing is, the way
he teIIs his story, Frank.
Just quite enough to be true.
I don't know, Mick. This kid feeIs
wrong to me.
But, I'II check out his story. AII of
it.
Start at The Association Bar.
And then, this Regina Campo. The way
he said she came on to her. . .
Sounds Iike a pro.
Yeah, write it down. AIso uh. . Mr. .
. Mr. Mustang?
AIright, I stiII don't get how that
works.
What? He and Reggie got into some rough
train then he punched her?
UnIess he was in on it.
Meaning. . . He hit her afterwards?
Bingo.
Jesus, Mick, are you starting to think
Louis is innocent?
He just might.
Besides, you know, my father aIways
said about an innocent cIient.
No, I've never heard this. Hi. . .
He said 'there's no cIient as scary as
an innocent man'.
That's right.
'Cos if you screw up and he goes to
prison. . . You're never gonna be abIe
to Iive with yourseIf.
So, there's onIy one verdict you can
put on the board, baby. . .
And that's an N G.
What do you say, Mags?
Frank, if you Iet a man drive home in
this condition. . .
I think that I can charge you both.
I'II take him to his house.
How are you gonna get home?
EarI couId pick up the car from me in
the morning.
I came with friends.
Later.
No, no, I got this.
I insist.
What?
MoonIight becomes you.
You do not do me any good, HaIIer.
Hey, Mick!
Jesus, Frank. What couIdn't wait?
Wanna watch a movie?
We caught a break.
The owner had a camera system set up
Iast month.
I had the. . . security tape transferred
to a disk.
So I couId manipuIate. . .
I know this pIace.
There's our boy, Louis.
And I wouId Iike you to meet. . .
Ms. Reggie Campo.
And there's. . . Mr. Mustang.
- Are you sure? - I wouIdn't have popped
a grand for the tape if I wasn't sure.
Now, watch.
Reggie gets up, goes to the Iadies
room. . .
Mr. Mustang chats up the bartender. So
that's where he goes. . .
And give Reggie her chance. . .
Watch her.
Wait, that's not how he said it went
down.
He said she gave him her address on a
napkin.
Okay, hoId on, Hoss. . . HoId on. . .
Let her go pee. Okay, here she comes.
There's your napkin.
Now, watch this.
She and Mr. Mustang decided it's time
to spIit. . .
Look, Iook. . . Look at his hand.
Look at his watch.
So he's Ieft handed. That's my bet.
FaciaI bIows are from the Ieft. This
guy's right handed.
Mick, you haven't been drinking enough.
You said you knew The Association?
You wouId reaIise, this shot is into
the mirror behind the bar.
'Cos that's where the owner set up the
camera so he couId watch his register!
- Things are backwards. - And Mr.
Mustang punches with his Ieft.
Yeah. . . you proud of yourseIf,
Frank?
I reaIIy reaIIy am.
But not just about this.
That feeIing I had about Reggie?
That she was seIIing it? I did a IittIe
bit of research. . .
She's our girI.
You teII me the cops don't have this?
How can they? There's onIy one and it's
not a copy.
Then make a copy.
What? You're gonna give it to the
prosecutor?
Yeah, a new guy named, Ted Minton.
He's gonna hand over the discovery fiIe.
Oh, poor bunny.
He's not gonna know what hit him.
How Iong 'tiI you think your man's back?
ProbabIy just a few more minutes.
Mr. HaIIer.
- There he is. - Sorry to keep you
waiting.
- The discovery fiIe. - I hope this
wiII be worth your whiIe.
Kinda Iight.
You have a pIace where we can pIay this?
What eIse do you have?
What eIse do I have?
Come on, Minton. Let's cut the
buIIshit here.
AIright? Not onIy your so-caIIed victim
a prostitute. . .
But I have her soIiciting my guy on
video.
You think the jury's gonna see this. . .
And think he had to rape her at knife
point just to have sex with her?
No.
Are you Iistening to what I'm saying?
Yes and it doesn't change the offer I'm
prepared to make.
Offer?
You going forward?
We wiII drop down to assauIt with the
deadIy.
Attempted sexuaI battery.
GuideIines put that on. . . 7 years,
maybe he'II do 4?
What am I missing here?
Hey, Frank!
What's up?
AIright, Iook here. These fiIes Iook
identicaI to me.
AIright, there's something we're
missing and we're not seeing it.
WeII, here's the discovery fiIe I got
from my cIerk in DA's office.
And this is the one I got from Minton.
Wow. . . Wow. . . Wow. . .
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Son of a bitch.
They switched up the fiIes. This is a
different knife.
- Hm-hm. . . - I've been taking care of
this guy for 10 years.
And he set me up.
WeII, he's off the christmas Iist.
He's on the shit Iist.
Good shot!
Looks a IittIe short to me.
You guys finish yourseIves. See you
Iater.
- They've cIosed down anyway. -
AIright.
Louis.
So, what happened? Did you see Minton?
Oh, I saw him.
We need to taIk.
You Iied to me, Louis.
You didn't teII me you were paying
Reggie Campo for sex.
I don't go Iookin' surprised. CouId've
easiIy toId me that in CeciI's office.
I don't want my mother to find out.
CeciI teIIs her everything.
Oh, so you decided to keep from me the
one thing. . .
That couId've made this triaI go away?
- Huh? - Is that what Minton said?
- No more triaI? - I said 'couId have'.
If that had been the onIy Iie you toId
me.
What do you mean?
Recognise that?
It's a picture of your knife.
The one you had on you when you went to
Reggie's.
The one the cops have.
That's why Ted Minton didn't focus to
answer shit, why shouId he?
- When he's got a knife with her bIood
and your initiaI? - That wasn't the
knife that was in the fiIe.
That's right, it wasn't.
The fiIe Frank got is what we caII a
'Ioaded deck'.
The cops use it to set us up. To make
us think they didn't have anything.
When in fact, they've got enough to put
your goIf pIaying ass for 20 years, big
boy.
Why did you Iie to me about the knife?
Louis, why wouId you Iie about
anything?
Everything you teII me is confidentiaI.
Attorney cIient priviIedges.
AIright, I didn't Iie. I said the
knife in the picture wasn't mine.
I said it twice and nobody Iistened to
me.
What are you now? The god damn Iawyer?
You said it wasn't yours. . .
What you shouId've said was 'I had a
knife, Mick'.
'But this isn't it'.
You brought a weapon to a meeting with a
prostitute.
So, you teII me, how the heII am I
supposed to make that Iook Iike she set
you up?
I. . . did not do this.
It's custom made.
It's a razor tip. It's got your
initiaIs engraved. . .
On the handIe.
I aIways carry it.
We show homes to peopIe we don't know!
There's one time. . .
My mother was showing a pIace.
It was in BeI Air, so she thought it
was okay to go aIone.
- He was there. - Who was there?
The man who raped her.
When she didn't come back. . .
I went to the house and found her.
That's when she stopped showing
property.
And I started carrying a knife.
AIways.
- Your mother wiII have to testify. -
No, no, I don't want that.
I don't give a damn what you want.
You wanna stay out of this shit house,
you do exactIy as I teII you. . .
From now on, you got it?
- Hey. . - Hey. . .
Success. We had fun.
- Got her? - Yeah.
At Ieast you did one thing right, huh?
We did a coupIe.
Good night.
WeII, Iook who's come caIIing.
Detective KurIen.
Hey, you been to San Quentin, IateIy?
See our boy, Martinez?
I asked you something.
How's Martinez doing up there? He made
the pucker-up and kiss me team?
I haven't taIked to him.
Right, I guess once they pIead guiIty
and go down, you don't have much use
for 'em, huh?
But uh. . .
He's away forever, right?
He got Iife, yeah.
So, he'II be out in 15.
Too bad, 'cos his victim, Donna
Renteria, she's dead forever.
How does someone Iike you sIeep at
night?
With aII the scum you represent?
Hey, KurIen.
Come here a second.
I had a cIient once.
He uh. . . decapitated his ex wife.
- Kept her head in the refrigerator. -
Nice, sweet.
The DA got greedy.
Tried to piIe on 2 unassauIt murders. .
.
Tricked up the evidence, tried to make
it Iook Iike my guy did it.
But you got your boy off.
And he's out waIking around now, right?
- WeII, fuck you, HaIIer. - No, fuck
the DA.
And the cops who heIped him.
It's caIIed the justice system, KurIen.
It's not the way it's supposed to work.
WeII, Iook who's here?
- Kids. . . Maggie. - Hey. . .
You Iike a beer?
A coId beer. Scotty!
Oh, we couId share this.
No, I'm good.
AIright, aIright. We swapped spits
before.
TeII me about your uh. . . Your buddy,
Minton.
Who says he's my buddy?
WeII, he was saying that you were good.
With that guy, CorIiss, right?
Yeah.
How did you know?
You'II take the guy's head off first
down.
Hope so. So what uh. . .
Ted taIked to you about CorIiss?
No, no, I sent him to Ted.
He thought I was on the case because I'm
his first appearance.
But I shouId not be teIIing you any of
this.
No, I knew.
I knew a guy Iike Minton wouIdn't have
bothered putting ajaiIhouse snitch on
the stand.
I mean, that's what he is, right?
Can we just have a friendIy beer and not
taIk about work?
Let's grab a tabIe up back and grab
something to eat.
We can taIk about our daughter?
Okay.
Yeah.
I bet she didn't know 3D movies couId be
so much fun.
I was watching her.
- FiIIing the cup. - Right.
Yeah.
Hey, you didn't know Minton had CorIiss
'tiI I bIabbed, did you?
I knew he was on at something.
Screw it, I'm not gonna defend Minton.
He fights too dirty.
- Is this from Maggie McPherson? - Hey.
. .
You know there are Iines I won't cross.
Don't you?
Can you give me a Iift?
[Whispering] She's gonna wake up and
she's gonna see us here.
[Whispering] It's not fair.
How did she get in here?
She comes in when she has nightmares.
How often does she have nightmares?
Don't start.
You don't know what it's Iike to raise a
chiId aIone.
I'II Ieave. Come back in an hour. . .
We'II go together to pick up your car. .
.
Then, I can take HayIey to schooI.
Just Iike that? You're gonna start
taking her to schooI?
Do you remember what we taIked about
Iast night?
Yes, I remember what we taIked about
Iast night.
But I thought you were just trying to
get my head into your case or get me in
bed.
Can't Iive with you, can I?
No, you can't. Not when you're being a
defense Iawyer.
Not when I'm trying to keep dirt bags
off the streets.
And you keep putting them there.
- Heard it aII before, Mag! - Hm-hm.
Donna Renteria.
Oh, man, they have my picture
everywhere, man.
They're gonna bring me in anyway, so
I'm fucked.
Thought you toId KurIen you were in her
apartment? He didn't have that.
- No, no. . . - He didn't have it.
He didn't even have any prints.
No, but that's just. . . It was true. .
.
I saw her at The Arizona. . . I was uh.
. .
She said, if I paid her more money than
the other guy. . .
Then we can go to her pIace.
Nobody saw any other guy.
There was another guy! It was. . . It
was uh. . .
A white guy. He was right by the bar.
The coroner says her vagina was
brutaIised.
Are you my Iawyer, man?
- I'm trying to be. - Look, when I
Ieft, that chick was fine.
Look, I sIept with her, okay.
I did, but I didn't hurt her. I
promise.
Three peopIe saw you throw a knife into
the LA River.
- Huh? HeIp me. - I had that knife in
my car.
I knew they were gonna find it, man.
They were gonna pin it on me.
- I know! - Look, if aII you did was
have sex with her. . .
Then why didn't you Ieave any prints,
huh?
- I mean the pIace was wiped down cIean.
- I didn't wipe it down, though!
You Ieft semen on the toweI?
You remember that? Did you forget the
toweI?
No! I didn't forget anything man!
I ust used that toweI, I paid her and I
Ieft.
That defense ain't gonna make.
- Dude, don't say that! - It won't
make, man.
There's not a chance in heII with that
defense.
- You know what they're asking for? -
What?
They want the death penaIty, man.
They wanna take your ass down. They
wanna burn you, man.
Listen.
I can see to it that that never . . .
happened.
But not if you don't pIead.
Oh, you want me to say I did it?
There's a deaI to be made here.
And I can do it.
I can get you Iife.
Now, Iife means you're paroIed in 15.
It keeps the needIe out of your arm,
man.
It's our onIy pIay, man.
This paroIe. . . You know what it
means? That means I didn't do it!
That's the best I can get for you, man.
I don't wanna go to jaiI for something I
didn't do, man.
You know what's that's gonna do to my
mom, bro?
I ain't going to jaiI for something I
didn't do, bro!
Come on, man.
PIease heIp me, bro. PIease heIp me.
CALIFORNIA STATE PRISON SAN QUENTIN
I'm not gonna ask how you are, 'cos I
know.
No, bro.
You don't know.
But I need to ask you some questions,
Jesus.
Oh, questions?
Now?
You know what? You didn't ask me a Iot
of questions back then.
You never asked me. 'Did you kiII her?'
No.
PIease, I'm trying to make this right.
I need you to teII me what happened at
The Arizona Bar that night, one more
time.
PIease.
She was workin'.
I Iiked her.
I mean, out of them, I Iiked her. She
was the one.
You know, she caught my eye.
They were going around in a IittIe
circIe, you know.
She was acting aII cute and shit.
I don't know how this turns out, you
know. . .
No, it's fine. You wanna dance?
Yeah, I wanna dance.
I can give you a private dance.
I picked her.
I asked her to dance for me.
# And we strated talking.#
#You know, she said that I couId take
her home. #
So, how much for me to come over?
WeII, usuaIIy I charge a thousand. But
for you. . .
$300, 'cos you're sexy.
#And she was good, man, yeah. #
#So I did. #
But I ain't kiII her.
You said there was another guy, right?
Yeah.
She was taIking to him.
And then she came back to me.
Okay.
I got some pictures, aIright? Some mug
shots.
Jesus, see if you can ID. . .
That other guy at the cIub.
TeII me if you recognise him.
No.
How about this guy, Jesus?
Recognise him?
Uh-uh.
Okay, take your time.
Yeah, yeah. This guy?
Is this the other guy?
Is this guy in the cIub that night?
Guard!
- Jesus. - Having fun?
- Is this the other guy? - Why you pIay
me, bro?
Why are you bothering me with this
anymore?
- Jesus, is this the guy? - What does
it matter, man?
I'm right here. Right where you wanted
me, bro!
Is this the guy? This is the guy?
You know what? I don't trust you, bro!
Jesus, I'm trying to make it right!
- It never wiII! - Interview's over.
Okay, that's my boy, that's my boy. .
.
Get out of here, yeah!
Hey! You okay? Where've you been today?
Been trying to caII you.
I've been to San Quentin.
To see Jesus Martinez.
About what happened after. . .
He Ieft Donna Renteria's apartment.
- After he kiIIed her? - He didn't kiII
her, Frank.
He went there.
He had sex.
FIushed the condom down the toiIet.
Wiped his his print on a pink toweI and
he went off.
But he didn't kiII her.
Come on, Mick, we've been through this
a hundred times.
#The reaI kiIIer. . . #
#She Iet him in. #
#Maybe uh. . . he faked Iike he was
Martinez's friend and acted Iike he had
an appointment. #
#Like the guy in the bar?#
#Right. He comes in. He punches her. #
#She's not gonna be Iike Iike Reggie
Campo. #
#Cos this time, the bitch puIIs a
knife. #
#Takes her and puts her on the tabIe.
Puts on a condom and rapes her. #
#And when he's done. . . #
#She was stabbed. . . over and over. . .
#
#52 times Iike he was something of his
god damn mind. #
Do I have to teII you what kind of knife
it was?
A short bIade foIding knife?
Just Iike RouIet's.
Okay, okay, Iet's take it a IittIe bit
easier on that, okay?
Why, Frank? Why didn't I Iisten?
Listen, I got a basebaII bat if you
reaIIy wanna beat yourseIf up.
I don't wanna beat myseIf up. Son of a
bitch toId me he didn't do it.
AIright? There was the DNA.
And there was the knife that ditched.
But there was no way I was gonna Iisten
to him.
There was no way I wouId beIieve that he
didn't do it.
I couIdn't beIieve him!
I couIdn't beIieve, that I actuaIIy. .
.
CouId represent an innocent man.
Just Iike my father warned me about.
Mick, come on, they aII said they
didn't do it.
- You know that. - So, what did I do?
I get him to pIead.
I get his sister to beg him to pIead.
'Cos he got no case.
So I gave him the best deaI I can. You
know, I feeI pretty god damn good about
it.
'Cos hey, I got the son of a bitch off
death row.
I got him 15 years instead of the
needIe.
Yeah.
I showed him RouIet's picture.
Okay.
RouIet is using Martinez as the other
guy in the bar?
Like Mr. Mustang in this case?
So, he's not just getting off and
kiIIing women.
It's seeing somebody eIse do the time.
That's his MO.
What did Martinez say?
Enough.
Enough for me to know. I gotta . . . I
gotta find . . .
What you gotta do, is find a way to put
RouIet in Renteria's apartment the night
she was murdered.
- That's what you gotta do. - I have to
find a way to make it right, Frank.
I gotta make it right.
WeII, you can't bring him to the cops
'cos he's your cIient.
And you can't take him to the DA 'cos
you'II Iose your Iicence.
Worse, any evidence we found wouId be
inadmissibIe . . . attorney cIient
priviIedge.
It'II ruin any case that we couId ever
have against him.
That's why the son of a bitch hired me.
He's got me in his trick bag.
You got one cIient in jaiI
For what your other cIient did.
What are you gonna do, Mick?
- Hey, Mick, you okay, buddy? -
Frank, Frank, Iisten to me. I got it.
- What? - You know how RouIet said aII
we'II find on him is parking tickets,
right?
- Right. - I just don't buy that
anymore.
Now, there are others.
Other girIs he did.
Renteria and Campo, I mean, they Iook
too much aIike.
Like their sisters. And the injury to
the right side of their face is too
simiIar.
Right? This guy's got a type, Frank.
There are other cases out there. And
you can find them.
Now, you gotta do this, I can't.
- I'm his Iawyer. - Okay, okay, I'm
on it.
AIright. I gotta take this.
- Maggie, hey. - Hey, did you get my
voicemaiI?
Uh, I've been up at San Quentin to see
an oId cIient.
How's HayIey?
#She's good. She's got soccer this
weekend. #
Saturday, right?
- Hm-hm. - I Iook forward to it.
#Great. TaIk Iater. #
If you're wondering how I got in. . .
I'm in reaI estate, so, if I wanna get
into a friend's house. . .
No, we're not friends.
You're my cIient.
I'm your Iawyer.
My Iawyer.
See, that's exactIy what I wanted to
remind you of.
I'm about to go on triaI.
And yet. . .
I couIdn't reach you.
Now I found out where you were aII day.
Heard you teII Maggie.
- You shit. - You went to see Jesus
Martinez.
And I know what you taIked about.
Donna Renteria.
You're right, Mick.
I kiIIed her.
There. No reason why I shouIdn't teII
my own Iawyer.
Since it's aII confidentiaI.
Attorney cIient priviIedge.
Isn't that what you toId me?
It's time for you to go, Louis.
AIright.
That's a cute picture of your daughter,
HayIey.
She's very pretty.
- She's got soccer practice tomorrow,
right? - Don't.
Don't what?
You think you're the first cIient to
ever threaten me with my famiIy? Huh?
AII I said was she's pretty.
Are you scared, Louis?
Because where you are, right now. . .
You're in a very dangerous pIace.
#So, in concIusion. . . #
#What this case is about. . . #
#What this case is aII about. . . #
#Is a predator. #
On the night of March 6th. . .
Louis RouIet was out staIking his prey.
Now, you're going to hear from the
victim herseIf, about her IifestyIe. .
.
One that we wouId not condone.
But remember.
Anyone.
Can be a victim of a vioIent crime.
This case is cIear.
It's straight forward.
A man attacked a woman in her home.
In order to rape and kiII her.
And it is onIy by the grace of God.
That she's here to teII her story.
Ladies and gentIemen.
My name is MichaeI HaIIer.
And I'm representing Louis RouIet.
Now, Mr. Minton. . .
Doesn't wanna use the word prostitute. .
.
For the woman who was supposed to be
Louis' victim.
He needn't worry.
Because this case isn't about how she
makes her money.
This case is about her actions.
How she saw a man with signs of weaIth.
. .
As a ticket out of the Iife she was in.
And chose to target him.
Now, what she didn't count on, was
you.
How you put two and two together. . .
And Iet your common sense teII you. . .
Who the reaI predator is, in this case.
Thank you for your time.
The court wiII adjourn untiI Monday.
And the State wiII caII its first
witness.
Go, HayIey, go! Turn, turn, turn!
Left foot! Left foot!
Hey, Mick.
Hey, Maggie.
What are you doing here?
I'm gonna take HayIey home.
You've got some pIace to be.
What are you taIking about? What
happened?
Hey, hey, sir, stop.
That's my famiIy.
- Sir! - FamiIy.
- This is a cIosed crime scene. -
Sorry, name's Mick HaIIer.
- SobeI, SobeI! - Yeah, yeah, yeah. .
.
Listen, sIow down a second.
- SIow down. - What happened?
Somebody shot him. In the chest and the
head.
And they shot the dog too.
His body is right in front of the door.
Great, this is just what we need.
So you've uh. . . been here before.
You can teII us if anything is unusuaI.
Anything weird?
Like, throughout this whoIe house. . .
Why is it that aII I see are pictures of
this guy?
My partner's asking if Frank Levin was
gay?
- Is that reIevant? - Yeah, it's aII
reIevant.
He's an ex cop.
Cops against persons in Chicago.
Is that botch enough for you, Lankford?
I don't see anything that I can heIp you
here.
AIright, hey, HaIIer.
I don't need to teII you to stick around
town, where I can find you, do I?
Am I a suspect?
When do you retire, Lankford?
- When do I retire? - Yeah.
18 months, why?
I make sure I show the next one so I can
kick your ass.
VaI!
Hey, Mick! The heII you banging on the
door Iike that for, man?
Are you nuts?
Dude, dude, you Iook terribIe.
Frank Levin was murdered.
Oh man, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry to hear that. - RouIet did
it.
RouIet? I thought you and Frank were
defending him? Why wouId he take Frank
out?
That makes no sense.
You know, VaI. I figure you know
exactIy how it went down.
How wouId I know about it? What are you
taIking about?
'Cos you Iied to me.
You didn't send me the RouIet case.
- He asked for me. - Okay, okay,
that's true, man.
But you know what I said? 'HaIIer's your
man, go for HaIIer'.
I did that for you.
You Iied to me once.
So what? Do you think I wouId Iie about
this?
Give me a IittIe respect, give me a
IittIe credit. I'm not gonna Iie about
this kind of shit.
The poIice checked the tracer that you
put on RouIet. It says he was no way
near Frank's house.
So maybe it wasn't him, Mick.
Maybe it wasn't him. Nobody can beat
the tracer, huh?
It was him. RouIet kiIIed Frank.
- It was RouIet. - I don't Iike the way
you're foIIowing me. . .
I don't Iike the way you corner me,
man. I don't Iike the way you're
taIking to me, okay?
RouIet kiIIed Frank, VaI.
What do you think? You think I cut the
kid Ioose, so he couId murder Frank?
Crazy RouIet kiIIed Frank!
Mick, I'm sorry about Frank, but I
didn't do it, man.
You're the onIy one that couId've taken
it off him.
Being married to you sucked. But being
your car service. . .
Maggie.
- Yeah? - You know what I used to be
afraid of, Maggie?
Yeah. . . Me.
That I wouIdn't recognise the innocents.
That they'II be right there in front of
me, but I just wouIdn't see it.
Yeah.
You know, when I taIked to Minton. . .
GuiIty or not guiIty, just as innocent,
you know?
You know what I'm afraid of now?
EviI.
Pure eviI.
Maggie. . .
Did I get Frank Levin kiIIed?
Micky, no.
#New Message, yesterday, 11:07 AM. #
#Mick, it's me, I tried you on your
ceII. . . #
#Sorry to interrupt your date with
HayIey, but. . . #
#You asked me to do some digging? On
RouIet?#
#WeII, I might have found Martinez's
ticket, Micky. #
#His ticket out of Quentin. #
#Uh. . . Someone's at the door. Look,
you go and you have a good time with
HayIey. #
#And I'II fiII you in when I know it's
for sure. #
#I gotta go. #
[Phone Ringing]
- Detective SobeI. - SobeI, Mick
HaIIer here.
Listen, I just checked my messages.
It turns out, Frank caIIed me just
before he was kiIIed.
The message came in at 11:07.
He said he found something. Something
that couId heIp an oId cIient of ours
get out of prison.
#Okay, who's the cIient?#
#Jesus Martinez. He's in San Quentin. #
Okay, did he say anything eIse?
Yeah, he made ajoke.
Uh. . . He said something about finding
Martinez's ticket out of the queue.
And then someone came to the door.
That's when he hung up.
Listen, whoever came to the door. . .
That's your kiIIer.
Okay, you got me a copy of the tape.
#Yeah, I'II give it to you right away.
#
How is it going with the case? You
getting somewhere?
Yeah, uh. . . we did catch a break.
We found a buIIet casing in the room
from a . 22.
That's good, Frank Levin owned a . 22.
You'II find one registered to him.
#Yeah, we did, but uh. . . #
- It wasn't a MusIin. - A what?
A CoIt Woodsman.
It's an oId antique job.
#That's the gun that kiIIed him. #
Morning, Mick.
It's too bad about Frank Levin.
Got any idea who did it?
Yeah, I'm pretty certain I do.
Mr. TaIbot.
You were with Ms. Campo on the night of
March 6th.
Yupe. We went on a date to The
Association.
Then I took her back to her pIace.
For another date.
And, did you have sexuaI reIations?
About four hundred bucks worth.
And she earned every singIe cent.
What time did you Ieave her apartment?
Oh, I don't know uh. . . About 5
minutes before 10?
Did she say whether she had another
appointment?
Oh, no, no, she acted Iike she was
done for the night.
Objection, Your Honour.
I don't think Mr. TaIbot's quaIified to
interpret Ms. Campo's thinking or
pIans.
I mean, she acted satisfied.
Sustained. Go on, Mr. Minton.
When you Ieft, Mr. TaIbot.
What condition was she in?
Was she hurt?
No, she was fine.
She did not Iook Iike this?
Man.
What kind of sick bastard that did
something Iike that?
Answer the question.
No.
No, we made pIeasurabIe and consensuaI
Iove.
I mean that's what Iife's aII about,
right?
Mr. TaIbot, are you a right handed?
Or Ieft handed?
Left.
- Left? - Yeah.
Isn't it true that before you Ieft Ms.
Campo's apartment. . .
She asked you to repeatedIy strike her
in the face with your Ieft fist?
Your Honour, Mr. HaIIer's just
muddying the water without rigid
statements.
It's part of the defense theory, Your
Honour.
The witness can answer.
I'm sorry.
Can you repeat the question?
This is by your hand, isn't it, Mr.
TaIbot?
Admit it, this whoIe thing is a set-up.
By you and Ms. Campo.
Framing my cIient, Louis RouIet, isn't
it?
I never hit her. Or any other woman,
you understand?
You know a prostitute named ShaquiIIe
Barton?
Working name is uh. . . ShaquiIIa
ShackIes?
Yeah, yeah, I seen her once.
And if I brought her in here, can she
say 'Yes, Mr. TaIbot, he did strike
me'?
- With his Ieft fist, in my face? -
She'd be Iying.
I tried ShaquiIIa once.
I'm not into that rough stuff.
I'm a missionary man.
It's a strong Ieft.
Am I on triaI here?
Not yet.
Good afternoon, detectives.
What can I do for you?
This warrant is buIIshit.
WeII, it's good enough to search your
house.
It wouId've been smart if you'd toId me
that you had a Woodsman?
There's one registered to you.
Let's go for a drive.
AIright.
Let's bag the box.
Can't do baIIistics on a box, can you?
Modern technoIogy.
So uh, why didn't you report this
stoIen?
I don't know.
Maybe I shouId have.
You think?
StiII and aII, we're gonna have a Iook
around the pIace, huh?
Go crazy. You got the warrant.
AIright, start with the couch.
Sir?
Stand up.
Hey, you know, we got a history on the
piece.
Turns out, it once beIonged to Micky
Cowen?
The gangster from the '40s?
I know. My father, he uh. . .
represented him.
Got him off for using it for seIf
defence, so. . .
Micky made him the present of it.
Nice present.
PearI handIe, coIIectors' piece.
How sweet.
You know, that uh. . . That Micky
Cowen shooting. . .
It's. . . It's pretty famous.
It turns out that the county, stiII has
the evidence on storage.
- The buIIet. - You can match the
casing from a sIug that's 50 years oId?
It wouId be easier with the gun, but. .
.
Yeah.
How Iong wiII baIIistics take?
Hey, Mick.
I got something for you.
You asked me to find out that witness'
name.
Is it CorIiss?
Dwayne Geoffrey CorIiss. Right.
He's a Iow Iife type. Not much came up.
But, sometimes he goes by DJ.
With punctuation? And when you read it
that way. . .
TeII me.
WeII, he's pIayed the courtroom snitch
a Iot.
Here and in Arizona.
Both times, they got him earIy reIease.
AIright, this couId be good.
AII I gotta do is find him.
They put him on a pre-chiId rehab at
USC.
I just got Iucky.
There she is.
How are you, sweety?
You aIright?
AIright, Iisten.
I'm actuaIIy not in here about you.
I need you to do something for me.
Keep moving!
Let's go, Iet's go!
Stay on the waII, aII the way down!
That's the bucks, boys, Iet's go.
Stay on the Iine.
CorIiss, right?
I onIy came to say what is required.
Rusky! Ready for the Iine!
You don't know me.
You taIk to the DA. . .
He can get a way to get both of us out.
Step through!
So, HaIIer, you had an interesting
visitor Iast night.
Worry about yourseIf, Ted.
You're dying the death of a thousand
razors up there and you don't even know
it.
CIass witness, Your Honour.
The Prosecution caIIs Regina Campo.
It's true that I uh. . . Lied to the
poIice.
I knew the defendant when he came to the
door.
Ms. Campo. . .
Why did you Iie?
Because I'm scared.
I didn't think the poIice wouId beIieve
me. . .
And I wanted to make sure they arrested
him.
'Cos he's an animaI.
- Do you regret your decision now? -
Yes.
If it heIps him get free and do this to
somebody eIse.
That's prejudiciary, Your Honour.
Sustained.
I have no further questions for Ms.
Campo.
Your witness, Mr. HaIIer.
Ms. Campo.
Have you engaged to an attorney?
To sue. . . Louis RouIet for the events
that happened on the eve of March 6th?
No, I haven't.
Have you taIked to an attorney?
I haven't hired anyone.
No, have you taIked to one?
About a possibIe Iawsuit?
It was nothing more than taIk.
Did you ask him if you couId sue him for
damages?
I thought what you say to Iawyers is
private?
If you wish, you can teII the jurors.
I think I'd Iike to keep it private.
Let's taIk about the night at The
Association Bar.
Have you ever seen Louis RouIet before
that night?
Yes, there and other pIaces.
Ever noticed that he wore a RoIex watch?
No.
Or that he drove one of 2 vehicIes?
A Maserati and a Range Rover?
I never saw him driving.
And what made you approach him?
I saw him Ieave with girIs uh. . . who
do what I do.
With prostitutes?
Then go to a hoteI or one of their
apartments, right?
I don't know where.
WeII, how do you know they Ieft?
Maybe they just went out for a smoke?
Because, I saw them getting in his car.
. .
- And drive away. - No, wait a minute.
You just testified that you had never
seen Mr. RouIet drive.
Now you're saying, yes, you did see
Mr. RouIet get in his car
And Ieave with a prostitute Iike
yourseIf?
Which one is it?
I saw him get in his car, but I didn't
know what kind of car it was.
You know the difference between a
Maserati and a Range Rover?
One is smaII, one is big, I guess.
Okay.
The other women.
Had Ieft with Louis.
When you saw them again. . .
Did any of them ever have injuries or
any of them beaten?
I don't know, I didn't ask.
But girIs in your profession, you do
taIk to each other. . .
About customers, right?
You warned each other. . . if someone's
a freak or something?
Yeah, usuaIIy.
And did any of them ever warned you or
have one bad thing to say about Louis
RouIet?
No.
No one.
So you beIieved you'd be safe?
I thought he was a known quantity and I
needed the money, so. . .
So you thought, he couId soIve your
probIems with money?
- No! - No?
Isn't that why you're sitting here?
Because you zeroed in on him.
No!
I mean, yes, but it wasn't Iike that.
He attacked me. I swear.
And. . . AIright, Iet's pause that
right there.
Just to confirm. . . This is you?
Right, Ms. Campo?
Yes.
What was on the napkin?
My name and address.
And your price?
Yes, $400.
It's a hard Iine of work.
Yes, and dangerous.
In fact, haven't you toId your friends
many times. . .
That you were Iooking for a way out?
I'm not proud of what I do.
I know.
And isn't it true. . .
And nothing wiII be easier to
understand. . .
That you saw Louis RouIet and his money
as that way out?
No! That's not what this is about!
Are you not Iistening to me?
No further questions, Your Honour.
Mr. Minton.
Do you have another witness for us?
Minton Iooks worried.
Not worried enough.
No.
The State rests, Your Honour.
Then the defense wiII caII its first
witness after Iunch.
Yes, I recognise this knife.
It's the one that my son has carried
with him for protection.
For the Iast 4 years, aImost exactIy.
Why wouId he need protection?
ReaItors aIone in the house are
sometimes robbed or. . .
Hurt?
Even raped or murdered.
Has Louis ever been subject to such
crime?
Oh no.
But he knew someone who was.
Raped and robbed by a man.
Louis found her.
It was terribIe.
So, the first thing he did afterwards,
was getting himseIf a knife.
To carry it with him at aII times.
Thank you, Ms. Windsor.
I have no further questions, Your
Honour.
Your witness, Mr. Minton.
Ms. Windsor.
You seemed pretty exact about when it
was your son started carrying around
this. . .
This weapon.
- A five inch foIding knife. - Yes, I
am.
The incident took pIace on June 9th,
2007.
Was it in the newspapers?
Do you somehow remember it because. . .
The poIice came to taIk to Louis?
No, there was no poIice investigation.
Then, how do you remember the exact
date?
Were you given it before your testimony
here today?
I remember the date because. . .
I'II never forget the date I was
attacked.
And Louis won't forget it either.
He found me in the house tied up.
My cIothes were ripped.
It was traumatic for him.
Mr. Minton?
Is there anything eIse you wish to ask?
No, Your Honour.
I've been thinking about those thousand
razors?
We've hads an offer.
You spend 6 months in the county jaiI.
Like I toId you from the beginning.
No deaIs, no bargaining, I'm innocent.
Save it. You make the caII. I don't
give a shit.
- You got my answer. - Yes, I do.
I'II pass it aIong.
You do that.
Oh, Louis.
Tomorrow. . .
I'm putting you on the stand.
I'm ready.
Oh, you'd better be.
Hey, EarI.
There's something, I need you to get
for me.
Your Honour, the defense caIIs Louis
Ross RouIet.
I knocked uh. . . She Iooked through her
side window. . .
And saw that it was me.
And opened the door.
Then, I waIked pass her towards the
Iiving room.
What happened next?
Something hit me from behind.
I bIacked out.
I have no idea for how Iong.
- Is that aII? - When I woke up, uh. .
.
Two guys were sitting on me?
TeIIing me not to move.
I couIdn't anyway. I was. . .
I was scared.
But you had bIood on your sweater.
And on your Ieft hand.
Someone put it there because I didn't.
- You didn't strike Ms. Campo with your
Ieft fist? - No.
- Threatened to rape her? - No. . .
- Threatened to kiII her? - No! I am not
that guy!
I. . .
Do you have any idea what it's Iike. . .
To be accused of something Iike this?
To sit there. . . And Iisten to peopIe
teII Iies?
About you? About you having done
something this sick and depraved?
CaII you an animaI?
TaIk about your sex Iife, humiIiate
you?
Listen, I understand the process. I
know I had to sit there. . .
And better be quIet.
And wait my chance.
But if guiIty peopIe have rights, what
about innocent peopIe?
I am innocent.
I'm innocent and I want this behind me.
I have no further questions, Your
Honour.
According to you. . .
Ms. Campo. . . punched. . .
HerseIf?
Or she had. . . . Someone she had never
met.
VioIentIy and visciousIy beat her as a
part of a set up?
AII I know is I didn't.
This knife that you aIways carry. . .
How did she know she'd find it on you as
part of the set up?
Guess she couIdn't. CouId she?
I never take it out.
I never show it to anyone. . .
So, she must have just found it in my
pocket after. . .
She or whoever knocked me out.
- Isn't that right? - I wouId prefer if
I ask the questions.
Okay.
Mr. RouIet, I'd Iike you to take uh. .
.
Take a Iook at this photo.
TeII me again.
Do you think, Regina Campo wouId or
couId. . .
Have done this to herseIf?
I don't know who did it.
But it wasn't me.
Nobody deserves that to happen.
What do you mean by 'deserves'?
Do you mean. . . Crimes of vioIence. . .
OnIy comes down to a woman getting what
she deserves?
I mean, no matter what she does. . .
Or who she is.
No woman deserves that.
I have nothing further, Your Honour.
Mr. RouIet, you're excused.
Thank you.
The defense rests, Your Honour.
Before deciding to rest this case, the
State wouId Iike to take the night,
Your Honour.
For what purpose?
To consider a rebuttaI witness.
What witness is he taIking about?
I have no idea.
The court wiII adjourn 'tiI 10 o'cIock
tomorrow.
- Morning, BiII. - Morning.
I'm gonna go grab some coffee. You want
some?
No, man, I'm off caffeine.
Right, is that the custody Iist?
- Yeah. - Let me see if I any of my
cIients are on there.
Sure.
CORLISS, DWAYNE.
Lorna, Minton's putting CorIiss on.
- He's aIready in Iock-up. - But that
is great!
Yeah, it's good. How did it go with
you? You served KurIen?
- Yes, I did. - Okay.
I'm going back to court now.
Stand by.
Okay.
Hey, HaIIer, what is this buIIshit?
I have nothing to do with this case?
Subpoena to appear as a witness.
You'II just have to wait and see.
It's a IegaI document, detective.
Hey.
GIad you made it.
- Is he Iooking romantic. - Ever so
speciaIIy.
See you Iater.
Mr. Minton.
Does the State have any rebuttaI?
The State intends to caII Dwayne
Geoffrey CorIiss, as a rebuttaI
witness, Your Honour.
Judge, who is this witness?
And why wasn't I toId about him untiI
now?
BaiIiff?
Remove the jury.
A fair question.
Mr. Minton?
Dwayne CorIiss is a co-operating witness
who spoke with Mr. RouIet in custody.
- FoIIowing arrest. - That's a Iie! I
didn't speak to anyone!
QuIet, Mr. RouIet!
Mr. HaIIer, controI your cIient.
Let me take it from here.
Judge, I share my cIient's outrage.
How Iong has the State been sitting on
this testimony?
Mr. CorIiss just came forward
yesterday, Your Honour.
Yesterday?
This is incredibIe.
Do you want to go back and taIk to him?
Give him the time? I'd aIIow it.
No, you know, thank you, though,
Judge.
I think we aII know what this is.
Mr. Minton's putting ajaiIhouse snitch
on the stand.
Everything he says wiII be a Iie.
- That's groundIess, Your Honour. - I
want my objection noted.
Then, I'm going to ruIe.
He can testify.
CaII the jury in.
May I ask one induIgence, Your Honour?
May I step into the haIIway and. . .
Make a caII to an investigator for
whatever good it may do at this Iate
date?
Thank you, Your Honour.
Yupe, I'm here.
Come into the court house at exactIy
10:15 with the printouts.
Mr. CorIiss.
Are you incarcerated at this time?
Um. . .
No, now, I'm just in the courtroom.
But you are currentIy being heId in a
jaiI ward at USC HospitaI, correct?
Yeah, since I got arrested.
For burgIary and drug possession?
That's right.
Now. . .
Do you know the defendant?
Yeah.
I met him in Iock-up.
We've had a stopover from jaiI.
Then we were together in the tank when
we came for first appearances.
TaIk at that time?
Yeah.
TaIk about how bad are the cigarettes.
Anything eIse?
Uh. . you know. . . what are you in
for?
Like that.
And. . . . Did he say what he was in
for?
He said, for giving a bitch exactIy
what she deserved.
Those were his words.
For giving a bitch exactIy what she
deserved.
Now. . . Have I or anyone eIse promised
you anything in exchange for your
testimony today?
No.
Just the right thing to do.
Thank you, Your Honour.
How many times, have you been arrested,
Mr. CorIiss?
About 7 times in L. A.
CoupIe more in Phoenix.
And New York, if you wanna count those.
Yeah, so you know how the system works,
yeah?
I tried to survive.
Does that sometimes mean ratting out
feIIow inmates?
Your Honour, I object.
Take a seat, Mr. Minton.
I gave you Ieeway for bringing this
witness in.
Thank you, Your Honour.
But I'II rephrase.
What I'm asking you, is how many times
have you snitched. . .
On a feIIow inmate?
- This makes me four. - This makes your
fourth time?
Four times you've testified?
For the prosecution? Against a feIIow
inmate?
Makes you a popuIar man, Mr. CorIiss.
Sounds Iike peopIe just come up to you.
. .
And they teII you the crimes they've
committed. . .
So you can come in here and testify
against them.
PeopIe taIk to me. I'm a friendIy guy.
You're a friendIy guy?
Can you say you and my cIient were
friends?
Louis RouIet?
So he just said to you. . .
What you just toId us and toId the jury
that. . .
That he gave a woman what she deserved?
And then the two of you are back to
taIking about cigarettes?
Not exactIy.
It's Iike he was braggin'.
ToId me he did it before.
He said the other time, he kiIIed the
bitch.
Got away with it then.
Can get away with it now.
Mr. HaIIer?
I have no more questions, Your Honour.
Redirect, Your Honour.
- What the heII is this? - You teII me.
What the heII did you say to this guy,
huh?
Nothing. This is a set-up.
- And you're doing this. - How?
How am I doing this?
Huh?
You said he was bragging.
- How? - WeII. . .
Like he toId me the detaiIs.
Of the other one.
That he kiIIed.
She was a. . . dancer . . .
At some cIub.
And she had. . .
Sexy snake tattoo wrapped around her
body.
Did he say anything eIse?
Hm. . . no.
No.
Snake girI stuff was it.
How does he know this, Louis?
- You think I know? - If you didn't teII
him that shit, somebody did.
Better start thinking about who that
couId be.
Then I have no further questions, Your
Honour.
Any re-crossing from the defense?
- A moment with my staff, Your Honour.
- Be quick.
Is it aII here?
- Yeah. - Okay, good.
Listen, you go on now, Ieave the
buiIding. I don't want anyone asking
you questions, got it?
- Okay. - AIright.
Dwayne.
Mind if I caII you that?
Sure, man.
Wow on the assistant.
You're a funny guy, DJ.
DJ.
Isn't that what they caII you uh. . .
For exampIe, down in Phoenix?
Maybe.
And my assistant, one whose numbers you
want. . .
She was reading on a uh. . .
On the internet about a DJ CorIiss.
Arrested in 1989 on drug charges,
hometown Imesa, Arizona?
Oh yeah, that'd be me.
So you remember Fred BentIey, right?
Uh. . . Your Honour. . .
Where's the defense going with this?
Make a connection soon, Mr. HaIIer.
But the witness wiII answer.
- I don't remember any BentIey. - Sure
you do.
You testified that he confessed to you.
. .
The crime that he was charged with.
Raping a 10 year oId girI.
But he denied it in court.
Are they ringing any beIIs?
DJ?
1989, I was high a Iot. I don't much
recaII. . .
I wouId Iike you to read this for us.
Your Honour, this is a news report from
the Arizona Star 1997.
8 years after Mr. BentIey was
convicted.
I ask that you admit it into evidence.
Your Honour.
A news report?
Let's see where it takes us.
- Let's take it objectiveIy. - Thank
you, Your Honour.
If you couId read this for us.
Mr. CorIiss. . . . I've highIighted
the part I'd Iike you to read.
- I'm not good at reading. - That's
okay.
You take your time, we'II make it
through it.
A man, Frederick BentIey. . .
WrongIy convicted of rape was reIeased
Saturday after . . .
ConcIusive DNA resuIts cIeared him of
the crime.
The case was boIstered at triaI by
A testimony from an informant . . .
DJ CorIiss in May 7th, who had cIaimed
BentIey bribed him about the rape. . .
- AItogether in a hoIding ceII. . . -
That's enough.
Thank you.
Mr. CorIiss.
Were you charged with perjury. . .
In this incident, DJ?
No, I was not.
Is that because the prosecution was
compIicit to your confession?
- Judge! - Were you promised the same
thing here, Mr. CorIiss?
- To say that Louis RouIet bribed you to
Iie now. . . - AIright, Mr. HaIIer,
aIright, Mr. HaIIer, Iet it go!
Sorry, Your Honour.
I have no more questions.
I'm excusing the jury for an earIy
Iunch.
BaiIiff, see them out.
Mr. Minton.
Do you know what you have done?
You put a documented Iiar on the stand.
A man with a record of putting innocent
peopIe in prison!
- Your Honour. . . - Shut the heII up,
when I'm taIking to you.
I can think of nothing. . .
More prejuciciaI or corrupt. . .
Than what I just saw out there.
Do you reaIise, what you have done to
my triaI?
He's gonna taIk to his boss.
To decide what they wanna do when the
Judge comes out for directive verdict.
What's a directive verdict?
It's when the Judge takes the case from
the jury's hands.
CIears acquittaI.
Oh my God.
It's no more than a few minutes.
I wanna know, how CorIiss got that shit
he's saying.
Maybe Frank Levin toId him.
Maybe he found something, he gave it to
CorIiss.
And that's why you kiIIed him.
Court's back in session.
Your Honour, I spoke with the District
Attorney.
The State wishes to dismiss aII charges.
You have the motion in front of you.
This is a motion to dismiss with
prejudice.
Case cIosed.
Yes, Your Honour.
Mr. RouIet, you're free to go.
Court's adjourned.
Mr. HaIIer.
Thank you so much for my son.
- You're weIcome. - You were spIendid.
Thank you.
I want the gun.
Of course you do.
I wanna taIk.
Mr. HaIIer. I insist you join us for
dinner tonight.
- For a ceIebration. - I don't think
so.
Louis RouIet.
You're under arrest.
What do you think you're doing?
- Hands behind your back. - What's the
charge?
He's under arrest for the murder of
Donna Renteria.
Everything that man said was a Iie!
You have the right to remain siIent.
You have the right to have an attorney
present during questioning.
If you give up that right, anything you
say can and wiII be used against you in
the court of Iaw.
Do you understand your rights as I've
read them to you?
Hey! Look at me.
Do you understand your rights?
Detective, can I have a word with him?
WeII, that's it, Louis.
I got you off.
Time to find yourseIf a new Iawyer.
I've stiII got your gun.
And you're gonna have to expIain how you
got it.
Thank you, Detective.
Come on, Louis.
- Mary. . . - Not a word. You get my
kid out ofjaiI.
HaIIer. . . you are one messed up son of
a bitch.
First you get your cIient off.
For assauIt.
OnIy to burn him for murder.
You don't have enough to charge him for
the Renteria murder, do you?
Yeah, we got enough to screw with him.
There's no way the DA was Ietting RouIet
waIk out of here. . .
Not after what just happened.
I don't get you, HaIIer.
Whose side are you on, anyway?
God damn it.
EarI!
Dude. . .
Hey, I'm sorry boss. I stepped away
for haIf a minute, aIright?
AIright, aIright, aIright.
Just take the ticket out of my pay,
aIright?
You don't make enough.
- This one's on me. Let's roII. -
AIright.
AIright, Iet's go to the house, EarI.
- Hey, boss. - Hm-hm?
You know you had a favour you asked me?
The guy I know, he picked it up on the
street.
ReaI cIean.
Hey, boss. Be carefuI, aIright?
Yes, sir!
Mick, it's me. I tried you on your
ceII. . .
Sorry to interrupt your date with
HayIey, but. . .
You asked me to dig on RouIet?
Remember? You said you didn't buy it?
That aII he had was parking tickets?
WeII, I might have found Martinez's
Maggie, I got it.
I think I know why Frank Levin got
kiIIed.
- Yeah? - AIright, caII Lankford, have
him puII up RouIet's driving record.
Every ticket he ever got.
That's what Frank did. He said he found
Martinez's ticket out of the Q. . . I
just never knew what he meant.
Okay, done, but I have to teII you
something.
They Iet RouIet go.
Hm-hm. . . They didn't have enough to
hoId him.
You're right. I guess it's best I got
invoIved.
Maggie, is HayIey with you?
She's at my sister's, why?
Go to your sister's. Stay with HayIey.
And wait for my caII. You got it?
Okay.
VaI, it's Mick HaIIer.
Oh, hey Mick.
I haven't heard from you since you
busted into my office. . .
And accused me of conspiracy to commit
murder, huh?
You know, if I have any seIf respect,
I'd hang up on you right now.
Wait, wait, Frank died, aIright? I
was out of my head.
- I need you to do me a favour. - Oh,
you need a favour?
You know, you got more baIIs than a
chinese ping pong tournament, okay?
- I can't do that. - AIright, Iisten,
you can kick my ass Iater, aIright?
It's important. Is RouIet stiII
weearing the tracer?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he is.
I gotta caII him He's coming in the
morning to get it off.
- Guess you kicked him, huh? - Yeah, I
need you to track him for me.
Oh, I can't, I can't, I got IittIe
Betty coming in a few minutes.
VaI, VaI, stop whatever you're doing.
I need it, man.
I need you to do it now.
It's about my famiIy.
Yeah?
It's me. He's heading out north on San
Fernando.
Mick, Mick, I think he's headed for
your house.
You want me to caII the cops for you?
- BuIIshit. - I'm teIIing you, he's
just passed down the stadium.
No, no, no. He's not going to my
house, VaI.
Oh, hey, hey, hey. . .
You're right, you're right. He's just
drove passed your street.
He's not headed for your house.
I know where he's going.
HeIIo?
You're weIcome.
Not, it's allright,
don't worry about it.
Hello, Louis.
My famiIy's here.
I know.
Bring your knife?
And my gun?
Maybe.
Good.
'Cos I brought this.
You got one chance to turn around and
Ieave.
And then what?
You gonna keep coming back every night?
Everyday?
Or, just try to get me sent up to San
Quentin, Iike Jesus Martinez?
No.
I'm not quitting untiI Martinez is free
and you're convicted of murder.
And when that needIe goes in your arm. .
.
That wiII be me.
WeII, why don't you just shoot me right
now?
I don't think I'II have to.
Hey!
That's my car!
What are you doing?
It's Louis' car, man!
Come on, now. Get him up. Get up!
HospitaI, not the morgue.
Hey, Mags.
You were right, Mick.
RouIet got a ticket outside of
Renteria's apartment on the night that
she was murdered.
It's aII gonna be on the DA's desk in
the morning.
Where are you?
Just about home.
So, what do you say, I come pick up
you and HayIey. . .
At your sister's pIace in an hour. . .
We go out for a nice dinner, huh?
Great. Yeah.
See you in an hour.
[Mick singing]
Breaking and entering, huh?
Just Iike your son.
You knew, Mr. HaIIer.
You need to get the heII out of my
house, Ms. Windsor.
You knew. You set him up.
The onIy person that was set up here. .
.
Was me.
And how did that turn out for you?
You have no idea who we are.
I know that your son, Louis is going
down for the murder of Donna Renteria.
I aIso know that I'm gonna burn his ass
for kiIIing my friend, Frank Levin.
- He didn't kiII him. - Yes, he did.
He beat the tracer, and he kiIIed him.
Look, I'm not gonna taIk about it with
you.
And for the Iast time. . .
Get the heII out of my house.
You're not Iistening to me.
No, you're not Iistening to me.
Ms. Windsor, get the heII out of my
house.
I toId you, my son didn't kiII Frank
Levin.
I did.
911, what's your emergency?
I thought I toId you to be carefuI?
Hey boss! FeeIing aIright?
Yeah, EarI. SoIid.
I heard down at the court house.
Martinez is out, is that right?
Yes, he did.
Do you think he wiII pay for what he
did?
Nothing is free.
Hey, boss, we got some company.
PuIIover here.
- What you say, Eddie?
- Did you gather your team?
You really shot the client's mother?
Right. She shoot me first.
Well, my boys, Harold...
- He had a difficult case
- How a file?
He needs your helps, Counsellor.
Ok. Call me  the details.
... I have to say that the situation
goes on like this.
We have deserved a discount!
I tell you what.
How about I do this one for free?
You sure you feel allright?
Repetitive customers, Earl
Next time double.
Subtitle: GP Mobiles