Simply Releases Toppers
Simply The Best
Proudly Presents Toy Story 3
Translated by Simply Releases Toppers
Tokke, and Biteme Suurtje
Money, money.
You have a date with justice.
- Sorry, Sheriff ...
I am married.
And eye-pirate?
You dropped something.
Give it up, your end is near.
I always wanted to
end with a bang.
No!
- The orphans!
I do not want to leave early,
but our ride is here.
It's me or the children. Choose.
Ride like the wind.
Keep quiet.
Woody, hurry up.
No ...
But I can catch the train.
- Now some catching criminals.
Infinity and beyond.
Reach for the sky.
- You can not make me.
I brought my attack dog
with a force field.
And I eat my dinosaur
that force fields.
Malicious Pig.
That evil Doctor Mr Pig.
Buzz, shoot your laser on my badge.
- No, I will kill you.
Just do it.
You go to jail. Watch out.
Mom!
- Do go if I am not there.
No, Molly ...
- It's okay.
A baby of 1.5 meters from space.
And she tramples everything.
Run for your lives!
The red light means
that it works?
Say happy birthday to Molly.
Happy birthday.
- Charming.
Look how big you are.
Buzz Light year to rescue.
Good job.
Everyone in position.
- I think my other eye.
Whose foot is in my face
- my, give back.
You saved our lives.
We are eternally grateful.
Buzz, do you mind if I
sit down next to you?
Yes, no, why should I care?
It's hot here.
- Here they come.
Sergeant, did you?
- Mission completed.
Careful.
Guys, we have a chance.
Everybody ready?
- Ready. Ahead with it.
Buzz, make the call.
Target's move.
Just as we practiced.
Hello, is anyone there?
Molly, stay out of my room.
- I am not there.
Anyone who has sat on my stuff
- I do not.
That went well.
- He held me really down.
This is bad.
- He is 17 years.
There is no longer
with us played.
Guys, we do a meeting.
Not again.
- Get everyone together.
We're together, Woody.
We all knew that surgery
was a gamble Runtime.
More a failure.
- It is not about
to be played ...
But to be there for Andy.
We know that.
We can try again, right?
I termination, boys. We stop it.
Andy goes to college soon.
This was our last chance.
We go to the attic.
Keep your tools close.
Spare parts, batteries ...
everything for a little
transition period.
Transition? We have been there.
We knew this day was
coming there.
Yes, but now he is.
- Any toy that goes.
What are you doing?
- The war is over.
We will fight elsewhere.
- Elsewhere?
Absent without leave
- we have our duty.
Andy is grown.
And come and face ...
and trash bags upstairs,
we are first in.
Dirt Bags
- Who said anything about that?
It was an honor to fight with you.
Good luck.
That will you need.
- No, wait.
Are we disposed of
- No, no.
How do you know
- we are left behind.
It's good, Jessie.
- Why do they then departed.
Should we leave
- we went not to the attic?
I hate this uncertainty.
- Wait. Just silence.
No one is thrown away.
We're all still here.
We lost a couple indeed ...
Wheezy and Etch.
- Bo Peep.
Yes, even Bo.
All good toys for new owners.
But at every garage sale
each spring cleaning ...
Andy loved us.
He must care about us
if we were not here.
Andy brings us nice snug
and safe in the attic.
And we are all together.
- Exactly.
There are games and books there.
- Racetrack circuit.
Thank you.
- And the old TV.
Voila, the old TV.
And those guys from
the Christmas tree.
These are also great, right?
On one day, with luck, Andy
himself has children.
And then he plays
with us, right?
We will always be there for him.
- Come ...
Let our parts and take
a trip to go.
I do my best for another.
- Where did you this time?
A dark and dusty.
Let's see what price
we get on eBay.
Andy makes sure for us.
It assures them, h
- I do not know, Buzz.
What else can I say?
We are all means
always together.
To infinity and beyond.
I get your stereo?
- No.
I get your computer
Your video games
- forget it, Molly.
Andy, let us begin.
Everything you do not bring ...
or go to the attic,
or in the trash.
I leave Friday only.
- It afvaldag.
It's simple.
Skateboard: College.
Little League trophy.
Maybe attic.
Clocks House: Waste.
The rest is up to you.
- Why did you have?
Molly, my room.
- Still three days
and it's mine.
You'll also still work.
You have more toys
than you can play.
They can make other
children happy.
Which children
- one from the crche.
They always ask for donations.
- What is that?
No buts, choose what you want
to donate and I put them off.
Ocharme, Barbie.
- I get a corvette.
Andy, make decisions.
Like
- what you going to do this.
Donate to Sunnyside?
Maybe sell online?
Mom, nobody would want them.
They are waste.
- You have until Friday.
Everything is not wrapped,
or attic ...
is thrown away.
- Whatever.
What happens
- we dispose idiot.
Need some help
- I got it.
Will you miss me when I'm gone?
If I say no, will I still
have your room?
No.
- Yes, then.
I can not breathe.
- This is not true.
Still, what's that sound?
Andy.
That is not a waste.
Remember, Woody.
Buster, come here.
Boy, the steps.
No, Buster. No.
Stand up.
We stand on the sidewalk.
- I knew it.
Everybody pulling.
It will not slip.
It is of polyethylene.
There must be a way out.
- Andy is not. What's the point?
Point, point!
Push!
- I hear the dustcart.
It comes closer.
Buzz. Jessie.
Andy threw us away.
- He called our waste.
How could he?
It succeeds at nothing.
- This we should know.
It's just like Emily.
- The sergeant was right.
Woody and wrong.
- Wait. Not hysterical.
Since it is the perfect time.
- Be hysterical.
Maybe, but not now.
I know what to do.
What?
This we have done years ago.
- What about Woody?
He's okay, Buzz. Andy takes him.
We gotta go.
You're right. Forward.
Buzz, what's going on?
That box is given.
Everything under control. We have a plan.
- We go to the crche.
Are you crazy?
Andy was our disposal.
- No, he wanted you
in the attic.
How did we put on the sidewalk
- a mistake.
Andy's Mom found your waste.
- Andy put us in a garbage bag.
And called our waste.
- You gotta believe me.
Of course, high school boy.
- Andy moves on, Woody.
We must do the same.
From the box immediately.
Buzzy help me, this thing should be ...
- Woody, wait.
We must do what is
best for everyone.
Great, it takes forever
to get back.
It's okay, Barbie.
Gonna be okay.
Molly and I were together
for years.
I can not believe they throw me.
Welcome to the club.
- Listen ...
we need to go back to Andy.
We hide under the seat us ...
- Let it move you.
He does not want us anymore.
- He put you in the attic!
He left us behind on the sidewalk.
- Both, calm.
Wait until you see how the crche is.
- What is it?
A sad, lonely place for
old toys with no owner.
You may well comfort.
- You'll see when
we get there ...
begging you to return.
Does anyone?
- There is a playground.
We have the prize.
- So far sad and lonely.
Keep this in perspective.
- Perspective?
This place is perfect.
- It is very beautiful.
There is a rainbow at the door.
Hi, there.
- That's a long time ago.
I wanted toys this issue.
Is that Bonnie?
Look how big you already are.
- Say hello, baby.
Hello.
- How are your children?
These are not kids anymore.
Andy goes to college.
Can you believe it
- they do not miss them?
No, it is never played.
Do you see any children?
- Where are they us?
Look.
- What?
I see nothing.
Outside playtime.
What do we do now?
- Back to Andy.
Does anyone out
- who want an exit.
Let them play with us.
- The other toys can be jealous.
I want to see. It's my turn.
New toys!
Hi, nice.
- Buzz Light year
to your service.
Thank you. May I?
The gripper.
Hi, there.
I thought all new voices.
Welcome to Sunnyside.
I Lotso the bear, but
call me Lotso.
Buzz Light year, we come in ...
What you should know about me
is that I am a knuffelaar.
You seem to have been
through a lot.
Horrible.
- Now you are safe.
We are all cast-offs.
Dumped, given ...
garage sales and second hand.
You will discover that this is the
best thing you could happen.
Mr. Lotso, they play here
every day with toys?
All day. Five days a week.
What if the children grow up
- I'll tell you.
When they get old, there
will be new to.
If they are old, replace
them new.
You never outgrow them,
or never left ...
or forgotten.
No owners, no means
broken heart.
A miracle.
- And you wanted to keep Andy.
Because we are his toys.
- You were given by him, h?
It's his loss. He can not hurt.
Let your place.
... Ken where is that boy. Ken!
New toys.
- So there.
Who is ready for Ken's
dream tour?
Show them where they reside.
- If you want to go here ...
I'm Ken.
- Barbie.
Have we met?
- I would not know.
I love your legwarmers.
- Beautiful Ascot.
Come on, Ken. Break does not last forever.
- This way, everyone.
You have a good prospect.
They love new toys.
What a nice bear.
- It smells like strawberries.
Here we have all but
demands toys.
Spare parts, super glue,
and a lot of batteries.
If you think getting
old, stop worrying.
Our Beer SPA keep brand new.
I live here.
Ken his dream house.
With a disco, a Dune Buggy.
And a room for clothes to fit.
You have everything.
- Everything except
someone to share.
If you need anything, ask me.
We are al
Thank you, Big Baby.
Meet our new friends.
Poor baby, we are
thrown together.
Abandoned by the same owner.
But here are not necessary ...
we live in ourselves.
Our own masters.
Our own destiny.
Watch out for Puddles.
You stay here.
The Caterpillar Room.
Watch this space again.
The prize.
Hello.
- Hello.
It is so beautiful.
What?
H, baby.
How long ago was it that was
played there with you?
Years ago.
- Wait ...
a few minutes, that bubble,
and are you dreams.
Really play. I can not wait.
If you would excuse us,
we go back best.
Welcome to Sunnyside.
- Thank you. Bye.
I'll see again
- I see you tonight.
In my dreams.
- Ken, a quick bit.
Barbie, come with me
to my dream home.
I know we only know each other.
You do not know me
from GI Joe ...
but when I look at you ... it seems
- if we made for each other?
Yes
- I'm coming, Lotso.
I'm so excited.
That seems to me children.
- I want to be played ...
Why does time slow.
- How many are there?
I admit that this is fun.
But we must go home.
- Here we have a new life.
A chance to return children happy.
- Why do not you?
Yes, stay.
- Come on.
It is played.
- No, guys. No.
We all have a child. Andy.
And if he wants us at the high
school, or in the attic ...
we should be there for him.
I'm going home.
Everyone should accompany me.
Come on, Buzz.
Our mission is completed
with Andy.
What?
- We must stay together.
Without Andy, we were
not together.
Look at your shoe, you too Jessie,
what name is on it?
Perhaps Andy does not care about us.
- Of course. To us all.
I saw that he wanted to put you in the attic.
Times now not turn
your back on him.
Wake up. It's over.
Andy is grown.
Well, that's perfect.
How selfish of you.
So this is it end?
After everything we've
been through?
No, Bullseye, you must continue.
No, I said stay.
I do not want you just
sitting in the attic.
Stay.
Bonnie.
I gotta go.
Bonnie, are you here?
Come on ... No, no.
What is that?
That's better.
Bonnie! There you are.
Come on, time to go home.
No, no ...
Reach for the sky.
Inne, love, moe ...
You're my favorite deputy.
Bonnie!
- I'm coming.
Great.
Everything will be fine.
- Woody goes along with Andy.
As he always wanted.
- He's crazy.
College is no place for toys.
- These serve as gaming.
Buzz talking about gaming.
They are insisting.
How much?
- A lot.
I can hardly wait.
- In position.
I am a first time played.
... Rex
- Come to daddy.
There's a snake in my boot.
I would like to your party, but
first I am singing a song.
A sheriff!
On the side, Mr..
Pricklepants. We have a guest.
Would you like coffee?
It is good for you, but not
too much, otherwise you ...
Do you ... I'll be back.
Hello, excuse me.
Where am I?
- He asks only slightly.
Excuse me, I want to
stay in my role.
My name is Buttercup.
Baron von Sush know you al
Hi, I'm Trixie.
I do not know where I am.
- Or a café in Paris ...
or a tavern in New Jersey.
I just come from the doctor ...
with life-changing news.
- Just have fun ...
I will take.
- No, no ...
Who wants to Sludge?
A secret ingredients.
Jelly Beans.
Someone has poisoned the water hole.
- Poisoned?
Who does anything in common?
The terrifying witch. Watch out.
She used her witch powers.
I know a shelter.
They never find us here.
What is wrong?
They found us.
We must have a spaceship,
to escape from the witch.
You're doing great.
- Are you classically trained?
How do I get out of here
- there is no way out.
Joke, the door is over there.
- You jumped right in there.
I'm Dolly.
- Woody.
Are you serious?
You can change him,
and so new room.
And that says a doll
named Dolly.
Who's new?
- Are you a real cowboy?
Actually ...
- Of course not.
He even has a hat.
- That I have ...
My hat.
- There you go.
I found a spaceship.
- Showtime.
Fast, inside. Straps, sheets up.
Hang on, it can be bumpy.
Three, two, n, up.
You saved us, you're our hero.
I have pain in my side.
Where's my tail?
Someone need a hand?
Where's my nose?
- Here.
Here's your arm.
Where's my mustache?
I remember not playing.
Andy z never played with us.
- We make the most of it.
Toddlers who do not know how to play.
- They are too young.
And they're sticky.
- We have been in the
Butterfly House.
With the big kids.
- That is correct.
I'm going to talk to
Lotso us to move.
Damn, try that.
Closed.
- Here, too.
Try the windows.
- Negative.
It is a Snekler 380.
Dear child protection ever.
We're trapped.
- Viel someone on the skylight?
How do we get there?
Everyone, I count to three.
And ... two
- three!
Release.
Forward.
He has succeeded.
Good job, Buzz.
They had a nice gaming
- Silent, They'll hear you.
You start.
- I ...
Keep ...
- From you.
Now I want to finish it all.
First.
I ...
- Hou ...
Yours.
- See, it always works.
You are so smart.
- Come on, Romeo.
I'm going to miss you.
Come on.
There we go.
- Come on.
No more money there.
Point to here.
- On the duck.
That's a duck.
- Won!
The last round.
- You're lost.
Minimum bid: 5 monopoly.
Wild coyote.
Exchange of triple aces.
What do you think of the
new 'here to stay?
Please.
- Cowgirl?
Dinosaur
- Small toddler.
But that space guy.
It can be useful.
He is not the sharpest knife in the
place where they keep the knives.
Yes, you.
You have one myself, right?
Calm, Twitch.
Barbie is different.
- Hear the weakling.
What do you expect to show girls toy
- I'm not a girl toy!
Why do you say?
- All that is disposable toys.
We are lucky if they
survive one week.
Look who's here.
Let me go.
- Take him to the library.
No!
1225 Sycamore.
Woody, what are you doing?
I gotta get outta here.
- Going?
But you did not enjoy
- yes, more than in years.
I belong to someone else.
- Who is Yitna?
It is pronounced Yitn.
- It says Andy.
He is my Bonnie.
And he leaves soon.
I gotta get home.
- Where is that?
Elm Street, 2304 Elm.
Do you have a map?
- Doing. Trixie.
I start the computer.
Loosen, cowards.
Lotso I want to speak.
Quiet, Buck Rogers.
You speak with Lotso
when we say ...
Know what's going on?
Why is that toy-related?
He had escaped.
- Escaped?
No, not if we treat our guests.
I never do. See that. I am sorry
Lotso, there is a mistake.
- A mistake?
The kids in the Caterpillar
Room are too young for us.
We respectfully request a transfer
to the Butterfly House.
Request.
- But Lotso ...
Silence. He shows initiative.
Leadership. This is a keeper.
Heard? A keeper.
We bring you the bigger.
From now you get
verything you want.
Perfect, I get my friends.
- Wait, Buzz.
Caterpillars Children
who have little toy.
My friends are not there.
- None of us.
I do agree, therefore,
for our community ...
let the new toys for the rough
work to do for the elderly.
That seems to be correct.
But I can not accept.
A family stays together.
A family man, h. Why do not you?
Back in the chair break.
Let me go.
Send Bookworm inside.
That's it. Misplaced.
Let's see.
Tools, Maintenance ...
Remove the screws to the
battery to arrive.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Your Buzz Light year action figure back
to his original creation to bring ...
slide the button over
the 'Play' to 'Demo'.
Stop! No, no.
What was that?
- Sounds from the beginning
to take off.
I will look.
See something?
- No, it's dark.
Wait, I'm Andy.
- What?
That is impossible.
- I really see him.
In his room. My other eye!
I've left behind.
This is so strange. He grabs at.
This is Buster. On the side.
Andy is in the corridor.
He looks in the attic.
There's Mommy.
Why is he so angry?
This is terrible.
He searches and searches for us.
He seeks us
- Andy wants us now.
I just knew.
- He wished us well
in the attic.
Woody would tell the truth.
- You did not believe him.
You first.
- We need to go home.
Lotso.
- How are you tonight?
Thank God, you've seen Buzz
- We gotta go.
Way? You have a pass.
Recently we had no more volunteers
for the toddlers.
They like so many new toys.
Love?
There has been chewed on
us, kicked, gekwijld ...
Just look at my pocket book.
The thing is, sweet potato,
you do not leave Sunnyside.
Sweet potato?
Who do you think you 't you?
I have over 30 tools, and I
deserve more respect ...
That's better.
Nobody takes my wife's
mouth off, except me.
Give back, hairy air freshener.
We're going home, guys.
- You not going anywhere.
Who is against us?
Buzz, you're back. Buzz?
Watch out.
Caught inoperative,
commander Lotso.
What are you doing?
- Silence.
You are captured by the Galactic Alliance.
- Galactic Alliance?
Well done, Light year.
Lock them up.
Yes, sir.
Where are you going?
We are your friends.
- Spare me your lies.
Your emperor is defeated and I am immune
to your charming good looks.
Stay away from my wife.
Let me go, slobbering idiot.
- He's not.
This potato ways to learn.
Take him to the box.
- Put me down, you idiot.
Where are you taking me to?
Naughty baby.
Ken, what's going on?
- Barbie.
You would be the dream
home waiting.
What are you doing with my friends
- you go.
Wait, Barbie.
- Do not touch me.
It's over.
- Barbie, I ...
Give back my scarf.
Light year, explain where they sleep.
- Yes, sir.
Prisoners sleep in their cells.
Anyone who plays his cell,
sleeping in the box.
Appl between sunrise and sunset,
If a prisoner appl misses
sleeps in the box.
Prisoners say nothing, to
something they said.
If a prisoner talk back ... he sleeps
- in the box.
Understood.
At ease, soldier.
They are neutralized.
Remember, they will say anything,
so you start to doubt yourself.
Do not worry, sir doubt
that I had ...
is from the academy beaten me.
We do things here
in Sunnyside so.
If you start bottom, pay your debts,
life can be great here.
If you our complications
on the writing goes ...
rather tries to leave, then
you hurt yourself.
Woody, what have you done with him
- but you sleep good.
Tomorrow you have a
whole day to play.
1225 Syca ...
Who is Velocistar237?
This is a toy dinosaur from the street.
That's nothing. I rule here.
Only a dinosaur.
Sycamore. Enter.
Please do not be far away.
It's just around the corner.
Look at me, I'm big toys.
I see you on the Saka.
If you ever get the crche
of Sunnyside ...
say that Woody has come home.
- Did you in Sunnyside?
How did you escape?
- That was not easy.
What do you mean, escape?
Sunnyside is a place of destruction
and despair.
Managed by a bad bear, which
smells like strawberries.
Lotso
- Fluffy and cuddly
on the outside ...
inside he is a monster.
- How do you know?
Chuckles will tell you.
I've known Lotso.
He was good toys. A friend.
We had the same child. Daisy.
I was there when Lotso
was extracted.
Daisy loved us all.
But Lotso was special.
They did everything together.
I've never seen a child in love
and toys were on display.
One day we went riding.
On a stopover to play some.
After lunch Daisy fell asleep.
She never came back.
Lotso did not give up.
It took an eternity, but finally
we were at Daisy.
But then it was too late.
let's change that
day inside Lotso.
Something snapped.
- They replaced us.
Come on.
- She just replace you.
No, all of us.
They do not love you.
Come on.
We were lost. Discarded.
Unloved, not wanted.
Then we found Sunnyside.
But Lotso was my friend anymore.
He was nobody's friend.
He took on Sunnyside, and threw
it down whole system.
How did you get it out?
- I was broke.
Bonnie found me and took me home.
Other toys were not so lucky.
It's not what Lotso done,
new toy has no chance.
My friends are there.
- You can not go back.
Now go back is suicide.
- And You then Andy?
He never went to school?
Silence, music pig. Stop it.
I miss Woody too.
But he will never come back.
All wake up.
- Commander, Lotso, sir.
All quiet, nothing to report.
- Fine, Light year.
We need you at 'command to space needed.
- What have you done
with my husband?
Big Baby.
Honey.
It was cold and dark.
Nothing but sand and a couple
of "Lincoln Logs".
I think those were not
"Lincoln Logs".
Get it done.
There is a matchday
with destiny.
You could not have come back, cowboy.
They are nice rage gone
since you left.
More guards, more patrols.
You and your friends will
never get out here now.
I am already once released.
- You're a lucky time.
My advice? Keep your head down.
You survive it.
- Yeah, how long?
I've been here for years.
They never break me.
These are toys but n way away.
Poor guy.
Morning, the garbage truck.
Then go to the landfill.
- I appreciate your concern.
A child is waiting for
us, so we go away.
If you help us, one of the other
toys, I am very grateful to you.
If you want out, you have got
to get through the doors.
Every night locked.
On the inside and outside.
The keys hang from a hook in the office.
- Roger. What else?
The car of Lotso driving
around all night.
The hall, the lobby, the playground ...
- And the wall?
2.5 meters high.
Brick wall.
You can not get through.
You go over or lies underneath.
It all seems so very bad.
- That it is not.
Your real problem is the monkey.
The monkey is the eye in the sky.
He sees everything.
Classrooms ...
corridors.
Even the playground.
He can open doors, sneaking
past guards ...
climbing over the wall, if you
do not shut that monkey ...
you go nowhere.
Would you come here?
Touch the monkey than lost.
Pause. Come on, kids.
Boys.
- Woody?
You're still alive.
- Of course.
My hat. Where's Buzz?
Lotso has something to do with him.
- He thinks he 's a real
space ranger is.
No.
- Yes, the return of
astronomical idiot.
We had Andy not to leave.
I was wrong.
Jessie is right. She was wrong.
No, it's my fault that
I am with you gone.
From now on, we stay together.
But, Andy goes to school.
School.
You must go home before
Andy leaves tomorrow.
Tomorrow? That means ...
- that we break.
Tonight.
- Impossible.
You can not get out.
- That may be.
But n away.
Slinky Dog
- Present.
Green boys. Cowboy girl.
Here.
- Horse?
Piggy Bank.
- Yes.
Tyranosaurus
- Here.
Barbie
Potato Head?
Super Troopman, wake up.
Impossible.
Bit late for a walk,
Potato Head?
That's Mr. Potato Head to you.
- You have to show a mouth full.
You Ascot bearing pink nose.
You're not a toy.
You're a tool.
You're an inflated ball.
Take him to the box.
- No, not the box.
I'm sorry, I did not mean it.
I love the Ascot.
I'm going to look.
- Well done, Light year.
Continue with your space thing.
- Thank you.
Yes, sir, mature man.
Ken?
What do you want?
- I love it any more here.
I want to go to the Butterfly House.
With you.
There was yesterday to remember.
- I was wrong.
I want with yours.
In your dream house.
Please come get me here.
Good.
But things are complicated.
You must do what I say.
- I promise you.
I'll do anything.
I Excuse your diapers.
Grab the tape.
And here the magic happens.
Take all your clothes again.
That me would never
have brought to it.
Tennis Apparel.
- Check this out.
Kung Fu fighting, Canvas Hero
with a sports pennant.
Flower Power.
Nobody appreciates
garments here.
Nobody.
- Do you want to show off
a few items of clothing?
But a few.
Where is the key.
Gotcha.
What do you do.
Stay away from my stuff.
Come on, Porky.
Not fighting. Stop.
You can not hit each other.
That's my job.
Prison uprising.
Remove the tortilla.
Ready
- Ready.
Barbie?
No more games.
Lotso What has done with Buzz?
How we put it back
- you can not let me talk.
I wish that you tried.
Let's see. Hawaiian swimwear.
Barbie, which was an original.
Go ahead.
There are still plenty of.
Glitter tuxedo.
Who cares. It was still common.
A Negro jacket.
- Not the Negro jacket.
This is 1976?
The Groofy collection, yes.
- What a shame.
No.
There is a manual.
Lotso Buzz has put in demo mode.
- Where's the manual?
Why could not wait until tomorrow?
Please.
Why does it take so long?
How can we make Buzz again?
What are you looking at?
Fly away, coward.
Great.
Give it up. No one can hear you.
What
- No one can hear you.
What?
- He said, 'nobody can' ...
Silence. Woody, you're back.
Stop him. Let him not.
- I am hostage to
my own prisoners.
Fast. There is a switch on his back.
- Let me go, rig.
The Galactic court has
no mercy with you.
Why does not it?
Where's the manual?
There's gotta be a small hole under the switch.
- A small hole. Found.
Reset your Buzz Light year
by a paper clip in ...
Use your finger.
- What now?
Hold the button down
but five seconds.
It's my fault.
Starlog, I'm awakened from hyper
sleep on a strange planet.
What have you done?
- What you've told me.
I am surrounded by
unknown creatures.
Friend or foe.
We're all friends.
I must have crashed, and
my memory is erased.
Has anyone seen my spaceship?
- We have to restore.
How do we do?
- This piece is in Spanish.
We have no time. Come on, El Buzzo.
- My ship has landed well.
Good luck, cowboy.
Here they come.
Buzz?
What took you so long
- it was complicated.
Where's Potato Head
- Not seen.
Buzz.
My desert flower.
Have you made Buzz?
- Something.
Behind you. There is someone.
You do not believe what I've
been through tonight.
Is everything okay?
- I feel fresh and healthy.
It's awful.
- You are dropped.
And so big.
You are beautiful to see
for detachable eyes.
All safe.
Come on.
We're almost there.
Backwards.
Come on.
Miss, you are the prettiest
flower in the room.
And together we fight the evil.
Woody.
We're almost there.
- After it.
Push me up.
Buzz Light year comes
to the rescue.
Open.
- Well done, Buzz. Come on.
Is it safe?
- Where do I find out.
Woody, are you okay?
- Yeah, come on down.
Not all at once.
- What did he say?
In my opinion, all at once.
- No.
Thanks.
- You're welcome.
We're almost there.
- Slink, you think you make it?
I may be old, I can still jump.
Succeeded.
- All right, Slink.
Climb over it.
Are you lost, little dog?
Look who's back.
I'm sorry, cowboy.
They have broken me.
What do you all?
Back to your child at the races?
He wants you anymore.
- You're lying.
Is that so? Tell me again ...
if your child loves you,
why is he leaving?
Think you're special?
You're a piece of plastic ...
made to throw away.
When you talk about the devil.
We have toys in our Butterfly
House needed ...
and you must avoid the truck.
Come back to our family back.
This is not a family but a prison.
You are a liar and
a bully beast.
I prefer to rot away in the garbage
truck than your family to come.
Jessie is right.
Authority to obtain
consent by ...
not by threat of force.
If that's what you want.
Wait, Barbie.
Do not do this, Lotso.
She is a Barbie doll.
If there are one
hundred million.
For me.
Well, go even towards them.
Sunnyside can be great when
we see each other fairly.
Lotso has a pyramid made us,
and stands on top of itself.
Does anyone agree with Ken?
I have not thrown away, that
your child has done.
They do not really like that toy, but when
you chew it in the garbage truck is.
Wait. And then Daisy?
I do not know what you're talking about.
- Daisy.
You did everything with her.
Then she gave us discarded.
- No, it's your loss.
She has replaced us.
- She replace you.
If you could not have her,
then no one could.
You have lied to Big Baby, and
you've lied all this time.
Where did you get that
- she loved you, Lotso.
She never loved me.
- So many toys as
a child can love.
Do you want your mom back? She never loved you.
Do not be a baby.
Push them all in there.
This happens when you try
to think of Dumbo's.
We all waste that will
be discarded.
This is just a toy.
Stop. Put me down, you idiot.
No, wait. Baby, wait.
He's gone.
- Holy shit.
Hurry.
Please.
- Come on.
Woody.
Since there is n.
Come on.
No, Barbie.
Woody.
No.
Can you hear me?
Is everything okay?
Of course not, idiot.
We're doomed.
Everyone at Buzz far.
Are we all? Slinky. Rex?
Against the wall. Quickly.
- Miss, where are you?
That they never get.
Watch out.
Has anyone seen him
- I found him.
Is everything okay?
That I was not
- You're back.
Yes, I'm back.
Where have I been?
Beyond infinity, space ranger.
Where are we now.
- The garbage truck, heading
for the dustbin.
We go there.
Have all your parts?
My babies.
- No, guys.
No.
Hold on.
What should we do
- it'll be fine if
we stick together.
It is a magnet. Watch out.
No worries, Slink.
We'll get you well down.
I see it from here.
Grab something from solid metal.
You heard him.
It does not work.
Help me. I'm trapped.
Help me.
Thanks.
- Not thank me now.
Hurry.
Thank you, Sheriff.
We are all here together.
However, boys?
Boys
- Woody, we're down here.
I see daylight. We manage.
That is no daylight.
Run.
Sheriff, the button. Help me.
Come on.
Press the button.
Hurry.
Press it.
Where is your child
now, Sheriff?
No.
- Lotso.
What should we do?
All those nasty things I said
about Andy's attic ...
I take it all back.
- I.
What you say.
Honey, you were so brave.
You saved our lives.
- And we are eternally grateful.
My boys.
- Dad.
Where is Lotso? That hairball?
I would like to loose
or stabbing.
Forget it, guys.
He is not worth it.
What have you got?
- If n I had as a child.
Strawberries.
Keep your mouth shut.
Woody, we need you to get home.
- It was a schoolboy.
And you? I mean ...
Perhaps the attic
not a great idea.
We're Andy's toys.
- We will for him.
Together.
If he had not gone.
- Wait. I look here.
Andy is still packing.
But he is almost ready.
He lives on the other side of town.
- We're never on time.
Come on, Buster.
- Honey, you have everything?
Still a few boxes, Mom.
- Come on!
The coast is safe.
Since you already had!
This is not goodbye.
Woody, great fun.
- Yes, but not to much.
Woody, take good care of Andy.
- He's a good guy ...
but he must have a haircut.
- Will do.
Will you save it in the attic
- Of course not ...
In addition, I know how
to put Buzz in Spanish.
My what?
You know where to
find us, cowboy?
Have you already said goodbye Molly
- At least ten times.
Mom, it's all good.
I wish I could stay
with you always.
That you will too.
Buster you gonna say goodbye?
Of course. Who is a good dog?
Pack your stuff.
- Buster, Molly lets
not get my stuff.
Mom, do you really think
I should donate it?
That you have to know sweetie.
Whatever you want.
Do NOT go inside the haunted
in the bakery.
Are you crazy, you still
raises the spirits.
Watch out, the ghosts
throwing pies.
Andy? See you at this.
Going to high school
- yes, at this time.
What can we do for you
- I have some toys.
You hear that, Bonnie
- Bonnie So you're ...
I'm Andy.
Someone told me that you
can play very well.
These were mine, but
since I go ...
I am looking for someone
who is very special ...
to playing with them.
This is Jesse's the toughest in
the entire western cowgirl ...
she loves "critters", but not without
her best friend Bullseye.
Look.
This is Rex, the meanest, most terrible
dinosaur that ever was.
Potato Heads.
Mr. and mevouw. Keep them well together,
because they are in love.
And Slinky, is the most loyal
dog you could ever imagine.
Hamm, saves you money ...
but, he is the biggest crook you
know, bad doctor Pork Chop.
And these youngsters come from a strange
alien planet, Planet Pizza.
And this is Buzz Light year,
the coolest toy ever ...
look, he can fly and
shoot laser ...
He has sworn to protect the area
against the evil Emperor Zurg.
To infinity and beyond.
You must promise to look
after them well ..
they mean a lot to me.
My cowboy?
Woody? What is he doing here?
There's a snake in my boot.
Woody is my friend so long
I can remember ...
He is brave, as it
is for cowboys ...
and sweet and smart, but what
Woody is really special ...
He will never leave, never!
He will be there for you
through thick and thin.
Would you care for him?
Okay.
Doctor Pork Chop is
the ghost bakery.
The ghosts are leaving,
she will stop Woody.
Buzz Light year will save them.
Thanks, guys.
Look mom, they all
play together.
Come on, let's go eat.
See ya, buddy.
Translated by Simply Releases Toppers Tokke, and Biteme
Suurtje Downloaded from www.simplyreleases.com