Be good.
- Bye.
Have fun.
- Where can I find Frank Barnes?
- Sir?
Frank Barnes.
Good luck.
Thanks.
Excuse me, I'm looking for Frank Barnes.
I'm here.
I Will Colson. 'Ll Work together today
the train 1206.
- 1206?
- Yes, that's.
- That, and your papers?
- Yes. Want to take a look?
How you doing?
Is there a problem?
No problem. I just don't like
working in a damn daycare center.
Yes ...
No I do not like to work
a home for retirees.
All right.
I'll tell you WHAT I'll Finish my coffee
and meet you on the wagon.
Sound's good.
- 1206.
- Yes, that's the one.
You know it's union, right?
I heard they made him a shop steward.
Contact the ETU.
From the first year?
Hell, you know how he got hired.
Name's Colson.
His two uncles are running
things over at Thornwood.
And his older brother is the chief Deacon.
The whole family's from Stanton.
No wonder.
Ya know they shitcan guys everyday. Ya got
the right last name and rookie's paygrade...
you got a job.
What the hell are these guys doing?
Dewey. Elise.
Sorry to break up charm school.
What the hell is that beast still
doing on the D16?
I told you I need that track clear.
Relax, Manny, w're just about to move that.
Like hell you are, my ass.
We have 150 schools students coming on a
field trip on D16, I need that track clear.
D-10's clear, you can set it there.
Okay, you know your lines.
Welcome to the Railroad safety campaign.
We're a program made to educate people like
yourself
about railway safety.
Hey, settle down.
Let's have a show of hands.
Who has ridden a train before?
All right.
All aboard.
So, what's our day?
They got us going on light power
Supposed to pick up 25 cars just passed
Stanton and straight shot to Wilkinson.
Any slow orders?
No.
Are you sure?
Maybe hot I didn't red?
No. No slow orders.
All right.
Dewey, what the hell's
taking you so long?
It's 39 cars, the thing's a half a mile
long, for Christ's sake.
Elise, channel up.
Starts, Dewey.
Do you believe this shit?
Hey, hold up, you forgot to tie in the
air at this point.
Yeah, so?
So, you don't have any air brakes.
Tie the hose once we park
for Inspection.
OK.
I only got one rule.
One rule only.
If you're gonna do something, do it right.
If you do not know how to do it,
you ask me. All right?
Likewise, if you need anything from me
speak up
because ... you're the conductor.
Once we get our freight,
it's your train.
I'm just the guy driving it.
How long you been out of training?
About four months.
- Four months?
- Yeah. Wow.
Full on, you're our
best rookie.
- How long you been railroading?
- 28 years.
November 13, 1981. 28 years.
What did you do before that?
Oh...
I do not know. Bunch of different jobs.
No railroad.
Nah, just uh...
I did something different.
Something different?
What do you mean, something better?
Something ...
- Just different?
- Different.
Dewey, don't want to rush you?
I'd like to eat lunch at some point.
Yes.
Hey.
Your lawyer just called.
You got a break.
The hearing was moved up to this morning.
Looks like we're going home.
That's great, but ...
Did you tell them I was working?
I can't come in.
Yes, yes, yes.
He said no problem.
- It's looking good.
- All right.
Call me an hour to see what's happening.
- I will, Give me a call.
You're ready to pull out or what?
Coming.
All right.
We're leaving.
What's our fuel guages?
- Fuel guage?
- 2900.
2900?
Parking brake released.
Good, good, good.
Bulletins updated.
Revision done, reserves as well.
We are ready to go.
Good. All right.
29 cars, there are 10 to go, you're good.
29 so far ...
Dewey.
Dewey?
Hold your horses.
What's wrong?
The damn switch is not pulled.
Track's not for D16.
What's up?
What's your stopping distance?
At least 20 cars to a stop.
Damn it!
Can we back up, we still
have a little time.
Off.
Do not leave that cab, man.
Don't worry, I'll set the independent.
Dewey!
Come on, come back.
Better get back on.
I'm on it, I'm on it.
Damn!
Shit.
You better get back on on, dickhead.
Shit!
I'm an idiot.
An idiot.
God damn it!
Now, what the hell do we do?
Nicole's birthday.
Shoo
t.
Ooh, you're trouble.
Don't talk about it.
Put your sister on the phone, please.
Dad.
She doesn't want to talk with you.
What? Listen ... just tell her that I didn't
forgot what day it is ...
Just ... I was running late.
She's gotta date tonight.
With who?
Just put your sister on the phone.
Wait, here she is.
Nikki.
- Hello.
- Listen, Just, I ...
Eh, look, I didn't forget... I
Frank, the coaches are already there.
What's wrong?
No, it's no problem...
except, you got it backwards.
Turntable house goes on my end,
you're on the ballast.
On my end.
Other than that, no problem.
No problem at all.
Like I told you,
if you do not know something,
just ask, that's all.
Got it.
I hope so.
Whatever.
Excuse me?
Shit, let's make the new guy
prove himself bullshit.
Gotta tell you, I heard it before.
It gets old really fast.
Well, that's how it is at
the retirement home.
The company wants to get rid
of us old heads,
They give all the jobs to you new guys.
You, yellow vests.
I not trying to take anything
from anybody.
As reassuring as that is,
a lot of guys don't see it that way.
I'm here. I'm walking in right now.
I got a car full of donuts for those kids.
Coaster, what train?
Connie.
How the hell did this happen?
- It got away.
- It GOT away from you?
It's a train, Dewey, not a chipmonk.
I had to get off to throw a switch.
You got off the cab?
Ya. It's gets worse ...
Uh ...
Air brakes weren't tied on.
They aren't tied on, still.
We've gotta unmanned train rolling into
opposing traffic, with no airbrakes?
That's what you to tell me?
I set the independent brakes.
That'll for sure stop it.
How fast is it going?
No more than 10 miles per.
OK, go jump on the highway
and go after it.
- Now!
- Okay. Ballbuster.
Call the field trip.
I do not care where they are on the mainline,
we need to get them to the nearsest siding.
Train Campaign, Train Campaign
this is dispatch, do you copy?
Train Campaign. Answering dispatch,
how can I help you? Over.
Campaign, this is Fuller. There is an
unauthorized activity on your track.
We you to divert to a siding at Portfield.
Dispatch, please repeat.
Please repeat, over.
What time is train time?
Anytime.
Divert to a siding at Portfield.
Do you copy?
I copy. I'll divert to a siding
at Portfield? Over.
Get me Triple 7's cargo information.
I have to call corporate and report this.
Now, Dewey said he aplied the independents
So, the friction should stop the damn
thing that after a few miles.
But, we need to alert every northbound
train on the the main line.
The first 20 miles of track take priority.
I don't care if you're talking about
spot welding or
ground operations in Afghanistan.
- It's all about precision.
- Right.
Thanks.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
Hello?
Ned, where are you?
Oh, Connie, hey. Um. I'm just
driving in now.
I gotta go.
Well, how far are you from milepost 5?
Roughly, 6 minutes.
Traffic, contingent.
Great, I need you to haul ass over there
to throw a siding switch.
Because we have a coaster.
A coaster? Really?
Yep, it should be at milepost 5
in 15 minutes.
Enough time to go to the switch,
get it off the mainline and onto that siding.
- You want me to climb on board and stop it?
What? No, no, no.
We got two arses on their way on the road
you just throw that switch, Ned.
Roger, that.
Can always count on him,
to be late.
I'll see you later.
See ya.
What do we do when we get to
a railroad crossing?
Stop! Look! And, Listen!
I can't hear you!
Stanton you know?
Yes. Ever.
My whole family's from Stanton.
You married?
Yes.
Well, sorta. It's a long story.
Got a long day.
How about you, Frank?
It's a short story.
Once.
I have two beautiful daugthers. Though
The 18 and 19 years.
Both waitressing trying to work their way to college.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Where at?
Hooters.
The so is called.
That's right, Hooters.
Clear that grin off your face.
- I am a fan.
- Yes.
You're blushing.
I'm used to it.
Connie, a call on line 2.
This is Connie Fuller at xxx yard.
On hold.
Did I hear, you gotta coaster?
Yeah, that sorta thing happens,
We're on it.
You want a triple relay?
Listen, I need to speak to
Mr. Darby, directly.
I see. Um, can you
have him call me, then?
No, I'm about to release it myself...
Who the hell are you?
I'm here for the railway
safety campaign.
Scott Werner, the regional authority.
Federal Safety Inspector. I'm supposed
to give a presentation to the children ...
Awesome.
Bunny!
Can you help me out here?
You see this guy right there?
- He's gonna tell you what track. Okay?
- Thank you for your alignment
Thanks, beautiful.
- I'm glad you liked it. Great.
Shit. Where the hell is this thing?
Hazardous Material
Bunny!
I need to know exactly what's in cars
7 to 10. Get a hold of the shipper, please.
Kiddin me.
- Where's the train?
- What doesit look like the God damned train is?
I do not know where it is
You think I hid
in my back pocket?
- You said ...
- Give me a Connie.
- You're a jackassl.
- Its Ned.
- I do not know anything.
- You two have given it in the bar.
Shut the fuck up.
I had to pull the emergency line.
Connie, its Ned.
Did you throw that switch yet?
Yes, 6 minutes ago.
But your train is not here.
I thought it might be going a little
slower than you guessed.
But these two numbnuts that you sent, just
showed up and haven't seen it either.
Are you saying our train has
already passed?
Yes ma'am, that would be my guess.
It's not a coaster, that train
is under power.
That would be my guess, too.
Put Dewey on the phone.
Sure.
He wants to talk with you, asshole.
- I need you to rally
every cell in that brain of yours.
When you applied the independent
was the trottle in the
forward position?
Yeah, I had to get it moving.
In what position was the
trottle set?
Damn it, Dewey, in what position?
Connie, the trottle was in notch 8,
full power.
OK, it was 39 cars.
OK. Take the southbound track...
Catch up, see if it's still going
slow enough for one of your...
You've got until ...
milepost 13, where the track splits.
Let me talk to Ned, again.
Nice job, asshole.
Ned, I want to go back to your car
and follow the main line, okay?
I want to somebody on that train.
You've got it. Roger, that.
Do not you hear.
The railway is safe.
Yes!
You're good.
Keep it coming, you've got 10 yards.
20 feet.
Slow 'er down.
All right, you're good.
Yeah, what's going on?
Got a minute?
I thought he said it was looking good.
That's what he thought.
Turns out the judge they
assigned was a real hardass.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Look.
The restraining order is being
continued for another 30 days.
30 days?
What am I supposed to do for 30 days?
- Stay away from my kid?
And, then, there's a hearing after that, I guess.
What's taking you so long, Will?
Call that lawyer and you tell
him to stick it up his ass ...
Will, pick up the radio.
I gotta go.
Will pick up the radio.
Over.
Are you there?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Get off the phone,
Knock off the handbrakes.
Get up here.
Time to go.
We got work to do.
Copy.
No, it's definitely under power,
we're not sure of the exact speed, yet.
Why don't all these trains have some
kind of dead man brake.
There's a rod the engineer has to hit per-
iodically or airbrakes automatically applied.
Unfortunately, this trains airbrakes
were disconnected.
Sir, I would gladly explain the particulars
of locomotive operation to you
if we had time, but right now
I really need your assistance to post two
officers at all crossings.
One question.
How do you all plan to stop him?
We're working on it.
Go, go, go. Switch coming up.
- Are you sure that you can do this?
- Get me along side the cab.
- Get along side of it.
- I'm trying.
Go, go, go.
There's little.
You got it. Go, go.
Dewey ...
It's too fast, speed up.
Come on, give it up.
Jump, jump.
Come on, man, do it!
Danny, take care!
Now what the hell are we doing?
How many cars we supposed
to cut in?
20. Why?
20 cars. OK.
See the switch there, up ahead of us?
- The switch over there.
- Yes.
Look in the mirror.
You see the one behind us?
Way back there, you see it?
That's exactly 21 cars
between the two stands.
Do not ask me where I know.
So, why is it that there's still more
than 4 and a half more cars yet to clear?
Because ...
- Excuse me?
- Because I ...
- Because I cut too many cars.
- Too many cars?
Maybe if you we're not on my ass, all the
time, I'd be able to think straight.
- What do you mean, maybe it's my fault?
- I have done this to exercise.
I'm just saying we should do the job.
If you were ready,
you would not put 5 more.
It was your fault.
I had my training, all right?
Yes, but we're in the real world,
this ain't training.
In training they just give you an "F".
Out here, you get killed.
I screwed up, OK?
Stop. Roll back and I'll
cut the extra cars.
What? Roll back?
Oh, Lord, we can't stop out
here on the main.
We can't go miles on
the Main Line, and then stop.
You don't take accounts this size, that
distance in reverse.
Then, let's turn in, the next siding.
Next siding is not for 10 miles.
If you do that, we'll be late.
I don't want to be late.
- We have the green light.
- Green light, my ass.
What do you mean, my ass.
You're a Colson.
What does that mean?
- Ask your uncle.
- It's my uncle?
- No, it's about five cars in addition.
- A time to stop and cut them loose?
You're the engineer, but it's
God damned my train.
- Yes, it's your train.
- I am wretched chief of the train.
- That's true.
- 1206, check in.
Well, you sure, I'll green
sheet your ass.
The so think?
1206, this is the dispatcher.
What's your location? Over.
- Is something funny?
- No.
- Then why are you laughing?
- Because it's funny.
You're a funny guy.
Well trained, but funny.
Yes, there are 1206.
We're 60 miles from Wilkinson.
At 40 minutes out of Fuller yard.
Negative, 1206.
Pull your train to the next siding,
until further instructed. Over.
What's up?
There's another man's train out of
Fuller, on the Northbound track. Over.
On our track!?
A coaster?
We don't have all the details yet. Just
proceed to the next siding, hold tight. Over.
Next siding is not for ten miles.
Control to 1206.
Get to that siding and sit tight,
'til we give you the all clear. Over.
Affirmative.
It's coming right at us.
More word on that runaway freight train
in rural Pennsylvania.
The train, AWVR 777,
Otherwise known as the "Triple 7"
left Fuller yard
in northern Pennsylvania
sometime before 8 A.M. this morning.
And, no one on board.
Live, local, late breaking...
The engineer, they say, made an error
in controlling the train.
Before leaving the locomotive, he attempted
to apply the independent brakes.
And then, by the time he
realized his mistake,
the train was going too fast
for him to climb back on.
We're being told now by a spokesman for
the Public Utilities Commission,
that this employee will
be held accountable.
- Connie.
- Yes.
Headquarters on the phone.
It's Galvin.
Mr Galvin, how are you?
- God damn it, how could this happen?
- It was an unfortunate combination of
human error and bad luck.
Luck?
I was a yardmaster for 10 years,
Ms Hooper
Luck has no
business in a rail yard.
What are you worried about,
in terms of cargo?
Well, obviously the diesel fuel is a concern.
I said, cargo.
OK, well, cars 7-10 and 16-19 have a
chemical called molten phenol
and we're still trying to connect with the
shipper to determine exactly what that is.
It's used in the manufacture of glue.
Can you hold on one moment?
- You know what is phenol?
- Yes.
Uh... Mr Galvin, we have a
FRS inspector with us.
I can put you on speakerphone?
Region 2 Federal Safety Inspector,
- Scott Werner. How can I help you?
- Please tell me what you know about molten phenol.
Well, look, it's serious stuff.
Um, very toxic, highly combustible.
Well, that's terrific.
Hooper, get state police back on the line,
make sure they have a HAZMAT team briefed and ready?
And, asked them to put a spotter chopper over triple 7.
I take it you sided all rail
traffic?
On our end, yes.
Bruster's notifying his own.
Sir, how are we going to handle this?
I mean, this train is on route to pass
through some highly populated areas.
We have a strategy call in ... about 2 minutes.
- All right, I'll be ready.
- You will not be on the call, Ms. Hooper.
- Excuse me?
- You will be advised.
We now coordinate with local authorities.
God knows, we have more than 100
crossings that need to be secured.
173. Railroad crossings.
Between here and AWVR substation
in Bruster.
Listen ... Mr Galvin,
this train is half a mile long
and it's traveling at speed
into population,
with 8 freight cars
of hazardous chemicals
and 5,000 gallons of diesel fuel.
So, we're not just talking a train here,
we're talking about a missile
the size of the Chrysler building.
So, what is your point, Miss Hooper?
My point is, after it crosses into Finley,
are about 12 miles of vacant farmland.
But after that, it's nothing but
town after town.
All the way to Stanton.
We have a very limited window here.
So, what are suggesting that
we do, derail it?
Yes, sir, I am.
While we still can.
Mr Galvin, I understand that's going
to cost the company a lot of money.
Do you think!?
Miss Hooper, we are not intentionally
going to destroy one of our own trains.
Not when we can still stop it.
We can avoid more losses.
I'm going to extend to you, my last ounce
of goodwill, pretend this conversation never happened.
As if I'm worried about my job.
Findlay
Northern Pennsylvania.
Ma'am,
please stay in your van.
Let's go.
Please, remain in the van.
You can tell us what's going on.
All crossings are closed off for 20 miles.
Ma'am, for your safety,
you please get back into your van.
I'm not getting back into the vehicle,
we need to know what's going on.
Get out of there. Train's coming.
Off the line.
1206 to dispatch.
Over.
- What's wrong?
We're not going to fit in that siding,
that's the problem.
1206 to dispatch.
Over.
1206, you in the siding yet.
What's your location?
We're not going to make it.
Can't do it.
Too much train.
I'm going to need you to realign the
switch so we can proceed to the next siding.
1206, you have to get off the main.
Over.
I understand. But you have to
understand this. We're not going to fit.
I'll hold.
1206, stand by.
That siding is a good 3,000 feet,
head to head.
Check your timetable.
It's going to tell you the siding
is 4,111 feet.
But that's the signal to the signal.
In reality, it's more like 2,500 feet.
You add those five cars
that YOU picked up.
- We can fit.
- No, we won't fit.
Dispatch, this is 1206.
Can you tell us where the nearest
rip track is?
1206, there's one in 6.2 miles.
How fast are you going?
55 miles an hour.
1206, go faster. Over.
Why, is that coaster still
on the main?
1206, Triple 7 is not a coaster.
I repeat, is not a coaster.
Over.
You telling me it's under power?
Get in the God damned siding.
1206, stand by.
1206, if you're going for it, that rip
track is confirm vacant.
It's your call, Frank. We need to
throw the switch, if you're staying on.
We're both staying on,
pull the brake, Frank.
Pull the brake,.
I know what what the hell I'm doing.
Bullshit, you're gonna get us killed.
Hey!
1206, I need an answer.
Realign it ... the switch.
Over.
Train was just going, no one in it.
It just took off.
They were yelling over the radio, earlier.
There was a runaway train coming through.
Could be coming to our town next. And, the
high school is right next to those train tracks.
Just a few moments ago, this train came
barreling down these tracks.
Looking at the numbers?
Should 777 derail,
we're looking at a major disaster.
If one of those Phenol vapor cars blew...
can easily decimate an entire town.
That train is carrying eight of them.
Environmental liability, track damage,
car and locomotive loss.
We're looking at a projected cost,
easily over a $100 million.
And the resulting stock devaluation?
Our projections indicate,
it could be ... in the
30-40 % range.
I say we vote for Mr Galvin's option.
I've already prepared for a
substation at Bruster,
They just need a go-ahead.
You have it.
Okay, everybody out.
Hoffman, you stay here, Baker, get me
a track schematic Fuller to Stanton.
This is Owen.
71, 70, 71, that's
with a gun.
- So the red means ...
- Triple 7 blew through a signal.
Everything in red means trouble
on the Main line.
That's a lot of red.
Connie, Mr Galvin on line 2.
This is Connie Hooper.
Have all the mainline crossings
been closed?
Yes, we have coordinated with PSP.
You have established strategy in place?
It's already under way.
By the activity going
on behind me,
it is evident that a plan to
stop the runaway train is under way.
But for now,
nobody at AWVR is commenting.
We just witnessed AWVR employee, Ryan
Scott, boarding a rescue helicopter.
He is a 22 year old Marine vet,
who just returned from Afghanistan.
- I now need a police escort, now.
It says here you're a welder?
Lead Welder!
Dude, I do got a lot of time.
Look, you can call my yard,
and ask for Connie Hooper.
Connie sent you?
That's what I said.
I need your help.
1206, this is dispatch.
1206, we ran the math.
1206, if you were over 2,000,
you wouldn't have fit.
Good call.
Over.
Thanks, but need to know
where that train is.
How far away is it?
1206, we're not exactly sure.
You're not sure?
Find out!
I'm flying above central
Pennsylvania.
In what emergency responders want to
close all activities along the line.
And possibly evacuate all homes within
a mile radius of the track.
There's thousands of gallons of fuel
on board, which is highly flammable.
We're still awaiting word on that.
This is Galvin's strategy!?
Seems to be a locomotive in front
in an attempt to slow it down.
Now we're getting a chopper
and Ryan Scott.
The company still refuses
to comment.
We just learned that 26 year
rail company veteran,
Judd Stewart, is at the controls of the
engine trying to stop the runaway train.
This one is your plan?
A guy hanging from the helicopter?
Still hauling at 55.
Get her down to 40 and keep braking.
Shit.
That's it, keep slowing. Get her
down to 40, and we'll send our boy down.
Unbelievable.
Do it!
Come on.
Incredibly dangerous maneuver.
Do it! Do it again!
I'm under 40, is he on yet?
Come on!
Looks like Ryan is injured.
He missed.
Come on.
Just keep braking. Try to slow.
Try to get 777 off the Main.
Switch has been thrown.
Slow down to hell.
Slow down, slow down,
it's going too fast.
Okay, okay.
Holy shit.
Maybe it derailed.
Wow, I can't believe how
horrendous that was.
Oh, my God, Galvin you asshole.
Fuller yard. Fuller yard.
This is 1206.
We're passing milepost 5-2,
heading north on Main run.
1206, who am I speaking with?
Frank Barnes, the engineer.
This is Connie Hooper, Yardmaster
at Fuller.
Why are you still on the main line?
We were directed to a siding that's a
no go. We're heading to a rip track.
I just passed milepost 5-0.
We need to know the location of your
yard's train.
It just passed milepost 47.
Holy shit.
They tried to side it when it jumped the
switch and derailed the lash-up.
Lash-up?
Who was driving?
Company employee for 26 years,
Judd Stewart was killed today
trying to stop the train
in central Pennsylvania.
Judd Stewart.
Stewart?
You said, Stewart?
Judd Stewart, an engineer from Bruster.
You know him?
What's you power at the point?
5,000 horses. She's not a hot shot,
but, she's a ... still got some
life left in her. Over.
Give her all you got.
Tell Galvin we got two guys on
the Main line, about to
to play chicken with our our train.
We tried to stop him.
We blew it.
That train's gotta go down.
- The only question is how to minimizedamage.
- Be quiet.
We just learned, there is yet another
train on this track.
Headed directly at the runaway.
What the hell is that?
We got to learn about it on ...
damn TV?
Nicole, Nicole, listen, don't hang up.
Don't hang up.
Dad, am busy, okay?
Well. I just wanted to ...
- Dad ...
- I just wanted to say that I love you.
Okay, fine.
- Dad, what's wrong?
- Nothing, nothing, I just ...
Dad, what's wrong?
Tell your sister
I love you both.
Okay? I gotta go.
What's happening?
1206, how you holding up?
I'm about a half a mile from that
rip track. Over.
Chances are, you're gonna see
the triple 7, any minute.
Affirmative.
Why are you braking?
Trust me. If we head in this hot,
We'll tear right off the track.
Jeez.
Get her down to 40 and brace yourself.
You need to get at least 10 cars
into the siding.
Yes!
1206. 1206.
I'm at 1206. Go.
They're evacuating Arklow.
They're going to derail the train.
What are they using?
Standard dynamite.
Going to derail her.
What are you doing?
I got a look at that last car coupler.
It was open.
If we take off right now, we can get back
on the Main. Chase it down in reverse.
Woah, wait a minute.
No way to stop that kind of power.
Grab it by the tail. Boom!
Gun it in the opposite direction.
You heard what they said, if that goes
down we'll be a wreck on a wreck.
Doesn't matter.
Good chance the derailer won't work.
It's called a derailer
for Christ's sake.
A train of this size,
going that fast
- It will vaporize anything that gets inits way.
- Bullshit!
- They wouldn't use it.
- They're wrong, all right?
They're wrong.
Are you in or are you not?
If you want to get yourself killed,
you do it alone.
You know what? Ask your wife what she feels.
Wait.
If you are right and the derailer fails,
what are the odds it makes it to Stanton?
You saw the train. What do you think?
1206, this is Connie Hooper,
Are you there?
1206, Over.
I wanted to see how you boys
are doing.
We're doing about 60 miles
an hour, Connie.
Sorry ... I don't understand.
We're going after your train.
1206, I'm not hearing you.
The rear knuckle was left open, so
if we can catch up,
we can tie it on our locomotive.
Try and slow down triple 7.
- Frank, you can't.
- We've already are.
One derailer's not going to cut it,
Connie.
Who said anything about the derailer?
Dispatch. He said they were to evacuate
Arklow. Two plus two is four.
- It's Ned, says he's still following.
- No, tell him we'll call him back.
Get me to Galvin, now!
Frank, that train carrying 30,000
gallons of toxic chemicals.
They had a window before.
But that train's going into
populated areas.
There's no way they derail, now.
Are you sure about that?
- Look, let me make some calls.
- Make some calls, please!
What do you think?
You think he can catch up?
Well, possibly.
But even if they do, we're talking about
coupling at 10 times the normal speed.
In reverse...
I thought you were in favor of derailment.
Yeah, yeah, when they were in the
middle of nowhere.
Not now, when its just
town after town out there.
Mr. Galvin says he'll have
to call you back.
This is Connie Hooper for Mr. Galvin.
Mr. Galvin has a meeting.
Then maybe you can tell me. Is the company
planning on derailing Triple 7?
Last I heard, Galvin was
dead-set against it.
Sorry, I'd like to help, but can't.
No, of course you're not at liberty to.
Frank's right.
How fast do you think is a single
engine like this?
- Unattached?
- Yeah.
50, 55
But, that was going forward.
1206, you there?
This is 1206, Over.
Frank, you're right.
About the derailment ...
They're planning an attempt
outside of Arklow.
Tell them idiots it ain't gonna work.
That portable derailer is worthless.
She already told us.
Frank, this is Oscar Galvin,
v.p. of operations.
Patched in at his request, open mike.
Yeah, we are derailing Triple 7, Frank.
It's a done decision.
Like it or not, it's
our best option at this stage.
Less collateral damage in Arklow.
It's already being evacuated. And, we can't
let Triple 7 make it to Stanton.
Look, Mr Galvin, with all due respect,
I've been railroading for 28 years.
I'm telling you we got a real chance
to stop this thing.
No, we already tried.
That was from the front.
We're long hood, lean back.
It's a different situation.
We got more control now.
What if I cancel the derailer,
and you fail, Frank? Huh...
The train will be doing 70 MPH
into that elevated "S" curve at Stanton.
The damage will be 100 times worse.
Right, I'm just telling you,
the portable derailer is worthless.
You got too much train travelling
entirely too fast.
Maybe 1206 should just stay on
it as a back up.
But, I am not jeopardizing more
personnel and more property,
just because some engineer
wants to play hero.
End of discussion.
That train is our property,
it's our decision.
Now, you stop your pursuit
or I will fire you.
You already did.
Already did what?
You've already fired me.
I received my 90 days notice
in the mail,
72 days ago.
Forced early retirement, half benefits.
So you're gonna risk your life for us,
with three weeks left?
Not for you ...
I'm not doing it for you.
Frank ...
Give me that.
Mr Galvin, this is Will Colson,
your conductor.
I'm letting you know,
we're gonna run this bitch down.
Maybe you didn't hear what I just said,
Colson. I will fire you!
That's too bad.
I was just starting to like his job.
Damn it, you listen to me.
Son of a bitch, you will be fired.
You're breaking up.
Sorry ...
- This garbage, is not ...
- I think they're gone.
Well, this is your headache, now, Hooper.
Now, you get them off the Main or
consider yourself shitcanned, too.
I like that.
Bring up the slides of Arklow.
Take a look behind me and see emergency
evacuation efforts are currently in effect
right here in the tiny town of Arklow.
1206 to Fuller yard.
Connie, are you there? Over.
- Frank ... I'm real sorry about Galvin.
- It's okay. Listen, listen.
- Is he off?
- Yeah, he's gone
OK, listen up.
I want you to do us a favor.
I need you to keep us posted on the speed
and location of Triple 7.
Location and speed.
Over.
Connie?
Frank, Triple 7 is 9 miles out of
Arklow. You got some catching up to do.
9 miles out of Arklow.
- What did you say your wife's first name?
- Darcy.
So, what's the long story
you didn't want to make long?
I came home from work
two weeks ago, and she's uh ...
texting on the phone.
I asked her who and she told me, nobody.
I said "let me see the phone"
and she says, no.
And, this goes on...
- Five, six times ...
- Wait, wait, you're losing me.
- She's texting? - There's this guy
we both went to school with.
He's a cop. He's a PA state trooper.
He's always had a thing for Darcy,
since we met.
1206, where are you?
1206, here Connie.
I just passed milepost 57.
You are about a mile and a half behind.
How far out of Arklow is Triple 7?
7 1/2 miles, it picked upspeed.
You better step on it.
I'm stepping on it. In and around it,
through it, Connie. Thank you. Over.
And the phone messages continued and
each time she continued to deny.
She starts to walk away. I grab for it.
- Did you hit her?
- No, no.
I mean, I scared her but
I didn't hurt her.
Well, anyway, I drive to this guys house,
to talk,
that among men, in my car.
He started to tell me that I got it
all wrong. They're just friends
and he stops when he sees
the gun I got sitting on the ...
- Oooh!
She's my wife, you find another friend.
- You pulled a gun on a cop?
- Frank?
Frank, Triple 7 has just passed
milepost 61.
Thank you, Connie.
- Want to hear the kicker?
- Yes, I do.
It wasn't even him that was texting her.
It was my sister-in-law.
Hey, by the time I got home,
his buddy is waiting for me.
Just waiting to serve me
with a restraining order.
Darcy wouldn't even looked at me.
So, now I'm living with my brother.
There was a hearing today. The judge
ordered a 30 day extension.
It's like, one day, everything is going
Okay, and then...
the next, it's all falling apart
faster than you can put it back together.
Yeah ... never too late, though.
The plan to derail this 39 car
runaway train is just minutes away now.
...tremendous amount of activity going on.
Will this train be able to be stopped.
1206, Connie, just passed
milepost 62. Milepost 62. Over.
There's still a mile gap,
maybe more.
We are gaining on him, Frank.
Hold on tight.
Just want to shot trains.
Okay, we go
Come, Be ready. It's moment of truth.
Just north of Arklow.
OK, Remember, it's a Red button!
Now!
Open fire! Open fire!
Damn!
Open fire!
We were aiming at the same level, by firing
shotgun rounds at the fuel stop safety switch.
And So ... some shots were fired.
That safety switch is a mighty small target
and, it's right nex to a fuel tank.
We're not going to catch him before Arklow.
Frank, you're closing the gap.
You should cut your speed, allow
yourself some stopping distance, just in case.
No can do, Connie.
If we slow down now, we'll never catch him.
Not before Stanton.
Over.
It's your call.
However, we have now also learned,
that two railroad employees
are now in pursuit of train 777
in a single locomotive.
It is unclear what's their plan ...
Connie Hooper for you.
Did I or did I not tell you
to get 1206 off the Main?
I asked them nicely.
...This is impossible!
- You're 100 % sure that derailer won'twork?
- Yes. 100 %.
- Now
- Which one is it?
- 50-50.
- 25.
And if it does?
If does ... then we're
a wreck on a wreck.
I'am with engineer Jim Deveroux.
The train is getting close.
How will this derailer work?
Well, basically, it works like a ramp.
Train comes along, this piece here,
will lift the flange
and and pull it outside the rail.
That will cause the train
to flip over on its right hand side.
Son of a bitch won't even know...
What ... What in the hell was that?
That ... was 10 million pounds of train,
Mr Galvin.
And, this is the sound of me
saving your ass.
Frank, do you copy?
- Frank?
- 1206. Over.
You were right.
Jesus Christ!
Bringing you live coverage right now of
what could very well result
in one of the worst disasters in the
history of the state of Pennsylvania.
The particulars are still
being examined, but
authorities are far more focused
on the potential destruction that would
result if train 777
were to derail in Stanton.
What did you mean
about being married once?
Alice, my wife ...she died of cancer.
- Four years ago.
- Sorry.
Me too ...
Me too.
Every night I come home,
tell her about my day ...
where I had been ...
what I hauled.
Who annoyed me.
- You can offend someone?
- You'd be amazed.
You should call your wife.
I would but ... but it's her day off.
She's probably sleeping.
Don't make excuses. Wake her up.
I called her for the past 2 weeks,
but she never called me back.
She won't. You got to call her,
that's how it works.
You quit too easy.
Stanton, Pennsylvania.
Darcy!
Darcy.
I've been calling...
and calling.
What is wrong?
As we told you earlier today,
those emergency evacuations
began early this morning.
As they try to move people out of
harms way.
Yeah, I know, I'm watching TV.
Arklow, Pennnsylvannia
Two railroad employees are presently in
pursuit of Train 777
in a single locomotive.
No one seems exactly clear on what their
plans are to catch up with that train.
We just learned the railroad employee,
Frank Barnes,
a 28 year veteran of the
the train company responsible
for the runaway
and Will Colson, a conductor,
Are now on board other ...
Yes, we're on our way.
And get this. They were travelling
at speeds up to 70 MPH ... in reverse.
Triple 7 is now just
miles away
the more populated town of Stanton.
Let's go, boys!
You're getting close, gap is but a mile
and Triple 7 is 10 miles to Stanton.
Now, listen, Frank.
I got a guy here named Werner from
the FRA...
Now, I'm inclined to divert your
judgement here, but he ...
All right. Put him on.
We can use all the help that we can get.
Press this and hold to talk.
It's about slowing down Triple 7,
once you've tied on. I know...
I know conventional wisdon says to just
gun it in the opposite direction.
But, you'll have a better shot
alternating full trottle
with dynamic braking.
Yeah. But we can't afford
to lose counter-trust.
What you'll lose in counter-trust
will compensate for in traction force.
Are you sure about that?
Well, it's more of a hunch based on
some quick calculations.
It's a hunch!?
We're going 70 MPH and
he gives us a hunch.
Okay, thank you.
Put Connie back on, please.
- It's me, Frank. - Yeah, Connie,
this guy know what he's talking about?
In a perfect world ...
Yes. I would says, yes.
In a perfect world, okay.
We now have more now on that runaway
freight train in rural Pennsylvania,
we've been advised of an ambitous plan
to bring it to a stop.
A single locomotive moves in from behind
catches up... hooks up
and then brakes
in an effort to slow it down.
We passed milepost 76, Connie.
Over.
- You're only half mile away.
- Half mile. Over.
Frank, running in reverse,
how are you going to gauge our gap distance?
I'll go out there and signal you by hand.
- At 70 MPH?
- I ask you, you need help?
All right.
Radio and hand signs to communicate.
Okay?
- Now, be careful.
- I will.
- And, oh, take that vest off.
- Why?
Just take it off. I do not want to look out
this window and see a yellow vest. Freak me out.
Come on, answer.
Come on.
- Leave me a message...
- Damn.
Come on, Frank.
Trying. Over.
All right, here she comes.
3 cars?
Three cars, steady. Copy.
All right. Steady! Steady!
Two cars?
Yeah, two cars. Steady.
Steady on one.
Keep it coming. Keep it coming.
Keep it coming!
Steady! ... Steady!
Plan go into operation
Will Colson is tring to hook up 1206 with
Triple 7. Coulson, the conductor...
It seems something is terribly wrong.
Will, what was that?
Lost brake fluid.
Are we tied on?
Will, what's going on?
Right now we are looking at live
pictures of this rescue operation
Are we tied on?
No, fricking thing didn't work.
I'll try again.
Will, use hand signals.
Are we tied on?
We're good, we're good.
Shit!
Frank, I fell hook.
Repeat. What?
Are we tied in..
The locking hook pin didn't fall.
What?
Pin didn't fall.
It's not a locked-in.
Okay, well, look.
Try to get down to see what
you can do. Be careful.
Be careful.
Will.
Not slowing down, it's
gaining right speed now.
He's reaching down
trying to couple...
Will, can you read me?
He's gone.
Will Colson is down.
We do not see him.
Helicopter 43, can you zoom in
do not see that conductor, Colson.
Come on, baby.
Will, can you read me?
Will!
Chopper 43, zoom in.
There is Will Colson.
Looks like Will Colson is in trouble.
Shit.
Will.
We are now being told, that the
connection has been made.
It looks as though this train is
now attached to 1206.
1206 is successfuly attached
to the Triple 7.
It looks like Will Colson is injured.
All right?
I'm great.
Don't touch that, don't touch that.
Just wrap it up with this.
Wrap it real tight. All around.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, great.
Colson has caught up to the runaway train
and .....
Let's go, Darcy.
But the train continues to speed in
excess of 75 miles an hour.
Heading to Stanton.
Connie, how far got?
How far is Stanton?
Over.
4 miles. You guys are doing great.
But, you're cutting it close, though.
How's Will?
He's, uh ...
He's different. Over.
Done.
You ready for a little tug-of-war?
Let s do it.
Match our speed with theirs ...
- Frank Roth.
- I know. Only scratches, that's all.
Scratches.
Here in Stanton, the evacuation procedures
continue for the entire town.
This is the town where the that main line
train track turns into an elevated curve.
They say there is virtually no chance that
this speeding, out of control train
Will make it through that curve.
Please slow down.
But I'll do.
Shit.
Now the dynamics.
Open easily.
Christ, slowing down.
Seems to be working.
Come on, Frank.
Come on, baby.
What's the speed?
We're under 50.
Connie, how far away?
3 miles. We have men on the
ground ready to hop on board.
- As soon as you guys get it under control.
- Tell them to be ready to hop. Over.
Shit!
- What is it?
- Gaining speed.
The systems is too heavy.
Being dragged.
Connie!
I'm here, Frank.
We're going to be coming in too hot.
I do not know.
Limit on that curve that is 15.
I do not know if you can take it much faster.
Maybe 20, 25, max.
We may not have a choice.
Just tell them it's going
to be real hot.
What about the braking
of the freight cars?
Good, good.
- All right, I'm on it.
- No, no. Sit down. No, no.
I've got it. Sit tight. Sit tight.
I'll go.
No, no, come on. You better stay here
and I go out.
Just keep it at 4.
- You, all right? Take it easy.
- Yeah.
Hold that dynamic out, 4,
4, with the trottle combined.
Hold it up at 4, how you run the
clock out, doesn't matter.
Hey, don't get sentimental on me.
Makes me think I'm gonna die.
Just hold it at 4.
Come on, Frank.
WAVR officials have no comment.
Barnes is attempting to manually
brake the last car.
Actually, Barnes is
on the train
leaping over cars.
Let's go, Frank.
Looks like Triple 7 is slowing down.
Come on Dad, Kill it.
Will, how fast are you going?
34.
We're dropping, 33 ...
Think it'll work?
Theoretically.
Provided, that locomotive's independent
brake holds up.
We continue to bring you live coverage of
this breaking news event from the town of Stanton.
Emergency officials have created
this perimeter ...
Please evacuate the building,
immediately.
Damn!
Frank.
Yeah, yeah, I hear you, I hear you.
We just lost our brakes.
- They lost their brakes. High flames ...
- Shit.
Frank, Frank, you all right?
I'm here, Will, what happened?
We're picking up speed, again.
Can you still slow him down?
We're almost at the curve.
Frank, our engine block's overheated.
I don't think those handbrakes are
going to stop it, going too fast.
Just hang on to the independent.
I'll tell you when.
Elevated and strictly class 2
speed restricted to 15 miles per hour.
Impact with three of these buildings
directly below will be unavoidable..
..As will contact with all of the
fuel storage tanks situated here.
Will.
Will?
Okay, okay, but we take speed again.
Will!
We're coming into the curve!
Get ready!
Will!
Get on the independent!
The independentele is hard to get.
We're going to jump right off.
We have no choice.
Will!
Hang on!
Try, try again.
Now!
Frank, you all right?
We made it!
Through the turn!
Triple 7 did it. It made it through
the Staton curve.
Triple 7 is through the Stanton curve,
but, by no means out of trouble.
Triple 7 is gaining speed, it is
out of control, and has to derail.
Frank Barnes and Will Colson will be
the victims of the
biggest rail disaster
the history of the north-east.
It looks like Frank Barnes is
making an all out effort...
This is a remarkable effort, now, to
get to the front of Triple 7.
Frank!
Frank, we're 60 and we're gonna
hit 80 in no time.
He's not going to make it.
It looks like the gap between cars
has stopped him.
Come on, Dad.
But the train continues to speed
in excess of 75 miles an hour.
Frank.
Frank!
Will! We got a problem here!
I do not think I can make it!
Oh, God!
Who's that?
Unbelievable!
Unbelievable.
Hello.
Ned, it's Connie.
I'm a little busy right now, Connie.
I'll Call you back.
Come on!
Jump into the back of the car!
Hop into the back of the truck!
Connie!
Connie, is that truck for us?
Yes it is, Will. You can do this.
Come on, you can do this.
Come on.
It looks like he's trying to synchronize
with the speed of the train.
Jump, you pussy!
Jump in the back!
Yes!
Look at what's happening now.
The red pick-up...
racing toward the end of the train.
Come on!
Frank!
Go, Go, Go!
Go, go, go!
Go, go!
Now WIll is running out of parallel road
Come on, Will.
Come on, Come on!
Come on!
God damn it, over shot it.
Come on.
Come on, damn! Do it!
Come on, jump!
Do it! Jump!
Yes!
Oh, God!
Colson, successfully making it in to
the cab, now he controls.
Job of reporting 43 to you,
this remarkable aftermath.
We're talking about the heroic work
of two men...
Frank Barnes and Will Colson.
Southern Pennsylvania
will always indebted to them.
Missed Call
Darcy.
We did It.
I knew that when there's a job here we do it.
Good accuracy.
Good job, kid.
- Ned! - Ned!
- You!
Ned, were you worried?
If I worried?
No, not really.
It's all about precision.
I was and she says she ...
- Your flowers are going corporate, you know
- Yes?
Debt of gratitude ... blah, blah, blah.
Same here.
They are pretty good, actually.
Yes, it did.
What was your first reaction when you
realized what was happening?
I felt I was in my comfort zone.
- Mine was about my job?
- So was mine, didn't want to leave it.
- You'd be stupid enough to do it.
- Yeah. That's what I told them.
So, they better think about giving
me a medal, too.
- But me?
- What about you?
Do you have any better of an idea
as to how this happened?
- Do you want to you know how it happened?
- Thank you very much evry body ...You had an experience.
Sir?
I wonder if you can help me.
- Connie?
- I can't decide which one of you I'm going to kiss first.
Me!
Problem solved.
- Get him, Connie.
- Okay, bring it on.
Your Daughters?
Chopper 43,...
Over, and out.