(MOB CLAMORING)
(SCREAMING)
It's alive.
It's alive. It's alive!
There he is!
Hit it again !
Success!
Count, it's just you.
I was beginning to
lose faith, Victor.
A pity your moment of
triumph is being spoiled
over a little thing
like grave robbery.
Yes.
I must escape this place.
Where are you going to run,
Victor?
Your peculiar experiments
have made you unwelcome
in most of
the civilized world.
I'll take him away, far away,
where no one will ever find
him.
No, Victor.
The time
has come for me
to take command of him.
What are you saying?
Why do you think
I brought you here?
Gave you this castle?
Equipped your laboratory?
You said. . .
You said you
believed in my work.
And I do.
But now that it is,
as you yourself have said,
a triumph of science
over God,
it must now
serve my purpose.
What purpose?
Good God !
I would kill myself
before helping in
such a task.
Feel free.
I don't actually
need you anymore, Victor.
I just need him.
He is the key.
I could never allow him
to be used for such evil.
I could.
In fact, my brides
are insisting upon it.
Igor, help me!
IGOR: You have been
so kind to me, Doctor,
caring, thoughtful.
But he pays me.
Stay back.
You can't kill me, Victor.
Ah !
l'm already dead.
(GRUNTING)
Dr. Frankenstein !
Look,
it's headed
for the windmill !
Come on !
(GROWLING)
Burn it!
Burn it down !
MONSTER: Why?
Why?
WOMAN: Vampires.
MAN 1 : Run for your lives!
MAN 2: (IN HUNGARIAN)
Vampires!
Father.
(BRIDES
SHRIEKING AND WAILING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(MR. HYDE LAUGHING)
(SNARLING)
Evening.
You're a big one.
You'll be hard to digest.
I'd hate to be
such a nuisance.
I missed you in London.
No, you bloody did
not! You got me good.
Dr. Jekyll, you're wanted
by the Knights of the
Holy Order. . .
It's Mr. Hyde now.
. . .for the murder of
12 men, six women, four. . .
Children, three goats, and
a rather nasty massacre of
poultry!
So you're
the great Van Helsing.
And you're
a deranged psychopath.
We all have our
little problems.
My superiors
would like for me
to take you alive
so that they
may extricate
your better half.
I bet they bloody would.
Personally,
I'd rather just kill
you and call it a day.
But let's make it
your decision,
shall we?
Do let's.
(BUMP)
Here I come,
ready or not!
The bell !
(LAUGHING)
(MUFFLED WHIRRING)
No, no.
(GRUNTING)
I'll bet that's upsetting.
Paris!
Come here.
I think you'll find the view
over here rather spectacular.
It's been
a pleasure knowing you.
Au revoir!
Oh, no.
My turn.
(IN LATIN)
May he rest in peace.
(PEOPLE MUTTERING)
Van Helsing.
You murderer!
Bless me, Father,
for I have. . .
Sinned. Yes, I know.
You're very good at that.
You shattered
the Rose Window.
Not to split hairs, sir,
but Mr. Hyde did the
shattering.
13th century.
Over 600 years old.
I wish
you a week
in hell for that.
It would be
a nice reprieve.
Don't get me wrong.
Your results are
unquestionable
but your methods attract
far too much attention.
"Wanted" posters?
We are not pleased.
Do you think I like being
the most wanted man in
Europe?
Why don't
you and the Order
do something about it?
Because we do not exist.
Well, then neither do I.
When we found you crawling
up the steps of this church,
half-dead,
it was clear to all of us
that you had been sent
to do God's work.
Why can't he do it himself?
Don't blaspheme.
You already
lost your memory as
a penance for past sins.
If you wish
to recover it
I suggest
you continue
to heed the call.
Without us,
the world would
be in darkness.
Governments and
empires come and go
but we have kept mankind
safe since time immemorial.
We are the last
defense against evil.
An evil that
the rest of mankind
has no idea even exists.
To you, these monsters
are just evil beings
to be vanquished.
I'm the one standing
there when they die
and become
the men they once were.
For you, my good son,
this is all a test
of faith.
And now, we need
you to go to the East.
To the far side of Romania.
An accursed land
terrorized by all sorts
of nightmarish creatures.
Lorded over by
a certain Count Dracula.
Dracula?
Yes.
You've never faced
one like this before.
Our story
begins 450 years ago
when
a Transylvanian knight,
named Valerious the Elder,
promised God that his family
would never rest nor enter
heaven
until they vanquished
Dracula from their land.
They have
not succeeded
and they are
running out of family.
His descendant
Boris Valerious,
King of the Gypsies.
He disappeared
almost 12 months ago.
His only son, Prince Velkan,
and his daughter,
Princess Anna.
If the two of them are killed
before Dracula is vanquished,
nine generations of their
family will never enter
the gates of St. Peter.
For more than
four centuries
this family has
defended our left flank.
They gave their lives.
We cannot let them
slip into purgatory.
So you're
sending me into hell.
In a manner.
Valerious the Elder left
this here 400 years ago.
We don't know its purpose
but he would not
have left it lightly.
The Latin
inscription
translates as,
"In the name of God,
open this door."
There is an insignia.
Yes, it matches your ring.
I think that in Transylvania
you may find the answer you
seek.
CARL: Faster, please.
Faster!
(MAN EXCLAIMS)
Getting there.
Carl !
There you are.
Did you
bring Mr. Hyde back,
or did you kill him?
You killed him,
didn't you?
That's why
they get so annoyed.
When they ask you
to bring someone
back,
they don't mean
as a corpse.
All right, you're
in a mood. Come on.
I have some things that'll
put the bit back in your
mouth.
Any idiot
can make a sword.
Sorry, Father.
Come along, Carl.
Here, take this.
Rings of garlic, holy water,
silver stake, crucifix.
Why can't I
have one of those?
You've never
gone after vampires
before now, have you?
Vampires,
gargoyles, warlocks,
they're all the same.
Best when cooked well.
No, they're
not all the same.
A vampire is
nothing like a warlock.
My granny could
kill a warlock.
Carl,
you've never even
been out of the abbey.
How do you know
about vampires?
I read.
Here's something new.
Glycerin 48.
(MONKS SCREAM)
CARL: Sorry!
MAN: What in the name of
Allah is wrong with you?
The air around here
is thick with envy.
This is my latest invention.
It's gas-propelled.
Capable of
catapulting arrows
in rapid succession
at tremendous velocity.
Just pull
the trigger and hold on.
I've heard the stories
from Transylvania.
Trust me,
you'll need this.
A work of
certifiable genius.
If you don't say so yourself.
No, I did say so myself.
I'm a veritable
cornucopia of talent.
Did you invent this?
I've been working
on that for 1 2 years.
It's compressed
magma from Mt. Vesuvius
with pure alkaline
from the Gobi Desert.
It's one of a kind.
What's it for?
I don't know, but I'm
sure it'll come in handy.
12 years, and you
don't know what it does?
I didn't say that.
I said I didn't
know what it's for.
What it does is to
create a light source
equal to
the intensity of the sun.
This will come in handy how?
I don't know.
You can blind
your enemies.
Charbroil a herd of
charging wildebeest.
Use your imagination.
No, I'm gonna use yours.
That's why
you're coming with me.
Holy hell be
damned that I am !
You cursed.
Not very well,
but you're a monk.
You shouldn't curse at all.
Actually,
I'm still just a friar.
I can curse all I want,
damn it!
The Cardinal
has ordered you
to keep me alive.
For as long as possible.
But I'm not a field man.
I don't want to
go to Transylvania.
(LOUD GROWLING)
Come on.
Dracula unleashed
you for a reason.
(SNARLING)
Pull me up!
It's stuck!
No, Anna,
it will kill you !
That's my brother out there.
Cut the rope! Cut it now!
Velkan !
My gun ! Find my gun !
Find Velkan's gun.
It has to be
the silver bullets.
Anna, hurry!
Move.
Anna, look out!
Run !
(VELKAN SCREAMING)
(SPLASH)
Velkan.
God
help us.
So, what do you remember?
Not now, Carl.
There must be something.
I remember fighting
the Romans at Masada.
That was in 73 A. D.
You asked.
What are we doing here?
Why is it so important
to kill this Dracula,
anyway?
Because he's
the son of the Devil.
I mean, besides that.
If we kill him, anything
bitten or created by
him will also die.
I mean, besides that.
Welcome to Transylvania.
(SIGHING)
Is it always like this?
Pretty much.
ANNA: You, turn around.
Let me see your faces.
Why?
Because we don't
trust strangers.
Strangers don't
last long here.
5'7" by 2'3".
Gentlemen,
you will now
be disarmed.
You can try.
ANNA:
You refuse to
obey our laws?
The laws of men
mean little to me.
Fine.
Kill them.
I'm here to help you.
I don't need any help.
Really?
Everybody inside!
WOMAN: Hide the children !
Stay here.
You stay here.
They're trying to kill me.
Marishka,
kill the stranger.
Love to.
ANNA: Run !
Carl, it's not working.
CARL:
Try aiming
at their hearts.
(SCREECHING)
It's the sun.
Van Helsing.
Do you like to fly, Anna?
(SCREAMING)
Hello, Anna.
Nice to see you, too, Aleera.
Did I do something
to you in a past life?
Don't play coy
with me, Princess.
I know what lurks
in your lusting heart.
I hope you have
a heart, Aleera,
because someday
I'm going to drive
a stake through it.
This should do the trick.
Holy water!
Stop your teasing, Marishka,
and finish him.
Too bad. So sad.
The church !
Thirty years old.
Perfectly aged.
Hello, Anna, my dear.
The last of
the Valerious.
(SNARLING)
(LAUGHING)
I can feel fresh blood
rushing through her veins.
Here she comes!
I want first bite.
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(COW MOOING)
WOMAN: He killed a bride!
MAN 1 : He killed Marishka!
MAN 2: You killed Marishka!
MAN 3: You killed a vampire!
But isn't that
a good thing?
Vampires only kill
what they need to
survive.
One or two
people a month.
Now they will
kill for revenge.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Are you always this popular?
Pretty much.
So what name,
my good sir, do I
carve on your gravestone?
His name is Van Helsing.
(ALL MURMURING)
Your reputation
precedes you.
Next time stay close.
You're no good to me dead.
Well, I'll say this for you.
You've got courage.
He's the first one to kill
a vampire in over 100 years.
I'd say that's
earned him a drink.
Marishka!
DRACULA:
Why can't they
just leave us alone?
We never kill
more than our fill
and less than our share.
Can they say the same?
Did I not stress how important
it was to be finished with
Anna Valerious
before she destroys
what we are trying
to create?
ALEERA: We lost Marishka.
VERONA: Master.
There, there, my darlings.
Do not worry.
I shall find another bride.
What?
Do we mean
so little to you?
Have you no heart?
No, I have no heart!
I feel no love!
Nor fear,
nor joy,
nor sorrow!
I am hollow.
And I will live forever.
My Lord.
It is not so bad.
DRACULA:
I am at war with the world
and every living soul in it.
But soon the final
battle will begin.
I must go and find out
who our new visitor is.
(GROWLING)
You will have to make
a little apéritif out
of him.
We are much
too close to success
to be interrupted now.
ALEERA: No!
VERONA: The last
experiment was a failure!
Please,
say you will
not try again.
My heart could not bear
the sorrow if we fail again.
(SNARLING)
Come.
Do not fear me.
Everybody else fears me.
Not my brides.
Igor.
Yes, Master.
Why do you
torment that thing so?
It's what I do.
Remember, Igor,
"Do unto others. . ."
Before they do
unto me, Master.
Now go, all of you !
To Castle Frankenstein !
ALEERA:
Yes, we will try again.
So, how did you get here?
We came by sea.
ANNA: Really? The sea?
CARL: Well, yes.
ANNA: The Adriatic Sea?
VAN HELSlNG:
So, where do
I find Dracula?
ANNA: He used to live in this
very house four centuries ago.
No one knows
where he lives now.
Father would stare at
that painting for hours
looking for Dracula's lair.
So that's why you've come?
I can help you.
No one can help me.
I can try.
You can die trying.
All of my family has.
I can handle this myself.
So I noticed.
The vampires
attacked in daylight.
They never do that.
I was unprepared.
It won't happen again.
So why did they
attack in daylight?
Clearly they wanted
to catch me off guard.
They seem
almost desperate to
finish off my family.
Why is that? Why now?
You ask a lot of questions.
Usually I ask only two.
What are
we dealing with?
How do I kill it?
My father spent
most of his life
looking for
answers year after year.
Tearing through the tower,
combing through the
family archives.
Carl, the tower. Start there.
Right.
The only way to save your
family is to stay alive
till Dracula's killed.
And who will
kill him if not me?
Who will show
courage if not me?
Go alone and you'll be
outmanned and outpositioned.
And you can't
see in the dark.
In the morning,
we will hunt him
but we'll do it together.
Some say you're a murderer,
Mr. Van Helsing.
Others say you're a holy man.
Which is it?
It's a bit of both, I think.
I promised you a drink.
Yes, you did.
The bar is down the hall.
Help yourself.
As for me,
I'm going to finish
this once and for all.
I'm sorry you have to
carry this burden alone.
On the contrary,
I would wish for
it no other way.
I'm sorry about your
father and brother.
I will see them again.
We Transylvanians always look
on the brighter side of death.
There's
a brighter
side of death?
Yes. It's just harder to see.
I'm sorry about that, too.
Van Helsing !
Van Helsing?
(BANG)
(THUD)
Velkan?
Anna.
Oh, my God, you're alive.
No. Anna,
I only have a moment.
But there's a werewolf. . .
Never mind ! Listen to me!
I know Dracula's secret.
He has a. . .
Velkan?
Please.
No!
(GRUNTING)
Run, Anna.
VAN HELSING: Anna!
Are you all right?
(SNIFFING)
Why does it smell
like wet dog in here?
Werewolf!
Right.
You'll be needing
silver bullets, then.
Well done.
Who's hunting whom?
Nice night.
This is a bit
tight for me.
But for you
it's a perfect fit.
What a coincidence.
I see the wolf man
hasn't killed you yet.
Don't worry,
he's getting to it.
You don't seem
too bothered by him.
I'm no threat to him.
I'm just the one who
cleans up after him,
if you get my meaning.
Little late to be
digging graves,
isn't it?
Never too late
to dig graves.
You never know when
you'll need a fresh one.
Oh, sorry.
It's just my nature.
ANNA: No.
VAN HELSING: Move!
ANNA: No!
Why?
You're choking me!
Give me a reason not to.
I can't. If people knew. . .
He's not your
brother anymore, Anna!
You knew?
Yes.
Before
or after I stopped
you from shooting him?
Before.
And still you
tried to kill him !
He's a werewolf!
He's gonna kill people!
He can't help it!
It's not his fault!
I know,
but he'll do it anyway!
Do you
understand forgiveness?
Yes. I ask for it often.
They say Dracula has a cure.
If there's a chance
I can save my brother,
I'm going after it.
No.
I need to find Dracula.
And I need to
find my brother!
He gave his life for me.
He's the only
family I have left.
I despise Dracula more
than you can ever imagine.
He has taken
everything from me,
leaving me
alone in this world.
To have memories of
those you loved and
lost
is perhaps harder than
to have no memories
at all.
All right.
We'll look
for your brother.
lgor.
Yes, Master.
How long before we are ready?
Soon, Master. Very soon.
It is difficult without the
good doctor but the Dwergi,
they are doing well?
(IN HUNGARIAN) No!
Good.
ANNA: For me,
this is all personal.
It's all about
family and honor.
Why do you do it,
this job of yours?
What do you hope
to get out of it?
I don't know.
Maybe some self-realization.
What have you got
out of it so far?
Nightmares.
Werewolves only shed
before the first full moon.
Before the curse has
completely consumed them.
VAN HELSING:
What is this place?
ANNA: Castle Frankenstein.
But it should be abandoned.
I don't understand.
The man who lived here
was killed a year ago.
A grave robber,
among other things.
A year ago.
It was just after that
that your father went
missing.
Yes. He was
looking for Dracula.
He was on his
way to the sea.
I have never
been to the sea.
I'll bet it's beautiful.
Werewolves
are such a nuisance
during their first full moon.
So hard to control.
I send you on
a simple errand
to find out who
our new visitor is
and you have to stop
for a little chat
with your sister.
Leave her out of this, Count.
She doesn't know your secret.
And I am soon to
take it to my grave.
Don't wish for
death so quickly.
I intend for you
to be quite useful.
I would rather
die than help you.
Don't be boring.
Everyone who says that dies.
Besides, tonight,
after the final
stroke of midnight,
you will have no
choice but to obey me.
Look familiar?
Father?
No!
He proved useless.
But I'm hoping,
with werewolf venom
running through your veins
you will be of
greater benefit!
I may have failed to kill you,
Count, but my sister will not.
Never!
Dwergi.
Dwergi?
Dracula's servants.
lndustrious but
extremely vicious.
If you get the chance to kill
one, do it because they'll
do worse to you.
Right.
(DWERGI CHATTERING)
They say
they're using my brother
in some sort of experiment.
My brother
is still battling
the sickness within him.
There's still hope.
Anna.
There is no hope
for your brother.
But we can still protect
others by killing Dracula.
Let us begin !
(IN HUNGARIAN)
No slacking! Up!
VAN HELSING: You ever
see these things before?
ANNA: No.
What do you
think they are?
Offspring.
ANNA: What?
VAN HELSING: A man with
three gorgeous women
for 400 years.
Yes, vampires are
the walking dead.
It only makes sense
their children are
born dead.
He's obviously trying
to bring them to life.
Ladies first.
Dracula
and his brides only kill
one or two people a month.
If he brings all
these things to
life. . .
Throw the switches!
IGOR: Yes, Master.
(HEARTS BEATING)
What are you doing?
I want to see
what we're up
against.
So this is what you
get when vampires mate.
(SNARLING)
(ANNA SCREAMS)
Come on !
They need to feed.
Teach them how. Teach them !
(BOTH SHRIEKING)
And beg the Devil
that this time
they stay alive.
This is where I come in.
No, wait!
Now that I have
your attention.
Yes, well,
that's interesting.
(SHRIEKING)
That's not good.
Must warn somebody.
I can tell the character of
a man by the sound of
his heartbeat.
Usually when I approach
I can almost
dance to the beat.
Strange that
yours is so steady.
IGOR: (IN HUNGARIAN)
Hurry up!
We must keep
the atmosphere
electrified !
Accelerate the generators!
Power the dynamos!
We are losing power.
The human is insufficient.
Velkan.
Oh, my God.
Feed, my darlings! Feed !
(IN LATIN)
May he rest in peace.
Hello, Gabriel.
(DWERGI SHOUTING)
We must not lose
the master's progeny!
Is this your silver stake?
How long has it been?
300, 400 years?
You don't remember, do you?
Exactly what is it I
should be remembering?
You are
the great Van Helsing.
Trained by
monks and mullahs
from Tibet to Istanbul.
Protected by
Rome herself.
But, like me,
hunted by all others.
The Knights of the Holy
Order know all about you.
It's no surprise you
would know about me.
Yes,
but it's much
more than this.
We have such history,
you and I, Gabriel.
Have you ever wondered why
you have such horrible
nightmares?
Horrific scenes of
ancient battles past.
How do you know me?
Velkan.
Anna.
No. Don't unstrap me.
Don't unstrap me.
No, you must not! No! Stop!
Stop it.
I'm getting
you out of here.
Velkan,
it's all right.
I'm taking you home.
(VELKAN ROARING)
So would you like me to
refresh your memory
a little?
A few details
from your sordid past.
Perhaps that is a conversation
for another time.
Allow me to
reintroduce myself.
I am Count
Vladislaus Dragulia.
Born 1422.
Murdered 1462.
Help me!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
I think we've
overstayed our welcome.
MAN 1 :
Have you found the children?
MAN 2: Not yet.
What happened?
They just died.
How can I ever repay you?
But you can't do that.
You are a monk.
Well,
actually I'm just a friar.
I am sorry, master.
We try and we try,
but I fear we
are not so smart
as Dr. Frankenstein.
Truly.
It would appear the good
doctor took the key to
life to his grave.
Hunt them down.
Kill them both.
ANNA: A silver stake?
A crucifix?
What,
did you think we haven't
tried everything before?
We've shot him,
stabbed him, clubbed him,
sprayed him with holy water,
staked him through the heart,
and still he lives!
Do you understand?
No one knows how
to kill Dracula.
Well,
I could have used that
information a little earlier.
Don't give me that look.
You were right. I'm sorry.
He's not my brother anymore.
Do you have any family,
Mr. Van Helsing?
Not sure.
I hope to find out someday.
That's what keeps me going.
Here's to what
keeps you going.
Absinthe. Strong stuff.
Don't let it
touch your tongue.
It'll knock you on your. . .
Vampire.
Vampires!
(EXCLAIMING IN FRIGHT)
Now I remember.
"Even a man
who is pure in heart
And says his prayers by night
"May become a wolf
when the wolfbane blooms
"And the moon
is shining bright
"Or crave another's blood
when the sun goes down
"And his body
takes to flight"
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
There's something down here.
And it's carnivorous.
Whatever it is,
it appears to be human.
I'd say
he's a size 17.
Around 360 pounds.
8.5 to 9 feet tall.
He has a bad
gimp in his right leg
and three copper teeth.
How do you know
he has copper teeth?
Because he's standing
right behind you. Move!
Oh, my God !
The Frankenstein monster!
Monster?
Who's the monster here?
I have done nothing wrong
and yet you and your kind
all wish me dead !
What do you want?
To exist.
Don't!
We must kill it.
Wait.
If you value your lives
and the lives of your kind,
you will kill me.
No.
If Dracula finds me.
I am the key to
my father's machine.
The key to life.
Life for Dracula's children.
He already
awakened them last night.
Two.
And those were
from only one bride.
From one single birthing.
And they died as they
did the last time
he tried.
Only with me can he
give them lasting life.
There are more?
More of those things?
Thousands.
Thousands more.
No.
You heard what he said.
My life,
my job is to
vanquish evil.
I can sense evil.
This thing, man,
whatever it is
evil may have created it,
may have left its mark on it.
But evil
does not rule it,
so I cannot kill it.
I can.
Not while I'm here.
Your family
has spent 400 years
trying to kill Dracula.
Maybe this poor creature
can help us find a way.
(SOFT CLICK)
Oh, my God. He's seen us.
Now they'll come for him.
Neither you nor I will
be able to stop them.
If I can get him to Rome,
we can protect him there.
And then the painting
came alive and the two
creatures attacked each other.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
Listen, Carl,
whatever you do,
don't stare at him.
I'm staring at him.
Is that a man?
Actually, it's seven men.
Parts of them, anyway.
By exposing me,
you have condemned me!
Me and all of humanity!
Nothing is faster
than Transylvanian horses.
Not even a werewolf.
Anything else,
you're on your own.
Let me go.
Where are you
going to go?
I don't know if you've seen
a mirror lately but you
kind of stick out in a crowd.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
We must not let
the creature be
destroyed !
ALEERA: Save him !
Save the monster!
Stakes!
No!
CARL: Oh, my God.
CARL:
What are you
doing out here?
ANNA: Carl !
CARL: Right.
Don't let go!
I can help!
You won't kill me?
Only if you don't hurry!
(GROWLING)
Velkan.
Anna.
Forgive me.
I will see you again.
You killed him.
Now you know why
they call me murderer.
Oh, my God.
You've been bitten.
Anna.
So much trouble
to my master.
So much trouble.
What do you want?
The master commands a trade.
The monster for the Princess.
Somewhere public.
Lots of people.
A place
where your master
will be less inclined
to expose his other side.
Tomorrow night is
All Hallows' Eve.
Here in Budapest, there is
a wonderful masquerade ball.
(LAUGHING)
Are you all right?
No.
He has been bitten.
Bitten by a werewolf.
Now you will become that
which you have hunted
so passionately.
I am sorry.
May others
be as passionate in
their hunting of you.
Well, they won't
find him in here.
I'm sure this is
some sort of sin.
Don't worry,
God will forgive us.
We need to save Anna.
You don't think
the hat's a bit much?
Carl, help me!
Right.
How many commandments
can we break in one day?
Anyway, according to the book
you won't turn into a werewolf
until the rising of your first
full moon.
That's two nights
from now.
Even then, you'll
still be able to fight
Dracula's hold over you
until the final
stroke of midnight.
VAN HELSING:
Sounds like I have
nothing to worry about.
CARL: My God,
you should be terrified.
VAN HELSING: Thank you.
Sorry.
We still
have 48 hours
to find a solution.
You sure he can't
get out of there?
Not without some
help from the dead.
(SINGING EERIE OPERA)
(ANNA EXCLAIMING)
How does it feel to be
a puppet on my string?
I won't let you
trade me, Count.
I have
no intention
of trading you.
And if I know Van Helsing,
which I do,
he is not planning on
making a trade, either.
Neither of us has
ever settled for half.
There they are.
You make my skin crawl.
This is not all I
could do with your skin.
Carl,
I need you
to do something.
I'm not gonna
like this, am I?
Don't we make
a lovely couple?
Oh, my God.
I am looking for
a new bride, Anna.
Someone strong and beautiful.
(MAN GRUNTING)
One brief moment of pain,
and we can be
together forever.
You have no heartbeat.
Perhaps it just needs
to be rekindled.
Anna. Anna!
Wake up.
DRACULA: Gabriel.
Oh, Gabriel.
Welcome to my summer palace.
Master! Look, Master!
We have him, Master.
We have him.
You wretched undead !
I shall have my revenge!
"Though I walk
through the valley
of the shadow of death
"I shall fear no evil."
You are nothing
but damned bones
and damned souls,
and will burn in
the flames of Hell !
Now that everything
is as it should be,
ladies and gentlemen,
I give to you,
Van Helsing !
Come on.
Yes!
Now l know what it's for.
Where are we going?
BOTH: Through that window!
Carl, you're a genius!
A genius with access
to unstable chemicals.
Say goodbye to your friends.
I'll find you !
I'll get you back
and set you free!
I swear to God !
I must save him.
No, you can't.
Why?
I cabled Rome earlier
to apprise them of
our situation.
What did they say?
Even if you
somehow kill Dracula,
Rome orders
you to destroy
Frankenstein as well.
He isn't evil.
But they say he
isn't human, either.
Do they know him?
Have they spoken
to him?
Who are they to judge?
They want you to destroy him
so he can never be used to
harm humanity.
What of me?
Did you tell them
what l'm to become?
Did they tell
you how to kill me?
The correct
angle of the stake
as it enters my heart?
The exact measure of
silver in each bullet?
ANNA: Stop!
No, I left you out!
I'm sorry.
It's starting.
ANNA: They must have taken
all the equipment to
Dracula's lair.
Wherever that is.
Look, there's still time.
Dracula can't
bring his children
to life until the sun sets.
The sun sets
in two hours.
We've been
looking for him for
more than 400 years!
Yes, well, I wasn't around
for those 400 years, now,
was I?
VAN HELSING:
All right, Carl,
what have you learned?
That Count Dracula
was actually the son
of Valerious the Elder.
The son of your ancestor.
Everybody knows that.
What else?
All right. Well, according to
this rubbing it all started
when Dracula was murdered.
Do you know
who murdered him?
No,
there's just
some vague reference
to the Left Hand of God.
And in 1462,
when Dracula died,
he made
a covenant
with the Devil.
And was given a new life.
But the only way he could
sustain that life was by
drinking blood.
Excuse me.
Are you going to
let me tell the story?
BOTH: Sorry.
And your ancestor,
having sired this
evil creature,
went to Rome to
seek forgiveness.
That's when
the bargain
was made.
He was to kill Dracula
in return for
eternal salvation
of his entire family
right down the line
all the way to you.
ANNA: But he couldn't do it.
As evil as
Dracula was, my ancestor
couldn't kill his own son.
So he banished him
to an icy fortress
sending him
through a door from
which there was no return.
And then the Devil
gave him wings.
Yes.
All right,
so where is this door?
I don't know.
But when
your ancestor couldn't
kill his son, he left clues.
So that
future generations
might do it for him.
That must
be what my father
was looking for in here.
Clues to the
door's location.
The door.
Of course.
You said
your father spent hours
staring at this painting,
trying to find the lair.
I think
you were right.
Quite literally.
I think this is the door.
He just didn't know
how to open it.
Look.
A Latin inscription.
Maybe
it works like that
painting in the tower.
If this were a door,
my father would have
opened it long ago.
I can't
finish the inscription.
There's a piece missing.
Your father
didn't have this.
Where did
you get that?
Carl, finish it.
(READlNG lN LATlN)
In the name of God,
open this door.
A mirror.
Dracula has
no reflection
in the mirror.
But why?
Maybe, to Dracula
it's not a mirror
at all.
It's cold.
And it's snowing.
See you on
the other side.
Be careful.
Castle Dracula.
CARL: Do we have a plan?
lt doesn't have to be
Wellington's at Waterloo,
but some sort of
plan would be nice.
VAN HELSING:
We're going to
go stop Dracula.
ANNA: And kill
anything that
gets in our way.
CARL: Well, you let
me know how that goes.
Well,
as grateful as l am
to be out of the cold,
that doesn't seem
like a good thing.
(GROWLING)
We'd better get moving.
CARL: So are
all of those. . .
ANNA: Yes.
CARL:
And inside them are. . .
VAN HELSING: Yes.
IGOR:
Igor do this!
Igor do that!
How did you find. . .
It's impossible!
Please don't kill me!
Why not?
Well, I. . .
(MONSTER SCREAMING)
My master has awakened.
There is a cure.
What?
Dracula.
He has a cure to remove
the curse of the werewolf!
Go,
find the cure!
Save yourself!
Come on.
You heard him.
Let's find it.
Wait. Why does
Dracula have
a cure?
I don't care!
I do.
Why does he need one?
Why?
Because the only thing
that can kill him is
a werewolf.
The painting.
That's what it meant.
But Dracula's been
using werewolves to do
his bidding for centuries.
Yes, but if one ever had
the will to turn on him,
he'd need a cure
to remove the curse and
make him human before
it bit him.
You're going to take these
two and lead them to the
antidote.
No, I'm not.
Yes, I am.
Here's
the plan. When the bell
begins to toll midnight,
you'll be able
to kill Dracula.
We just need to find the
cure and get it into you
before the final stroke.
Are you insane?
What kind of plan is that?
If they even suspect
you of misleading them. . .
Clip off one of his fingers.
I'll clip off something.
The tower over there,
that's where it is.
And what about
the other tower?
Give me that!
That is where
we reassembled
the laboratory.
Would I lie to you?
Not if you wanted to live.
Now, if I'm not
cured by the twelfth
stroke of midnight. . .
I don't think I could.
You must.
Come on.
I don't like this plan.
We don't have a choice.
Just don't get killed.
You still don't understand.
It doesn't matter
what happens to me.
We must save my family.
If you're late,
run like hell.
Don't be late.
(WHlSPERING) Now go. Go.
MONSTER: Get off me,
you vermin from hell !
What are you
complaining about?
This is why you were made!
To prove that God is not
the only one who can
create life!
And now you must give
that life to my children.
Up!
There it is.
I'll go first.
ANNA: Carl !
Stay as long as you like.
You try to get lgor.
Igor get you !
Go ahead. Grab it.
You go ahead and grab it.
If there's one thing I've
learned it's never to be
the first to stick
your hand in
a viscous material.
Did I scare you?
No.
Then maybe I need to
try a little harder.
Viscous material !
What did I tell you?
Get it!
(SCREAMING)
Hot.
Come on !
Yes.
We've got
to get the antidote
to Van Helsing ! Go!
You can't go until
I say you can go!
Keep running, Carl !
And I'll say you can
go when you're dead !
Oh, my God !
What are you doing?
You must find the cure!
My friends are
doing it for me.
Friends.
Yes. You want one?
I can't unscrew the bolts.
This is gonna hurt.
I am accustomed to pain.
lt lets you
know you're alive.
(SCREAMING)
Give me life!
One more bolt and
my young will live.
(GROWLING)
VAN HELSING:
You're almost
out, my friend !
(SCREAMING)
(HEART BEATING)
Help me!
But you're supposed to die.
I want to live.
All right!
Be happy in the knowledge
that I shall weep
over your dead body.
Hang on !
I'll swing you loose!
You are too late,
my friend.
My children live.
Then the only way to
kill them is to kill you.
Correct.
So be it.
One.
(SCREAMING)
No, this cannot be.
(GROWLING)
We are both part of
the same grand game,
Gabriel.
But we need not find
ourselves on opposite
sides of the board.
MONSTER: Go!
Go and help
Van Helsing !
Now!
Thank you.
Oh, my God ! Anna,
I need a little help!
Hurry!
Throw it to me, Carl !
Yes!
You are being used,
Gabriel, as was I.
But I escaped. So can you.
Anna, my love,
it is your blood that
shall keep me beautiful.
What do you think of that?
I think
if you're going to
kill someone, kill them.
Don't stand there
talking about it.
(SCREAMING)
Don't you understand?
We could be friends.
Partners!
Brothers-in-arms!
(GROWLING)
Did l mention that it
was you who murdered me?
It must be such a burden.
Such a curse to be the
Left Hand of God.
All I want is life,
Gabriel.
The continuation
of my kind.
And perhaps
the return of my ring.
Don't be afraid, Gabriel.
Don't be afraid.
I shall give you
back your life,
your memory.
Some things are
better left forgotten.
(SCREAMING)
For God !
God forgive me.
(GROWLING)
She's dead.
(HOWLING)
(SOBBING)
CARL: (IN LATIN)
"Eternal rest grant unto her,
"Oh, Lord,
and let perpetual light
"shine upon her.
On her soul and
the souls of all
"On her soul and
"the dead
faithful have mercy."